<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Video Lead Marketing - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Video Lead Marketing - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>VideoProfitFX 1.1</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1759-videoprofitfx.html</link>
<description>Name : VideoProfitFX Lead Finder Version : 1.1 OS : Windows/MAC Type : Video Lead Finder Price : $37 Homepage : SalePage Video Lead Finder Finds Businesses In Need of Video! Plus it Checks If A Business Has... Facebook Page, Twitter Page, LinkedIn Page YouTube Channel, WordPress, If Website Is Responsive/Mobile Ready Plus Preview Their Website and Email Businesses Right In The Software! You Can Export All of the data to CSV Format As Well! This Full Featured Lead Finder Software ONLY Included with VideoProfitFX!</description>
<category>Video Lead Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="https://vmfx1.s3.amazonaws.com/oto2videoprofitfx_table.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2016 21:54:26 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features The Profit Maker For VideoMakerFX! Special Software That Finds Businesses That NEED Video &amp; Your Services! VideoProfitFX Focuses On Selling Videos To Businesses</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/t8QY3b-GxuE?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> The Profit Maker For VideoMakerFX!<br /></li><li> Special Software That Finds Businesses That NEED Video & Your Services!<br /></li><li> VideoProfitFX Focuses On Selling Videos To Businesses <br /></li></ul><br /><img src="https://vmfx1.s3.amazonaws.com/oto2videoprofitfx_table.png" alt="VideoProfitFX 1.1" title="VideoProfitFX 1.1"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="VideoProfitFX 1.1" title="VideoProfitFX 1.1"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Video Lead Finder Pro 2.02</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1328-video-lead-finder.html</link>
<description>Name : Video Lead Finder Version : 2.02 Pro (latest version, dont see fake from other site) OS : Windows/MAC Type : Video Marketing Tools Price : $300 Homepage : SalePage Video Lead Finder is your own personal video lead factory. You enter the keyword you want to target, and it finds you the best video prospects by focusing solely on the businesses already spending money with AdWords. IT can cast the.com worldwide or focus just on your home town, depending on how local you want to be. Video Lead Finder runs out and finds all the top video leads, checks their ads for improvements and finds out if they’ve got a video or not. All at the push of a button.</description>
<category>Video Lead Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2015 12:20:19 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Enter a keyword and location – Video Lead Finder goes through the first 3 pages of Google’s search results and pulls every lead already using AdWords. That means they are ALREADY spending money on THEIR leads so if you approach them with a surefire way to increase leads they will be much more likely to have interest. And we all know videos have quickly become the most powerful medium online. Every ad is analyzed for strengths and weaknesses – Video Lead Finder users will have additional insight on how each campaign can generate more clicks. You will have access to important data at your fingertips that other businesses would kill to have. Every landing page is checked for video presence – This is my favorite feature. In addition to pulling all AdWords data for all of the search results, you will find out if there is a video present on their landing page. Why does that matter? Because you are selling video marketing services to improve their business and Video Lead Finder will give you their contact info including phone number so you can approach them directly!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><div class="dlevideoplayer" style="width:100%;max-width:425px;"><ul data-theme="default" data-preload="metadata"><li data-title="" data-type="youtube" data-url="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2k9SCKIHmpA"></li></ul></div></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Enter a keyword and location – Video Lead Finder goes through the first 3 pages of Google’s search results and pulls every lead already using AdWords. That means they are ALREADY spending money on THEIR leads so if you approach them with a surefire way to increase leads they will be much more likely to have interest. And we all know videos have quickly become the most powerful medium online.<br /></li><li> Every ad is analyzed for strengths and weaknesses – Video Lead Finder users will have additional insight on how each campaign can generate more clicks. You will have access to important data at your fingertips that other businesses would kill to have.<br /></li><li> Every landing page is checked for video presence – This is my favorite feature. In addition to pulling all AdWords data for all of the search results, you will find out if there is a video present on their landing page. Why does that matter? Because you are selling video marketing services to improve their business and Video Lead Finder will give you their contact info including phone number so you can approach them directly!<br /></li></ul><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Video Lead Finder Pro 2.02" title="Video Lead Finder Pro 2.02"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>GSA Clip Spider 2.73</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1349-gsa-clip-spider.html</link>
<description>Software to download all the movie clips from a website automatically. This clip spider finds every video on a webpage and downloads it.</description>
<category>Video Lead Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://clip.spider.gsa-online.de/images/clip_spider/filter_options.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://clip.spider.gsa-online.de/images/clip_spider/clip_spider.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-05/1431542544_1zf7i83.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-05/1431542806_gsa-ser-extension.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-05/1431542756_gsa-trial-reset.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2015 14:24:17 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>With this program you can download all the movie clips from a webserver automatically (with or without sublinks). It&#039;s very easy to use and gives you amazing results within seconds. This download manager for movies searches all your favorit web links, spiders, parses, grabs, extracts and crawls all the movies you would have downloaded by hand.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/1ChzvhKAnoo?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br />With this program you can download all the movie clips from a webserver automatically (with or without sublinks). It's very easy to use and gives you amazing results within seconds. This download manager for movies searches all your favorit web links, spiders, parses, grabs, extracts and crawls all the movies you would have downloaded by hand.<br /><img src="http://clip.spider.gsa-online.de/images/clip_spider/filter_options.png" alt="GSA Clip Spider 2.73" title="GSA Clip Spider 2.73"  /><br /><img src="http://clip.spider.gsa-online.de/images/clip_spider/clip_spider.png" alt="GSA Clip Spider 2.73" title="GSA Clip Spider 2.73"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="GSA Clip Spider 2.73" title="GSA Clip Spider 2.73"  /></div><br /><div class="quote"><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>