<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Email Marketing - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Email Marketing - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>Craigslist AutoPosting Tools 1.72</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1631-auto-posting-tools.html</link>
<description>Name : Craigslist Auto Posting Tools Version : 1.72 OS : Windows Type : Craigslist Marketing Tools, Facebook Group Marketing Tools, Facebook Fanpage Tools,..Many More,..45 Modules Price : $99 Homepage : SalePage Craigslist Auto Posting Software first video for auto posting ads to Craigslist. #1 Craigslist posting tool to manage, create, and post multiple ads to CL with a single click of a button. Learn how to setup your ad content so that you can start posting your ad campaigns today! If you are in this page probably is because you are interested in increasing your clients, having more traffic to your site, promoting products online. The software i am about to show you will help you to do all that and much more. This software is a compilation of multiple software, each with powerful features like Facebook posting, fiver scrapping, Craigslist posting, Craigslist flagging, Paypal link generator and much more. In this page you will find some videos presenting you the many features that we have. That’s not all, we are always updating the software to make it more powerful, with more functionality and more features. I want to thank you for your interest in this software that will change your life. You think you want this software, but the truth is, YOU NEED THIS SOFTWARE!! That’s Right you need the software to take your marketing to the next level. This is a list of the modules available in the software. With a little description on what they do. And how you can use them for your business.</description>
<category>Classifieds Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://autopostingtools.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/11/craigslist-auto-posting-features.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 13:06:45 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Craigslist Auto Posting And AutoRenewing : Create a list of ads,then let the program post the ads at the specified time, Multiple Account use Proxy Support, Auto renew your old ads. Craigslist Ad Flagging : Remove the ads of your competitors, Place the URL of the page of Craigslist where your competitors areUse proxy and flag all of their ads, Since you flagged them with multiple proxy Craigslist will think other people flag them. It will remove the ads of your competitors and leave only your ads. Youtube Video Downloader : Download videos to your computer, to watch them offline, or use it to get traffic, download a video with many views, re-brand it and re-upload it with your links to offers, affiliate links or subscription to your list. Facebook Group Commentor : Login to your Account, create a list of all your groups, Load your comments, and it will comment automatically to all your Facebook Groups, Save time and get more exposure to your offers. Email Scrapper and Email Sender : Do you need to create an email list? Well we can help you with that, this module will look for emails related to the keywords you specified. This is useful because you find people interested on the keyword you try to target, so people is more likely to take the offer you promote because they are interested. This generate you a list of emails that you can export to mail chimp and send emails to them or use the email sender and let it work for you. Youtube Video Scrapper : This is like the search video option in YouTube but here you can save the list of videos into excel, then you can contact the most popular videos offer them 10 dollars for putting a link with an offer that will generate you money, use the trafic of the video to your favor. Or you can tell them to work with you and split profits, you give the offer and he just put the link, both make money. Win- Win Situation. Facebook Fanpage Scrapper : Get a list of fan pages based on keywords, Get laser targeted traffic by getting a list of fanpages related to your keyword. If you are in marketing you can grab all marketing fan pages, comment there promoting you marketing related offer. Craigslist and Fiver Arbitrage : Scrape Craigslist and find people that need a service then Scrape fiverr find people that would do the service for 5 dollars then resell that service to other people at a higher price. Keep the difference. That simple.Make money being the middle man. Badoo Girl Liker : Badoo is a site that allows you to meet other people, for dating or friends. You like other people and if they like you back you can talk with them. Its boring to be liking people all day, so let the software like everybody if they like you back you will have more friends, if they don’t then doesn’t matter it took you 1 minute to set up the software. Google Keyword Scrapper : Get the top 10 websites for a keyword and get the information of that site, like title of the page, description of the page and keywords they try to target. Analyze your competition. Become the God of SEO. ClickBank Top Products : Clickbank is the bigger retailer of digital products, promote the best affiliate offers and generate recurring income. Paypal Payment Link Creator : Create payment buttons almost instantaneous without going to PayPal. Create payment link and create short link. Free Proxies Scrapper : If you ever need to access to a site anonymously, generate fake views or just change your ip for privacy, you need proxies, this modules will generate 200 proxys for you, the proxys are checked regularly so you only will have proxies that work. Yelp Company Scrapper : Get more leads for your promotions. This will go to yelp and will get the top 10 companies for any keyword you selected. Then you can visit their ads, or website and then call them to offer a service that they need. Youtube and Google Keyword Suggestion Tool 2016 – Lasser Target Keywords : When you look on google or YouTube , it give you suggestions of what other people typed this are popular and hot keywords, this module extract the keywords and give it to you in a list : Mega Spinner (Create sppined Articles) : Do you want your ads to be different every time you post on Craigslist or Kijiji.This software will help you to create the spin sintaxis of the ads. That means you post the same ad changing a few words here and there creating multiple variations of the same ad or article. you can type a keyword and it will give you synonyms of that words. Don’t reinvent the wheel. Youtube Keyword Scrapper : Steal the traffic of your competitors, if you analyze the keyword from multiple videos related, you will see which keywords are more often used, then you can create a new title and description using those keywords. Generating more traffic to your video using the help of your competitors without them knowing. They will wonder about your secret. Keyword Variation Generator : From a list of keywords, it will give you multiple variations of the keywords, very useful for SEO and dominating any niche : Kijiji Posting : Kijiji is a classified website just like craiglist, very popular in Canada, Post on Kijiji with the same Features as Craigslist Auto Posting Software : Torrent Scrapper (The Pirate Bay and Kick Ass Torrent) : Used in conjunction with utorrent and you can download pretty much everything, software, music, videos and ebooks. It uses The pirate bay and kick ass torrent as content provider. Youtube Video Views Increaser : This software will visit your youtube videos many times, generating more views, you can have multiple videos at the same time, and it will generate traffic to the videos, you can use it for your own channel or sell the traffic to other people. You get traffic on demand with just a few clicks. Link Cloacker Generator : It will generate php files to redirect your visitors to any page you like, the link would look like http://yoursite.com/go/anything-you-want and you can chose the url that it will link to, plus if you want to direct the traffic to a different page, you can change it afterwards : Bulk Shortened links : Shorten multiple links and give it to you in a list. YouTube Comment Scrapper : Do you want to get the comments from a video, but you have to select each comment and copy paste it onto excel, Forget that! Use this software just place the YouTube video id, and get all the comments from that video. Ebay Best Selling Items Scraper, Most Popular Keywords, Auction sniper.Get the price and URL of the best selling products by keyword, you will find the best selling items by category, the most searched keywords by category, eBay keyword suggestion tool, see what people is looking for, provide it to them its just like printing money. Also spy on your competitions, see what items they are selling and how well they sell, so you only chose products that do sell. Reddit Scrapping : Are you looking for interesting content for you posts, or articles, well you are lucky. This software scrape the content from the site Reddit where users thumbs up images, videos, articles they like. If it got likes on Reddit that means is interesting, so you can use this for you Facebook post to generate more likes and more engagement in your fanpage/blog/website. Email, text encryption : Paste your text in the software and encrypt it, this means that the text will not be readable for anyone that does not have the software and the password. Fully secure conversations trough email. (Since the text is encrypted) : Image Extractor : Want to get all images from a website only with a few clicks. Then use this module. In this module you type the URL with all the pictures that you want to download to your computer, and the software will create a list of the images, and download them individually or all of them and save them in a folder of your choice : Twitter Tweets Extractor : Get all the tweets of your favorite artist, get quotes, get jokes, get comments made to the specific account that you chose : Google Image Scraper – Affiliate HTML Code Image Creator : Search google images and create HTML code with your affiliate link. Anonymous Web browser : Simple Web browser that allows you to change proxy and user agent, you can clear cookies. You can navigate anonymously using proxies. You can create accounts to any site because you will be consider a different user. You can vote multiple times in contests, you by pass sites that banned your ip. Manual Posting to 28 Classified sites : Simple but powerful, you can use your Craigslist ads already spinned, sing up with the same account as Craigslist and use this module to copy and paste into all the 28 different classified sites, you need more exposure for your ads. Use this and promote anything that you want. You make more sells as your ads will get more exposure to more classified sites. Fake Name Generator : Whenever you are creating fake accounts or fake profiles, this will give you the name, address, phone and fake information that will allow you to create hundredths of accounts as easy as copying and pasting the information that we give you. Article Scrapper : Do you need content for your website or eBook? use this software to scrape articles, then you can use the articles as content, you can modify them and then get more exposure for your business. look articles related by keyword. Qr Code Generator : This will generate you a qr code image that you can use in your graphic design images, to redirect people to your website, you can use it to store information for people to read with their mobile devices, put your affiliate or cpa offer links in the qr code and make people buy from your their phone. Project and task management module : Track your activities to do, your activities complete, check on the calendar whatever appointment you have. Email yourself the activities for today. Keep organized and order your to do list by priority, Improve your productivity. Tee spring analyzer : Make money selling t-shirst easy to follow system that will analyze your competition, see what t-shirts do sell and get ideas on what you can sell. Customer Relationship Managment (CRM) : Keep a track of your clients, suppliers, freelancers, all in one software, you can email them directly trough the software, you can track the interactions with your customers. Check their information right away with our built in search feature by different search types. city, phone, country and more Point of sale system with inventory : Create invoices or quotes for your clients, you can save your products and services and then select them in the make a sale section, it will tell you the total and will generate you a PDF with a payment link to PayPal, so people can pay you in PayPal optimizing the your process, You can track your orders and see the total revenue you make every month Landing Page Creator : Create amazing landing pages that will save the information of your visitors (Name and Email) then it will send them to your affiliate page, Build your list while you do your affiliate marketing, make money and then with your list you can email them and promote anything you want. The money is on the list. Mobile Checker – Email Sender : Search google based on a keyword, then analyze the results to see if they are mobile friendly, if they are not get their email information and email them with your mobile websites services. Make almost instant money, since the google updates they give preference to sites that are mobile friendly. Yellow Pages Lead Finder – Email Sender : Get leads from yellow pages based on keyword, then it will check if those users are on social media and create a seo report about those sites. Then contact the owners and offer your services about seo, website development and traffic generation Twitter Auto Follower : Want more twitter followers to promote yourself or your business, give the twitter id of someone relevant in your niche, and follow his fan base, the software will follow them and then they will follow you back. Wait 2 days and then remove the people that did not follow you back. Increase your fan base is so easy and made on autopilot. Kijiji Ad Scrapper : Type a keyword and find people looking for those services, if i type website development i will find people that need a website, then i can contact them and make money. Getting clients have never been that easier. Facebook Fanpage Commentor : Use the list of fanpages that we extract with the fanpage extractor and post on every single one of them with multiple accounts, proxy support and cookies cleaning</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Vty51Rm1YyU?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Craigslist Auto Posting And AutoRenewing : Create a list of ads,then let the program post the ads at the specified time, Multiple Account use Proxy Support, Auto renew your old ads.<br></li><li> Craigslist Ad Flagging : Remove the ads of your competitors, Place the URL of the page of Craigslist where your competitors areUse proxy and flag all of their ads, Since you flagged them with multiple proxy Craigslist will think other people flag them. It will remove the ads of your competitors and leave only your ads.<br></li><li> Youtube Video Downloader : Download videos to your computer, to watch them offline, or use it to get traffic, download a video with many views, re-brand it and re-upload it with your links to offers, affiliate links or subscription to your list.<br></li><li> Facebook Group Commentor : Login to your Account, create a list of all your groups, Load your comments, and it will comment automatically to all your Facebook Groups, Save time and get more exposure to your offers.<br></li><li> Email Scrapper and Email Sender : Do you need to create an email list? Well we can help you with that, this module will look for emails related to the keywords you specified. This is useful because you find people interested on the keyword you try to target, so people is more likely to take the offer you promote because they are interested. This generate you a list of emails that you can export to mail chimp and send emails to them or use the email sender and let it work for you.<br></li><li> Youtube Video Scrapper : This is like the search video option in YouTube but here you can save the list of videos into excel, then you can contact the most popular videos offer them 10 dollars for putting a link with an offer that will generate you money, use the trafic of the video to your favor. Or you can tell them to work with you and split profits, you give the offer and he just put the link, both make money. Win- Win Situation.<br></li><li> Facebook Fanpage Scrapper : Get a list of fan pages based on keywords, Get laser targeted traffic by getting a list of fanpages related to your keyword. If you are in marketing you can grab all marketing fan pages, comment there promoting you marketing related offer.<br></li><li> Craigslist and Fiver Arbitrage : Scrape Craigslist and find people that need a service then Scrape fiverr find people that would do the service for 5 dollars then resell that service to other people at a higher price. Keep the difference. That simple.Make money being the middle man.<br></li><li> Badoo Girl Liker : Badoo is a site that allows you to meet other people, for dating or friends. You like other people and if they like you back you can talk with them. Its boring to be liking people all day, so let the software like everybody if they like you back you will have more friends, if they don’t then doesn’t matter it took you 1 minute to set up the software.<br></li><li> Google Keyword Scrapper : Get the top 10 websites for a keyword and get the information of that site, like title of the page, description of the page and keywords they try to target. Analyze your competition. Become the God of SEO.<br></li><li> ClickBank Top Products : Clickbank is the bigger retailer of digital products, promote the best affiliate offers and generate recurring income.<br></li><li> Paypal Payment Link Creator : Create payment buttons almost instantaneous without going to PayPal. Create payment link and create short link.<br></li><li> Free Proxies Scrapper : If you ever need to access to a site anonymously, generate fake views or just change your ip for privacy, you need proxies, this modules will generate 200 proxys for you, the proxys are checked regularly so you only will have proxies that work.<br></li><li> Yelp Company Scrapper : Get more leads for your promotions. This will go to yelp and will get the top 10 companies for any keyword you selected. Then you can visit their ads, or website and then call them to offer a service that they need.<br></li><li> Youtube and Google Keyword Suggestion Tool 2016 – Lasser Target Keywords : When you look on google or YouTube , it give you suggestions of what other people typed this are popular and hot keywords, this module extract the keywords and give it to you in a list : <br></li><li> Mega Spinner (Create sppined Articles) : Do you want your ads to be different every time you post on Craigslist or Kijiji.This software will help you to create the spin sintaxis of the ads. That means you post the same ad changing a few words here and there creating multiple variations of the same ad or article. you can type a keyword and it will give you synonyms of that words. Don’t reinvent the wheel.<br></li><li> Youtube Keyword Scrapper : Steal the traffic of your competitors, if you analyze the keyword from multiple videos related, you will see which keywords are more often used, then you can create a new title and description using those keywords. Generating more traffic to your video using the help of your competitors without them knowing. They will wonder about your secret.<br></li><li> Keyword Variation Generator : From a list of keywords, it will give you multiple variations of the keywords, very useful for SEO and dominating any niche : <br></li><li> Kijiji Posting : Kijiji is a classified website just like craiglist, very popular in Canada, Post on Kijiji with the same Features as Craigslist Auto Posting Software : <br></li><li> Torrent Scrapper (The Pirate Bay and Kick Ass Torrent) : Used in conjunction with utorrent and you can download pretty much everything, software, music, videos and ebooks. It uses The pirate bay and kick ass torrent as content provider.<br></li><li> Youtube Video Views Increaser : This software will visit your youtube videos many times, generating more views, you can have multiple videos at the same time, and it will generate traffic to the videos, you can use it for your own channel or sell the traffic to other people. You get traffic on demand with just a few clicks.<br></li><li> Link Cloacker Generator : It will generate php files to redirect your visitors to any page you like, the link would look like <a href="http://yoursite.com/go/anything-you-want"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">http://yoursite.com/go/anything-you-want</a> and you can chose the url that it will link to, plus if you want to direct the traffic to a different page, you can change it afterwards : <br></li><li> Bulk Shortened links : Shorten multiple links and give it to you in a list.<br></li><li> YouTube Comment Scrapper : Do you want to get the comments from a video, but you have to select each comment and copy paste it onto excel, Forget that! Use this software just place the YouTube video id, and get all the comments from that video.<br></li><li> Ebay Best Selling Items Scraper, Most Popular Keywords, Auction sniper.Get the price and URL of the best selling products by keyword, you will find the best selling items by category, the most searched keywords by category, eBay keyword suggestion tool, see what people is looking for, provide it to them its just like printing money. Also spy on your competitions, see what items they are selling and how well they sell, so you only chose products that do sell.<br></li><li> Reddit Scrapping : Are you looking for interesting content for you posts, or articles, well you are lucky. This software scrape the content from the site Reddit where users thumbs up images, videos, articles they like. If it got likes on Reddit that means is interesting, so you can use this for you Facebook post to generate more likes and more engagement in your fanpage/blog/website.<br></li><li> Email, text encryption : Paste your text in the software and encrypt it, this means that the text will not be readable for anyone that does not have the software and the password. Fully secure conversations trough email. (Since the text is encrypted) : <br></li><li> Image Extractor : Want to get all images from a website only with a few clicks. Then use this module. In this module you type the URL with all the pictures that you want to download to your computer, and the software will create a list of the images, and download them individually or all of them and save them in a folder of your choice : <br></li><li> Twitter Tweets Extractor : Get all the tweets of your favorite artist, get quotes, get jokes, get comments made to the specific account that you chose : <br></li><li> Google Image Scraper – Affiliate HTML Code Image Creator : Search google images and create HTML code with your affiliate link.<br></li><li> Anonymous Web browser : Simple Web browser that allows you to change proxy and user agent, you can clear cookies. You can navigate anonymously using proxies. You can create accounts to any site because you will be consider a different user. You can vote multiple times in contests, you by pass sites that banned your ip.<br></li><li> Manual Posting to 28 Classified sites : Simple but powerful, you can use your Craigslist ads already spinned, sing up with the same account as Craigslist and use this module to copy and paste into all the 28 different classified sites, you need more exposure for your ads. Use this and promote anything that you want. You make more sells as your ads will get more exposure to more classified sites.<br></li><li> Fake Name Generator : Whenever you are creating fake accounts or fake profiles, this will give you the name, address, phone and fake information that will allow you to create hundredths of accounts as easy as copying and pasting the information that we give you.<br></li><li> Article Scrapper : Do you need content for your website or eBook? use this software to scrape articles, then you can use the articles as content, you can modify them and then get more exposure for your business. look articles related by keyword.<br></li><li> Qr Code Generator : This will generate you a qr code image that you can use in your graphic design images, to redirect people to your website, you can use it to store information for people to read with their mobile devices, put your affiliate or cpa offer links in the qr code and make people buy from your their phone.<br></li><li> Project and task management module : Track your activities to do, your activities complete, check on the calendar whatever appointment you have. Email yourself the activities for today. Keep organized and order your to do list by priority, Improve your productivity.<br></li><li> Tee spring analyzer : Make money selling t-shirst easy to follow system that will analyze your competition, see what t-shirts do sell and get ideas on what you can sell.<br></li><li> Customer Relationship Managment (CRM) : Keep a track of your clients, suppliers, freelancers, all in one software, you can email them directly trough the software, you can track the interactions with your customers. Check their information right away with our built in search feature by different search types. city, phone, country and more<br></li><li> Point of sale system with inventory : Create invoices or quotes for your clients, you can save your products and services and then select them in the make a sale section, it will tell you the total and will generate you a PDF with a payment link to PayPal, so people can pay you in PayPal optimizing the your process, You can track your orders and see the total revenue you make every month<br></li><li> Landing Page Creator : Create amazing landing pages that will save the information of your visitors (Name and Email) then it will send them to your affiliate page, Build your list while you do your affiliate marketing, make money and then with your list you can email them and promote anything you want. The money is on the list.<br></li><li> Mobile Checker – Email Sender : Search google based on a keyword, then analyze the results to see if they are mobile friendly, if they are not get their email information and email them with your mobile websites services. Make almost instant money, since the google updates they give preference to sites that are mobile friendly.<br></li><li> Yellow Pages Lead Finder – Email Sender : Get leads from yellow pages based on keyword, then it will check if those users are on social media and create a seo report about those sites. Then contact the owners and offer your services about seo, website development and traffic generation<br></li><li> Twitter Auto Follower : Want more twitter followers to promote yourself or your business, give the twitter id of someone relevant in your niche, and follow his fan base, the software will follow them and then they will follow you back. Wait 2 days and then remove the people that did not follow you back. Increase your fan base is so easy and made on autopilot.<br></li><li> Kijiji Ad Scrapper : Type a keyword and find people looking for those services, if i type website development i will find people that need a website, then i can contact them and make money. Getting clients have never been that easier.<br></li><li> Facebook Fanpage Commentor : Use the list of fanpages that we extract with the fanpage extractor and post on every single one of them with multiple accounts, proxy support and cookies cleaning<br><br></li></ul><br><img src="http://autopostingtools.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/11/craigslist-auto-posting-features.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Craigslist AutoPosting Tools 1.72"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>GumtreeDominator 1.13</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/886-gumtreedominator.html</link>
<description>Name : GumtreeDominator Version : 1.13 OS : Windows Type : Gumtree Marketing Price : $499 Homepage : SalePage GumtreeDominator is specially designed to get data for respective niches, so that every business gets their targeted audience easily. Data from various Gumtree categories can be easily extracted according to selected location(s) or directly scrape using URL. It allows saving data in CSV format while running your email marketing campaigns. It&#039;s incredibly easy to configure the scraper and you can start scraping the data within minutes of installing GumtreeDominator. With around 8 million unique visitors a month, Gumtree.com is one of the most visited sites in the UK. Gumtree registers its presence in multiple cities across numerous countries including the United Kingdom, Poland, France, Canada, Australia, New Zealand, South Africa and Hong Kong. Gumtree has the #1 classifieds site in the UK, Australia, South Africa and Singapore. Gumtree largest category of classifieds adverts (goods for sale) attracts up to 2 million ads being every month, along with being a preferred destination for around 200,000 motors listings across the UK any time. Gumtree is also the second largest UK listings site for jobs and the third largest for property. The site recorded 8.1 million unique visitors (as of June 2014). This has immense significance for a marketer trying to attract generate more traffic to its site and thereby converting the traffic to leads, leads to customers and customers to revenue.</description>
<category>Classifieds Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 13:05:50 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Select Campaign : Create, edit or delete a campaigns. Gumtree Scraper : Fetch all the data in a chose Classifieds Category for a specific Country, State/County. Gumtree Data : Store, organize, export or delete data collected from Gumtree. Proxy Setting : Get uninterrupted experience while scraping Gumtree data. Campaign Manager : Maintain records and status of all campaigns.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/T9t6-k6cxE0?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Select Campaign : Create, edit or delete a campaigns.<br></li><li> Gumtree Scraper : Fetch all the data in a chose Classifieds Category for a specific Country, State/County.<br></li><li> Gumtree Data : Store, organize, export or delete data collected from Gumtree.<br></li><li> Proxy Setting : Get uninterrupted experience while scraping Gumtree data.<br></li><li> Campaign Manager : Maintain records and status of all campaigns.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="GumtreeDominator 1.13"><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>CraigsList Dominator 3.02</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/875-craigslist-dominator.html</link>
<description>Name :CraigsList Dominator Version : 3.02 OS : Windows Type : CraigsList Marketing Price : $499 Homepage : SalePage CraigsDominator specially designs to get data for respective niches, so that every business gets their targeted audience easily. Data from various Craigslist categories can be easily extracted according to selected location(s) or directly scrape using URL. It allows saving data in CSV format while running your email marketing campaigns. It&#039;s incredibly easy to configure the scraper and you can start scraping the data within minutes after installing. Craigslist is one big market: according to company executives, the site draws more than 50 billion page views each month. Craiglist, one of the best online classified ads websites, helps business owner across all verticals and niches to advertise, recruit and promote their business to a huge audience in no time and cost. From e-commerce websites to furniture wholesalers, businesses are realizing the marketing power of Craigslist. It gets an estimated 10 million unique visitors per day. With an online classified ads format organized by either region or city, Craigslist connects buyers and sellers in more than 300 communities. Numerous major corporations are now advertising on Craiglist as it?€™s so well-known as a one-stop shopping point for its users. If you&#039;ve never heard of Craigslist or never considered using the site effectively to market your business, CraigsDominator will show you how you can use Craigslist to boost your sales.</description>
<category>Classifieds Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 13:05:29 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Select Campaign : This feature used to create, edit or delete a campaign. You have to select a campaign before performing any operation for respective country/location. Craigslist Scraper : This feature allows user to fetch all the data from the Craigslist site using Direct URL and Location wise method Craigslist Data : Craigslist data feature, specially designed for storing data. It has 2 submodule, one for storing scraped data and one for storing sent mail data. Proxy Setting : Proxy setting provides you to add public and private proxy, to make your process easy and reduce the chance of IP ban. Campaign Manager : Storing all the details regarding the campaign with proper location, category, running status and starting date for a campaign.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/hfsD7cjpcP4?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Select Campaign : This feature used to create, edit or delete a campaign. You have to select a campaign before performing any operation for respective country/location.<br></li><li> Craigslist Scraper : This feature allows user to fetch all the data from the Craigslist site using Direct URL and Location wise method<br></li><li> Craigslist Data : Craigslist data feature, specially designed for storing data. It has 2 submodule, one for storing scraped data and one for storing sent mail data.<br></li><li> Proxy Setting : Proxy setting provides you to add public and private proxy, to make your process easy and reduce the chance of IP ban.<br></li><li> Campaign Manager : Storing all the details regarding the campaign with proper location, category, running status and starting date for a campaign.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="CraigsList Dominator 3.02"><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Black Bulk Mail Elite 1.4.5</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1060-black-bulk-mail.html</link>
<description>Name : Black Bulk Mail Version : Elite 1.4.5 OS : Windows Type : Email Marketing Tools Price : $699 Homepage : SalePage BlackBulkMail - The Smartest Mailer On the Earth! BlackBulkMail can not only uses the biggest email services(hotmail/outlook/live, yahoo, gmail and aol) to send emails, but also it can let you create yourself sending template to send emails using any email account. BlackBulkMail uses webmail (no smtp) to send emails just like you do in your regular browser.</description>
<category>Bulk Mail Sender</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.blackbulkmail.com/css/images/slide-img.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 13:02:05 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Task - Create, Manage and Run Unlimited Task(s) Create and run unlimited task(s) at the same time. Create and run a maximum of 2 task(s) at the same time. Create and run a maximum of 1 task at the same time. Send emails using webmail with no need for smtp. Send unlimited emails using yahoo/outlook/gmail/aol/hotmail accounts super fast. Customize your sending settings using &#039;TO&#039;, &#039;BCC&#039; or &#039;CC&#039; and set the number of recipients per email. Seed email function - add your own email addresses so that you can monitor your inbox success rate. Suppress list - BBM will not send emails to the recipients in this list. (List normally supplied by your CPA company) Loop send option to guarantee that all emails are sent successfully. BBM is 100% set and forget. Realtime sending stats. Account - Perfect Account Management Manage millions of accounts for different task(s). Auto-categorized accounts based on account status (valid, invalid, banned, blocked and locked etc) Remove non functional accounts automatically, so that all tasks will always use working accounts to send emails. Template - Create Amazing Email Template Easily! Add unlimited email templates, so that you can run different campaigns at the same time. Create and send html email templates. Create and send plaint text email templates. Load csv files to create personalised variables in the email template, so that you can send emails such as: &quot;Hi [name],&quot;. Supports the use of tokenized variables or spun text to create unique subjects and messages. Settings - Proxy, Captcha and Spinner Settings Supports unlimited threads for every task to send emails super fast. Supports a maximum of 3 threads for every task to send emails fast. Only supports 1 thread for every task. Auto-captcha solving solution support. Select proxies randomly. Can auto-bind proxy with accounts so that the account logs in with te same IP every time. Helps to prevent account ban. Stats - Full Statistical Functions! Get realtime and full sending stats for every task (Sent, Left, Success Amount, Failed Amount and Speed etc.) Get realtime accounts status stats (valid, invalid, locked, need verify and blocked etc.) Get email open stats. Get update freely.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/9VKDWp58cDk?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Task - Create, Manage and Run Unlimited Task(s)<br></li><li> Create and run unlimited task(s) at the same time. 			<br></li><li> Create and run a maximum of 2 task(s) at the same time. 			<br></li><li> Create and run a maximum of 1 task at the same time. 			<br></li><li> Send emails using webmail with no need for smtp. 			<br></li><li> Send unlimited emails using yahoo/outlook/gmail/aol/hotmail accounts super fast. 			<br></li><li> Customize your sending settings using 'TO', 'BCC' or 'CC' and set the number of recipients per email. 			<br></li><li> Seed email function - add your own email addresses so that you can monitor your inbox success rate. 			<br></li><li> Suppress list - BBM will not send emails to the recipients in this list. (List normally supplied by your CPA company) 			<br></li><li> Loop send option to guarantee that all emails are sent successfully. BBM is 100% set and forget. 			<br></li><li> Realtime sending stats. 			<br></li><li> Account - Perfect Account Management<br></li><li> Manage millions of accounts for different task(s). 			<br></li><li> Auto-categorized accounts based on account status (valid, invalid, banned, blocked and locked etc) 			<br></li><li> Remove non functional accounts automatically, so that all tasks will always use working accounts to send emails. 			<br></li><li> Template - Create Amazing Email Template Easily!<br></li><li> Add unlimited email templates, so that you can run different campaigns at the same time. 			<br></li><li> Create and send html email templates. 			<br></li><li> Create and send plaint text email templates. 			<br></li><li> Load csv files to create personalised variables in the email template, so that you can send emails such as: "Hi [name],". 			<br></li><li> Supports the use of tokenized variables or spun text to create unique subjects and messages. 			<br></li><li> Settings - Proxy, Captcha and Spinner Settings<br></li><li> Supports unlimited threads for every task to send emails super fast. 			<br></li><li> Supports a maximum of 3 threads for every task to send emails fast. 			<br></li><li> Only supports 1 thread for every task. 			<br></li><li> Auto-captcha solving solution support. 			<br></li><li> Select proxies randomly. 			<br></li><li> Can auto-bind proxy with accounts so that the account logs in with te same IP every time. Helps to prevent account ban. 			<br></li><li> Stats - Full Statistical Functions!<br></li><li> Get realtime and full sending stats for every task (Sent, Left, Success Amount, Failed Amount and Speed etc.) 			<br></li><li> Get realtime accounts status stats (valid, invalid, locked, need verify and blocked etc.) 			<br></li><li> Get email open stats. 			<br></li><li> Get update freely.<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://www.blackbulkmail.com/css/images/slide-img.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Black Bulk Mail Elite 1.4.5"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Lead Power Machine 1.0.13</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1156-lead-power-machine.html</link>
<description>Name : Lead Power Machine Version : 1.0.13 OS : Windows/MAC Type : Lead Marketing Price : $1250 Homepage : SalePage Here&#039;s the best way ever to find prospects... Sell them products they desperately want and need for $500 to $1K each, and... Automatically create the product with 5 mouse clicks. Check this out.</description>
<category>Local Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 15:46:05 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features With Lead Power Machine, I Can Determine Which Ones Have Websites and Mobile Websites, Instantly Create Mobile Websites and Apps, Instantly E-mail and Automatically Follow Up with Leads even with Video E-mail, and More ... All Faster, Easier, and More Effortless Than Ever Before! Get Instantaneous Access to Tens, Hundreds or Even Thousands of Leads- Email All Your Leads with a Touch of a Button No messing around with websites that don&#039;t convert or search engine optimization techniques that don&#039;t work You get immediate access to REAL TIME generated leads that YOU CONTROL No more paying for leads! Identify hundreds even thousands of &quot;targeted&quot; motivated buyers easily and effortlessly, and you can even email them all with the click of a mouse Be Able to run software runs practically on autopilot Gain an UNFAIR ADVANTAGE over your competition in any area in the country or internationally!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/eiQbPMny9f0?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> With Lead Power Machine, I Can Determine Which Ones Have Websites and Mobile Websites, Instantly Create Mobile Websites and Apps, Instantly E-mail and Automatically Follow Up with Leads even with Video E-mail, and More ... All Faster, Easier, and More Effortless Than Ever Before!<br></li><li> Get Instantaneous Access to Tens, Hundreds or Even Thousands of Leads- Email All Your Leads with a Touch of a Button<br></li><li> No messing around with websites that don't convert or search engine optimization techniques that don't work<br></li><li> You get immediate access to REAL TIME generated leads that YOU CONTROL<br></li><li> No more paying for leads!<br></li><li> Identify hundreds even thousands of "targeted" motivated buyers easily and effortlessly, and you can even email them all with the click of a mouse<br></li><li> Be Able to run software runs practically on autopilot<br></li><li> Gain an UNFAIR ADVANTAGE over your competition in any area in the country or internationally!<br></li></ul><br><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Lead Power Machine 1.0.13"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Online Lead Finder 3.5.36</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/909-online-lead-finder.html</link>
<description>Name : Online Lead Finder Version : 3.5.36 Sliver &amp;amp; Social Bot OS : Windows Type : Social Bot and Lead Marketing Price : $797 Homepage : SalePage You&#039;re About To Discover A Software Tool That Tirelessly Works for You To Find HOT Leads and Create Massive Profits!&quot; We all know that you can&#039;t do business without leads that then turn into suspects, prospects, and paying customers. You need lots of leads to work in order to generate your sales, whether it&#039;s Inte.com marketing, insurance, affiliate marketing, real estate, eBay, auto related, or any of a hundred other businesses.</description>
<category>Local Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-07/thumbs/1437773655_olftgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 12:05:33 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Cragislist, BackPage, Ebay Lead Search Yellow Pages Scraper Automated Twitter Marketing Twitter Trends Demand Traffic Facebook Lead Serve Social Lead Detective Google Maps Extractor Yahoo Auto Answer Bot Social Mail Hacker Linked Lead Connect Email Gunner FB Open Graph Investigator Miracle Traffic Bot YouTube Dominator Details Classifieds Posters : Craigslist Poster, Backpage Poster Twitter Marketing : Twitter Trends Finder, Twitter Follow/UnFollow Bot, Twitter Message Bot Google/Plus : Google Lead Sleuth, Google Plus Lead Detective FaceBook Marketing : FB Open Graph Investigator (Graph Search, Facebook Friend Request), FB Lead Server (By Keyword, Events, Groups) Social Email Extractor : Extract &amp;amp; Filter From GooglePlus,Facebook,Twitter,MySpace,Linkedin, Plurk, Reddit, Friendster, Badoo, Ning, Xing Linkedin Marketing : Message to Linkedin Member, Get Linkedin Group Category, Join Linkedin Group, Invite to Linkedin Group, Export Connection Member, Share with Linkedin Groups Facebook Marketing : Search and Like Page, Send Message to Page, Search and Join Group,Export Facebook Group Category, Send Message to Facebook Groups, Send File to Facebook Groups, Create Event For Facebook Groups Instagram Marketing : Search and Follow/UnFollow Yahoo Marketing : Search and Join Yahoo Group, Yahoo Mass Mailer, Post to Yahoo Group SEO Marketing: + Article Submision : Support Articlecube, ezinearticles, Articlecity, Articlebase, Articlestarts, Artipot, Pubartilces + PressRelease Submission : Support BigNews, BriefingWire, Kontax, Pressbox, Postafreepressrelease, PrUrgent, Powerhomebiz + Social Bookmarking : Support delicious, folkd, SocioPost, Startaid, 1look4 + Video Submison : Support bofunk, Veoh, Photobuck, 4Shared, Engagemedia, Vimeo + WordPress Search &amp;amp; Commenter Youtube Send Message and Comments Pinterest Marketing : Gather pin/usernameID&#039;s, Autofollow/unfollow, Auto Like, Auto Comment, Auto Repin, Auto invite Classifieds ADPosters : Support 33 Popular Classified sites, Article Spin, Parse &amp;amp; Auto Register. Bulk Mailer Article Scraper Yellow Pages Lead Scraper HomeAdvisor Lead Scraper US Business Listing Lead Scraper Google Lead Scraper Local SEO Intel Yahoo Answer Bot : Search and Answer, Real Time Questions - Answer, Vote Answer Bot, Best Answer Bot</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/EpdvDwnNoYY?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><p><br></p><br><h3>Features</h3><br><p><br><ul><li> Cragislist, BackPage, Ebay Lead Search<br></li><li> Yellow Pages Scraper<br></li><li> Automated Twitter Marketing<br></li><li> Twitter Trends Demand Traffic<br></li><li> Facebook Lead Serve<br></li><li> Social Lead Detective<br></li><li> Google Maps Extractor<br></li><li> Yahoo Auto Answer Bot<br></li><li> Social Mail Hacker<br></li><li> Linked Lead Connect<br></li><li> Email Gunner<br></li><li> FB Open Graph Investigator<br></li><li> Miracle Traffic Bot<br></li><li> YouTube Dominator<br></li></ul><br>Details<br><ul><li> Classifieds Posters : Craigslist Poster, Backpage Poster<br></li><li> Twitter Marketing : Twitter Trends Finder, Twitter Follow/UnFollow Bot, Twitter Message Bot<br></li><li> Google/Plus : Google Lead Sleuth, Google Plus Lead Detective<br></li><li> FaceBook Marketing : FB Open Graph Investigator (Graph Search, Facebook Friend Request), FB Lead Server (By Keyword, Events, Groups)<br></li><li> Social Email Extractor : Extract &amp; Filter From GooglePlus,Facebook,Twitter,MySpace,Linkedin, Plurk, Reddit, Friendster, Badoo, Ning, Xing<br></li><li> Linkedin Marketing : Message to Linkedin Member, Get Linkedin Group Category, Join Linkedin Group, Invite to Linkedin Group, Export Connection Member, Share with Linkedin Groups<br></li><li> Facebook Marketing : Search and Like Page, Send Message to Page, Search and Join Group,Export Facebook Group Category, Send Message to Facebook Groups, Send File to Facebook Groups, Create Event For Facebook Groups<br></li><li> Instagram Marketing : Search and Follow/UnFollow<br></li><li> Yahoo Marketing : Search and Join Yahoo Group, Yahoo Mass Mailer, Post to Yahoo Group<br></li><li> SEO Marketing: <br></li><li> + Article Submision : Support Articlecube, ezinearticles, Articlecity, Articlebase, Articlestarts, Artipot, Pubartilces<br></li><li> + PressRelease Submission : Support BigNews, BriefingWire, Kontax, Pressbox, Postafreepressrelease, PrUrgent, Powerhomebiz<br></li><li> + Social Bookmarking : Support delicious, folkd, SocioPost, Startaid, 1look4<br></li><li> + Video Submison : Support bofunk, Veoh, Photobuck, 4Shared, Engagemedia, Vimeo<br></li><li> + WordPress Search &amp; Commenter<br></li><li> Youtube Send Message and Comments <br></li><li> Pinterest Marketing : Gather pin/usernameID's, Autofollow/unfollow, Auto Like, Auto Comment, Auto Repin, Auto invite<br></li><li> Classifieds ADPosters : Support 33 Popular Classified sites, Article Spin, Parse &amp; Auto Register.<br></li><li> Bulk Mailer<br></li><li> Article Scraper<br></li><li> Yellow Pages Lead Scraper<br></li><li> HomeAdvisor Lead Scraper<br></li><li> US Business Listing Lead Scraper<br></li><li> Google Lead Scraper<br></li><li> Local SEO Intel<br></li><li> Yahoo Answer Bot : Search and Answer, Real Time Questions - Answer, Vote Answer Bot, Best Answer Bot<br></li></ul><br><a href="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-07/1437773655_olftgmember.png" class="highslide" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-07/thumbs/1437773655_olftgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=''></a></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Online Lead Finder 3.5.36"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Paigham Bot 9.0.7.6</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1973-paigham-bot.html</link>
<description>Name : Paigham Bot Version : 9.0.7.6 OS : Windows Type : Traffic Generator Software Price : $499 Homepage : SalePage Paigham Bot is one of the most effective marketing applications on the market today. It is able to accurately gather data from search engines in any industry or niche and provides contact details for businesses and people that are most important to you i.e. YOUR MOST PRIZED PROSPECTS-AND WILL CONTACT THEM FOR YOU.</description>
<category>Local Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://i.imgur.com/86eAR68.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 07:47:32 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features BRAND NEW USER INTERFACE (allows for easier user application management) New Keyword Management Module(Manually add, edit, delete and track your keywords) New Search Engine Selectors (Additional Google.com extensions) Separate Scraping and Posting Modules (Allows for easier campaign management) Advanced Tag Control Module Tag Collector Enhanced targeting abilities with the Smart Niche &amp;amp; Search Engine Filters. Powerful Short Codes-Incorporate data from each site into your message Updated Captcha Solving API Integration (Use your DBC account to solve captcha’s) Individual Module reports (exportable txt and csv files) Two Proxy Management Integration tools (Upload Proxies or Connect Your HMA Account) Acquire Data From Your Audience (Social Accounts, Phone #’s, emails and more) Directly contact your audience automatically (Has ability to post to 100 sites per minute) Multiple Posting Variations (Send 100% Unique Messages To Each Prospect) Footprint Management Tools (Easily modify your search engine operators) Scraping Throttle (Control how fast Paigham Bot Finds new sites) Multi-Threading Abilities (Run up to 20 Posting threads)</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/oVk064qJ9sg?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><p><br></p><br><h3>Features</h3><br><p><br><ul><li> BRAND NEW USER INTERFACE (allows for easier user application management)<br></li><li> New Keyword Management Module(Manually add, edit, delete and track your keywords)<br></li><li> New Search Engine Selectors (Additional Google.com extensions)<br></li><li> Separate Scraping and Posting Modules (Allows for easier campaign management)<br></li><li> Advanced Tag Control Module<br></li><li> Tag Collector<br></li><li> Enhanced targeting abilities with the Smart Niche &amp; Search Engine Filters.<br></li><li> Powerful Short Codes-Incorporate data from each site into your message<br></li><li> Updated Captcha Solving API Integration (Use your DBC account to solve captcha’s)<br></li><li> Individual Module reports (exportable txt and csv files)<br></li><li> Two Proxy Management Integration tools (Upload Proxies or Connect Your HMA Account)<br></li><li> Acquire Data From Your Audience (Social Accounts, Phone #’s, emails and more)<br></li><li> Directly contact your audience automatically (Has ability to post to 100 sites per minute)<br></li><li> Multiple Posting Variations (Send 100% Unique Messages To Each Prospect)<br></li><li> Footprint Management Tools (Easily modify your search engine operators)<br></li><li> Scraping Throttle (Control how fast Paigham Bot Finds new sites)<br></li><li> Multi-Threading Abilities (Run up to 20 Posting threads)<br><br></li></ul><br><img src="http://i.imgur.com/86eAR68.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Paigham Bot 9.0.7.6"></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Atomic Mail Verifier 9.41</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1520-atomic-mail-verifier.html</link>
<description>Name : Atomic Mail Verifier Version : 9.41 OS : Windows Type : Mail Verifier Price : $50 Homepage : SalePage After conducting market research and obtaining a list of email addresses, one of the most important tasks for effective email marketing is to verify the existence of email addresses. This will help you to avoid sending messages to nonexistent email addresses The program uses three methods to verify the validity of email addresses. This allows you to check addresses quickly and efficiently. All procedures are performed in multithread mode, and they use all the features of the Inte.com channel. Simply upload the list of addresses into the program, click “Check” – and you can go on with your day. Free email verifier no longer requires your participation and will carefully analyze email addresses, presenting, as a result, the status of each address (whether the mailbox exists, is it correct, and so on). Periodically checking your email addresses with the use of email verifier software is a very useful practice. In such a way you can drop out many invalid contacts of your customer database. With a great variety of features, Atomic Mail Verifier is a market leader. Its detailed check will make your mailing list relevant. By choosing email address verifier, you made the right and rational investment towards the development of your business. Features like quick verification speed, unlimited lists, export and import opportunities, and integration with other Atomic products will make you a fan of this free bulk email verifier!</description>
<category>Mail Verifier</category>
<enclosure url="https://cdn.atompark.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/10/export_wizard.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 00:02:06 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Three-level validity check You can verify emails in three steps. This three-level validity check gives the most effective results. Each of the three steps can be executed separately, or combined to form one big verification process. The steps are: Syntax check. This is basic verification. Addressesare checked for correspondence to the RFC registration. Domain check. The domain’s existence is checked. In the case of a nonexistent domain, the email address would also be nonexistent. Email address check. This is the last step of full verification. Atomic Mail Verifier searches for a domain’s SMTP server, and checks the user’s existence. With such reliable verification, you can exclude as many nonexistent email addresses as possible. You will also prevent deletion of truly valid emails using an email list cleaning software. Advanced validation The user is free to choose the necessary type of validation: Standard. This type of check involves standard verification algorithms. Advanced validation. If you’ve got multiple domains, this type of validation will be especially effective. In the filter settings, pick out the domains you want to be checked. Advanced validation dramatically increases the quality of email verification and have an effect on email open rate for future campaigns. Domain rules You have the opportunity to set rules for existing domains. You just need to select a domain and specify a rule for it. What does a rule look like? It is a kind of default status for selected domains. Here are some available rules: Always “Correct” Always “Incorrect” Always “Missed” Always “Unchecked” Filter rule existence provides a good opportunity to control the process of verification. Verification with Facebook The program gives users the opportunity to check the validity of emails and the existence of their owners by checking for accounts on Facebook. At the end of the verification process, the user gets all information available about the email address’ owner from his or her personal Facebook page. Mailing list import You can load lists from: Clipboard *.doc, *.docx, *.txt, *.xls, and *.xlsx files Outlook Address Book Due to the program’s full integration with other Atomic products, mailing lists can be imported directly from Atomic Lead Extractor, Atomic Newsgroup Explorer, and Atomic WHOIS Explorer. Proxy support Atomic Mail Verifier supports several types of proxy servers: Socks 4 proxy, Socks 4a proxy, and Socks 5 proxy. You can manually set the settings of your proxy server (“General Settings / Proxy”). The program constantly monitors the proxy servers. The frequency of proxy checks are also set by the user. Export functions All the verified addresses can be saved to: MS Office (Word, Excel) Open Office (Writer, Calc) Text file Clipboard The saved document will contain only existing addresses. If you need to export all email addresses (correct, incorrect, and unchecked) to a different file format, use Export Wizard. It will save the data in the form of columns with names and statuses.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><div class="dlevideoplayer" style="width:100%;max-width:425px;">
			<ul data-theme="default" data-preload="metadata">
				<li data-title="file" data-type="m4v" data-url="https://embed-ssl.wistia.com/deliveries/23c8d28aded7760c31094570dc1eb0b72a24f65c/file.mp4" ></li>
			</ul>
		</div></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><b>Three-level validity check</b><br>You can verify emails in three steps. This three-level validity check gives the most effective results. Each of the three steps can be executed separately, or combined to form one big verification process. The steps are:<br><ul><li> Syntax check. This is basic verification. Addressesare checked for correspondence to the RFC registration.<br></li><li> Domain check. The domain’s existence is checked. In the case of a nonexistent domain, the email address would also be nonexistent.<br></li><li> Email address check. This is the last step of full verification. Atomic Mail Verifier searches for a domain’s SMTP server, and checks the user’s existence.<br></li></ul><br>With such reliable verification, you can exclude as many nonexistent email addresses as possible. You will also prevent deletion of truly valid emails using an email list cleaning software.<br><b>Advanced validation</b><br> The user is free to choose the necessary type of validation:<br><ul><li> Standard. This type of check involves standard verification algorithms.<br></li><li> Advanced validation. If you’ve got multiple domains, this type of validation will be especially effective. In the filter settings, pick out the domains you want to be checked. Advanced validation dramatically increases the quality of email verification and have an effect on email open rate for future campaigns.<br></li></ul><br><b>Domain rules</b><br>You have the opportunity to set rules for existing domains. You just need to select a domain and specify a rule for it. What does a rule look like? It is a kind of default status for selected domains. Here are some available rules:<br><ul><li> Always “Correct”<br></li><li> Always “Incorrect”<br></li><li> Always “Missed”<br></li><li> Always “Unchecked”<br></li></ul><br>Filter rule existence provides a good opportunity to control the process of verification.<br><br><b>Verification with Facebook</b><br><br>The program gives users the opportunity to check the validity of emails and the existence of their owners by checking for accounts on Facebook. At the end of the verification process, the user gets all information available about the email address’ owner from his or her personal Facebook page.<br><b>Mailing list import</b><br>You can load lists from:<br><ul><li> Clipboard<br></li><li> *.doc, *.docx, *.txt, *.xls, and *.xlsx files<br></li><li> Outlook Address Book<br></li><li> Due to the program’s full integration with other Atomic products, mailing lists can be imported directly from Atomic Lead Extractor, Atomic Newsgroup Explorer, and Atomic WHOIS Explorer.<br></li></ul><br><b>Proxy support</b><br>Atomic Mail Verifier supports several types of proxy servers: Socks 4 proxy, Socks 4a proxy, and Socks 5 proxy.<br><br>You can manually set the settings of your proxy server (“General Settings / Proxy”). The program constantly monitors the proxy servers. The frequency of proxy checks are also set by the user.<br><b>Export functions</b><br>All the verified addresses can be saved to:<br><ul><li> MS Office (Word, Excel)<br></li><li> Open Office (Writer, Calc)<br></li><li> Text file<br></li><li> Clipboard<br></li></ul><br>The saved document will contain only existing addresses. If you need to export all email addresses (correct, incorrect, and unchecked) to a different file format, use Export Wizard. It will save the data in the form of columns with names and statuses.<br><img src="https://cdn.atompark.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/10/export_wizard.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Atomic Mail Verifier 9.41"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>TeKnife Yellow Pages Scraper 1.0.2</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4279-teknife-yellow-pages-scraper.html</link>
<description>Name : TeKnife Yellow Pages Scraper Version : 1.0.2 OS : Windows Type : Yellow Pages Scraper Price : $0 Homepage : SalePage TeKnife Yellow Pages Scraper</description>
<category>Local Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 09:22:41 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Extract Full Data from Yellow Pages based on keywords and locations . Proxy support . 7 Days Free Trial Full Functionality .</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Extract Full Data from Yellow Pages based on keywords and locations .<br></li><li> Proxy support .<br></li><li> 7 Days Free Trial Full Functionality .<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="TeKnife Yellow Pages Scraper 1.0.2"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Email List Cleaner 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4207-email-list-cleaner.html</link>
<description>list] Name : Email List Cleaner Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Email Marketing Tool Price : $59 Homepage : SalePage Email List Cleaner is a software tool that allows users to import their email lists then each email address will be filtered through up to 10 different rules to determine if its a real valid email address that is worth sending emails to.</description>
<category>List Managers</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2018 21:55:36 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Here is the list of filters that are applied to each email address. - SMTP check - We will connect to the server (so if the email address is alex@gmail.com we connect to gmail.com MX records) mailbox then ask the mail server if the mailbox exists. While this works perfectly for gmail from any IP address some other mail servers such as hotmail will not allow this check from a residential IP address as rDNS must be setup. However as we only mark the email address as invalid if we receive a mailbox does not exist error we eliminate any false positives. - Gibberish check - We check each email address for mixes of letters and numbers that contain few unique letters and numbers. For example abcde@gmail.com would pass but aaaa@gmail.com would fail the list clean. - Rude word check - Swear words and words that are not commonly in email addresses cause these emails to be filtered out. - Valid email (loose check) - Checks email address to see if they contain only letters and numbers, - _ and @ - Valid email (loose check) - Checks email address to see if they conform to the RFC 5322 standard. - Known temp disposable email domain - Checks to see if the email contains a known temp disposable email domain from the softwares internal database of known temp disposable email domains - Suspected temp disposable email domain - At the start of the run this settings will search Google for keywords such as &quot;disposable email address&quot;. Then it will crawl all the results extracting and validating all the domains it can find on these disposable email address websites, while being careful not to exclude known good email domains. - Email domain DNS resolves - Checks to see if the domain on the email has DNS that successfully resolves. - Check if domain has MX records - Checks the email domain to see if it has MX records set. - Duplicate check - Checks to see if email address is a duplicate and already in imported email list.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/GDYb4mfsRGc?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Here is the list of filters that are applied to each email address. <br></li><li> - SMTP check - We will connect to the server (so if the email address is alex@gmail.com we connect to gmail.com MX records) mailbox then ask the mail server if the mailbox exists. While this works perfectly for gmail from any IP address some other mail servers such as hotmail will not allow this check from a residential IP address as rDNS must be setup. However as we only mark the email address as invalid if we receive a mailbox does not exist error we eliminate any false positives.<br></li><li> - Gibberish check - We check each email address for mixes of letters and numbers that contain few unique letters and numbers. For example abcde@gmail.com would pass but aaaa@gmail.com would fail the list clean.<br></li><li> - Rude word check - Swear words and words that are not commonly in email addresses cause these emails to be filtered out.<br></li><li> - Valid email (loose check) - Checks email address to see if they contain only letters and numbers, - _ and @<br></li><li> - Valid email (loose check) - Checks email address to see if they conform to the RFC 5322 standard.<br></li><li> - Known temp disposable email domain - Checks to see if the email contains a known temp disposable email domain from the softwares internal database of known temp disposable email domains<br></li><li> - Suspected temp disposable email domain - At the start of the run this settings will search Google for keywords such as "disposable email address". Then it will crawl all the results extracting and validating all the domains it can find on these disposable email address websites, while being careful not to exclude known good email domains.<br></li><li> - Email domain DNS resolves - Checks to see if the domain on the email has DNS that successfully resolves.<br></li><li> - Check if domain has MX records - Checks the email domain to see if it has MX records set.<br></li><li> - Duplicate check - Checks to see if email address is a duplicate and already in imported email list.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Email List Cleaner 1.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>