<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Captcha Solver - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Captcha Solver - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>GSA Captcha Breaker 3.73</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1029-gsa-captcha-breaker.html</link>
<description>GSA Captcha Breaker is the revolutionary breakthrough software that effortlessly analyses and solves captchas for you. After you get GSA Captcha Breaker, you won&#039;t need to type in captchas manually or pay others to solve them again. Paid captcha services like decaptcher or death-by-captcha are going up in price with no end in sight. The GSA Captcha Breaker program faithfully simulates these captcha services. Just say no to monthly fees. Not only will you have cutting edge decaptcher and death-by-captcha simulation power, you will be able to work with any other software that uses those services. GSA Captcha Breaker is incredibly simple to use. As soon as it starts up, you are ready. Just go to the program that makes use of captcha services and type in any login/password.</description>
<category>Captcha Solver</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-05/1431542544_1zf7i83.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-05/1431542806_gsa-ser-extension.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-05/1431542756_gsa-trial-reset.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2018 22:59:04 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>But the software does not stop there. You will still have the option to make use of captcha services (e.g. if something is unsolvable or you set options to send all from a special captcha type straight to the service). This can be extremely useful for difficult captchas like reCaptcha. GSA Captcha Breaker is so advanced that, depending on the level of difficulty for the captchas you routinely need to solve, it is likely that the software will automatically solve all of your captchas on the spot. As needed, the smooth forwarding to paid captcha services functions under the hood for a seamlessly integrated fully satisfying captcha solving experience. The new GSA Captcha Breaker features very easy editing so you can add your own captcha solving algorithms. You can double click on one incoming captcha in the log and the editor opens so that you can run a “brute force” to find a good way to solve it. Your new captcha type is just 3 quick clicks away. You also have the ability to share your captcha type solves online with other users. This is just one of the many benefits you will gain when you join our exclusive GSA Captcha Breaker community. Why not take it for a test drive today? Download the FREE 5 day demo version right now. Remember, you pay nothing and it&#039;s totally risk-free. You get the full product with all the bells and whistles. The only limitation is that you will need to restart it after 100 captcha solves. When you purchase your single-PC license, that&#039;s it. There are no subscription fees. You will receive our life-time updates for free. We are famous for our unusually frequent updates. Your single-PC license can be installed on more than one computer as needed. However, you can RUN it on only ONE computer at the same time. Download your free fully-featured copy of GSA Captcha Breaker today. You have nothing to lose and everything to gain. Never pay per captcha again. Note: GSA Captcha Breaker should be used for research and by the visually impaired only. Any illegal use of GSA Captcha Breaker is strictly prohibited. Although the new GSA Captcha Breaker is the best captcha solving software on the pl.com, in the real world it is not possible for a software program to solve everything correctly all of the time. As you know, some captchas are hard to read and solve even for humans! Please keep that in mind and be patient when you see an inaccurate result. This really is the best captcha solution you can own. Here&#039;s What You Get with the Amazing New GSA Captcha Breaker: - loaded with more than 600 pre-configured captcha types to solve - works with every software using decaptcher or death-by-captcha (plus 5+ other services) - automatically sends unsolvable captchas to captcha services - includes powerful super easy editor for creating your own captcha definitions - employs multiple ocr techniques and other advanced self-made algorithms to solve captchas - solves most captcha types with a 100% success rate - makes you money every time you use it by cutting down your old captcha service costs - saves you bandwidth as captchas no longer need to be sent to captcha services - tested and working on all Windows systems from XP to Windows8 without any known problems and without the crashes you will experience from other tools in this market - import/share new or improved captcha types with others in our exclusive user community - just a one-time purchase with NO subscription plus generous FREE life-time updates - able to work as a proxy to simulate decaptcher and send to a cheaper service</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/dxpW6vvBNaY?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br>But the software does not stop there. You will still have the option to make use of captcha services (e.g. if something is unsolvable or you set options to send all from a special captcha type straight to the service). This can be extremely useful for difficult captchas like reCaptcha.<br><br>GSA Captcha Breaker is so advanced that, depending on the level of difficulty for the captchas you routinely need to solve, it is likely that the software will automatically solve all of your captchas on the spot. As needed, the smooth forwarding to paid captcha services functions under the hood for a seamlessly integrated fully satisfying captcha solving experience.<br><br>The new GSA Captcha Breaker features very easy editing so you can add your own captcha solving algorithms. You can double click on one incoming captcha in the log and the editor opens so that you can run a “brute force” to find a good way to solve it. Your new captcha type is just 3 quick clicks away.<br><br>You also have the ability to share your captcha type solves online with other users. This is just one of the many benefits you will gain when you join our exclusive GSA Captcha Breaker community.<br><br>Why not take it for a test drive today? Download the FREE 5 day demo version right now.<br><br>Remember, you pay nothing and it's totally risk-free. You get the full product with all the bells and whistles. The only limitation is that you will need to restart it after 100 captcha solves.<br><br>When you purchase your single-PC license, that's it. There are no subscription fees. You will receive our life-time updates for free. We are famous for our unusually frequent updates.<br><br>Your single-PC license can be installed on more than one computer as needed. However, you can RUN it on only ONE computer at the same time.<br><br>Download your free fully-featured copy of GSA Captcha Breaker today. You have nothing to lose and everything to gain. Never pay per captcha again.<br><br>Note: GSA Captcha Breaker should be used for research and by the visually impaired only. Any illegal use of GSA Captcha Breaker is strictly prohibited.<br><br>Although the new GSA Captcha Breaker is the best captcha solving software on the pl.com, in the real world it is not possible for a software program to solve everything correctly all of the time. As you know, some captchas are hard to read and solve even for humans! Please keep that in mind and be patient when you see an inaccurate result. This really is the best captcha solution you can own.<br>Here's What You Get with the Amazing New GSA Captcha Breaker:<br>- loaded with more than 600 pre-configured captcha types to solve<br>- works with every software using decaptcher or death-by-captcha (plus 5+ other services)<br>- automatically sends unsolvable captchas to captcha services<br>- includes powerful super easy editor for creating your own captcha definitions<br>- employs multiple ocr techniques and other advanced self-made algorithms to solve captchas<br>- solves most captcha types with a 100% success rate<br>- makes you money every time you use it by cutting down your old captcha service costs<br>- saves you bandwidth as captchas no longer need to be sent to captcha services<br>- tested and working on all Windows systems from XP to Windows8 without any known problems and without the crashes you will experience from other tools in this market<br>- import/share new or improved captcha types with others in our exclusive user community<br>- just a one-time purchase with NO subscription plus generous FREE life-time updates<br>- able to work as a proxy to simulate decaptcher and send to a cheaper service<br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="GSA Captcha Breaker 3.73"></div><br><div class="quote"><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Captcha Sniper X 5.17</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1039-captcha-sniper.html</link>
<description>Name : Captcha Sniper Version : X 5.17 OS : Windows Type : Captcha Slover Price : $97 Homepage : SalePage Captcha Sniper intercepts calls made to most popular captcha solving services including Decaptcha, Death By Captcha, AntiCaptcha and Bypass Captcha. Captcha Sniper solves the captcha and returns the text answer to the calling software and also includes a command line interface.</description>
<category>Captcha Solver</category>
<enclosure url="http://i.imgur.com/xYHPWbU.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 20:44:19 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Slash Your Captcha Solving Costs Solve Captchas On Your Desktop So Simple Even a NOOB Can Use It</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><div class="dlevideoplayer" style="width:100%;max-width:425px;">
			<ul data-theme="default" data-preload="metadata">
				<li data-title="CStwo" data-type="m4v" data-url="http://www.captchasniper.com/video/New/CStwo.mp4" ></li>
			</ul>
		</div></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Slash Your Captcha Solving Costs<br></li><li> Solve Captchas On Your Desktop<br></li><li> So Simple Even a NOOB Can Use It<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://i.imgur.com/xYHPWbU.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Captcha Sniper X 5.17"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>