<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Video Marketing - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Video Marketing - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>Live Event Blaster 2.02 Pro Local</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1749-live-event-blaster.html</link>
<description>Name : Live Event Blaster Version : 2.02 Pro Local OS : Windows Type : Youtube Marketing Price : $99 Homepage : SalePage We Will Change The Way You Are CREATING – UPLOADING – RANKING Videos On YouTube Find Out Why The Top Video Marketers Are Calling This “The Ultimate YouTube Super Weapon”…</description>
<category>Live Stream Tools</category>
<enclosure url="http://i.imgur.com/QJ0L67F.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="http://liveblaster.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/04/features-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2018 13:32:07 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Step 1 : You schedule a live event, YouTube will already index your event, giving you higher rankings than videos… Step 2 : You start streaming your live event . YouTube promotes your event using it’s internal engine! Step 3 : When you finish streaming, your event TRANSFORMS INTO A VIDEO…but keeps its original event rankings!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/262629560?app_id=122963" width="425" height="239" frameborder="0" title="New Sales Video - LEB 2" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Step 1 : You schedule a live event, YouTube will already index your event, giving you higher rankings than videos…<br></li><li> Step 2 : You start streaming your live event .  YouTube promotes your event using it’s internal engine!<br></li><li> Step 3 : When you finish streaming, your event TRANSFORMS INTO A VIDEO…but keeps its original event rankings!<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://i.imgur.com/QJ0L67F.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Live Event Blaster 2.02 Pro Local"><br><img src="http://liveblaster.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/04/features-2.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Soundcloud Manager 3.422</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/930-soundcloud-manager.html</link>
<description>Name : Soundcloud Manager by RootJazz Version : 3.422 OS : Windows Type : Social Marketing, SoundCloud Marketing Price : $97 Homepage : SalePage SoundcloudManager makes it easy to get your music heard above the rest. From track sharing, to initialising interactions with other users, to finding users interested in your music styles. SoundcloudManager gets you REAL followers, REAL likes, REAL comments, REAL plays and REAL reposts</description>
<category>Sound Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 12:56:40 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Increase Soundcloud plays Increase Soundcloud downloads Follow users Multi account follow Bulk create accounts Search and favourite tracks Search and repost tracks (Unique) Bulk Create playlists (Unique) Mass increase track favourites Mass increase track comments Mass increase user followings Mass increase Track Reposts (Unique) Share tracks to users and groups Comment on tracks</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/yfeGtyPpEiE?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><br><ul><li> Increase Soundcloud plays<br></li><li> Increase Soundcloud downloads<br></li><li> Follow users<br></li><li> Multi account follow<br></li><li> Bulk create accounts<br></li><li> Search and favourite tracks<br></li><li> Search and repost tracks (Unique)<br></li><li> Bulk Create playlists (Unique)<br></li><li> Mass increase track favourites<br></li><li> Mass increase track comments<br></li><li> Mass increase user followings<br></li><li> Mass increase Track Reposts (Unique)<br></li><li> Share tracks to users and groups<br></li><li> Comment on tracks<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Soundcloud Manager 3.422"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>VidIQ Vision EnterPrise 2.68.5</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4474-vidiq-vision.html</link>
<description>Name : VidIQ Vision EnterPrise Version : 2.68.5 OS : Windows Type : Video YouTube Tool Price : $39/m Homepage : SalePage Uncover YouTube video success secrets vidIQ Vision for Google Chrome helps you understand why videos are promoted in Related Videos, Search, and Recommended Videos</description>
<category>Youtube Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 11:09:51 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Rank The vidIQ Score helps judge the likelihood of a video being promoted in Related Videos, Search, and Recommended Videos. Discover Success on YouTube is about more than just views — Vision keeps you focused on the metrics that matter. Optimize Use what you learn to drive better decision making for your own content.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/y_AzfqVG8Jw?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Rank<br></li><li> The vidIQ Score helps judge the likelihood of a video being promoted in Related Videos, Search, and Recommended Videos.<br></li><li> Discover<br></li><li> Success on YouTube is about more than just views — Vision keeps you focused on the metrics that matter.<br></li><li> Optimize<br></li><li> Use what you learn to drive better decision making for your own content.<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="VidIQ Vision EnterPrise 2.68.5"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Playinator 7.10</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1751-playinator.html</link>
<description>Name : Playinator Version : 7.10 OS : Windows Type : Youtube Marketing Price : $69 Homepage : SalePage &quot;Tired of Getting Just a Few YouTube Video Views? Are your videos always remaining unseen by the rest of the world?&quot; Well, the solution is here... Playinator is an easy, efficient and fully automated software to increase YouTube views - that will increase the views in all of your videos, and will NOT freeze them at the 300 views mark!</description>
<category>Youtube Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.playinator.com/images/playinator_v6_website_11.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://www.playinator.com/screen_v6.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 16:24:12 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/oC080H67sAs?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><img src="http://www.playinator.com/images/playinator_v6_website_11.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Playinator 7.10"><br><img src="http://www.playinator.com/screen_v6.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Adobe Audition CC 2018 v11.1.1.3</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4489-adobe-audition.html</link>
<description>Name : Adobe Audition CC 2018 Version : v11.1.1.3 OS : Windows Type : Sound Creator Price : $120 Homepage : SalePage Audition CC is a comprehensive toolset that includes multitrack, waveform, and spectral display for creating, mixing, editing, and restoring audio content. This powerful audio workstation is designed to accelerate video production workflows and audio finishing — and deliver a polished mix with pristine sound</description>
<category>Sound Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 12 May 2018 05:46:43 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features What is Audition CC? Meet the industry’s best audio cleanup, restoration, and precision editing tool for video, podcasting, and sound effect design. Record, edit, and integrate music clips. This step-by-step tutorial guides you through the robust audio toolkit that is Adobe Audition, including its seamless workflow with Adobe Premiere Pro CC. Add oomph to your audio. Use the Essential Sound panel to achieve professional-quality audio — even if you’re not a professional.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/_0OZPx4FyD4?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> What is Audition CC?<br></li><li> Meet the industry’s best audio cleanup, restoration, and precision editing tool for video, podcasting, and sound effect design. <br></li><li> Record, edit, and integrate music clips. <br></li><li> This step-by-step tutorial guides you through the robust audio toolkit that is Adobe Audition, including its seamless workflow with Adobe Premiere Pro CC.<br></li><li> Add oomph to your audio.<br></li><li> Use the Essential Sound panel to achieve professional-quality audio — even if you’re not a professional.<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Adobe Audition CC 2018 v11.1.1.3"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Adobe Character Animator CC 2018 1.5</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4488-adobe-character-animator.html</link>
<description>Name : Adobe Character Animator CC 2018 Version : 1.5 OS : Windows Type : 2D Creator Price : $53/m Homepage : SalePage Create a 2D character and make it come alive. Character Animator CC copies your facial movements so your characters act — and react — realistically.</description>
<category>Video Creator</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 12 May 2018 05:46:12 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Start with a character. Build your character from scratch in Illustrator or Photoshop — or start with one of the puppets already available in Character Animator. Animations with legs — and arms and heads. Getting your character to move doesn’t take a lot of work. Control gestures like waving with your keyboard or MIDI device. Movements can be saved as buttons, sliders, or knobs so they’re easier to remember than key commands. And you can smooth transitions between facial poses for a hand-animated look. Put your best face forward. Character Animator tracks your facial expressions — from raised eyebrows to moving lips — in real time and records your motion and voice using your webcam and microphone. So when you look surprised, happy, or angry, your character does, too. It’s showtime. Send your character out into the world. Go live on Facebook or TV. Amuse your friends on social media. Or send it to Adobe Premiere Pro CC or After Effects CC to include in bigger projects like a movie or cartoon.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/lmPo0_WZyPU?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Start with a character.<br></li><li> Build your character from scratch in Illustrator or Photoshop — or start with one of the puppets already available in Character Animator.<br></li><li> Animations with legs — and arms and heads.<br></li><li> Getting your character to move doesn’t take a lot of work. Control gestures like waving with your keyboard or MIDI device. Movements can be saved as buttons, sliders, or knobs so they’re easier to remember than key commands. And you can smooth transitions between facial poses for a hand-animated look.<br></li><li> Put your best face forward.<br></li><li> Character Animator tracks your facial expressions — from raised eyebrows to moving lips — in real time and records your motion and voice using your webcam and microphone. So when you look surprised, happy, or angry, your character does, too.<br></li><li> It’s showtime.<br></li><li> Send your character out into the world. Go live on Facebook or TV. Amuse your friends on social media. Or send it to Adobe Premiere Pro CC or After Effects CC to include in bigger projects like a movie or cartoon.<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Adobe Character Animator CC 2018 1.5"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Channel Authority Builder Pro 1.4</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1379-channel-authority-builder-pro.html</link>
<description>Name : Channel Authority Builder Pro Version : 1.4 OS : Youtube Type : Youtube Marketing Tools Price : $97 Homepage : SalePage A Next Generation Video Marketing System That Helps You To Unlock The Power Of YouTube &amp;amp; Generate Millions Of Views To Your YouTube channel By Discovering Strategies Used By Market Leaders.. This Is The First YouTube Software That Is Focused Totally On Helping Marketers Build Authority Or Target YouTube’s Content Discovery Mechanisms. Most Of The Competing Products Just Go After Keywords Or Search. Channel Authority Builder is a tool which helps people in content planning to create strategic content that is relevant, targets other videos and can get people long term organic traffic, not from search but from YouTube’s content discovery. This is the strategy you need to unlock 80% of the traffic that you’re not getting targeting only keywords, and to create long-term authority channels.</description>
<category>Youtube Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 13:18:20 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Keyword Rank Tracker - Well, it comes with a keyword rank tracker that lets you monitor how your other videos are ranking for keywords on YouTube over time. Video Stats Monitor - Video stats monitor features lets you monitor all the current statistics of any video on YouTube on a daily basis. Channel Stats Monitor - It helps you to monitor all the current statistics for a channel on everyday basis. Latest Videos From Monitored Channels - Well, this is another innovative feature that lets you discover all the latest videos from all those channels you are monitoring. Sidebar Monitor - Lets you find whether you are appearing on a video&#039;s sidebar and the trends there. Related Channels Finder - with this feature you can quickly find all those channels that is related to a YouTube Channel. Trending Tags Finder - Here you can discover what new tags your competitors are targeting right now for the business to boost their videos. Popular Videos Finder - You can find what new videos from your competitors have actually become popular.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/nT5U9y5Mr8c?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Keyword Rank Tracker - Well, it comes with a keyword rank tracker that lets you monitor how your other videos are ranking for keywords on YouTube over time.<br></li><li> Video Stats Monitor - Video stats monitor features lets you monitor all the current statistics of any video on YouTube on a daily basis.<br></li><li> Channel Stats Monitor - It helps you to monitor all the current statistics for a channel on everyday basis.<br></li><li> Latest Videos From Monitored Channels - Well, this is another innovative feature that lets you discover all the latest videos from all those channels you are monitoring.<br></li><li> Sidebar Monitor - Lets you find whether you are appearing on a video's sidebar and the trends there.<br></li><li> Related Channels Finder - with this feature you can quickly find all those channels that is related to a YouTube Channel.<br></li><li> Trending Tags Finder - Here you can discover what new tags your competitors are targeting right now for the business to boost their videos.<br></li><li> Popular Videos Finder - You can find what new videos from your competitors have actually become popular.<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Channel Authority Builder Pro 1.4"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Live Caster Agency 1.5.5</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3629-livecaster-pro.html</link>
<description>Name : LiveCaster + OTOs Version : 1.5.5 Pro OS : Windows Type : Youtube Live Stream Marketing, Facebook Live Stream Marketing Price : $545 Homepage : SalePage This is the best livecasting software made for Facebook &amp;amp; YouTube. Ultra simple to use, it supports scheduling, one-click live mode. Can Cast pre-recorded videos as live to Facebook Personal feed, Pages &amp;amp; even Groups. It can also livecast to YouTube!</description>
<category>Live Stream Tools</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 13:17:35 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Cast pre-recorded videos as live to Facebook Personal feed, Pages &amp;amp; even Groups.And also YouTube channels! Pick up any pre-recorded video and cast it ‘live’ on Facebook or YouTube. Supports scheduling. Cast your videos at any time you want without being there. Cast multiple videos at the same time. Two or even three videos simultaneously. Lets you select the playback quality you want so you can pick up optimum playback for your inte.com speed. Cast live videos to Facebook groups, Facebook pages, Facebook personal feeds and YouTube channels. Casts direct from your computer, gets you the best results for SEO and rankings. Super easy to use! You won’t be wasting time trying to figure out things. Supports &amp;amp; converts from a variety of video formats an sizes. Powerful Scheduling : Schedule your videos for any time, and even schedule multiple videos to run at the same time. Universal Compatibility : Works with Facebook Groups, Pages, Personal Feed &amp;amp; Even YouTube Easy to Use Interface : No need to go through a complicated course to understand it. Everything is just accessible Gets You Higher Rankings : People want to watch live-streamed videos and it&#039;s the best way to link up with trending keywords while providing desired content to your audience and boosting your ranks. Free Traffic From Facebook : Live videos generate high buzz among audience and get your FaceBook pages organic traffic in droves Go Live Whenever You Want : This monster app allows you to livecast any prerecorded videos as live events on YouTube and Facebook. Super Robust Engine : LiveCaster allows you to schedule as many videos as you want to be casted as live event. All you have to do is set it once, and have the App running, along with an inte.com connection. LiveCaster is robust enough to work round the clock, 24/7 to get you maximum engagement from your audience.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/3A3t0UwIMlQ?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><p><br></p><br><h3>Features</h3><br><p><br><ul><li> Cast pre-recorded videos as live to Facebook Personal feed, Pages &amp; even Groups.And also YouTube channels!<br></li><li> Pick up any pre-recorded video and cast it ‘live’ on Facebook or YouTube.<br></li><li> Supports scheduling. Cast your videos at any time you want without being there.<br></li><li> Cast multiple videos at the same time. Two or even three videos simultaneously.<br></li><li> Lets you select the playback quality you want so you can pick up optimum playback for your inte.com speed.<br></li><li> Cast live videos to Facebook groups, Facebook pages, Facebook personal feeds and YouTube channels.<br></li><li> Casts direct from your computer, gets you the best results for SEO and rankings.<br></li><li> Super easy to use! You won’t be wasting time trying to figure out things.<br></li><li> Supports &amp; converts from a variety of video formats an sizes.<br></li><li> Powerful Scheduling : Schedule your videos for any time, and even schedule multiple videos to run at the same time.<br></li><li> Universal Compatibility : Works with Facebook Groups, Pages, Personal Feed &amp; Even YouTube<br></li><li> Easy to Use Interface : No need to go through a complicated course to understand it. Everything is just accessible<br></li><li> Gets You Higher Rankings : People want to watch live-streamed videos and it's the best way to link up with trending keywords while providing desired content to your audience and boosting your ranks.<br></li><li> Free Traffic From Facebook : Live videos generate high buzz among audience and get your FaceBook pages organic traffic in droves<br></li><li> Go Live Whenever You Want : This monster app allows you to livecast any prerecorded videos as live events on YouTube and Facebook.<br></li><li> Super Robust Engine : LiveCaster allows you to schedule as many videos as you want to be casted as live event. All you have to do is set it once, and have the App running, along with an inte.com connection. LiveCaster is robust enough to work round the clock, 24/7 to get you maximum engagement from your audience.</p><br><p><br></li></ul></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Live Caster Agency 1.5.5"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Tube Rank Jeet 4.2 Pro</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/945-tuberank-jeet.html</link>
<description>Name : Tuberank Jeet 3 Pro Version : 4.2 OS : Windows Type : Youtube Marketing Price : $67 Homepage : SalePage Rank Your YouTube Videos on Page #1! This revolutionary video optimization tool is your secret weapon to help you create killer video campaigns that spell DEFEAT for your competition. What are the places you get traffic from right now? Facebook? Google? Is YouTube of one of them? If all your traffic is coming only from Facebook and Google, you’re leaving a big empty hole in your strategy. It’s like running a car with one tyre flat. You’re moving, but it’s not fast enough, and you’re forced to watch all those other guys zip by. You see, YouTube is the third most popular website of the world with 1.3 billion active users, and over 1 billion video views per day. Yes, the world is watching YouTube and if you cannot be found there, you’re letting too much money escape!</description>
<category>Youtube Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://tuberankjeet.com/Content/salesimg/product.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 13:16:33 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Tells you what is the traffic and ranking potential for absolutely any keyword. Analyzes existing videos ranking for your niche or keyword and finds out what you need to beat them. Finds you three levels of keywords a) Long-tail for easy ranking, b) Medium value for traffic with minimal effort and c) High value for top quality traffic. Viewer sentiment analysis tells you what exactly people feel about your niche or keyword telling you where the market is headed. Grab stats and tags from any video you want, appear on its related videos bar. Proven algorithm gives you the ranking-recipe, telling you exactly what you need to do to rank. Everything right at your fingertips to make optimization a 2-minute process. Save your time! Uploads videos directly to YouTube, Vimeo (Pro Version) or Dailymotion (Pro Version)</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/W6dmHzPXEFQ?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Tells you what is the traffic and ranking potential for absolutely any keyword.<br></li><li> Analyzes existing videos ranking for your niche or keyword and finds out what you need to beat them.<br></li><li> Finds you three levels of keywords a) Long-tail for easy ranking, b) Medium value for traffic with minimal effort and c) High value for top quality traffic.<br></li><li> Viewer sentiment analysis tells you what exactly people feel about your niche or keyword telling you where the market is headed.<br></li><li> Grab stats and tags from any video you want, appear on its related videos bar.<br></li><li> Proven algorithm gives you the ranking-recipe, telling you exactly what you need to do to rank.<br></li><li> Everything right at your fingertips to make optimization a 2-minute process. Save your time!<br></li><li> Uploads videos directly to YouTube, Vimeo (Pro Version) or Dailymotion (Pro Version)<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://tuberankjeet.com/Content/salesimg/product.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Tube Rank Jeet 4.2 Pro"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Adult Video Blaster 1.55 Inner Circle</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1637-adult-video-blaster.html</link>
<description>Name : Adult Video Blaster Version : 1.55 Inner Circle OS : Windows Type : XXX Marketing Tools Price : $247 Homepage : SalePage “Just One Click, That’s All It Takes To Upload Your Videos To The Top 5 Adult Sites” Start Saving Time And Focus On Important Things, Let Adult Video Blaster Do The Work For You!</description>
<category>XXX Video Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://adultvideoblaster.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2-Side-Box_small_transp.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://adultvideoblaster.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/features-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 07:36:56 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Multiple account support : AVB supports multiple accounts for the top 5 adult video directories. Track views and position : Manage your video lists with ease. Track the current views and search positions for all uploaded videos. Built-in video editor : Automatically add watermark or append an intro video. No more wasting time editing videos the old way! Multiple tube sites : 1 Click and start uploading to pornhub, xhamster, xvideos, txxx, youporn, spankwire, redtube and more… Mass Upload On All Major Tube Sites With Ease! BULK WATERMARK AND EDIT VIDEOS! Easy import and upload Free For All https://files.fm/u/hs2cddj9 https://app.box.com/s/em7jruvl76vylc6m1djrej6ty4qrnyqm</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/161022535?app_id=122963" width="425" height="304" frameborder="0" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Multiple account support : AVB supports multiple accounts for the top 5 adult video directories.<br></li><li> Track views and position : Manage your video lists with ease. Track the current views and search positions for all uploaded videos.<br></li><li> Built-in video editor : Automatically add watermark or append an intro video. No more wasting time editing videos the old way!<br></li><li> Multiple tube sites : 1 Click and start uploading to pornhub, xhamster, xvideos, txxx, youporn, spankwire, redtube and more…<br></li><li> Mass Upload On All Major Tube Sites With Ease!<br></li><li> BULK WATERMARK AND EDIT VIDEOS!<br></li><li> Easy import and upload<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://adultvideoblaster.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2-Side-Box_small_transp.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Adult Video Blaster 1.55 Inner Circle"><br><img src="http://adultvideoblaster.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/features-1.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote">Free For All<br><a href="https://files.fm/u/hs2cddj9"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">https://files.fm/u/hs2cddj9</a><br><a href="https://app.box.com/s/em7jruvl76vylc6m1djrej6ty4qrnyqm"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">https://app.box.com/s/em7jruvl76vylc6m1djrej6ty4qrnyqm</a></div><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>