<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Article Submission - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Article Submission - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>SliQ Article Submitter 1.9.20</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1785-sliq-article-submitter.html</link>
<description>Name : SliQ Article Submitter Version : 1.9.20 OS : Windows Type : Article Submitter Price : $97 Homepage : SalePage SliQ Article Submitter is an easy to use program that can help you automate the article submission process. You can easily register with article directories and submit your articles. You can use this application to add your own lists of directories. SliQ Article Submitter makes the article submission process simple</description>
<category>Article Submission</category>
<enclosure url="http://i1-win.softpedia-static.com/screenshots/SliQ-Article-Submitter_3.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2016 21:21:20 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Three Step Submission Process Preparing to Submit Author Account Tab Article Details Tab Spinner Configuration Tab Captcha Decoder Tab Proxy Tab Directories Tab</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/YiBEt_f5dPE?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Three Step Submission Process<br /></li><li> Preparing to Submit<br /></li><li> Author Account Tab<br /></li><li> Article Details Tab<br /></li><li> Spinner Configuration Tab<br /></li><li> Captcha Decoder Tab<br /></li><li> Proxy Tab<br /></li><li> Directories Tab<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://i1-win.softpedia-static.com/screenshots/SliQ-Article-Submitter_3.png" alt="SliQ Article Submitter 1.9.20" title="SliQ Article Submitter 1.9.20"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="SliQ Article Submitter 1.9.20" title="SliQ Article Submitter 1.9.20"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Article Kevo 1.7.1 DB 2.43</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1124-article-kevo.html</link>
<description>Name : Article Kevo Version : 1.7.1 DB 2.43 OS : Windows Type : Article Marketing Tools Price : $97 Homepage : SalePage Article Kevo – The Ultimate Article Submitter Software &amp;amp; SEO Link Building Tool Article Kevo (also known as AKV) is an advanced article marketing software released in 2012. With AKV, you’ll never worry about running out of sites to submit articles to. AKV currently supports 24 platforms you can submit your links to ! “Get Top Rankings in Google in a few weeks even after Panda/Penguin Updates” The whole idea behind Article Kevo is simple. It was designed to allow users to submit articles to a lot of different sites, as easily and as efficiently as possible. Once you set it up initially, AKV can run for hours and hours on autopilot, submitting articles, bookmarks, profiles, building backlinks and giving your websites the exposure you want – all while you sit back, relax and perhaps sip Martini by the beach. Try it. AKV comes with a ready list of sites for you to sign up and submit articles to, this list is permanently updated as we scrape new sites and delete the dead ones and contains 1000-2500+ sites . Article Kevo also includes a lot of tools to help you Build and Maintain your own huge list of sites easilly. These days, with all the popular blog.comworks getting de-indexed, your best bet is to build your own !</description>
<category>Article Submission</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.articlekevo.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/11/SubmitTab-e1353405924776.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2016 08:32:28 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features AKV currently supports 24 platforms you can submit your links to ! 6 Article directory platforms – WordPress, Article Dashboard, Article Friendly, Article MS, ArticleBeach and ArticleScript 9 Web 2.0 platforms – WordPress, Blogetery, Blog, Livejournal, Tumblr, Edublogs and more… 3 Social Bookmarking platforms – Pligg, Scuttle and PHPDug 4 Wiki platforms – MediaWiki, WikkaWikki, TikiWiki and MoinMoin 3 Social Network platform – Elgg, PHPFox and Dolphin 1 Forum Profiles platform – SMF 4 Custom Sites …More to come! Import Your Own List : AKV allows you to import your own lists of article sites obtained from other software, or online into AKV. It will then be run through the template check and only passing sites will be added to your list. Add Your Own WP Blogs : If you have your own.comwork of self-hosted wordpress blogs, you can also add them to your AKV list. Simply fill out their common username and password, paste the list of blogs and hit save. Scrape Your Own List : AKV comes with it’s very own In-built Site Scraper specially designed to scrape sites of the supported platforms from Google and Bing. No more worries about running out of article sites to submit to. Web 2.0 module to create as many properties as you wish!… and build link wheels with em’ (beta) Multiple Author Accounts : Create as MANY or as LITTLE author accounts to submit articles from. No more worrying about leaving “footprints” and getting your sites penalized by the search engines. One Click Auto Fill Button : Hit AKV’s Prepopulate button ONCE and it’ll fill out most of the info for you (first name, last name, username, country, city, zip, phone number etc etc) Easy Signup + Confirm Emails : AKV signs up for accounts with the article directories and logs in to your email to confirm the emails automatically when you push a button. One Click Clean-Up : Money will come and go. The same goes for websites. That’s why AKV allows you to delete and clean up dead sites and blogs from your list in one EASY click. Never live with a huge list of cluttered sites again. Group Article Sites : A huge list of sites by itself is way too messy. With AKV, you can create as many groups as you want to organize the article sites for your specific needs. AutoApprove, By Niche, By Website etc etc. Advanced Sites List Filtering : Specify the criteria of sites you are looking for and hit refresh. AKV will then display only the matching sites (sites that have yet to be signed up for/pending email confirmation/only WP sites etc etc) Spins On Submit : AKV supports spin syntax, and spins articles on submit so that every piece is unique and different from the other. Drip Feed Submissions : With AKV, you can either submit articles to all the selected sites at once, or schedule them at certain submissions every 24 hours. Smart Queue Functionality : Our Smart Queue technology allows you to add submissions to a queue – even when there are submissions in progress. Multiple Threading : AKV opens up 25 threads in the background by default to carry out processes as quickly as possible. That’s like having 25 VAs working for you at once. Scheduler : With the scheduler, you can have a bird’s eye view on all the scheduled tasks and activate / deactivate them accordingly. LiveLink Reports : AKV allows you to obtain the latest livelink reports (the actual URLs of your articles sent out) for specific articles/author accounts. Extremely User Friendly. (Works Well With Others Too) Besides having a crisp design and a very user friendly interface, AKV is also integrated with several third party software and services so that you can conveniently use many of your tools from our interface. These third party software are generally not required to use AKV, but we’ve made them work together just in case you need to use them. Captchas Solving Services : AKV supports 6 captcha solving services – Captcha Sniper, DeathByCaptcha, ImageTyperz, BypassCaptcha, AntiGate and Decaptcher. Article Spinners : Need to spin your content in one click? You can do it from AKV’s interface if you have either SpinnerChief, The Best Spinner, SpinChimp, Spin Rewriter or WordAI. If your preferred Spinner is missing from the list just let us know, we’ll be glad to add it ! Articles Scraper : It’s a breeze to add articles to AKV, but it’s even easier to harvest some and use them as seed content for your own articles. Afraid of leaving those dreaded ‘footprints’? Article Kevo allows you to add free or private proxies as one of it’s options. Not sure where to find proxies? Sure. Just use the “Autopopulate from free proxy lists” feature to generate 100s of free proxies in a few quick seconds. AKV pinger : We got that. Just open up AKV’s Pinger from the Tools section, paste your links on the left and hit on Ping the Urls to mass ping those links. Now your links are getting some attention! AKV indexer : We got that too. AKV’s unique Indexer features a fast indexer for your Web 2.0 properties and domains, API Integration with major Link Indexing Services and an inhouse link indexation checker. A simple yet powerful tool to keep tight control over your link building campaigns ! Ability to mass import/export the entire database, article sites list, articles Preview Articles (before you save/submit them) Auto Detect Errors in Spin Syntax Spin Different Versions of An Article Into A Folder One Click Duplicate Articles/Author Accounts One Click to Generate 100s of FREE Proxies One Click to test all your Proxies One Click to send your backlinks to the Pinger and Indexer Sites Scraper – Scrape sites from from Google and Bing Anchor Text – Generates spin syntax for a set of URL and keywords (mostly for resource box links) List Randomizer – Randomizes a list of input (get your livelinks in random order before you send them for indexation) Resource Box Generator – Helps you generate a template resource box with custom links Easy Summary Box Generator – Enter your keywords and the tool will generate a summary box for your article instantly And More! … ScreenShot</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/dLkpDthsfc8?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div>
<p></p>
<h3>Features</h3>
<p><br>AKV currently supports 24 platforms you can submit your links to !<br><ul><li> 6 Article directory platforms – WordPress, Article Dashboard, Article Friendly, Article MS, ArticleBeach and ArticleScript<br></li><li> 9 Web 2.0 platforms – WordPress, Blogetery, Blog, Livejournal, Tumblr, Edublogs and more…<br></li><li> 3 Social Bookmarking platforms – Pligg, Scuttle and PHPDug<br></li><li> 4 Wiki platforms – MediaWiki, WikkaWikki, TikiWiki and MoinMoin<br></li><li> 3 Social Network platform – Elgg, PHPFox and Dolphin<br></li><li> 1 Forum Profiles platform – SMF<br></li><li> 4 Custom Sites<br></li><li> …More to come!<br></li></ul><br><ul><li> Import Your Own List : AKV allows you to import your own lists of article sites obtained from other software, or online into AKV. It will then be run through the template check and only passing sites will be added to your list.<br></li><li> Add Your Own WP Blogs : If you have your own.comwork of self-hosted wordpress blogs, you can also add them to your AKV list. Simply fill out their common username and password, paste the list of blogs and hit save.<br></li><li> Scrape Your Own List : AKV comes with it’s very own In-built Site Scraper specially designed to scrape sites of the supported platforms from Google and Bing. No more worries about running out of article sites to submit to.<br></li><li> Web 2.0 module to create as many properties as you wish!… and build link wheels with em’ (beta)<br></li><li> Multiple Author Accounts : Create as MANY or as LITTLE author accounts to submit articles from. No more worrying about leaving “footprints” and getting your sites penalized by the search engines.<br></li><li> One Click Auto Fill Button : Hit AKV’s Prepopulate button ONCE and it’ll fill out most of the info for you (first name, last name, username, country, city, zip, phone number etc etc)<br></li><li> Easy Signup + Confirm Emails : AKV signs up for accounts with the article directories and logs in to your email to confirm the emails automatically when you push a button.<br></li><li> One Click Clean-Up : Money will come and go. The same goes for websites. That’s why AKV allows you to delete and clean up dead sites and blogs from your list in one EASY click. Never live with a huge list of cluttered sites again.<br></li><li> Group Article Sites : A huge list of sites by itself is way too messy. With AKV, you can create as many groups as you want to organize the article sites for your specific needs. AutoApprove, By Niche, By Website etc etc.<br></li><li> Advanced Sites List Filtering : Specify the criteria of sites you are looking for and hit refresh. AKV will then display only the matching sites (sites that have yet to be signed up for/pending email confirmation/only WP sites etc etc)<br></li><li> Spins On Submit : AKV supports spin syntax, and spins articles on submit so that every piece is unique and different from the other.<br></li><li> Drip Feed Submissions : With AKV, you can either submit articles to all the selected sites at once, or schedule them at certain submissions every 24 hours.<br></li><li> Smart Queue Functionality : Our Smart Queue technology allows you to add submissions to a queue – even when there are submissions in progress.<br></li><li> Multiple Threading : AKV opens up 25 threads in the background by default to carry out processes as quickly as possible. That’s like having 25 VAs working for you at once.<br></li><li> Scheduler : With the scheduler, you can have a bird’s eye view on all the scheduled tasks and activate / deactivate them accordingly.<br></li><li> LiveLink Reports : AKV allows you to obtain the latest livelink reports (the actual URLs of your articles sent out) for specific articles/author accounts.<br></li><li> Extremely User Friendly. (Works Well With Others Too)<br></li><li> Besides having a crisp design and a very user friendly interface, AKV is also integrated with several third party software and services so that you can conveniently use many of your tools from our interface. These third party software are generally not required to use AKV, but we’ve made them work together just in case you need to use them.<br></li><li> Captchas Solving Services : AKV supports 6 captcha solving services – Captcha Sniper, DeathByCaptcha, ImageTyperz, BypassCaptcha, AntiGate and Decaptcher.<br></li><li> Article Spinners : Need to spin your content in one click? You can do it from AKV’s interface if you have either SpinnerChief, The Best Spinner, SpinChimp, Spin Rewriter or WordAI. If your preferred Spinner is missing from the list just let us know, we’ll be glad to add it !<br></li><li> Articles Scraper : It’s a breeze to add articles to AKV, but it’s even easier to harvest some and use them as seed content for your own articles.<br></li><li> Afraid of leaving those dreaded ‘footprints’?<br></li><li> Article Kevo allows you to add free or private proxies as one of it’s options. Not sure where to find proxies? Sure. Just use the “Autopopulate from free proxy lists” feature to generate 100s of free proxies in a few quick seconds.<br></li><li> AKV pinger : We got that. Just open up AKV’s Pinger from the Tools section, paste your links on the left and hit on Ping the Urls to mass ping those links. Now your links are getting some attention!<br></li><li> AKV indexer : We got that too. AKV’s unique Indexer features a fast indexer for your Web 2.0 properties and domains, API Integration with major Link Indexing Services and an inhouse link indexation checker. A simple yet powerful tool to keep tight control over your link building campaigns !<br></li><li> Ability to mass import/export the entire database, article sites list, articles<br></li><li> Preview Articles (before you save/submit them)<br></li><li> Auto Detect Errors in Spin Syntax<br></li><li> Spin Different Versions of An Article Into A Folder<br></li><li> One Click Duplicate Articles/Author Accounts<br></li><li> One Click to Generate 100s of FREE Proxies<br></li><li> One Click to test all your Proxies<br></li><li> One Click to send your backlinks to the Pinger and Indexer<br></li><li> Sites Scraper – Scrape sites from from Google and Bing<br></li><li> Anchor Text – Generates spin syntax for a set of URL and keywords (mostly for resource box links)<br></li><li> List Randomizer – Randomizes a list of input (get your livelinks in random order before you send them for indexation)<br></li><li> Resource Box Generator – Helps you generate a template resource box with custom links<br></li><li> Easy Summary Box Generator – Enter your keywords and the tool will generate a summary box for your article instantly<br></li><li> And More!<br></li><li> …<br></li></ul><br><br></p>
<h3>ScreenShot</h3>
<p><br><img src="http://www.articlekevo.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/11/SubmitTab-e1353405924776.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Article Kevo 1.7.1 DB 2.43"></p>
<div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Article Submitter Plus 1.1.6 Build 494</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1133-article-submitter-plus.html</link>
<description>Name : Article Submitter Plus Version : 1.1.6 Build 494 OS : Windows Type : Article Submission Tools Price : $97 Homepage : SalePage Article Submitter Plus can automatically spin and submit unique variations of your articles to over 500 sites, literally at the push of a button! It can submit to sites like Article Beach, Article Dashboard, Article Friendly, Article Friendly Ultimate, Article MS, Wordpress and so on. In fact, our developers are constantly adding more and more sites day by day so probably in a couple of months, we&#039;ll have over 10,000 sites to submit your articles and get backlinks from. The best part is, you can even add your own list of sites running on the same platform and Article Submitter Plus can easily handle it!</description>
<category>Article Submission</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.articlesubmitterplus.com/images/asp-article.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2015 23:07:27 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Multi-threading technology, Article Submitter Plus works at lightning speed and creates accounts or even submits articles to multiple sites simultaneously. It can create accounts on 500 sites in less than 5 minutes! It can submit an article to all sites in less than 15 minutes. And the process is completely automated! You don&#039;t have to babysit and monitor every action. Generate spintax automatically, with the help of Spin Rewriter or The Best Spinner API. However, no API is required for spinning! Auto scheduler so you can choose to submit all articles either instantly or spread them over several days. Auto updater so when a new version comes out (which will happen frequently), Article Submitter Plus can update on its own! No need to uninstall and reinstall countless times losing all your data. :::Free Members ::: Download Now Password : www.tgmember.com :::ViP Only:::</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><video width="640" height="480" preload="metadata" poster="rss.xml" controls="controls">
						<source type="video/mp4" src="http://s3.amazonaws.com/article-submitter-plus/ShortMusic97.mp4"></source>
						</video></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Multi-threading technology, Article Submitter Plus works at lightning speed and creates accounts or even submits articles to multiple sites simultaneously. It can create accounts on 500 sites in less than 5 minutes!<br /></li><li> It can submit an article to all sites in less than 15 minutes. And the process is completely automated! You don't have to babysit and monitor every action.<br /></li><li> Generate spintax automatically, with the help of Spin Rewriter or The Best Spinner API. However, no API is required for spinning!<br /></li><li> Auto scheduler so you can choose to submit all articles either instantly or spread them over several days.<br /></li><li> Auto updater so when a new version comes out (which will happen frequently), Article Submitter Plus can update on its own! No need to uninstall and reinstall countless times losing all your data.<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://www.articlesubmitterplus.com/images/asp-article.jpg" alt="Article Submitter Plus 1.1.6 Build 494" title="Article Submitter Plus 1.1.6 Build 494"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><span style="font-size:12pt;"><b><span style="color:#006600">:::Free Members  :::</span></b></span><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" alt="Article Submitter Plus 1.1.6 Build 494" title="Article Submitter Plus 1.1.6 Build 494"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><a href="http://www.tgmember.com/engine/go.php?url=aHR0cHM6Ly9kcml2ZS5nb29nbGUuY29tL3VjP2V4cG9ydD1kb3dubG9hZCZhbXA7aWQ9MEJfcGF3cGRwZjBSQWVUSmhUbVl6VEdRMk16QQ%3D%3D"  target="_blank">Download Now</a><br />Password : www.tgmember.com<br /></div><br /></div><br /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><span style="font-size:12pt;"><b><span style="color:#FF0000">:::ViP Only:::</span></b></span><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Article Submitter Plus 1.1.6 Build 494" title="Article Submitter Plus 1.1.6 Build 494"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>