<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Optimize/Security Plugins - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Optimize/Security Plugins - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>WP Rocket 2.11.6</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/847-wp-rocket.html</link>
<description>Name : WP Rocket Version : 2.11.6 Type : Cache plugin Price : $39 Homepage : Salepage Don&#039;t waste your time struggling with complex plugin settings. WP Rocket launches upon activation - minimal configuration, immediate results.</description>
<category>Optimize/Security Plugins</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 16:05:38 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Page Caching : Caching creates an ultra-fast load time, essential for improving Search Engine Optimization and increasing conversions. When you turn on WP Rocket, page caching is immediately activated. Cache Preloading : Because our crawler simulates a visit to preload the cache, the indexing of your website by search engines is instantly improved. Images on Request : Images are loaded only as your visitor scrolls down the page, improving the load time of the page. YouTube, Facebook, Yahoo and other major websites are using this technique. Now yours can too. Static Files Compression : WP Rocket reduces the weight of your HTML, jаvascript and CSS files through minification. Lighter files means faster load time! Developer friendly : WP Rocket&#039;s code is developed according to WordPress best practices. It is clean, commented and has loads of hooks so developers can easily make advanced customizations. 2.9.8.1 Wp.Rocket.2.9.8.1.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Wp.Rocket.2.9.8.1.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Wp.Rocket.2.9.8.1.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Wp.Rocket.2.9.8.1.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Wp.Rocket.2.9.8.1.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar 2.9.5 Wp.Rocket2.9.5.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Wp.Rocket2.9.5.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Wp.Rocket2.9.5.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Wp.Rocket2.9.5.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Wp.Rocket2.9.5.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<p><br></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/jFKEv2kLijQ?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><p><br><b>Features</b><br><ul><li> Page Caching : Caching creates an ultra-fast load time, essential for improving Search Engine Optimization and increasing conversions. When you turn on WP Rocket, page caching is immediately activated.<br></li><li> Cache Preloading : Because our crawler simulates a visit to preload the cache, the indexing of your website by search engines is instantly improved.<br></li><li> Images on Request : Images are loaded only as your visitor scrolls down the page, improving the load time of the page. YouTube, Facebook, Yahoo and other major websites are using this technique. Now yours can too. <br></li><li> Static Files Compression : WP Rocket reduces the weight of your HTML, jаvascript and CSS files through minification. Lighter files means faster load time!<br></li><li> Developer friendly : WP Rocket's code is developed according to WordPress best practices. It is clean, commented and has loads of hooks so developers can easily make advanced customizations.<br></li></ul></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="WP Rocket 2.11.6"><br><div class="quote"><br>2.9.8.1<br><a href="https://clicknupload.link/ue6xp4z8db7i"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Wp.Rocket.2.9.8.1.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://dailyuploads.com/burqify4ytzh"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Wp.Rocket.2.9.8.1.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://uploadocean.com/8pbg0qkhv6gu"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Wp.Rocket.2.9.8.1.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://uplod.ws/qq98hbf3ghy6"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Wp.Rocket.2.9.8.1.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://userscloud.com/04iahxrcmyvl"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Wp.Rocket.2.9.8.1.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br>2.9.5<br><a href="https://clicknupload.link/h6gsldm44vbd"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Wp.Rocket2.9.5.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://dailyuploads.com/m8uwadayk16m"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Wp.Rocket2.9.5.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://uploadocean.com/yilo5ipa3qde"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Wp.Rocket2.9.5.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://uplod.ws/irqg5pbqd0q3"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Wp.Rocket2.9.5.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://userscloud.com/j4kpxmgkcm42"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Wp.Rocket2.9.5.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br></div></div><br><p><br></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""> <br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>iThemes Security Pro 4.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/811-ithemes-security-pro.html</link>
<description>Name : Security Pro Version : 4.0 Type : Security Plugin Price : $247 Homepage : Salepage THE BEST WORDPRESS SECURITY PLUGIN, BETTER WP SECURITY, IS NOW... iThemes Security shows you a list of things to do to make your site more secure with a simple way to turn options on or off. We&#039;ve simplified these steps and provided descriptions of each action so you know exactly what&#039;s happening on your site. You shouldn&#039;t have to be a security pro to use a security plugin. And isn&#039;t that the point?</description>
<category>Optimize/Security Plugins</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 14:29:22 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>[media=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HZkGOaKB6xI] Features Brute Force Protection : Limit the number of failed login attempts allowed per user. If someone is trying to guess your password, they&#039;ll get locked out after a few tries. You can even whitelist your own IP, so you&#039;re allowed more login attempts. File Change Detection: If someone manages to get into your site, they&#039;ll probably add, remove or change a file. Get email alerts showing any file changes so you know if you&#039;ve been hacked. 404 Detection: If a bot is scanning your site for vulnerabilities, it will generate a lot of 404 errors. iThemes Security will lock out that IP after the limit you set (20 errors in 5 minutes by default). Strong Password Enforcement: Set which level of users on your site (admins, editors, users, etc.) need to have strong passwords. This is one of the best ways to secure your site. Lock Out Bad Users: Keep bad users away from your site if they have too many failed login attempts, a lot of 404 errors or if they&#039;re on a bot blacklist. Away Mode: Not making changes to your site 24 hours a day? Make the admin area inaccessible during specific hours so no one else can sneak in. Hide Login &amp;amp; Admin: You can change the URL of your login area and admin area so attackers won&#039;t know where to look. This feature is also great to help clients remember their login link. Database Backups: Schedule database backups and have them emailed to you. Or you can get BackupBuddy to step up your backup game. Make complete backups and send them to off-site storage destinations. Email Notifications: Get email notifications when someone gets locked out after too many failed login attempts or when a file on your site has been changed. Dashboard Widget: Get a quick view of important security stats for your site and easily perform security actions like temporarily whitelisting your IP - without having to navigate to the plugin&#039;s settings. Online File Comparisons: iThemes Security Pro compares changes made to any WordPress core file on your system with the version on WordPress.org to determine if the change was malicious. Geo-IP Banning: Getting a lot of spam or brute force attacks from a specific, obscure country? Block IP addresses by country with Geo-IP banning. Ithemes.Security.Pro.3.6.2.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Ithemes.Security.Pro.3.6.2.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Ithemes.Security.Pro.3.6.2.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Ithemes.Security.Pro.3.6.2.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Ithemes.Security.Pro.3.6.2.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;">[media=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HZkGOaKB6xI]</div><br><b>Features</b><br><ul><li> Brute Force Protection : Limit the number of failed login attempts allowed per user. If someone is trying to guess your password, they'll get locked out after a few tries. You can even whitelist your own IP, so you're allowed more login attempts. <br></li><li> File Change Detection: If someone manages to get into your site, they'll probably add, remove or change a file. Get email alerts showing any file changes so you know if you've been hacked. <br></li><li> 404 Detection: If a bot is scanning your site for vulnerabilities, it will generate a lot of 404 errors. iThemes Security will lock out that IP after the limit you set (20 errors in 5 minutes by default). <br></li><li> Strong Password Enforcement: Set which level of users on your site (admins, editors, users, etc.) need to have strong passwords. This is one of the best ways to secure your site. <br></li><li> Lock Out Bad Users: Keep bad users away from your site if they have too many failed login attempts, a lot of 404 errors or if they're on a bot blacklist. <br></li><li> Away Mode: Not making changes to your site 24 hours a day? Make the admin area inaccessible during specific hours so no one else can sneak in. <br></li><li> Hide Login &amp; Admin: You can change the URL of your login area and admin area so attackers won't know where to look. This feature is also great to help clients remember their login link. <br></li><li> Database Backups: Schedule database backups and have them emailed to you. Or you can get BackupBuddy to step up your backup game. Make complete backups and send them to off-site storage destinations. <br></li><li> Email Notifications: Get email notifications when someone gets locked out after too many failed login attempts or when a file on your site has been changed. <br></li><li> Dashboard Widget: Get a quick view of important security stats for your site and easily perform security actions like temporarily whitelisting your IP - without having to navigate to the plugin's settings. <br></li><li> Online File Comparisons: iThemes Security Pro compares changes made to any WordPress core file on your system with the version on WordPress.org to determine if the change was malicious. <br></li><li> Geo-IP Banning: Getting a lot of spam or brute force attacks from a specific, obscure country? Block IP addresses by country with Geo-IP banning.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="iThemes Security Pro 4.0"><br><div class="quote"><br><a href="https://clicknupload.link.link/z4jxg6f9j8g8"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Ithemes.Security.Pro.3.6.2.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://dailyuploads.com/3evzrmw11p93"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Ithemes.Security.Pro.3.6.2.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://uploadocean.com/m89gxt55xe3k"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Ithemes.Security.Pro.3.6.2.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://uplod.ws/74nxn6nnnyuk"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Ithemes.Security.Pro.3.6.2.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://userscloud.com/o74z1s4vrqzl"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Ithemes.Security.Pro.3.6.2.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br></div><br></div><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""> <br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Spyder Spanker Nuke 5.7.1</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1414-spyder-spanker-nuke.html</link>
<description>Name : Spyder Spanker Version : Nuke 5.7.1 Type : Misc Price : $159 Homepage : SalePage This WordPress plugin will stop malicious spiders and robots from stealing your data and resources.</description>
<category>Optimize/Security Plugins</category>
<enclosure url="http://spyderspanker.com/templates/css/images/front/xSS-WSO_04.jpg.pagespeed.ic.JtBcFDEw3x.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/SSimages/feimages/SS-WSO_02.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2015 20:11:04 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Block countries by selecting country Block all and only Allow what you want STOPS MOZ and Semalt! Improved Share Settings – Select only those you want Restore To Factory Defaults</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Rw-6WLkFTV8?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Block countries by selecting country<br /></li><li> Block all and only Allow what you want<br /></li><li> STOPS MOZ and Semalt!<br /></li><li> Improved Share Settings – Select only those you want<br /></li><li> Restore To Factory Defaults<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://spyderspanker.com/templates/css/images/front/xSS-WSO_04.jpg.pagespeed.ic.JtBcFDEw3x.jpg" alt="Spyder Spanker Nuke 5.7.1" title="Spyder Spanker Nuke 5.7.1"  /><br /><img src="https://s3.amazonaws.com/SSimages/feimages/SS-WSO_02.jpg" alt="Spyder Spanker Nuke 5.7.1" title="Spyder Spanker Nuke 5.7.1"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Spyder Spanker Nuke 5.7.1" title="Spyder Spanker Nuke 5.7.1"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Hide My WP 5.5.1</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/807-hide-my-wp.html</link>
<description>Name : Hide My WP Version : 5.5.1 Type : Sercurity Plugin Price : $22 Homepage : SalePage Hide My WP control access to PHP files. It protects your site from almost 90% of SQL-Injection and XSS attacks caused by direct access to PHP files. This means you can install unsafe plugins without worry about security. You know hackers, spammers and bots all love WordPress, too with Hide My WP they can&#039;t recognize (or access to) WordPress and simply ignore you!</description>
<category>Optimize/Security Plugins</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2015 00:47:23 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features The magic starts now. But before it stick in your mind we don&#039;t change any file or folder and everything is in its default location! we just control access to it and this guarantees maximum compatibility for the plugin. Hide wp-login.php Hide or change wp-admin and all of its files (for untrusted users) Change WordPress theme directory, remove theme Info from stylesheet, replace default WP classes and finally minify it! Change plugins directory and hash plugins name Change upload URL, wp-includes folder, AJAX URL, etc. Change WordPress queries URL Change or disable feeds Hide all other WordPress files! Disable WordPress archives, categories, tags, pages, posts, etc Continue reading there&#039;s still more! Easily replace any words in your html output file! Notify you when someone is mousing about your WordPress site (included with visitor details like IP, user agent, referrer and even username!) Compress html output and remove comments in source code Remove WordPress meta Info from header and feeds Change default WordPress email sender Custom 404 page! Remove unnecessary menu classes Clean up body classes</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<br /><div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/kT6c7VDgs5A?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li>The magic starts now. But before it stick in your mind we don't change any file or folder and everything is in its default location! we just control access to it and this guarantees maximum compatibility for the plugin.<br /></li><li>Hide wp-login.php<br /></li><li>Hide or change wp-admin and all of its files (for untrusted users)<br /></li><li>Change WordPress theme directory, remove theme Info from stylesheet, replace default WP classes and finally minify it!<br /></li><li>Change plugins directory and hash plugins name<br /></li><li>Change upload URL, wp-includes folder, AJAX URL, etc.<br /></li><li>Change WordPress queries URL<br /></li><li>Change or disable feeds<br /></li><li>Hide all other WordPress files!<br /></li><li>Disable WordPress archives, categories, tags, pages, posts, etc<br /></li><li>Continue reading there's still more!<br /></li><li>Easily replace any words in your html output file!<br /></li><li>Notify you when someone is mousing about your WordPress site (included with visitor details like IP, user agent, referrer and even username!)<br /></li><li>Compress html output and remove comments in source code<br /></li><li>Remove WordPress meta Info from header and feeds<br /></li><li>Change default WordPress email sender<br /></li><li>Custom 404 page!<br /></li><li>Remove unnecessary menu classes<br /></li><li>Clean up body classes<br /></li></ul><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Hide My WP 5.5.1" title="Hide My WP 5.5.1"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>