<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Skype Marketing - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Skype Marketing - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>Amolto Call Recorder for Skype 3.9.1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3942-amolto-call-recorder-for-skype.html</link>
<description>Name : Amolto Call Recorder for Skype Version : 3.9.1.0 OS : Windows Type : Keeping Track of Skype Conversations Price : $0 Homepage : SalePage This free tool is ideally suited for anyone who wants an efficient means of keeping track of his Skype conversations.</description>
<category>Skype Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 06:40:45 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FREE AUDIO - Unlimited recording time without losing quality VIDEO - Record your video Skype call in mp4 format SKYPE AUTO - Starts when a skype call starts SCREENCAST / AUDIOCAST - Record video/audio from any application</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> FREE AUDIO<br></li><li> - Unlimited recording time without losing quality<br></li><li> VIDEO<br></li><li> - Record your video Skype call in mp4 format<br></li><li> SKYPE AUTO<br></li><li> - Starts when a skype call starts<br></li><li> SCREENCAST / AUDIOCAST<br></li><li> - Record video/audio from any application<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Amolto Call Recorder for Skype 3.9.1.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Soft4 Skype Marketing 7.15</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2045-soft4skype-marketing.html</link>
<description>Name : Soft4Skype Marketing Version : 7.15 OS : Windows Type : Skype Marketing Tools Price : $125 Homepage : SalePage Skype Marketing Software - Bulk Message Sender On Skype Rounding out the top chat software, user support Skype chat, instant messaging and video calls on your computer with ease. Just install Skype is you can send messages, share files and talk to your friends, your relatives via video. But few people noticed that this is a powerful marketing tool can bring you long-term revenue streams from the inte.com. Business more effectively with Skype Soft 4 Marketing.</description>
<category>Skype Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://bptech.solid.vn/ImgUpload/skypemaketing1.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2016 14:09:06 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Automatically send messages and make friends to bulk users Skype Users automatically filter and connect with Skype users Automatically filters telephone and email on the website, forum ... .. Automatic import contacts from a .txt file, even on the list have different and more information are also still enter Automatically send bulk message to Skype account with speed 2-3 seconds / news Save results send when the machine is turned off suddenly Accounts from Excel Import Skype: Skype can import a list from a text file or series excel. Statistics detailing the message was sent, the message received, the message is waiting</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/qopqnEd-fRQ?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Automatically send messages and make friends to bulk users Skype<br /></li><li> Users automatically filter and connect with Skype users<br /></li><li> Automatically filters telephone and email on the website, forum ... ..<br /></li><li> Automatic import contacts from a .txt file, even on the list have different and more information are also still enter<br /></li><li> Automatically send bulk message to Skype account with speed 2-3 seconds / news<br /></li><li> Save results send when the machine is turned off suddenly<br /></li><li> Accounts from Excel Import Skype: Skype can import a list from a text file or series excel.<br /></li><li> Statistics detailing the message was sent, the message received, the message is waiting<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://bptech.solid.vn/ImgUpload/skypemaketing1.png" alt="Soft4 Skype Marketing 7.15" title="Soft4 Skype Marketing 7.15"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Soft4 Skype Marketing 7.15" title="Soft4 Skype Marketing 7.15"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Skype Marketing 2016 1.5</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2035-skype-marketing.html</link>
<description>Name : Skype Marketing 2016 Version : 1.5 OS : Windows Type : Skype Marketing Tools Price : $57 Homepage : SalePage Automatically add Message and Post Contacts to all your Skype contacts, no limits</description>
<category>Skype Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://i.imgur.com/er7LkzG.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2016 12:51:15 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features 1 - It is a search for Skype contacts by keyword Search any users and the program will bring you numerous results Put your message and click ADD ALL by the time the program adds it ALREADY HAVE their propaganda. Besides that... Here you can LIST ALL YOUR CONTACTS and SEND MESSAGES FOR ALL OF THEM notice how I set up my advertising.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/UNhCMK1Af7U?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br />1 - It is a search for Skype contacts by keyword<br />Search any users<br />and the program will bring you numerous results<br />Put your message<br />and click ADD ALL<br />by the time the program adds it ALREADY HAVE<br />their propaganda.<br /><br />Besides that...<br />Here you can LIST ALL YOUR CONTACTS<br />and SEND MESSAGES FOR ALL OF THEM<br />notice how I set up my advertising.<br /><img src="http://i.imgur.com/er7LkzG.png" alt="Skype Marketing 2016 1.5" title="Skype Marketing 2016 1.5"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Skype Marketing 2016 1.5" title="Skype Marketing 2016 1.5"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>SkyArt 1.2</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1734-skyart.html</link>
<description>Name : SkyArt Version : 1.2 OS : Windows Type : Skype Marketing Tools Price : $0 Homepage : SalePage its a skype bot, allow you to spam people ( you can custom the speed of messages ), you can send messages to all your firends list ( usefull ) and a &quot;SkyARt&quot;( its unfinished contains only 2 SkyART )</description>
<category>Skype Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2016 17:32:20 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>[media=https://player.vimeo.com/video/161022535] Features Mass messages to Friend List Spam 1 person Emoticon Art Mesage [img]http://gyazo.com/d31490e474615e80c2e1db08c444db90.png?1345581357[/img] [img]http://gyazo.com/2e10aa00722fe9fde3c73c550d29008b.png?1345581881[/img]</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;">[media=https://player.vimeo.com/video/161022535]</div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Mass messages to Friend List<br /></li><li> Spam 1 person<br /></li><li> Emoticon Art Mesage<br /></li></ul><br />[img]http://gyazo.com/d31490e474615e80c2e1db08c444db90.png?1345581357[/img]<br />[img]http://gyazo.com/2e10aa00722fe9fde3c73c550d29008b.png?1345581881[/img]<br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="SkyArt 1.2" title="SkyArt 1.2"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Skype ID Puller 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1690-skype-id-puller.html</link>
<description>Name : Skype ID Puller Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Skype Marketing Tool Price : $27 Homepage : SalePage Amazing new software lets you send unlimited message out on Skype in real time. Allows users to pull databases from all over the inte.com for Skype id&#039;s!</description>
<category>Skype Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/0slNqo1Q1uU/hqdefault.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2016 20:28:50 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features GET UNLIMITED SKYPE LEADS GET UNLIMITED SKYPE LEADS FROM 4 SEARCH ENGINES! IMPORT YOUR LIST OF EMAILS TO PULL SKYPE ID&#039;S OUT OF THEM! RUN MULTIPLE INSTANCES OF THE SOFTWARE NEVER PAY FOR SKYPE LEADS EVER AGAIN! THE ONLY SKYPE SOFTWARE YOU WILL EVER NEED!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/VsCOJjgtJoM?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> GET UNLIMITED SKYPE LEADS<br /></li><li> GET UNLIMITED SKYPE LEADS FROM 4 SEARCH ENGINES!<br /></li><li> IMPORT YOUR LIST OF EMAILS TO PULL SKYPE ID'S OUT OF THEM!<br /></li><li> RUN MULTIPLE INSTANCES OF THE SOFTWARE<br /></li><li> NEVER PAY FOR SKYPE LEADS EVER AGAIN!<br /></li><li> THE ONLY SKYPE SOFTWARE YOU WILL EVER NEED!<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/0slNqo1Q1uU/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Skype ID Puller 1.0" title="Skype ID Puller 1.0"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Skype ID Puller 1.0" title="Skype ID Puller 1.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Gorilla Email2Skype 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1555-gorilla-email2skype.html</link>
<description>Name : Gorilla Email2Skype Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Skype Marketing Tools Price : $44 Homepage : SalePage Gorilla Email2Skype is a downloadable software to which if a list of email addressess are given as input, the skype ids of all those people / organizations associated with those email addresses will be given as output. All the Skype IDs of professionals and organizations are available in the Gorilla email2Skpye software. If you want to make best out of any business, then, you can buy this software and use it extensively. Convert any email lists into corresponding skype ids list. Eg: If you have an email list of all &quot;gold dust buyers in taiwan&quot;, you can get skype ids of all &quot;gold dust buyers in taiwan&quot; using this tool in just few minutes. You can then use them for mass skype marketing through chat or instant message.</description>
<category>Skype Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://i.imgur.com/xqZcQEc.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 29 Feb 2016 20:52:32 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features You can get the quote directly from them by talking with them. You can ask them to draw a project as per your need. You can design immediately and alter them as per your plan. The whole project will be made available within no time. You can negotiate the cost also. To get new customers to your business, you have to first purchase the email list of your target audience from us (OR from anywhere else), along with the Email2Skype software. For example, if you are a medical transcription company in india looking for getting outsourced work from doctors in USA, first you have to purchase the email list of &quot;Doctors &amp;amp; Physicians in USA&quot; and then feed the list to the email2skype software to get thousands of sky ids of doctors in USA. Then you can add them to your skype account as friend and chat with them and makret your products / services. We also sell our entire email database of over 130 million records in over 28 countries under 234 categories which was updated in year 2014 for just $499 Our entire email list collection (42 GB Data) along with Gorilla Email2Skype software will be a great asset for you for your outbound marketing needs whatever be the type of your business. Labour is cheap in india. Hence if you need, we can give you a dedicated marketing staff for you to work 9 hours a day, 5 days a week for just $499 per month to market your product / service through skype chat using our softwares and databases. Please contact our sales department if you are looking for such outsourcing. ScreenShot</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/dS61whX-SS4?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> You can get the quote directly from them by talking with them.<br></li><li> You can ask them to draw a project as per your need.<br></li><li> You can design immediately and alter them as per your plan.<br></li><li> The whole project will be made available within no time.<br></li><li> You can negotiate the cost also.<br></li></ul><br><br>To get new customers to your business, you have to first purchase the email list of your target audience from us (OR from anywhere else), along with the Email2Skype software.<br>For example, if you are a medical transcription company in india looking for getting outsourced work from doctors in USA, first you have to purchase the email list of "Doctors &amp; Physicians in USA" and then feed the list to the email2skype software to get thousands of sky ids of doctors in USA.<br><br>Then you can add them to your skype account as friend and chat with them and makret your products / services.<br>We also sell our entire email database of over 130 million records in over 28 countries under 234 categories which was updated in year 2014 for just 9<br><br>Our entire email list collection (42 GB Data) along with Gorilla Email2Skype software will be a great asset for you for your outbound marketing needs whatever be the type of your business.<br><br>Labour is cheap in india. Hence if you need, we can give you a dedicated marketing staff for you to work 9 hours a day, 5 days a week for just 9 per month to market your product / service through skype chat using our softwares and databases. Please contact our sales department if you are looking for such outsourcing.<br><h3>ScreenShot</h3><br><img src="http://i.imgur.com/xqZcQEc.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Gorilla Email2Skype 1.0"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Gorilla Skype Extractor 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1556-gorilla-skype-extractor.html</link>
<description>Name : Gorilla Skype Extractor Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Skype Marketing Tools Price : $69 Homepage : SalePage Extract UNLIMITED Skype IDs of targeted people related to your business using given keywords. Eg: &quot;Software companies in california&quot; Add the extracted skype ids to your contacts in skype. Chat with them, introduce your products / services and grow your business. Best outbound sales tool of the year 2014. New invention by gorillacontact. Skype ID extractor is one of the forensic software types of utility which h is used for reading and also used for extracting required information from the Skype. It uses inte.com related telephone software for extracting the date from Skype. This Skype extractor will allow us to extract and other contacts present in Skype. It is also marked as one of the best tools in 2014 with its salient features present in the tool. The working procedure of the tool is very simple and it is, we need open this Skype extractor tool and enter the business keyword for which we need to extract Skype IDs. Then, we need to click start button to proceed. It will return our required output in desired format as well.</description>
<category>Skype Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://i.imgur.com/BM5TYA9.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 29 Feb 2016 20:52:12 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Extract UNLIMITED Skype IDs of targeted people related to your business using given keywords. Eg: &quot;Software companies in california&quot; Add the extracted skype ids to your contacts in skype. Chat with them, introduce your products / services and grow your business. Best outbound sales tool of the year 2014. New invention by gorillacontact. HOW IT WORKS??? Open skype extractor and give a keyword related to people whose skype ids has to be extracted and click start search button. Examples of keywords can be &quot;Software companies in malaysia&quot; or &quot;Hospitals in newyork&quot; It will then extract UNLIMTIED urls, email ids, phone numbers and skype IDs of people related to that keyword. Save the extracted data to an MS Excel worksheet and use it for outbound marketing. WHY WE DEVELOPED IT??? Before, we tried google adwords, seo and many other advertising methods to bring targeted traffic to our website. Adwords was too expensive and seo took very long time with no results due to high competetion. When found that, when 100 people visits our website 10 people will click on live chat button and will chat with our operators. 80% of our sales are happening after our customers chat with our staff in live chat room. We then realized the importance of one to one conversation with our customers in closing the sale. When a customer chat with the staff in an organisation, he/she clears all his/her doubts and attains a trust on the company which leads to a sale. live chat is more effective than email communication since it is a live and ongoing interaction where the staff is able to convince the customers through one-to-one interaction When we developed Skype id extractor for our own outbound marketing needs, we never thought it would change our business. Now our chat opearators are over whelmed with people in chat. Skype id extractor is the best outbound sales tool an organisation can get to get new targeted customers. ScreenShot</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/5D-x03nek-U?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Extract UNLIMITED Skype IDs of targeted people related to your business using given keywords. Eg: "Software companies in california"<br></li><li> Add the extracted skype ids to your contacts in skype.<br></li><li> Chat with them, introduce your products / services and grow your business.<br></li><li> Best outbound sales tool of the year 2014. New invention by gorillacontact.<br></li></ul> <br>HOW IT WORKS???<br><ul><li> Open skype extractor and give a keyword related to people whose skype ids has to be extracted and click start search button.<br></li><li> Examples of keywords can be "Software companies in malaysia" or "Hospitals in newyork"<br></li><li> It will then extract UNLIMTIED urls, email ids, phone numbers and skype IDs of people related to that keyword.<br></li><li> Save the extracted data to an MS Excel worksheet and use it for outbound marketing.<br></li></ul> <br>WHY WE DEVELOPED IT???<br><ul><li> Before, we tried google adwords, seo and many other advertising methods to bring targeted traffic to our website.<br></li><li> Adwords was too expensive and seo took very long time with no results due to high competetion.<br></li><li> When found that, when 100 people visits our website 10 people will click on live chat button and will chat with our operators.<br></li><li> 80% of our sales are happening after our customers chat with our staff in live chat room.<br></li><li> We then realized the importance of one to one conversation with our customers in closing the sale.<br></li><li> When a customer chat with the staff in an organisation, he/she clears all his/her doubts and attains a trust on the company which leads to a sale.<br></li><li> live chat is more effective than email communication since it is a live and ongoing interaction where the staff is able to convince the customers through one-to-one interaction<br></li><li> When we developed Skype id extractor for our own outbound marketing needs, we never thought it would change our business.<br></li><li> Now our chat opearators are over whelmed with people in chat.<br></li><li> Skype id extractor is the best outbound sales tool an organisation can get to get new targeted customers.<br></li></ul> <br><h3>ScreenShot</h3><br><img src="http://i.imgur.com/BM5TYA9.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Gorilla Skype Extractor 1.0"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Skype Suite 1.0.36</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1502-skype-suite.html</link>
<description>Name : Skype Suite Version : 1.0.36 OS : Windows Type : Skype Marketing Tools Price : $57 Homepage : SalePage Skype Suite (SS) has several modules that help you manage up to thousands of contacts on autopilot. Let us briefly introduce you to SS&#039;s main modules. Skype Suite is a tool you need, there&#039;s no doubt about it. The question at hand is wether or not you want to take advantage of its potential to make your business grow. With SS your business will be better than without SS, no discussion. When do you wish to sell more, earn more, and have more free time? If your answer is &quot;Right Now&quot; then choose the plan that best fits your budget.</description>
<category>Skype Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://skypesuite.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/4.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://skypesuite.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/5.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://skypesuite.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/3.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://skypesuite.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/2.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2016 02:21:18 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Module 1 - Auto Reply: SS offers you the possibility of becoming your virtual assistant. You can add key words and assign automatic responses for each of them. If this module is activated. When a contact sends you a message, SS checks if any of your pre-assigned keywords is included in the message. If SS detects a keyword, then it&#039;ll answer your contact using the default response for the keyword found. For example, if the keyword is “help” and the default response for that keyword was “For technical support please submit a ticket at our support desk in www.mywebsite.com/support” This is a possible scenario: Message sent by a user: Hello I need help Message sent by Skype Suite: For technical support please submit a ticket at our support desk in www.mywebsite.com/support Thus, SS would converse with your user giving them precise instructions. If SS can&#039;t find a keyword, then it&#039;ll use the default response you&#039;ve entered for this cases, which could be something like “This is a virtual assistant, at this time we are not available but we will contact you as soon as possible&quot;. Module 2- Appointment Manager: SS will schedule appointments at specific times for those contacts who message you while you&#039;re busy. You can select the interval time between one appointment and another. For example if Module 2 is activated when a user sends you a message, SS will reply by scheduling an appointment with the user. If you&#039;ve set a time interval of 30 minutes, and you received a message at 4:00PM, then SS will answer the user saying: &quot;Hello we&#039;re currently assisting other customers, but we&#039;ll be with you at 4:30 PM&quot;. You can configure the answer SS will give when scheduling an appointment. If there&#039;s already a scheduled appointment for that time, SS will schedule another appointment 30 minutes after that one, so for example if another user messages you, then the answer will be: &quot;Hello we&#039;re currently assisting other customers, but we&#039;ll be with you at 5:00PM”, which means that you&#039;d have two scheduled appointments, one for 4:30 and another one for 5:00. Thus, successively, SS will schedule and manage your appointments with any contact that tries to reach you via Skype. And that way you customer answers won&#039;t pile up, making it impossible for you to answer everyone. You&#039;ll never get any angry customers because you didn&#039;t answer them, and you&#039;ll never have to deal with 10 customers at once. SS will organize your schedule so you can respond to each contact with as much attention as they deserve and thus your business will grow healthily and your relationship with your customers will improve every day. They will congratulate you for your excellent customer service, and will be willing to buy or purchase your products or services because they&#039;ll know you&#039;ll always be in Skype to help them. Module 3 - Message Sender: If like me you have thousands of Skype contacts, surely sending messages to each of them might seem impossible or very laborious. There are other programs in the inte.com that send bulk messages to all of your contacts, but after trying all of these programs, I can state that several of them are of very low quality, as they send all of the messages at the same time, which causes Skype to block the messages and many never arrive. SS sends messages within time intervals, which you can assign, giving them a natural flow so that Skype filters don&#039;t block your messages. SS also gives you the ability to choose which contacts you want to send a message to and which you want to send bulk messages to. Thus you&#039;ll never bother users who don&#039;t want all that hassle, or you can send promotions just to contacts who will be interested in those promotions. Module 4 - Scheduler: This scheduler will help you plan your Skype working and rest times automatically. You can program the time at which you want to change your Skype status. For example, if you usually start working at 10:00 a.m., you can program SS so that your status switches to ONLINE at that specific time. If your lunch break is usually at 1:00PM, then you can program SS so it switches your status to AWAY at that time, if you get back to work at 2:00PM, you can again program SS to switch your status back to ONLINe at that time. If you finish work at 5:00PM, you can program SS to change your status to OFFLINE. That way, your work schedule will be well organized and your contacts or clients will know which are your working hours so they don&#039;t disturb you after hours. I developed this module with my experience in mind, because I often had clients who&#039;d get upset because they&#039;d think I didn&#039;t want to answer them. This was because, as my computer is always on, I would often forget to change my status to AWAY or OFFLINE, and so I was always ONLINE even if I wasn&#039;t even in my office. At my return I would find messages from angry customers, demanding me to return their money or even offending me. With the scheduler module you&#039;ll never get angry customers, and you&#039;ll also be able to educate them in getting to know and respect your service hours. Module 5 - Contact Classifier: This module provides you with the opportunity of classifying your contact in priority groups. For example, you can create a group within SS called “friends” and give this group a low priority, and then create one called “clients” and give it a high priority. If a contact from your high priority group sends you a message, SS will warn you with an alarm, which you can select. Meanwhile if you get a message from a low priority contact, then SS won&#039;t sound the alarm. Skype usually warns you with an alarm whenever any contact messages you, but SS will only warn you when a high priority contact messages you. Thus, you won&#039;t be bothered with alarms concerning messages from contacts that aren&#039;t that important.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/XiEgj1V737Q?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><b>Module 1 - Auto Reply: </b><br /><br />SS offers you the possibility of becoming your virtual assistant. You can add key words and assign automatic responses for each of them. If this module is activated. When a contact sends you a message, SS checks if any of your pre-assigned keywords is included in the message. If SS detects a keyword, then it'll answer your contact using the default response for the keyword found. For example, if the keyword is “help” and the default response for that keyword was “For technical support please submit a ticket at our support desk in www.mywebsite.com/support” This is a possible scenario:<br /><br />Message sent by a user: Hello I need help<br /><br />Message sent by Skype Suite:  For technical support please submit a ticket at our support desk in www.mywebsite.com/support<br /><br />Thus, SS would converse with your user giving them precise instructions. If SS can't find a keyword, then it'll use the default response you've entered for this cases, which could be something like “This is a virtual assistant, at this time we are not available but we will contact you as soon as possible".<br /><img src="http://skypesuite.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/4.png" style="float:left;" alt="Skype Suite 1.0.36" title="Skype Suite 1.0.36"  /><br /><b>Module 2- Appointment Manager:</b><br /><br />SS will schedule appointments at specific times for those contacts who message you while you're busy. You can select the interval time between one appointment and another. For example if Module 2 is activated when a user sends you a message, SS will reply by scheduling an appointment with the user.<br /><br />If you've set a time interval of 30 minutes, and you received a message at 4:00PM, then SS will answer the user saying: "Hello we're currently assisting other customers, but we'll be with you at 4:30 PM". You can configure the answer SS will give when scheduling an appointment. If there's already a scheduled appointment for that time, SS will schedule another appointment 30 minutes after that one, so for example if another user messages you, then the answer will be:  "Hello we're currently assisting other customers, but we'll be with you at 5:00PM”, which means that you'd have two scheduled appointments, one for 4:30 and another one for 5:00.<br /><br />Thus, successively, SS will schedule and manage your appointments with any contact that tries to reach you via Skype. And that way you customer answers won't pile up, making it impossible for you to answer everyone.<br /><br />You'll never get any angry customers because you didn't answer them, and you'll never have to deal with 10 customers at once. SS will organize your schedule so you can respond to each contact with as much attention as they deserve and thus your business will grow healthily and your relationship with your customers will improve every day. They will congratulate you for your excellent customer service, and will be willing to buy or purchase your products or services because they'll know you'll always be in Skype to help them.<br /><br /><img src="http://skypesuite.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/5.png" style="float:left;" alt="Skype Suite 1.0.36" title="Skype Suite 1.0.36"  /><br /><b>Module 3 - Message Sender:</b><br />If like me you have thousands of Skype contacts, surely sending messages to each of them might seem impossible or very laborious. There are other programs in the inte.com that send bulk messages to all of your contacts, but after trying all of these programs, I can state that several of them are of very low quality, as they send all of the messages at the same time, which causes Skype to block the messages and many never arrive. SS sends messages within time intervals, which you can assign, giving them a natural flow so that Skype filters don't block your messages.<br /><br /><br />SS also gives you the ability to choose which contacts you want to send a message to and which you want to send bulk messages to. Thus you'll never bother users who don't want all that hassle, or you can send promotions just to contacts who will be interested in those promotions.<br /><br /><img src="http://skypesuite.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/3.png" style="float:left;" alt="Skype Suite 1.0.36" title="Skype Suite 1.0.36"  /><br /><b>Module 4 - Scheduler:</b><br /><br />This scheduler will help you plan your Skype working and rest times automatically. You can program the time at which you want to change your Skype status. For example, if you usually start working at 10:00 a.m., you can program SS so that your status switches to ONLINE at that specific time. If your lunch break is usually at 1:00PM, then you can program SS so it switches your status to AWAY at that time, if you get back to work at 2:00PM, you can again program SS to switch your status back to ONLINe at that time. If you finish work at 5:00PM, you can program SS to change your status to  OFFLINE. That way, your work schedule will be well organized and your contacts or clients will know which are your working hours so they don't disturb you after hours.<br /><br />I developed this module with my experience in mind, because I often had clients who'd get upset because they'd think I didn't want to answer them. This was because, as my computer is always on, I would often forget to change my status to AWAY or OFFLINE, and so I was always ONLINE even if I wasn't even in my office. At my return I would find messages from angry customers, demanding me to return their money or even offending me. <br />With the scheduler module you'll never get angry customers, and you'll also be able to educate them in getting to know and respect your service hours. <br /><br /><img src="http://skypesuite.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/2.png" style="float:left;" alt="Skype Suite 1.0.36" title="Skype Suite 1.0.36"  /><br /><b>Module 5 - Contact Classifier:</b><br />This module provides you with the opportunity of classifying your contact in priority groups. For example, you can create a group within SS called “friends” and give this group a low priority, and then create one called “clients” and give it a high priority. If a contact from your high priority group sends you a message, SS will warn you with an alarm, which you can select. Meanwhile if you get a message from a low priority contact, then SS won't sound the alarm. Skype usually warns you with an alarm whenever any contact messages you, but SS will only warn you when a high priority contact messages you. <br /><br />Thus, you won't be bothered with alarms concerning messages from contacts that aren't that important. <br /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Skype Suite 1.0.36" title="Skype Suite 1.0.36"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Skyper Bruno 1.0.0.1</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1338-skyper-bruno.html</link>
<description>Name : Skyper Bruno Version : 1.0.0.1 OS : Windows Type : Skype Marketing Software Price : $59 Homepage : SalePage Skyper Bruno iS Skype Marketing Software</description>
<category>Skype Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-09/1443534370_640397046.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2015 20:19:51 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Bulk Contact Request Find Skype User Bulk Messager Sender Bulk Calling Text to Audio Message Recorder Auto Response</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/Bz5aipQEYV0?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Bulk Contact Request<br /></li><li> Find Skype User<br /></li><li> Bulk Messager Sender<br /></li><li> Bulk Calling<br /></li><li> Text to Audio Message Recorder<br /></li><li> Auto Response<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-09/1443534370_640397046.jpg" alt="Skyper Bruno 1.0.0.1" title="Skyper Bruno 1.0.0.1"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Skyper Bruno 1.0.0.1" title="Skyper Bruno 1.0.0.1"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>