<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>UnSupport - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>UnSupport - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>Trap Hunter 2018 v7.01</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1652-trap-hunter.html</link>
<description>Name : Trap Hunter 2018 Version : 7.01 OS : Windows Type : List Clean Price : $250/Monthy Homepage : SalePage The most advanced personal email hygiene system on the market! Trap Hunter utilizes several advanced algorithms specially designed to hunt down and remove even the nastiest hidden traps TRAP HUNTER will clean up your old unused data removing DEAD/EXPIRE Domains SPAM Traps and more. Giving you clean ready to mail data once again. Now you can turn worthless data into an active gold mine once again! By doing these steps you will stomp out nearly EVERY major trap in your lists all from YOUR home computer that includes Barracuda, Spamhaus, Mcafee, Cloudmark and many many many others. Trap Hunter will NOT affect your IP reputation nor will you get (any) complaints from your ISP! you are not mailing from this only running validation processes to remove complainers from all your active mailing subscriber lists or bought lists.</description>
<category>UnSupport</category>
<enclosure url="http://traphunter.com/img/trap-hunter-screenshot.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 20:38:31 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Email Syntax : Makes sure your emails are properly formatted no invalid chars etc. Keyword Filter : Trap Hunter goes across your list looking for any emails with forbidden keywords abuse, spam, report etc. Domain Filter : Trap Hunter will check your email list for any banned domains which includes spamtraps, legal litigators, temporary email providers and much more. MX Filters : Trap Hunter does a specialized scan it checks the MX records looking for certain variables if it finds one of these variables it marks the domain as a bad domain. Reverse MX : Trap Hunter Reverses the MX records to compare the active IPs to a large list of the nastiest complainer IPs. Spamcop, Spamhaus, SUrbl, Barracuda and more will be removed this way Auto Update : Every time you reload Trap Hunter, the software will check for any updates of suppression files or updates of the main software if it finds any it will auto update, this will make sure you always have the latest updates and all of the latest traps to be found! IP Protection : Trap Hunter is designed specifically so it will not effect your IP Reputation or get you any complaints with your ISP or HOME Inte.com provider! MX Banner Verification : Trap Hunter then also goes even a step further and attempts to make a connection to verify the MX banner it then uses a special testing process to determain if the MX record is indeed an active trap! A Record Verification : Verifies if there is a valid A Record (website) attached to the domain in the list. This removes alot of trap/junk domains and saves you considerable amounts of time and resources! DATA Types : Trap Hunter works with all Data Types including Full Records or Just Plain Emails. All Emails are accepted TLD, Cables, International, GI Data and so much more. Cleaning data has never been this easy before!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/37xCRCJpb2Q?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Email Syntax : Makes sure your emails are properly formatted no invalid chars etc.<br></li><li> Keyword Filter : Trap Hunter goes across your list looking for any emails with forbidden keywords abuse, spam, report etc.<br></li><li> Domain Filter : Trap Hunter will check your email list for any banned domains which includes spamtraps, legal litigators, temporary email providers and much more.<br></li><li> MX Filters : Trap Hunter does a specialized scan it checks the MX records looking for certain variables if it finds one of these variables it marks the domain as a bad domain.<br></li><li> Reverse MX : Trap Hunter Reverses the MX records to compare the active IPs to a large list of the nastiest complainer IPs. Spamcop, Spamhaus, SUrbl, Barracuda and more will be removed this way<br></li><li> Auto Update : Every time you reload Trap Hunter, the software will check for any updates of suppression files or updates of the main software if it finds any it will auto update, this will make sure you always have the latest updates and all of the latest traps to be found!<br></li><li> IP Protection : Trap Hunter is designed specifically so it will not effect your IP Reputation or get you any complaints with your ISP or HOME Inte.com provider!<br></li><li> MX Banner Verification : Trap Hunter then also goes even a step further and attempts to make a connection to verify the MX banner it then uses a special testing process to determain if the MX record is indeed an active trap!<br></li><li> A Record Verification : Verifies if there is a valid A Record (website) attached to the domain in the list. This removes alot of trap/junk domains and saves you considerable amounts of time and resources!<br></li><li> DATA Types : Trap Hunter works with all Data Types including Full Records or Just Plain Emails. All Emails are accepted TLD, Cables, International, GI Data and so much more. Cleaning data has never been this easy before!<br><br></li></ul><br><img src="http://traphunter.com/img/trap-hunter-screenshot.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Trap Hunter 2018 v7.01"><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>PPC Campaign Generator 2.95</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1154-ppc-campaign-generator.html</link>
<description>Name : PPC Campaign Generator Version : 2.95 OS : Windows Type : PPC Tools, BingAds Tools, Google Ads Tools Price : $47 Homepage : SalePage The Ultimate PPC Campaign Creation Software Tool Generate paid search campaigns on Google and Bing in minutes with PPC Campaign Generator software. PPC Campaign Generator is software that paid search marketers use to generate high-quality PPC campaigns fast and efficiently. Typically this software is used by digital marketing agencies, small business owners and affiliate marketers.</description>
<category>UnSupport</category>
<enclosure url="http://ppccampaigngenerator.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/05/PPC-Campaign-Generator-Software-Hero-Shot.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 21:55:21 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Keyword Research : Scrape keyword suggestions from Google, Bing, Yahoo and YouTube in literally seconds. You can also generate and save keyword combination lists. Keyword Grouper : Advanced keyword grouper functionality allowing you to analyze large lists of keywords and create relevant keyword groups with ease. Destination URL Tracking : No more concatenating URL structures in Excel! Dynamically generate campaign, adgroup, keyword and UTM variables for tracking campaigns in Google Analytics. Dynamically Generate Ads : Dynamically generate highly relevant PPC ads for each group using the root terms within the ads to achieve high click-through rates (CTRs).</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><div class="dlevideoplayer" style="width:100%;max-width:425px;"><ul data-theme="default" data-preload="metadata"><li data-title="" data-type="youtube" data-url="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=N33W31NmMYk"></li></ul></div></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Keyword Research : Scrape keyword suggestions from Google, Bing, Yahoo and YouTube in literally seconds. You can also generate and save keyword combination lists.<br /></li><li> Keyword Grouper : Advanced keyword grouper functionality allowing you to analyze large lists of keywords and create relevant keyword groups with ease.<br /></li><li> Destination URL Tracking : No more concatenating URL structures in Excel! Dynamically generate campaign, adgroup, keyword and UTM variables for tracking campaigns in Google Analytics.<br /></li><li> Dynamically Generate Ads : Dynamically generate highly relevant PPC ads for each group using the root terms within the ads to achieve high click-through rates (CTRs).<br /><br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://ppccampaigngenerator.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/05/PPC-Campaign-Generator-Software-Hero-Shot.png" alt="PPC Campaign Generator 2.95" title="PPC Campaign Generator 2.95"  /><br /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="PPC Campaign Generator 2.95" title="PPC Campaign Generator 2.95"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>DatPiff Promoter 1.2.9.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/877-datpiff-promoter.html</link>
<description>Name : DatPiff Promoter Version : 1.2.95.0 OS : Windows Type : Social Marketing, DatPiff Marketing, Sound Marketing tools Price : $97 DatPiffPromoter is the perfect tool, packed with the required features, that will make your audience grow, gaining thousands more plays every day! With the site receiving more than a million visitors and devoted users per month, you have every reason to get DatPiff plays and get to share your work with people who actually matter. This is one of the best ways that you can stand out from the rest of the crowd and slowly build useful stats. One particular from the biggest providers of mixtapes on the web, DatPiff was viewed as by quite a few to be the supply for mixtapes and freestyle. Currently, Datpiff has grown tremendously to become one of the largest online mixtape.comworks.</description>
<category>UnSupport</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2016 03:28:01 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Enhanced winsock technology Free lifetime automatic update Multi-Threading that further speeds up Proxy support with built-in downloader Easy to use layout Instant download CAPTCHA support Delay functionality User-Agent changer Song play increaser Video play increaser</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/jmPd2iMQZ_4?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Enhanced winsock technology<br /></li><li> Free lifetime automatic update<br /></li><li> Multi-Threading that further speeds up<br /></li><li> Proxy support with built-in downloader<br /></li><li> Easy to use layout<br /></li><li> Instant download<br /></li><li> CAPTCHA support<br /></li><li> Delay functionality<br /></li><li> User-Agent changer<br /></li><li> Song play increaser<br /></li><li> Video play increaser<br /></li></ul><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="DatPiff Promoter 1.2.9.0" title="DatPiff Promoter 1.2.9.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Pin Promoter 1.0.8.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/911-pin-promoter.html</link>
<description>Name : Pin Promoter Version : 1.0.8.0 OS : Windows Type : Pinterest Marketing, Social Marketing Price : $67 PinPromoter is the industry&#039;s most advanced Pinterest bot to systematically grow your Pinterest audience. Works by automating the tasks you normally do on Pinterest: following users, unfollowing users, commenting, pinning, liking and other features that will greatly enhance your exposure on Pinterest. PinPromoter PinPromoter allows you to follow and unfollow users automatically which leads to many people following you back and you retaining followers interested in your website. This is a great way to get organic followers and to gain quick exposure. Don&#039;t worry about following users you&#039;ve already followed, PinPromoter remembers what you&#039;ve done and avoids duplicating. Mass comment - you can comment on multiple pins or send multiple comments to the same pin gaining more and more popularity. Our mass comment tool supports spinning functionality so no two comments will be exactly the same!</description>
<category>UnSupport</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2016 03:38:31 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Enhanced winsock technology Free lifetime automatic update Multi-Threading that further speeds up Proxy support with built-in downloader Easy to use layout Instant download CAPTCHA support Delay functionality User-Agent changer Multiple account support Account statistics Mass account checker Mass follow/unfollow tool Mass repinner Mass liker Mass comment with spinning capability Mass pin downloader Mass pin uploader with unique image creation Scrape usernames from search results, followers, following and many more Scrape pins from users, categories and many more Scrape boards from users, categories and many more</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/B725G7dhdNM?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Enhanced winsock technology<br /></li><li> Free lifetime automatic update<br /></li><li> Multi-Threading that further speeds up<br /></li><li> Proxy support with built-in downloader<br /></li><li> Easy to use layout<br /></li><li> Instant download<br /></li><li> CAPTCHA support<br /></li><li> Delay functionality<br /></li><li> User-Agent changer<br /></li><li> Multiple account support<br /></li><li> Account statistics<br /></li><li> Mass account checker<br /></li><li> Mass follow/unfollow tool<br /></li><li> Mass repinner<br /></li><li> Mass liker<br /></li><li> Mass comment with spinning capability<br /></li><li> Mass pin downloader<br /></li><li> Mass pin uploader with unique image creation<br /></li><li> Scrape usernames from search results, followers, following and many more<br /></li><li> Scrape pins from users, categories and many more<br /></li><li> Scrape boards from users, categories and many more<br /><br /></li></ul><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Pin Promoter 1.0.8.0" title="Pin Promoter 1.0.8.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Tumb Dominator 1.0.7.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/946-tumb-dominator.html</link>
<description>Name : Tumb Dominator Version : 1.0.7.0 OS : Windows Type : Tumblr Marketing, Social Marketing Price : $67 TumbDominator is the industry&#039;s most advanced Tumblr bot to systematically grow your Tumblr audience. Works by automating the tasks you normally do on Tumblr: following users, unfollowing users, posting, reblogging and other features that will greatly enhance your exposure on Tumblr. TumbDominator allows you to follow and unfollow users automatically which leads to many people following you back and you retaining followers interested in your website. This is a great way to get organic followers and to gain quick exposure. Don&#039;t worry about following users you&#039;ve already followed, TumbDominator remembers what you&#039;ve done and avoids duplicating. Mass reblogging - you can reblog multiple posts or reblog the same post gaining more and more popularity. Our mass reblog tool supports spinning functionality so no two posts will be exactly the same!</description>
<category>UnSupport</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2016 01:07:34 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Enhanced winsock technology Free lifetime automatic update Multi-Threading that further speeds up Proxy support with built-in downloader Easy to use layout Instant download CAPTCHA support Delay functionality User-Agent changer Multiple account support Account statistics Mass account checker Mass follow/unfollow tool Mass reblogger Mass liker Mass fan messenger with spinning capability Mass poster with text spinning capability Mass blog creator Scrape usernames from search results, notes, tags and many more Scrape posts from users, tags and many more</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/A3JaqAaLy_4?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Enhanced winsock technology<br /></li><li> Free lifetime automatic update<br /></li><li> Multi-Threading that further speeds up<br /></li><li> Proxy support with built-in downloader<br /></li><li> Easy to use layout<br /></li><li> Instant download<br /></li><li> CAPTCHA support<br /></li><li> Delay functionality<br /></li><li> User-Agent changer<br /></li><li> Multiple account support<br /></li><li> Account statistics<br /></li><li> Mass account checker<br /></li><li> Mass follow/unfollow tool<br /></li><li> Mass reblogger<br /></li><li> Mass liker<br /></li><li> Mass fan messenger with spinning capability<br /></li><li> Mass poster with text spinning capability<br /></li><li> Mass blog creator<br /></li><li> Scrape usernames from search results, notes, tags and many more<br /></li><li> Scrape posts from users, tags and many more<br /><br /></li></ul><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Tumb Dominator 1.0.7.0" title="Tumb Dominator 1.0.7.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Mixcloud Bot 1.1.25.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/905-mixcloud-bot.html</link>
<description>Name : Mixcloud Bot Version : 1.1.25.0 OS : Windows Type : Mixcloud Marketing, Social Marketing Price : $59 MixcloudBot is the perfect tool that will make your audience explode, gaining thousands more plays every day! Mixcloud is an online music streaming service that allows for the listening and distribution of radio shows, DJ mixes and podcasts, which are crowdsourced by its registered users. Mixcloud allows all users to browse and stream audio content uploaded on its site. Registered users can upload content such as radio shows, DJ mixes, and podcasts, as well as promote and distribute their content through Mixcloud&#039;s own social.comworking widget. As of 2012, Mixcloud is reported to have over 3 million active users and over 500 thousand registered Facebook application users, making it the perfect place to start promoting your music and get to share your work with people who actually matter.</description>
<category>UnSupport</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2016 01:04:42 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Enhanced winsock technology Free lifetime automatic update Multi-Threading that further speeds up Proxy support with built-in downloader Easy to use layout Instant download CAPTCHA support Delay functionality User-Agent changer Song play increaser</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/wLlRJ5yTkHc?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Enhanced winsock technology<br></li><li> Free lifetime automatic update<br></li><li> Multi-Threading that further speeds up<br></li><li> Proxy support with built-in downloader<br></li><li> Easy to use layout<br></li><li> Instant download<br></li><li> CAPTCHA support<br></li><li> Delay functionality<br></li><li> User-Agent changer<br></li><li> Song play increaser<br><br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Mixcloud Bot 1.1.25.0"><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Tube Suite 2.1.6.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/944-tube-suite.html</link>
<description>Name : Tube Suite Version : 2.1.6.0 OS : Windows Type : Youtube Marketing Price : $0 TubeSuite is a video marketing software that automates the marketing process by providing a huge array of benefits to the users. TubeSuite is under beta testing and it is constantly being updated. YouTube is one of the best viewed sites nowadays in the inte.com. This is the main reason why YouTube Marketing is perhaps the most popular and easiest way to drive traffic to your website and attract more customers. More and more business owners are slowly discovering how YouTube marketing is going to benefit their business. Logically, increased traffic means increased sales online. One of the benefits is that YouTube is free and it draws the public more compared to any web 2.0 site. YouTube is world&#039;s no 1 social video website, gathering over 80 milion active members generating almost 3 billion views per day. On this purpose we developed an automated tool, to help all talented or business ready people achieve their goals and reach for dreams.</description>
<category>UnSupport</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2016 23:33:38 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Enhanced winsock technology Free lifetime automatic update Multi-Threading that further speeds up Proxy support with built-in downloader Easy to use layout Instant download CAPTCHA support Delay functionality User-Agent changer Video searcher Video downloader Video converter Account checker Video commenter Spintax support User searcher Addressbook adder</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/vGPCCqGb828?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Enhanced winsock technology<br /></li><li> Free lifetime automatic update<br /></li><li> Multi-Threading that further speeds up<br /></li><li> Proxy support with built-in downloader<br /></li><li> Easy to use layout<br /></li><li> Instant download<br /></li><li> CAPTCHA support<br /></li><li> Delay functionality<br /></li><li> User-Agent changer<br /></li><li> Video searcher<br /></li><li> Video downloader<br /></li><li> Video converter<br /></li><li> Account checker<br /></li><li> Video commenter<br /></li><li> Spintax support<br /></li><li> User searcher<br /></li><li> Addressbook adder<br /><br /></li></ul><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Tube Suite 2.1.6.0" title="Tube Suite 2.1.6.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Proxy Toolbox 1.1.0.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/916-proxy-toolbox.html</link>
<description>Name : Proxy Toolbox Version : 1.0.1.0 OS : Windows Type : Proxy Harvester Price : $0 Working on the Inte.com, it is often necessary to remain anonymous and to make actions using proxies. ProxyToolbox is the tool you need to download and check your daily need of proxies. As an inte.com user any activity you perform on the inte.com can be traced back to you with the help of your IP address, which is a unique code assigned to you by your Inte.com Service Provider. An easy way of protecting yourself is by using anonymous proxies, which hide your IP address from websites. A proxy is any software that supports the http proxy protocols. In it&#039;s simplest form a proxy is a relay for data between two computers. A proxy is a intermediate server that forwards information between to points. A proxy is like a middle man, between the host, the server that you are trying to download files off, and you sitting in front of your computer. A Proxy is a central machine on the.comwork that allows other machines in that.comwork to use a shared Inte.com connection.</description>
<category>UnSupport</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2016 23:31:53 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Enhanced winsock technology Free lifetime automatic update Multi-Threading that further speeds up Proxy support with built-in downloader Easy to use layout Instant download CAPTCHA support Delay functionality User-Agent changer HTTPs checker Country identifier POST checker Cookie checker Referer checker User-Agent checker Proxy downloader from various sources</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/gHDOJHmeYY8?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Enhanced winsock technology<br /></li><li> Free lifetime automatic update<br /></li><li> Multi-Threading that further speeds up<br /></li><li> Proxy support with built-in downloader<br /></li><li> Easy to use layout<br /></li><li> Instant download<br /></li><li> CAPTCHA support<br /></li><li> Delay functionality<br /></li><li> User-Agent changer<br /></li><li> HTTPs checker<br /></li><li> Country identifier<br /></li><li> POST checker<br /></li><li> Cookie checker<br /></li><li> Referer checker<br /></li><li> User-Agent checker<br /></li><li> Proxy downloader from various sources<br /></li></ul><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Proxy Toolbox 1.1.0.0" title="Proxy Toolbox 1.1.0.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>DailyMotion Bot 1.0.8.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/876-dailymotion-bot.html</link>
<description>Name : DailyMotion Bot Version : 1.0.8.0 OS : Windows Type : Video Marketing, DailyMotion Marketing Price : $37 DailyMotionBot is the perfect tool for getting unlimited video plays and push your video in Dailymotion most viewed charts. With the built-in proxy scraper you don&#039;t have to worry about buying proxies again, DailyMotionBot downloads fresh proxies for you which you can use to increase your play count. Increasing plays gets you higher in the Dailymotion search results and therefore gives rise to more additional plays and more exposure! Dailymotion is the world&#039;s second largest video-sharing website and was the 31st most visited website in the world with over 116 million unique visitors accessing the site each month. That makes it the perfect place for sharing your videos for maximum exposure.</description>
<category>UnSupport</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2016 22:24:06 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Enhanced winsock technology Free lifetime automatic update Multi-Threading that further speeds up Proxy support with built-in downloader Easy to use layout Instant download CAPTCHA support Delay functionality User-Agent changer Play increaser</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Ak8UWvTZuDU?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Enhanced winsock technology<br /></li><li> Free lifetime automatic update<br /></li><li> Multi-Threading that further speeds up<br /></li><li> Proxy support with built-in downloader<br /></li><li> Easy to use layout<br /></li><li> Instant download<br /></li><li> CAPTCHA support<br /></li><li> Delay functionality<br /></li><li> User-Agent changer<br /></li><li> Play increaser<br /></li></ul><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="DailyMotion Bot 1.0.8.0" title="DailyMotion Bot 1.0.8.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Mytube Manager Bot 1.2.3.1 Developer</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1164-mytube-rank-bot.html</link>
<description>Name : Mytube Manager Bot Version : 1.2.3.1 Developer OS : Windows Type : Youtube Marketing Bot Price : $199 GET THE MOST POWERFUL YOUTUBE RANK BOT EVER MADE! MyTube is amazing tool for getting ranked by keyword &amp; also increasing video plays what puts your video in YouTube Top ranked charts...</description>
<category>UnSupport</category>
<enclosure url="http://i.imgur.com/2cU92RV.gif" type="image/gif" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2015 01:37:59 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Multi URL Support MultiThreads Search video by keywords URL or Youtube API Random Browser Language Random Browser Resolution Desktop Useragents Random Youtube Page Language HMA VPN Pro (not included) IP Change every &quot;X&quot; min. IP Change every &quot;X&quot; Views Random Delay in keywords search Random Video Delay Random Schedule Delay Delete Browsing History &amp; Cookies Lifetime Free Updates</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ZZEBaDrYJ_M?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Multi URL Support<br /></li><li> MultiThreads<br /></li><li> Search video by keywords<br /></li><li> URL or Youtube API<br /></li><li> Random Browser Language<br /></li><li> Random Browser Resolution<br /></li><li> Desktop Useragents<br /></li><li> Random Youtube Page Language<br /></li><li> HMA VPN Pro (not included)<br /></li><li> IP Change every "X" min.<br /></li><li> IP Change every "X" Views<br /></li><li> Random Delay in keywords search<br /></li><li> Random Video Delay<br /></li><li> Random Schedule Delay<br /></li><li> Delete Browsing History & Cookies<br /></li><li> Lifetime Free Updates<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://i.imgur.com/2cU92RV.gif" alt="Mytube Manager Bot 1.2.3.1 Developer" title="Mytube Manager Bot 1.2.3.1 Developer"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Mytube Manager Bot 1.2.3.1 Developer" title="Mytube Manager Bot 1.2.3.1 Developer"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>