<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Account Creator - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Account Creator - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>PVA Creator Deluxe 1.54</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1819-pva-creator.html</link>
<description>Name : PVACreator Deluxe Version : 1.54 OS : Windows Type : PVA Account Creator Price : $918 Homepage : SalePage PVACreator is a super accounts bulk creating machine that can creating phone and email verified accounts for different sites. It can also solve captcha automatically and allow you to import proxies to register accounts.</description>
<category>Account Creator</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2018 13:32:37 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Smart Task Manager : PVACreator allows you to create/manage/run/pause/resume multi-accounts creating tasks at the same time. Every task has full stats of account creating, you can manage and check everything easily. Auto/Custom Data Settings : PVACreator can create randomly datas like first name, last name, sex and age etc... to create your accounts, you can also import yourself data to create your accounts. Customized Save Settings : You can custom the register information to save, like you can only save username and password, or you can also set to save username, password, register proxy, register phone number, first name, last name and others. All information can be saved with created accounts if you want. Captcha Auto-Solving and Proxy Support.PVACreator can solve captcha automatically when register accounts, and you can import proxies to use in PVACreator for creating many accounts. Phone Verify Automatically : PVACreator can get phone numbers and receive sms to verify your accounts automatically. Auto-Confirm Email : When some sites need email confirmation, PVACreator can do this for you automatically too. Multi-Threads Support : You can set PVACreator to run with multi-threads to speed up the registration and create accounts for different sites at the same time. Create PVA For : Instagram, Youtube, Gmail, Twitter, Outlook, LinkedIn, Facebook, Pinterest, Reddit, Slickdeals, Amazon, SoundCloud</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/LCEbJNqArsE?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Smart Task Manager : PVACreator allows you to create/manage/run/pause/resume multi-accounts creating tasks at the same time. Every task has full stats of account creating, you can manage and check everything easily.<br></li><li> Auto/Custom Data Settings : PVACreator can create randomly datas like first name, last name, sex and age etc... to create your accounts, you can also import yourself data to create your accounts.<br></li><li> Customized Save Settings : You can custom the register information to save, like you can only save username and password, or you can also set to save username, password, register proxy, register phone number, first name, last name and others. All information can be saved with created accounts if you want.<br></li><li> Captcha Auto-Solving and Proxy Support.PVACreator can solve captcha automatically when register accounts, and you can import proxies to use in PVACreator for creating many accounts.<br></li><li> Phone Verify Automatically : PVACreator can get phone numbers and receive sms to verify your accounts automatically.<br></li><li> Auto-Confirm Email : When some sites need email confirmation, PVACreator can do this for you automatically too.<br></li><li> Multi-Threads Support : You can set PVACreator to run with multi-threads to speed up the registration and create accounts for different sites at the same time.<br></li><li> Create PVA For :  Instagram, Youtube, Gmail, Twitter, Outlook, LinkedIn, Facebook, Pinterest, Reddit, Slickdeals, Amazon, SoundCloud<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="PVA Creator Deluxe 1.54"><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Turbo EAC 1.0.7 DB09</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2166-turbo-eac.html</link>
<description>Name : Turbo EAC Version : 1.0.7 DB09 OS : Windows Type : Email Creator Price : $97 Homepage : SalePage Every inte.com marketer nowadays takes the emails they use for granted. But have you ever wondered what’s at stake if you use bad emails for your campaigns? Think about how many links you lose daily while posting with bad emails? How many accounts will vanish along with banned email addresses? No matter what marketing strategy you use, having a quality source of reliable emails at hand is essential. From the creator of Turbo Web 2.0 we bring you the fastest, most reliable email account creator ever made: TurboEAC!</description>
<category>Account Creator</category>
<enclosure url="https://www.turboware.com/wp-content/uploads/format_5.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 14:51:40 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features SYSTEM FRIENDLY : By using our custom coded engine,the application will be very light on system usage, allowing it to run fast even on low performance computers. HIGH ACCURACY : We know that the success rate is very important for you. You will get the maximum success rate. CAPTCHA : Support for the most important captcha services (9 captcha services + custom service). Smart captcha retries based on the solving order set by the user. BULK ACCOUNTS : Optimized to select and create millions of emails accounts with just few clicks. FREE UPDATES : We are constantly adding new features and follow users requests. The included web 2.0 list is checked weekly and new sites are added to the database. All updates are completely free! USER FRIENDLY : Simple and easy to understand interface. PROXY SUPPORT : The proxy management interface comes with the options to test proxies, check response time, import/export list, delete bad proxies, etc. Supported proxies : socks, public/private and reverse proxies. SCRIPT BUILDER : Create your own templates by using our point and click visual script builder. Create your own scripts to add new email providers. EASY MANAGEMENT : Set task and click Start. You will get millions email accounts in no time, saved in a .txt file, ready to be imported in any application. SUPPORT : We are dedicated to offer the best support you can rely on. You have a question? You need support for any type of issue? We are glad to help! Very Fast! Easy to use. Create millions of accounts with just few clicks. Support for the most know captcha services. Proxy support (public/private/reverse/http and socks). Engine settings (hidden/visible/threads number). Username format composer. New email providers added constantly.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/AhqH4ypvaig?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><p></p><br><h3>Features</h3><br><p><br><ul><li> SYSTEM FRIENDLY : By using our custom coded engine,the application will be very light on system usage, allowing it to run fast even on low performance computers.<br></li><li> HIGH ACCURACY : We know that the success rate is very important for you. You will get the maximum success rate.<br></li><li> CAPTCHA : Support for the most important captcha services (9 captcha services + custom service). Smart captcha retries based on the solving order set by the user.<br></li><li> BULK ACCOUNTS : Optimized to select and create millions of emails accounts with just few clicks.<br></li><li> FREE UPDATES : We are constantly adding new features and follow users requests. The included web 2.0 list is checked weekly and new sites are added to the database. All updates are completely free!<br></li><li> USER FRIENDLY : Simple and easy to understand interface.<br></li><li> PROXY SUPPORT : The proxy management interface comes with the options to test proxies, check response time, import/export list, delete bad proxies, etc. Supported proxies : socks, public/private and reverse proxies.<br></li><li> SCRIPT BUILDER : Create your own templates by using our point and click visual script builder. Create your own scripts to add new email providers.<br></li><li> EASY MANAGEMENT : Set task and click Start. You will get millions email accounts in no time, saved in a .txt file, ready to be imported in any application.<br></li><li> SUPPORT : We are dedicated to offer the best support you can rely on. You have a question? You need support for any type of issue? We are glad to help!<br></li><li> Very Fast!<br></li><li> Easy to use.<br></li><li> Create millions of accounts with just few clicks.<br></li><li> Support for the most know captcha services.<br></li><li> Proxy support (public/private/reverse/http and socks).<br></li><li> Engine settings (hidden/visible/threads number).<br></li><li> Username format composer.<br></li><li> New email providers added constantly.<br></li></ul><br><img src="https://www.turboware.com/wp-content/uploads/format_5.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Turbo EAC 1.0.7 DB09"></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Browseo PVA Creator 3.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2060-browseo-pva-creator.html</link>
<description>Name : Browseo PVA Creator Version : 3.0 OS : Windows Type : PVA Facebook Creator, PVA Gmail Creator Price : $0 Homepage : SalePage Creates Clean Gmail AND Facebook PVA Accounts</description>
<category>Account Creator</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2016 19:42:41 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Create Unlimited Accounts : Create and Export or Create and Sync Unlimited Personas with BrowSEO Complete Control : Custom Email, Custom Username or Bulk Creation Your In Control Fully Integrated : Already own BrowSEO? Enjoy the custom integration! Create Away!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/C-oAlFXuCsw?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Create Unlimited Accounts : Create and Export or Create and Sync Unlimited Personas with BrowSEO<br></li><li> Complete Control : Custom Email, Custom Username or Bulk Creation Your In Control<br></li><li> Fully Integrated : Already own BrowSEO? Enjoy the custom integration! Create Away!<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Browseo PVA Creator 3.0"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>AccountsDominator 2.X</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/862-accountsdominator.html</link>
<description>Name :AccountsDominator Version : 2.X Nov 05, 2016 OS : Windows Type : Account Creator Price : $499 Homepage : SalePage Ultra powerful Account Creator - AccountsDominator One stop solution for creating and managing emails and social media accounts. AccountsDominator is a niche segment application which addresses needs of individuals or organizations to create multiple email and social media accounts with minimal effort. It gives ease of access to end users through its dynamic user interface. This addresses lot of issues which come up during early signup or registration process.</description>
<category>Account Creator</category>
<enclosure url="http://dominatorhouse.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/09/Screenshot_6-1.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://i.imgur.com/B2ivOYD.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="http://i.imgur.com/Xm7HRia.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="http://i.imgur.com/sOgOLh4.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="http://i.imgur.com/Xm7HRia.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="http://i.imgur.com/0PqQxQb.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="http://i.imgur.com/4mgSQZv.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2016 12:26:33 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Decodes Captchas : It has an automatic captcha decoder which make it easier to handle annoying captchas. Public and Private Proxies : People can avail proxies both public and private as per their requirements, it gives an experience with strong degree of freedom. Customize Your Account : AccountsDominator gives functionality to setup necessary preferences as per one&#039;s lifestyle and choices. E-Mail and Social A/C Creator : Highly versatile and feature rich interface through which users can create email and social media accounts. Hotmail Account Creator + Manager Yahoo Account Creator + Manager Facebook Account Creator + Manager+Account Verification Linkedin Account Creator+Profile Image Uploader+Account Verification Twitter Account Creator+ Manager+Account Verification Fake Email Creator Pinterest Account Creator+ Manager+Account Verification reditt account creator aol accountcreator Blink Account Creator Tumblr/Weebly Account Creator BigAdda Account Creator Doomby Account Creator Create accounts for EduBlogs CrunchBase Account Creator Squidoo account creator more...</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/3nxQL0wTMI0?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Decodes Captchas : It has an automatic captcha decoder which make it easier to handle annoying captchas.<br /></li><li> Public and Private Proxies : People can avail proxies both public and private as per their requirements, it gives an experience with strong degree of freedom.<br /></li><li> Customize Your Account : AccountsDominator gives functionality to setup necessary preferences as per one's lifestyle and choices.<br /></li><li> E-Mail and Social A/C Creator : Highly versatile and feature rich interface through which users can create email and social media accounts.<br /></li><li> Hotmail Account Creator + Manager<br /></li><li> Yahoo Account Creator + Manager<br /></li><li> Facebook Account Creator + Manager+Account Verification<br /></li><li> Linkedin Account Creator+Profile Image Uploader+Account Verification<br /></li><li> Twitter Account Creator+ Manager+Account Verification<br /></li><li> Fake Email Creator<br /></li><li> Pinterest Account Creator+ Manager+Account Verification<br /></li><li> reditt account creator<br /></li><li> aol accountcreator<br /></li><li> Blink Account Creator<br /></li><li> Tumblr/Weebly Account Creator<br /></li><li> BigAdda Account Creator<br /></li><li> Doomby Account Creator<br /></li><li> Create accounts for EduBlogs<br /></li><li> CrunchBase Account Creator<br /></li><li> Squidoo account creator<br /></li><li> more...<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://dominatorhouse.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/09/Screenshot_6-1.png" alt="AccountsDominator 2.X" title="AccountsDominator 2.X"  /><br /><img src="http://i.imgur.com/B2ivOYD.jpg" alt="AccountsDominator 2.X" title="AccountsDominator 2.X"  /><br /><img src="http://i.imgur.com/Xm7HRia.jpg" alt="AccountsDominator 2.X" title="AccountsDominator 2.X"  /><br /><img src="http://i.imgur.com/sOgOLh4.jpg" alt="AccountsDominator 2.X" title="AccountsDominator 2.X"  /><br /><img src="http://i.imgur.com/Xm7HRia.jpg" alt="AccountsDominator 2.X" title="AccountsDominator 2.X"  /><br /><img src="http://i.imgur.com/0PqQxQb.jpg" alt="AccountsDominator 2.X" title="AccountsDominator 2.X"  /><br /><img src="http://i.imgur.com/4mgSQZv.jpg" alt="AccountsDominator 2.X" title="AccountsDominator 2.X"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="AccountsDominator 2.X" title="AccountsDominator 2.X"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Account Stream Pro 2.1.2</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/861-account-stream.html</link>
<description>Name : Account Stream Version : Pro 1.3.3 &amp; 2.1.2 OS : Windows Type : HotMail Account Creator, MailRu Account Creator, Pinterest Account Creator, Instagram Account Creator Price : $97 Homepage : SalePage Stop Paying Account Resellers and Quickly Create Thousands of Hotmail Accounts Automatically IN MINUTES with Hotmail Account Stream Have you been stuck buying accounts at overpriced rates? Ever wonder why there isn&#039;t a reliable account creator that EVERYONE can use? The fact of the matter is those bots bog down your system with a dozen slow web browsers and the decent ones are private. Hotmail Account Stream is the beginning of a new way we use accounts. Have thousands of disposable accounts ready to use in minutes!</description>
<category>Account Creator</category>
<enclosure url="http://i.imgur.com/HttPcxN.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2015 22:26:10 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features In this test, 1000 accounts were created in 20 minutes WITH PUBLIC PROXIES This is accomplished with true socket-based multi-threading. Don&#039;t be fooled into buying bots that use hidden browsers that can only run 10 threads before your system slows to a crawl.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/uswWhUOBBOw?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br />In this test, 1000 accounts were created in 20 minutes WITH PUBLIC PROXIES<br />This is accomplished with true socket-based multi-threading.<br />Don't be fooled into buying bots that use hidden browsers that can only run 10 threads before your system slows to a crawl.<br /><img src="http://i.imgur.com/HttPcxN.png" alt="Account Stream Pro 2.1.2" title="Account Stream Pro 2.1.2"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Account Stream Pro 2.1.2" title="Account Stream Pro 2.1.2"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Account Creator Extreme 4.2.2</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1434-account-creator-extreme.html</link>
<description>Name : Account Creator Extreme Version : 4.2.2 OS : Windows Type : Account Creator Tools Price : $0 Homepage : SalePage The brand NEW Interest Architect is an extremely powerful Mac/PC software tool that helps you save 100&#039;s of hours of research time .. by uncovering thousands of profitable interest keyword phrases used for Facebook ad campaigns</description>
<category>Account Creator</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2015 17:51:32 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Automatically Creates Accounts On 20+ Websites Including Yahoo, Hotmail, Gmail, And Many More (Except Captcha) Bot Maker (create your own bots and automate webpages) Smart Autofill (submit even on unsupported sites) Manual Submitter (submit to custom email sites with the autofill menu &quot;right click&quot;) Generates Full Profile With One Click 5 Built In Disposable Email Services (One Click) Real Names and Usernames (Editable) Proxy Support Advanced Profile System Advanced Settings Customizable Theme Handy Rightclick Autofill Menu Over 200,000 Built In Names It will create accounts on following websites hotmail.com account creator Gmail.com Account Creator Facebook.com Account Creator Reddit.com Account Creator Yahoo.com Account Creator Twitter.com Account Creator Stumpleupon.com Account Creator Outlook.com Account Creator Myspace.com Account Creator Livejournal.com Account Creator Inbox.com Account Creator Pinterest.com Account Creator Devianart.com Account Creator Squidoo.com Account Creator Linkedin.com Account Creator Tagged.com Account Creator Bebo.com Account Creator Mocospace.com Account Creator Wordpress.com Account Creator Weebly.com Account Creator Digo.com Account Creator Ebay.com Account Creator Delicious.com Account Creator Fiverr.com Account Creator Soundcloud.com Account Creator Technorati.com Account Creator Wikipedia Account Creator</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/vMJWeHDXeaU?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Automatically Creates Accounts On 20+ Websites Including Yahoo, Hotmail, Gmail, And Many More (Except Captcha)<br /></li><li> Bot Maker (create your own bots and automate webpages)<br /></li><li> Smart Autofill (submit even on unsupported sites)<br /></li><li> Manual Submitter (submit to custom email sites with the autofill menu "right click")<br /></li><li> Generates Full Profile With One Click<br /></li><li> 5 Built In Disposable Email Services (One Click)<br /></li><li> Real Names and Usernames (Editable)<br /></li><li> Proxy Support<br /></li><li> Advanced Profile System<br /></li><li> Advanced Settings<br /></li><li> Customizable Theme<br /></li><li> Handy Rightclick Autofill Menu<br /></li><li> Over 200,000 Built In Names<br /></li></ul><br /><br />It will create accounts on following websites<br /><ul><li> hotmail.com account creator<br /></li><li> Gmail.com Account Creator<br /></li><li> Facebook.com Account Creator<br /></li><li> Reddit.com Account Creator<br /></li><li> Yahoo.com Account Creator<br /></li><li> Twitter.com Account Creator<br /></li><li> Stumpleupon.com Account Creator<br /></li><li> Outlook.com Account Creator<br /></li><li> Myspace.com Account Creator<br /></li><li> Livejournal.com Account Creator<br /></li><li> Inbox.com Account Creator<br /></li><li> Pinterest.com Account Creator<br /></li><li> Devianart.com Account Creator<br /></li><li> Squidoo.com Account Creator<br /></li><li> Linkedin.com Account Creator<br /></li><li> Tagged.com Account Creator<br /></li><li> Bebo.com Account Creator<br /></li><li> Mocospace.com Account Creator<br /></li><li> Wordpress.com Account Creator<br /></li><li> Weebly.com Account Creator<br /></li><li> Digo.com Account Creator<br /></li><li> Ebay.com Account Creator<br /></li><li> Delicious.com Account Creator<br /></li><li> Fiverr.com Account Creator<br /></li><li> Soundcloud.com Account Creator<br /></li><li> Technorati.com Account Creator<br /></li><li> Wikipedia Account Creator<br /></li></ul><br /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Account Creator Extreme 4.2.2" title="Account Creator Extreme 4.2.2"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>EA Creator 2.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1184-eacreator.html</link>
<description>Name :EA Creator Version : 2.0 OS : Windows Type : Email Creator Tools Price : $97 Homepage : SalePage EA Creator is The Fastest Hotmail Account Creator , AOL Email Account Creator. Create Thousands of Hotmail &amp; AOL Accounts Automatically IN MINUTES with This Power Multi-threading Tool!</description>
<category>Account Creator</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2015 02:39:58 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Easy to use! No special skills are required! The software works just like a wizard. After doing few very simple steps you&#039;ll have list of thousands of hotmail accounts in your hands really fast! You can customize your account&#039;s usernames using personal word lists, numbers. Support public proxies and private proxies: Load the list of proxies, press the button and see the magic! Multi-Threading allows you run up to 100 threads at once which mean u can create 100 accounts at same time. With Auto-solving captcha service like de-captcher.com, deathbycaptcha.com, you dont need to fill captcha manually. Auto create accounts every x days or x hours with Schedule Campaigns feature. You can set the date and time range for your account creation to start. NO monthly charges: .comime fee only! Stop Paying Account Resellers and Quickly Create Thousands of Hotmail Accounts Automatically IN MINUTES with FastHAC. Future Updates absolutely FREE! You&#039;ll make payment once and can use the software for lifetime. All the future updates are completely free for life!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/u51rMqM95j0?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Easy to use! No special skills are required! The software works just like a wizard. After doing few very simple steps you'll have list of thousands of hotmail accounts in your hands really fast!<br /></li><li> You can customize your account's usernames using personal word lists, numbers.<br /></li><li> Support public proxies and private proxies: Load the list of proxies, press the button and see the magic!<br /></li><li> Multi-Threading allows you run up to 100 threads at once which mean u can create 100 accounts at same time.<br /></li><li> With Auto-solving captcha service like de-captcher.com, deathbycaptcha.com, you dont need to fill captcha manually.<br /></li><li> Auto create accounts every x days or x hours with Schedule Campaigns feature. You can set the date and time range for your account creation to start.<br /></li><li> NO monthly charges: .comime fee only! Stop Paying Account Resellers and Quickly Create Thousands of Hotmail Accounts Automatically IN MINUTES with FastHAC.<br /></li><li> Future Updates absolutely FREE! You'll make payment once and can use the software for lifetime. All the future updates are completely free for life!<br /></li></ul><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/qyNi6UFHHNc?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="EA Creator 2.0" title="EA Creator 2.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Social Traffic Commando 1.0.6.76</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/925-social-traffic-commando.html</link>
<description>Name : Social Traffic Commando Version : 1.0.6.76 OS : Windows Type : Social Submission Price : $77 Homepage : SalePage &quot;What If You Could Have Your Own Version Of Social Adr But With UNLIMITED Accounts That YOU Control For A ONE TIME Cost! .And What If These Accounts Could Be Bulk Created (100&#039;s at a time) In Just ONE CLICK!. BUT, Not Only That!.What If Every Time You Make A Social Post From You Main Profile accounts, You Get 100&#039;s of Re-Shares Posted From Random Accounts and In Random Amounts Drip Fed Every Time!</description>
<category>Account Creator</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2015 00:25:13 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features One Click Bulk Profile creation Creates email and social accounts on complete autopilot NOW ADDS ACCOUNTS INTO WORDPRESS IN ONE CLICK! Can run the account creator 24/7 in the background minimized on your computer Create UNLIMITED accounts on top social sites similar to those in SocialAdr Random accounts used on every post to keep things looking natural Random amount of posts made every time Drip feed over social Re-shares over days Can use spinnable text input Posts To Google Plus, Facebook, Twitter, Stumble, Pinterest, Delicious and more BUT gets you re-shares from those accounts instead of just Social Syndication Just Added!.Post Link To Any Url Just Like In Social Adr Including Videos! And So Much More! :::Free Members ::: Download Now Password : www.tgmember.com :::ViP Only:::</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/GTwhx8UlwXI?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> One Click Bulk Profile creation<br /></li><li> Creates email and social accounts on complete autopilot<br /></li><li> NOW ADDS ACCOUNTS INTO WORDPRESS IN ONE CLICK!<br /></li><li> Can run the account creator 24/7 in the background minimized on your computer<br /></li><li> Create UNLIMITED accounts on top social  sites similar to those in SocialAdr<br /></li><li> Random accounts used on every post to keep things looking natural<br /></li><li> Random amount of posts made every time<br /></li><li> Drip feed over social Re-shares over days<br /></li><li> Can use spinnable text input<br /></li><li> Posts To Google Plus, Facebook, Twitter, Stumble, Pinterest, Delicious and more BUT gets you re-shares from those accounts instead of just Social Syndication<br /></li><li> Just Added!.Post Link To Any Url Just Like In Social Adr Including Videos!<br /></li><li> And So Much More!<br /><br /></li></ul><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><span style="font-size:12pt;"><b><span style="color:#006600">:::Free Members :::</span></b></span><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" alt="Social Traffic Commando 1.0.6.76" title="Social Traffic Commando 1.0.6.76"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><a href="http://www.tgmember.com/engine/go.php?url=aHR0cHM6Ly9tZWdhLmNvLm56LyMhanBKRVZJSUEhTmtHUnpYVXhfMzV5akloNFcyRHhSV0E1X3h4dGZXYXlvMFAyNndXa3BnWQ%3D%3D"  target="_blank">Download Now</a><br />Password : www.tgmember.com<br /></div><br /></div><br /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><span style="font-size:12pt;"><b><span style="color:#FF0000">:::ViP Only:::</span></b></span><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Social Traffic Commando 1.0.6.76" title="Social Traffic Commando 1.0.6.76"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Account Creator Chief 2.9</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1050-account-creator-chief.html</link>
<description>Name : AccountCreatorChief - The Best Account Creator Version : 2.9 OS : Windows Type : Account Creator Price : $97 Homepage : SalePage AccountCreatorChief is our newest software for creating bulk accounts, now it can create gmail, youtube, yahoo, hotmail, aol, google+ accounts. We will continue to add more account type like twitter, craigslist, facebook etc... in the next few weeks. The software works using multi-threads, so it is very fast to create bulk accounts. It also supports auto-captcha solving and proxy, so you can create accounts fully automatically and safely.</description>
<category>Account Creator</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2015 03:01:10 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Add Tasks, Run Tasks, Export Accounts, Very Easy to Use Proxy, Captcha Solving and Threads!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/CDBJkSRniLg?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Add Tasks, Run Tasks, Export Accounts, Very Easy to Use<br /></li><li>  Proxy, Captcha Solving and Threads!<br /></li></ul><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Account Creator Chief 2.9" title="Account Creator Chief 2.9"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>