<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>GB Spy Tools - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>GB Spy Tools - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>BuddyAd Native Annual</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4523-buddyad-native.html</link>
<description>GB Name : BuddyAd Native Version : Last OS : Anything Type : Native Ads Spy GB Price : $1359/y GB Cost : 94$/15 Peoples + 8$ Fee GB Joined : 10/15 Peoples GB Status : Going Homepage : SalePage #1 Widget-Based Spy Tool with Native, Pop and Adult Widget/Site ID Finder since 2016</description>
<category>GB Spy Tools</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 05:57:48 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FE - BuddyAd Native - $1359/y Native Spy Tool (widget based) All the features that you would expect from a spy tool.. and more! Widget IDs on Adult, Pop and Native Traffic BuddyAd is the only tool that can match a widget or site ID with the relative publisher IF it is on our db. We are constantly scanning the web for more placements, as well as constantly adding more.comworks and geos to our platform. Native Real Time Scan Not sure that your native campaign is properly running? Monitor your campaign and check if your banners are running on a particular website or widget ID (if we have it on our database) using our Real Time Scan. Get rid of bad placements. Content Recommendation Networks display your ads on thousands of websites. BuddyAd lets you discover premium placements with great quality of traffic so that you can avoid having your ads running on poor websites. We support BIG traffic sources.. and a few super-vertical ones! At BuddyAd we believe in traffic. That&#039;s why we included some of the major traffic sources and content recommendation.comworks out there including RevContent, Taboola, OutBrain, AdNow, Content.ad, MGID, Yahoo Gemini, ExoClick, PropellerAds, Reporo, Popcash and more.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/PdN-eXUWXvU?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><a href="http://buddyad.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>FE - BuddyAd Native  - 59/y</b></a><br><ul><li> Native Spy Tool (widget based)<br></li><li> All the features that you would expect from a spy tool.. and more!<br></li><li> Widget IDs on Adult, Pop and Native Traffic<br></li><li> BuddyAd is the only tool that can match a widget or site ID with the relative publisher IF it is on our db. We are constantly scanning the web for more placements, as well as constantly adding more.comworks and geos to our platform.<br></li><li> Native Real Time Scan<br></li><li> Not sure that your native campaign is properly running? Monitor your campaign and check if your banners are running on a particular website or widget ID (if we have it on our database) using our Real Time Scan.<br></li><li> Get rid of bad placements.<br></li><li> Content Recommendation Networks display your ads on thousands of websites. BuddyAd lets you discover premium placements with great quality of traffic so that you can avoid having your ads running on poor websites.<br></li><li> We support BIG traffic sources..<br></li><li> and a few super-vertical ones!<br></li><li> At BuddyAd we believe in traffic. That's why we included some of the major traffic sources and content recommendation.comworks out there including RevContent, Taboola, OutBrain, AdNow, Content.ad, MGID, Yahoo Gemini, ExoClick, PropellerAds, Reporo, Popcash and more. <br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="BuddyAd Native Annual"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Dropified Unlimited Annual</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4513-dropified-unlimited.html</link>
<description>GB Name : Dropified Unlimited Version : Last OS : Anything Type : Product Hunter GB Price : $1188 GB Cost : 80$/15 Peoples + 8$ Fee GB Joined : 10/15 Peoples GB Status : Going Homepage : SalePage Dropified’s ecosystem is leading the way in making normal ecommerce users become highly profitable power users. Our software suites will allow you as a distributor to find the best deals with the best margins for the best return on your dollar as an ecommerce supplier.</description>
<category>GB Spy Tools</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 05:57:06 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FE - Dropified Unlimited - $1188 Unlimited Store connections All Features Included Special Bonus Tools</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/159628928?app_id=122963" width="425" height="239" frameborder="0" title="Dropified App Unlimited" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><a href="https://www.dropified.com/pricing/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>FE - Dropified Unlimited  - 88</b></a><br><ul><li> Unlimited Store connections<br></li><li> All Features Included<br></li><li> Special Bonus Tools<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Dropified Unlimited Annual"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Tactical Arbitrage Full Suite</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4465-tactical-arbitrage-full-suite.html</link>
<description>GB Name : Tactical Arbitrage Full Suite Version : Last OS : Anything Type : DropShip Hjack GB Price : $1800/y GB Cost : 120$/15 peoples + 9.6$ Fee GB Joined : 10/15 Peoples GB Status : Going Homepage : SalePage Tactical Arbitrage is a technological software service designed by and operated by Visual Magic Productions Pty. Ltd., and is a business to business analysis service, comparing a significant number of data points extracted from API’s and from wholesale and retail sources, that assists in isolating profitable purchasing options for online Amazon sellers from a tactical scientific approach. Using powerful databases, we are able to provide rapid cached searching solutions of 100’s of sources, and bulk scanning of imported spreadsheets of data, that can be filtered, saved online and/or exported for further analysis and collaboration with your buying team, no matter the size. Tactical Arbitrage is used for online and retail arbitrage, encompassing the sourcing of products to resell using current Return on Investment (ROI) and past statistical and analytic trends, and includes resources to help source books and the analysis of wholesale manifests. In conjunction with a system of Saved Folders that auto-update and alert you to the latest data, saving and tracking your purchasing of products using our online folder management system is an effective means to look at potential repeat buys. If you would like to see Tactical Arbitrage in action and if it is suitable for your business needs, or experience it for yourself, please look for our regular webinars and information in our Youtube channel and at live demonstrations at conferences, and take advantage of our week long, $1 trial period, by using the links below.</description>
<category>GB Spy Tools</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 05:55:18 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FE - Tactical Arbitrage Full Suite - $1800/y Product Search Reverse Search Wholesale Amazon Flips Library Search</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/v8OqrXvj_7Y?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><a href="https://tacticalarbitrage.com/membership-account/membership-levels/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>FE - Tactical Arbitrage Full Suite - 00/y</b></a><br><ul><li> Product Search					<br></li><li> Reverse Search					<br></li><li> Wholesale					<br></li><li> Amazon Flips					<br></li><li> Library Search					<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Tactical Arbitrage Full Suite"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Text Suite Annual [Delivering]</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4074-text-suite-otos.html</link>
<description>GB Name : Text Suite Annual Version : Last OS : Anything Type : Unique Content Creator GB Price : $324/Y GB Cost : 32.5$/10 Peoples + 2.5$ Fee GB Joined : 8/10 Peoples GB Status : Delivered Homepage : SalePage Text Suite is the only content creation tool you&#039;ll ever need! TextSuite is the complete content research, creation, editing and publishing tool that will populate your sites with quality content in a few clicks.</description>
<category>GB Spy Tools</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 05:35:53 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features 75,000 IMAGE DATABASE + YOUTUBE INTEGRATION Make your articles come alive by adding copyright-free images from our database of over 75,000 images and embedding videos matching your search keywords from YouTube! 100,000 PLR ARTICLES + ARTICLEBUILDER.COM Need content? Text Suite comes loaded with more than 100,000 Private Label Rights articles that you can rewrite or use as-is and claim as your own work! Text Suite is also integrated with the massive, high quality content database available from ArticleBuilder.com. Hundreds of categories are represented in the database. RESEARCH, REWRITE AND SPIN Whether you prefer to do in-depth research from scratch to write your articles, or rewrite content from the massive PLR database, or spin any of that content into Super Spun Documents that can generate a huge number of original articles -- Text Suite has you covered. AUTO-POST TO UNLIMITED WORDPRESS BLOGS Whether you run a single blog or a.comwork of hundreds, Text Suite makes it easy to quickly post content to your blogs. A few clicks to select the blog and the post category and you&#039;ve got fresh content on your blog! We all know content is king, and making it easy to post that content makes it easy for you to make the search engines happy and drive traffic.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/vldoFblxSHo?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> 75,000 IMAGE DATABASE + YOUTUBE INTEGRATION<br></li><li> Make your articles come alive by adding copyright-free images from our database of over 75,000 images and embedding videos matching your search keywords from YouTube!<br></li><li> 100,000 PLR ARTICLES + ARTICLEBUILDER.COM<br></li><li> Need content? Text Suite comes loaded with more than 100,000 Private Label Rights articles that you can rewrite or use as-is and claim as your own work! Text Suite is also integrated with the massive, high quality content database available from ArticleBuilder.com. Hundreds of categories are represented in the database.<br></li><li> RESEARCH, REWRITE AND SPIN<br></li><li> Whether you prefer to do in-depth research from scratch to write your articles, or rewrite content from the massive PLR database, or spin any of that content into Super Spun Documents that can generate a huge number of original articles -- Text Suite has you covered.<br></li><li> AUTO-POST TO UNLIMITED WORDPRESS BLOGS<br></li><li> Whether you run a single blog or a.comwork of hundreds, Text Suite makes it easy to quickly post content to your blogs. A few clicks to select the blog and the post category and you've got fresh content on your blog! We all know content is king, and making it easy to post that content makes it easy for you to make the search engines happy and drive traffic.<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Text Suite Annual [Delivering]"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Perfecttense Annual</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4502-perfecttense-annual.html</link>
<description>GB Name : Perfecttense Annual Version : Last OS : Anything Type : Grammar Correction Tool GB Price : $97/y = $97 GB Cost : 10$/10 Peoples + 1$ Fee GB Joined : 5/10 Peoples GB Status : Going Homepage : SalePage Grammar correction. Automated. Perfect Tense gives you error-free content in seconds.</description>
<category>GB Spy Tools</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 08:10:42 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FE - Perfecttense Annual - $97/y Spelling and grammar correction Fixes all mistakes in one click Over 1,000 different grammar checks AI provides highest accuracy 5 day free trial API access</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/XGw2-p2WuJk?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><a href="https://www.perfecttense.com/#pricing"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer"><b>FE - Perfecttense Annual - /y</b></a><br><ul><li> Spelling and grammar correction<br></li><li> Fixes all mistakes in one click<br></li><li> Over 1,000 different grammar checks<br></li><li> AI provides highest accuracy<br></li><li> 5 day free trial<br></li><li> API access<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Perfecttense Annual"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>FB Candy BUSINESS [Instant Deliver]</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4431-fb-candy-business.html</link>
<description>GB Name : FB Candy BUSINESS Version : Last OS : Anything Type : Facebook Spy/Extractor Tools GB Price : $197(FE) = $197 GB Cost : 20$/10 Peoples + 1.5$ Fee GB Joined : 8/10 Peoples GB Status : Delivered Homepage : SalePage FFBCANDY is a Must Have tool For Any Professional Marketer to Extract REAL Email Addresses from Any Website ! Fast and Accurate. From FACEBOOK, It retrives all valid email addresses by Subjects, Keywords, Interests. From FACEBOOK GROUPS, It extracts all valid email addresses in all groups you join in or Any Public Groups. From FACEBOOK ACCOUNTS, It Extracts all Valid Email Addresses Of your Friends in Your Facebook Account, Or Friends Of Your Friends On Facebook</description>
<category>GB Spy Tools</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 10:47:41 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FE - FB Candy BUSINESS - $197 Facebook email extractor Facebook phone extractor Advanced facebook search Post &amp;amp; schedule Content search YellowPages email extractor Facebook Ads Spy Ads Analytics FBEcom Spy Product</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/vLrxu6fNOvo?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><a href="https://fbcandy.com/"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer"><b>FE - FB Candy BUSINESS - 7</b></a><br><ul><li> Facebook email extractor<br></li><li> Facebook phone extractor<br></li><li> Advanced facebook search<br></li><li> Post &amp; schedule<br></li><li> Content search<br></li><li> YellowPages email extractor<br></li><li> Facebook Ads Spy<br></li><li> Ads Analytics<br></li><li> FBEcom Spy Product<br></li></ul><br><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="FB Candy BUSINESS [Instant Deliver]"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Long Tail Pro 2018 + OTOs [Instant Deliver]</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4143-long-tail-pro-otos.html</link>
<description>GB Name : Long Tail Pro 2018 + OTOs Version : Last OS : Anything Type : Keyword Reasearch Tools GB Price : $27(FE) + $377(OTO1) + $97(OTO2) = $501 GB Cost : 37$/12 Peoples + 3$ Fee GB Joined : 8/12 Peoples GB Status : Delivered Homepage : SalePage Use Long Tail Pro’s step-by-step system to discover thousands of profitable, targeted keywords and calculate Keyword Competitiveness for almost any niche.</description>
<category>GB Spy Tools</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2018 06:16:23 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FE - Long Tail Pro Software - $27 Exact Search Volume, and Keyword Competitiveness -Tail Pro provides exact search volume data, as well as our industry-leading Keyword Competitiveness (KC) metric. You can search for specific keywords, or get hundreds of keyword suggestions at a time. Find Hundreds of New Low Competition Keywords -Use the Google AdWords Suggestions to find hundreds of new related keywords in minutes, for any country or language. Pick the Best Keywords, with Personalized Metrics -View your domain statistics and pick the best keywords for your site. Use Target KC to find out which keywords are easy, which ones will take extra effort, and which ones to avoid. OTO1 - LTP Annual Pro Plan - $377 2500 keywords per 24 hours Keyword results include Search volume (from Google data) Keyword Competitiveness score calculated by Long Tail Pro for each keyword searched Bid Competition 2500 Keyword Competitiveness calculations per 24 hours 2500 SERP lookups per 24 hours Rank Value feature to estimate the monthly value of ranking #1 for each keyword Personal Domain analysis and customized Keyword Competitiveness Targets FREE Access to the new Rank Tracker 200 Tracked Keywords Unlimited tracked domains Daily updates FREE Backlink Analysis 5000 backlink rows per 24 hours Search for all backlinks, new backlinks only, or lost backlinks only FREE Account Management 3 simultaneous login FREE Access to Long Tail University ($197 in Value) In-App Chat Support OTO2 - Long Tail University Training - $97 Introduction : To Keyword Research Lesson 1 : Types of Keywords Lesson 2 : How to Find Seed Keywords Lesson 3 : How to Expand Seed Keywords Lesson 4 : Criteria of a Winning Keyword Lesson 5 : How to Analyze Your Competition Lesson 6 : Competitor Keywords &amp;amp; SEM Rush Lesson 7 : Developing a Content Strategy Lesson 8 : How to Write Great Content Based On Keywords Lesson 9 : WordPress Settings &amp;amp; On-Page SEO Lesson 10 : Keyword Tracking and ROI Webinar #1: Simple Tweaks To Make Your Keywords Even Longer Tail. This is over an hour long IN-DEPTH content about using keyword modifiers to truly take your keyword research to the next level. I honestly think this webinar alone is worth the value of the course. Webinar #2: How to Legally Steal Your Competitors&#039; Keywords. In this webinar, I share more in-depth strategies for taking what&#039;s working (and what tools to use) for your competitors and applying it to your own sites. Webinar #3: How to Turn Great Keywords into Profitable Content. This hour long webinar shows the powerful strategies I use in my business to create amazing content from low competition keywords. All the webinars are followed by a question and answer session. Bonus Live Webinars! Gain Access to 5 Live Training Events Held by Spencer Haws!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/gKS8a7vhNWc?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><a href="https://learnu.lpages.co/long-tail-pro-launch-special/"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer"><b>FE - Long Tail Pro Software - </b></a><br><ul><li> Exact Search Volume, and Keyword Competitiveness<br></li><li> -Tail Pro provides exact search volume data, as well as our industry-leading Keyword Competitiveness (KC) metric. You can search for specific keywords, or get hundreds of keyword suggestions at a time.<br></li><li> Find Hundreds of New Low Competition Keywords <br></li><li> -Use the Google AdWords Suggestions to find hundreds of new related keywords in minutes, for any country or language.<br></li><li> Pick the Best Keywords, with Personalized Metrics<br></li><li> -View your domain statistics and pick the best keywords for your site. Use Target KC to find out which keywords are easy, which ones will take extra effort, and which ones to avoid.<br></li></ul><br><a href="https://learnu.lpages.co/long-tail-pro-starter-and-pro-annual-payment/"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer"><b>OTO1 - LTP Annual Pro Plan - 7</b></a><br><ul><li> 2500 keywords per 24 hours<br></li><li> Keyword results include Search volume (from Google data) Keyword Competitiveness score calculated by Long Tail Pro for each keyword searched Bid Competition<br></li><li> 2500 Keyword Competitiveness calculations per 24 hours<br></li><li> 2500 SERP lookups per 24 hours<br></li><li> Rank Value feature to estimate the monthly value of ranking #1 for each keyword<br></li><li> Personal Domain analysis and customized Keyword Competitiveness Targets<br></li><li> FREE Access to the new Rank Tracker 200 Tracked Keywords Unlimited tracked domains Daily updates<br></li><li> FREE Backlink Analysis 5000 backlink rows per 24 hours Search for all backlinks, new backlinks only, or lost backlinks only<br></li><li> FREE Account Management 3 simultaneous login<br></li><li> FREE Access to Long Tail University (7 in Value)<br></li><li> In-App Chat Support<br></li></ul><br><a href="http://www.longtailuniversity.com/long-tail-university-special-offer-best-keyword-research-course-training-pl.com/"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer"><b>OTO2 - Long Tail University Training - </b></a><br><ul><li> Introduction : To Keyword Research<br></li><li> Lesson 1 : Types of Keywords<br></li><li> Lesson 2 : How to Find Seed Keywords<br></li><li> Lesson 3 : How to Expand Seed Keywords<br></li><li> Lesson 4 : Criteria of a Winning Keyword<br></li><li> Lesson 5 : How to Analyze Your Competition<br></li><li> Lesson 6 : Competitor Keywords &amp; SEM Rush<br></li><li> Lesson 7 : Developing a Content Strategy<br></li><li> Lesson 8 : How to Write Great Content Based On Keywords<br></li><li> Lesson 9 : WordPress Settings &amp; On-Page SEO<br></li><li> Lesson 10 : Keyword Tracking and ROI<br></li><li> Webinar #1: Simple Tweaks To Make Your Keywords Even Longer Tail.  This is over an hour long IN-DEPTH content about using keyword modifiers to truly take your keyword research to the next level.  I honestly think this webinar alone is worth the value of the course.<br></li><li> Webinar #2: How to Legally Steal Your Competitors' Keywords.  In this webinar, I share more in-depth strategies for taking what's working (and what tools to use) for your competitors and applying it to your own sites.<br></li><li> Webinar #3: How to Turn Great Keywords into Profitable Content.  This hour long webinar shows the powerful strategies I use in my business to create amazing content from low competition keywords.<br></li><li> All the webinars are followed by a question and answer session.<br></li><li> Bonus Live Webinars! Gain Access to 5 Live Training Events Held by Spencer Haws!<br><br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Long Tail Pro 2018 + OTOs [Instant Deliver]"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>WordAi Yearly [Instant Deliver]</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4145-wordai.html</link>
<description>GB Name : WordAi Yearly Version : Last OS : Anything Type : Article Rewriter GB Price : $347 GB Cost : 35$/10 Peoples + 3$ Fee GB Joined : 8/10 Peoples GB Status : Delivered Homepage : SalePage Automatically create human quality content with WordAi WordAi uses artificial intelligence to understand text and is able to automatically rewrite your article with the same readability as a human writer! Sign up now and get unlimited human quality content at your fingertips!</description>
<category>GB Spy Tools</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 12 May 2018 10:28:03 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features WordAi Automatically Rewrites : Entire Sentences and Paragraphs -Unlike other spinners, WordAi fully understands what each word content means. It doesn&#039;t view sentences as just a list of words, it views them as real things that interact with each other. This human like understanding allows WordAI to automatically rewrite entire sentences from scratch. This high level of rewriting ensures that Google and Copyscape can&#039;t detect your content while still remaining human readable! WordAi&#039;s Brain Understands Concepts and Ideas -Before WordAi even starts spinning, it reads the entire article to understand both &quot;generally&quot; what the article is about and the &quot;specifics&quot; as to what exactly happens in the article. This allows WordAi to create complicated paragraph and document level spins based on its deep understanding of the article. Because no other machine has this level of deep understanding, it makes your content look human written. It is even able to correctly write high quality titles by identifying what the article is talking about. WordAi Understands That Words Have Different Meanings : And it picks the right one! -Don&#039;t you hate it when your synonyms make no {sense|perception}? Don&#039;t settle for the &quot;content garbage&quot; that most spinners vomit out. WordAi can tell subtle differences between words and makes sure each synonym it picks makes complete sense. This gives you articles that are automatically readable, without you needing to spend countless hours fixing them up!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/FF9P-atl0Kk?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> WordAi Automatically Rewrites : Entire Sentences and Paragraphs<br></li><li> -Unlike other spinners, WordAi fully understands what each word content means. It doesn't view sentences as just a list of words, it views them as real things that interact with each other. This human like understanding allows WordAI to automatically rewrite entire sentences from scratch. This high level of rewriting ensures that Google and Copyscape can't detect your content while still remaining human readable!<br></li><li> WordAi's Brain Understands Concepts and Ideas<br></li><li> -Before WordAi even starts spinning, it reads the entire article to understand both "generally" what the article is about and the "specifics" as to what exactly happens in the article. This allows WordAi to create complicated paragraph and document level spins based on its deep understanding of the article. Because no other machine has this level of deep understanding, it makes your content look human written. It is even able to correctly write high quality titles by identifying what the article is talking about.<br></li><li> WordAi Understands That Words Have Different Meanings : And it picks the right one!<br></li><li> -Don't you hate it when your synonyms make no {sense|perception}? Don't settle for the "content garbage" that most spinners vomit out. WordAi can tell subtle differences between words and makes sure each synonym it picks makes complete sense. This gives you articles that are automatically readable, without you needing to spend countless hours fixing them up!<br></li></ul><br><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="WordAi Yearly [Instant Deliver]"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>FB Ads Explorer [Instant Deliver]</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4298-fb-ads-explorer.html</link>
<description>GB Name : FB Ads Explorer Version : Last OS : Anything Type : FB Ads Interest GB Price : $297(FE) = $297 GB Cost : 30$/10 Peoples + 3$ Fee GB Joined : 8/10 Peoples GB Status : Delivered Homepage : SalePage Brand New Software Uncovers Deep Hidden Interests for Crushing FB Ads &amp;amp; Getting 5 - 10X ROI on Every Ad Spend...</description>
<category>GB Spy Tools</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 12 May 2018 10:27:57 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FE - FB Ads Explorer - $297 Our System is Entirely Cloud Based... ...AND NO EXPERIENCE REQUIRED! Yes, the entire platform is cloud-based... nothing for you to download or install. Just login, connect your Facebook account and begin uncovering those hidden interests. It works in split-seconds and there&#039;s no experience needed, it&#039;s as simple as typing you niche then click GO. Also your access is lifetime, you pay once and you use it for life... a powerful tool like this cost no less than $199 per month but for a limited time, you pay a little one time fee and get access for life. INFINITE SCALE HACKING CLASS The fastest way to grow your business from $200 a day to $3,000 per day is knowing exactly how to scale but the problem is that it’s not as simple as logging in to your ads manager and increasing your daily ads budget maybe from $50 per day to $250 per day. If it was that easy, everybody will be doing it and quite frankly every Facebook marketer would have been a millionaire. In this private training, I will teach you my Infinite Scale Formula that you can use to take any business from $100 a day to $2,000 per day within your first week and without shooting up your cost per click, cost per sale or eating into your revenue. We sell this a live class for $997, but if you get access to Ads Explorer today, you’ll get it fully recorded free as part of the exclusive bonuses. GET RESULTS TODAY GUARANTEE! Perhaps the most important thing today is our ultimate guarantee. I&#039;m not going to BS you with any hype... I will straightforward! Go ahead and get access to our software now, use it on any of your Facebook ads campaigns immediately and you&#039;ll see results today guaranteed! One of this must happen depending on your campaign objective... your cost per click must drop or you&#039;ll get more leads and sales than before without increasing your ad budget.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/R2Ac85bRrYs?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><a href="https://adsexplorer.io/"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer"><b>FE - FB Ads Explorer - 7</b></a><br><ul><li> Our System is Entirely Cloud Based...<br></li><li> ...AND NO EXPERIENCE REQUIRED!<br></li><li> Yes, the entire platform is cloud-based... nothing for you to download or install.<br></li><li> Just login, connect your Facebook account and begin uncovering those hidden interests.<br></li><li> It works in split-seconds and there's no experience needed, it's as simple as typing you niche then click GO.<br></li><li> Also your access is lifetime, you pay once and you use it for life... a powerful tool like this cost no less than 9 per month but for a limited time, you pay a little one time fee and get access for life.<br></li><li> INFINITE SCALE HACKING CLASS<br></li><li> The fastest way to grow your business from 0 a day to ,000 per day is knowing exactly how to scale but the problem is that it’s not as simple as logging in to your ads manager and increasing your daily ads budget maybe from  per day to 0 per day.<br></li><li> If it was that easy, everybody will be doing it and quite frankly every Facebook marketer would have been a millionaire.<br></li><li> In this private training, I will teach you my Infinite Scale Formula that you can use to take any business from 0 a day to ,000 per day within your first week and without shooting up your cost per click, cost per sale or eating into your revenue.<br></li><li> We sell this a live class for 7, but if you get access to Ads Explorer today, you’ll get it fully recorded free as part of the exclusive bonuses.<br></li><li> GET RESULTS TODAY GUARANTEE!<br></li><li> Perhaps the most important thing today is our ultimate guarantee.<br></li><li> I'm not going to BS you with any hype... I will straightforward!<br></li><li> Go ahead and get access to our software now, use it on any of your Facebook ads campaigns immediately and you'll see results today guaranteed!<br></li><li> One of this must happen depending on your campaign objective... your cost per click must drop or you'll get more leads and sales than before without increasing your ad budget.<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="FB Ads Explorer [Instant Deliver]"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Merch Informer Annual [Instant Deliver]</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3828-merchinformer.html</link>
<description>GB Name : Merch Informer Basic Annual Version : Last OS : Windows Type : Merch Spy GB Price : $210/y GB Cost : 30$/7 Peoples + 3$ Fee GB Joined : 5/7 Peoples GB Status : Delivered Homepage : SalePage Realize Your Merch Potential Amazon Merch research simplified and streamlined putting more money In your pocket</description>
<category>GB Spy Tools</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 12:20:07 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Merch Hunter : The ultimate tool for Merch by Amazon product research allows you to see ALL the Merch by Amazon t-shirts sorted by sales and best sellers rank with a single click. Explore historical data for each product to see exactly what strategies the top sellers are using to succeed. Do not waste time with manual research. Let the Merch Hunter do all the hard work for you! Product And Keyword Tracker : Sorting your data in Excel spreadsheets is a thing of the past! With our state of the art product and keyword tracker you can effortlessly track your Merch by Amazon shirts, Monitor pricing changes and how they affect sales, as well as monitor rankings while you sleep. The perfect module for keeping a close eye on your competition! Trademark Alerts : The must have tool for every Amazon seller! Never again will you put your Merch by Amazon account at risk from trademark infringement letters and takedowns. Track up to 8000 trademarks in real time and get notified with a phrase or slogan is no longer safe to use. Forget about manually checking USPTO daily and let us do the heavy lifting for you! Advanced Competition Checker : Don’t waste design slots by getting into the wrong niches. With Merch Informer’s advanced competition checker, you will now be able to get a better idea of what kind of competition you will be up against inside of Amazon’s algorithm for each design you do. Skyrocket your Merch by Amazon sales and never waste a design slot on an over saturated niche again! Product/Merchant Database Tailored For Sellers : Our product and merchant search modules are designed to present and structure the database in a convenient way for you – the seller. Comb through thousands of items and see what is selling in minutes. Perform a quick check for competition, trademark availability and a competition score on the go! Organized Favorites : Long gone are the days of manually adding your ideas and inspiration to spreadsheets and trying to keep them organized. With our favorites feature you can create organization trees to place designs and niches that you want to take another look at in the future. This is especially useful for breaking down different niches and keeping lists separate for designers! Keyword Finder : It’s time to remove guessing work from your research! With the revolutionary keyword finder algorithm we have developed, you will be able to find hundreds of keywords that Amazon is using to direct people to your niche within seconds. Find exactly what keywords and phrases your competition is targeting, how many sales each keyword can bring in, along with historical keyword popularity data and current competition with a single click. Listing Optimizer : Having the best designs ever are not good enough if you want to make sales. Do not let your competitors take the upper hand! Make sure that your Merch by Amazon listings are optimized in accordance with the Amazon A9 algorithm, so that you can drive thousands of visitors to your listings without spending a dime on expensive advertising!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/UERF-W0XWUA?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Merch Hunter : The ultimate tool for Merch by Amazon product research allows you to see ALL the Merch by Amazon t-shirts sorted by sales and best sellers rank with a single click. Explore historical data for each product to see exactly what strategies the top sellers are using to succeed. Do not waste time with manual research. Let the Merch Hunter do all the hard work for you!<br></li><li> Product And Keyword Tracker : Sorting your data in Excel spreadsheets is a thing of the past! With our state of the art product and keyword tracker you can effortlessly track your Merch by Amazon shirts, Monitor pricing changes and how they affect sales, as well as monitor rankings while you sleep. The perfect module for keeping a close eye on your competition! <br></li><li> Trademark Alerts : The must have tool for every Amazon seller! Never again will you put your Merch by Amazon account at risk from trademark infringement letters and takedowns. Track up to 8000 trademarks in real time and get notified with a phrase or slogan is no longer safe to use. Forget about manually checking USPTO daily and let us do the heavy lifting for you!  <br></li><li> Advanced Competition Checker : Don’t waste design slots by getting into the wrong niches. With Merch Informer’s advanced competition checker, you will now be able to get a better idea of what kind of competition you will be up against inside of Amazon’s algorithm for each design you do. Skyrocket your Merch by Amazon sales and never waste a design slot on an over saturated niche again! <br></li><li> Product/Merchant Database Tailored For Sellers : Our product and merchant search modules are designed to present and structure the database in a convenient way for you – the seller. Comb through thousands of items and see what is selling in minutes. Perform a quick check for competition, trademark availability and a competition score on the go! <br></li><li> Organized Favorites : Long gone are the days of manually adding your ideas and inspiration to spreadsheets and trying to keep them organized. With our favorites feature you can create organization trees to place designs and niches that you want to take another look at in the future. This is especially useful for breaking down different niches and keeping lists separate for designers! <br></li><li> Keyword Finder : It’s time to remove guessing work from your research! With the revolutionary keyword finder algorithm we have developed, you will be able to find hundreds of keywords that Amazon is using to direct people to your niche within seconds. Find exactly what keywords and phrases your competition is targeting, how many sales each keyword can bring in, along with historical keyword popularity data and current competition with a single click. <br></li><li> Listing Optimizer : Having the best designs ever are not good enough if you want to make sales. Do not let your competitors take the upper hand! Make sure that your Merch by Amazon listings are optimized in accordance with the Amazon A9 algorithm, so that you can drive thousands of visitors to your listings without spending a dime on expensive advertising!  <br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Merch Informer Annual [Instant Deliver]"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>