<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Twitter Marketing - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Twitter Marketing - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>Twt Dominator 5.5.0.21</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/955-twtdominator.html</link>
<description>Name :Twt Dominator Version : 5.5.0.21 OS : Windows Type : Twitter Marketing Price : $499 Homepage : SalePage TwtDominator lets you target with precision, connect directly with your audience, spread your message throughout the day, manage campaigns and do much more to make sure you achieve your marketing goal. There&#039;s no doubt that Twitter, with its more than 600 million users, has become a great marketing tool for business today. With growing targeting, analytics, promotional tactics and marketing tools provided by Twitter, it&#039;s definitely a great arsenal in your digital marketing tool kit. Now Brands have been opening Twitter accounts thick and fast like you, but how confident are you of obtaining real results, and are you able to measure the impact of their messaging on the microblogging.comwork? So the difficulty remains: Who will you reach on Twitter? How will you reach them? How effectively are you using this tool? How can you tell if you&#039;ve done a good job? etc.</description>
<category>Twitter Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 27 May 2018 11:22:36 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Follower : Follow multiple accounts from your accounts uploaded. Tweet : Keep your accounts active. Easily Retweet or Reply using trending keywords. Unfollower : Get rid of users who are not following you back easily with a click Account Actions : Allows you to always use the best accounts for your process and campaigns. Wait &amp;amp; Reply : Upload a list of Messages and Keywords let the software tweet and reply. Scrape Users : Scrape users from keywords, names and also get a list of trending hash tags easily. Tweet Creator : Tweet using keywords to the targeted users. Retweet &amp;amp; Favorite : Resell or increase RTs &amp;amp; FAVs of specific tweets in no time. Campaign Manager : Easily create different campaigns for different process and run them all together.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/haf09BOHCzw?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Follower : Follow multiple accounts from your accounts uploaded. <br></li><li> Tweet : Keep your accounts active. Easily Retweet or Reply using trending keywords. <br></li><li> Unfollower : Get rid of users who are not following you back easily with a click <br></li><li> Account Actions : Allows you to always use the best accounts for your process and campaigns. <br></li><li> Wait &amp; Reply : Upload a list of Messages and Keywords let the software tweet and reply. <br></li><li> Scrape Users : Scrape users from keywords, names and also get a list of trending hash tags easily. <br></li><li> Tweet Creator : Tweet using keywords to the targeted users. <br></li><li> Retweet &amp; Favorite : Resell or increase RTs &amp; FAVs of specific tweets in no time. <br></li><li> Campaign Manager : Easily create different campaigns for different process and run them all together. <br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Twt Dominator 5.5.0.21"><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Twitterdub 1.435</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1223-twitterdub.html</link>
<description>Name : Twitterdub by RootJazz Version : 1.435 OS : Windows Type : Twitter Marketing Bot Price : $77 Homepage : SalePage Twitterdub - The Ultimate in Twitter Automation The Ultimate Twitter Automation bot. Increase your followers, auto follow, auto like, auto comment and more! Increase your followers and profile popularity using Twitterdub...</description>
<category>Twitter Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 12:55:26 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Easy to use Promo module, click click jobs done Automatic Following Automatic unfollowing Automatic Liking Automatic Commenting Post Tweets / videos / audio / images RSS Post Tweets / videos / audio / images Schedule Tweets / videos / audio / images Instantly react to new followers / tweets / mentions Full account support, multi account support Full account support, update account details Full search support Build custom searches Advanced compound searches Action via search via media or authors Filter support of media / user properties Twitter List Scraper Email List Scraper Scrape profile details include location, language, ids, profile and more Manage an unlimited amount of accounts. Account Verification Account safeguards for safe usage Daily stats Full Spintax support Schedule all actions for Drip Feeding potential. Time delay between actions to appear realistic Multi actions at once to appear realistic Repeat all actions for constant promotions hands free! Frequent updates Good quality support via multiple systems Full Captcha API support All processes are stored so can be restarted in case of power failure Save / load actions for future use Detailed logs of all processes Import / Export features for profiles, proxies. It is your data to take and do what you want with Redo / retry / pause / cancel any action Money back Guarantee</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/TL80pg6IB0o?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Easy to use Promo module, click click jobs done<br></li><li> Automatic Following<br></li><li> Automatic unfollowing<br></li><li> Automatic Liking<br></li><li> Automatic Commenting<br></li><li> Post Tweets / videos / audio / images<br></li><li> RSS Post Tweets / videos / audio / images<br></li><li> Schedule Tweets / videos / audio / images<br></li><li> Instantly react to new followers / tweets / mentions<br></li><li> Full account support, multi account support<br></li><li> Full account support, update account details<br></li><li> Full search support<br></li><li> Build custom searches<br></li><li> Advanced compound searches<br></li><li> Action via search via media or authors<br></li><li> Filter support of media / user properties<br></li><li> Twitter List Scraper<br></li><li> Email List Scraper<br></li><li> Scrape profile details include location, language, ids, profile and more<br></li><li> Manage an unlimited amount of accounts.<br></li><li> Account Verification<br></li><li> Account safeguards for safe usage<br></li><li> Daily stats<br></li><li> Full Spintax support<br></li><li> Schedule all actions for Drip Feeding potential.<br></li><li> Time delay between actions to appear realistic<br></li><li> Multi actions at once to appear realistic<br></li><li> Repeat all actions for constant promotions hands free!<br></li><li> Frequent updates<br></li><li> Good quality support via multiple systems<br></li><li> Full Captcha API support<br></li><li> All processes are stored so can be restarted in case of power failure<br></li><li> Save / load actions for future use<br></li><li> Detailed logs of all processes<br></li><li> Import / Export features for profiles, proxies. It is your data to take and do what you want with<br></li><li> Redo / retry / pause / cancel any action<br></li><li> Money back Guarantee<br><br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Twitterdub 1.435"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Twitter Money Bot 3.9.0 GOLD</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/954-twitter-money-bot.html</link>
<description>Name :Twitter Money Bot Version : 3.9.0 GOLD OS : Windows Type : Twitter Marketing Price : $127 Homepage : SalePage Twitter Money Bot v3 has been released! – It is not just a Twitter Marketing Software anymore, but it’s also an Inte.com Marketing Money Creator Robot now! No matter what you do to make money from the inte.com but you will always need traffic and targeted visitors to promote your stuff (product as an affiliate, your own product, website, cpa offers etc.) on the inte.com. If there&#039;s no traffic, no one is going to be interested in your offer or service or product, they won&#039;t even notice your offer. And the social media, especially Twitter is a great traffic source for inte.com marketers. Twitter Money Bot will find and scrape targeted twitter users for you, and it&#039;ll follow them automatically, some of them are going to follow you back and you&#039;ll gain new followers on an autopilot. So you&#039;ll be able to advertise your offer to your new followers. This is the main idea of Twitter Marketing.</description>
<category>Twitter Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://twittermoneybot.com/Screenshots/TMB-Main-GUI.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 18:16:35 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Drive Thousands Of Visitors To Your Websites From Twitter or Get Thousands Of Twitter Followers On Twitter! How To Get Followers On Twitter And How does TMB Work? There are a lot of ways and methods to increase your twitter followers on Twitter. And Twitter Money Bot is a really glorious software that applies these Twitter Marketing methods “automatically”. When you try to do these tasks manually on Twitter, it becomes very boring and tiring. Our software will save lots of time for you. What Kind Of Tasks Are We Talking About? For example; Following Task. Following others is one of the best and fastest ways to get new followers on Twitter. If you follow people, some of them are definitely going to follow you back. You can try it manually on twitter and you’ll see that some of those people are going to follow you back especially if you followed some targeted group of people or people who related to your profile, interests and niche. However, as we said, after a while it’ll really become very tiring to do these kind of tasks with your hands one by one on Twitter. So guess what? You can’t do these tasks everyday manually and Twitter Money Bot will do all these tasks automatically with the click of a button! You better get this best Twitter marketing software! How Can I Make Money With Twitter? No matter what you do to make money from the inte.com but you will always need traffic and targeted visitors to promote your stuff (product as an affiliate, your own product, website, cpa offers etc.) on the inte.com. If there’s no traffic, no one is going to be interested in your offer or service or product, they won’t even notice your offer. And the social media, especially Twitter is a great traffic source for inte.com marketers. Twitter Money Bot will find and scrape targeted twitter users for you, and it’ll follow them automatically, some of them are going to follow you back and you’ll gain new followers on an autopilot. So you’ll be able to advertise your offer to your new followers. This is the main idea of Twitter Marketing. Why You Should Get the Twitter Money Bot v3 Twitter is among the biggest social.comwork which millions of celebrities, clubs, businesses, news agencies, artists and marketers use daily. It is a platform used by these people to promote themselves, their products, gather fans and followers, share information, generate traffic, leads and much more. You may initially think that Twitter is only good for tracking your favorite celebrities’ activities or swapping a few tweets with your friends but what you do not know is that fact that this popular social media platform can do a whole lot more. Several specialized services have actually tweaked it, turning ordinary Twitter accounts to carry on helpful tasks. The Twitter Money Bot can check your stats for you, help you manage your own calendar and remind you of tweets. In short, it is not just your ordinary Twitter marketing software, the newest version also serves as an Inte.com Marketing Money Creator Robot. The new Twitter Money Bot v3 comes with powerful options and features to help you boost Twitter marketing. It includes a mix of mass and automated features that can provide maximum flexibility to users. Do you want to know what Twitter Money Bot can do for you? Below is a description for every built-in characteristic that Twitter Money Bot has to offer: When you begin running the new Twitter Money Bot v3, it will execute various customizable Twitter tasks for you. All you need to do is to run Twitter Bot in the background to perform these tasks – automatic random tweeting, automatic adding of targeted users, automatic following back, and so much more. If you want to learn how to get followers on Twitter, Twitter Money Bot allows you to follow back new followers to leverage and expand your.comwork. Each time a new follower appears, Twitter Bot will automatically follow back for effective growth of potential prospects. Aside from that, our Twitter automation software will subsequently unfollow Twitter users who are not following you back after a few days. In this way, we can help you avoid following individuals who cannot read your tweets. This is excellent for keeping your list of followers active and clean. Do you need to spread certain information across your list of followers? The new Twitter Money Bot v3 has the capacity to send direct messages to all of them! As every Twitter Marketing Software needs a search feature, users can now look for users and targeted tweets to follow with our Twitter Bot. The great thing about this is that the results are exportable to text editors. The new V3 release enables users to work with multiple Twitter accounts. This feature is great if you want to load tweets, followers and friends coming from other profiles as you can easily import or export the data. Another important tip, if you want to mass unfollow users from several accounts, Twitter Money Bot allows you to do so. The new Twitter Money Bot v3 now has a local cache database which will help increase performance by huge margins and also avoid unneeded API connections. You can retrieve stored information with our software and the database will be consistently updated by the data sync service in order to make sure that your Twitter profile and Twitter Money Bot are synchronized. Aggregate RSS feeds and real-time website content automatically as tweets and directly post them to your account. Twitter Money Bot has a scheduler feature which allows you to set up tweets in advance. This will save you the time and effort and is effective as is starts the tasks on its own, according to the time frame you have set. You can schedule all your tweets through the Scheduler and you can watch all of them get posted without you having access to a mobile device or a computer. Experiment with different campaigns to find out which one works best for you. A great feature of our Twitter bot is that it enables you to import tweets from certain third party tools like a text file. You also have the luxury of formulating tweets in advance from almost anywhere in just a single shot. With all the features of our newest version of the Twitter Money Bot, it has everything that you need in order to grow your base of followers and promote anything at almost any time that you want to. There is no other tool that combines the powers of Twitter as a social media platform into just one software. This Twitter Bot is an automated and optimized version of Twitter that you can run seven days a week, 24 hours a day. Main Features Of Twitter Money Bot v3 Auto follow users from search results or txt files Follow other people’s followers or followings Unfollow users who don’t follow you back Mass Favorite And Mass Retweet Tweet Poster Reply And Mention Generator Mass Account Statistics Checker Twitter Account Creator Direct Message Sender Various Scrapers To Scrape Various Infos From Twitter Multi Threaded – Now v3 can work with multiple accounts at the same time! Proxy Support – Public And Private Proxies! Scheduler – Just Set Up Your Campaign To The Task Table And Leave It To The Scheduler, It Will Start Your Tasks In The List Automatically Random Delay Feature Mass Twitter User ID / Username Converter White List – The unfollower will never unfollow people who are in your white list… DeathByCaptcha Auto Captcha Solver API Has Been Integrated For Account Creator Able To Add Unlimited Twitter Accounts Extra Helpful Modules And Tools For SEO And Inte.com Marketing SERP Scraper – It Can Scrape Websites And URLs From Various Search Engines Blog Comment Poster – It Can Post Your Comments To WP Blogs, So You Can Get Comment Backlinks Article Scraper Keyword Scraper SEO / Website Analyzer Keyword Analyzer Mass Pinger Fast Indexer And More…</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/zBBkcbQotVA?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><b>Drive Thousands Of Visitors To Your Websites From Twitter or Get Thousands Of Twitter Followers On Twitter!</b><br><b>How To Get Followers On Twitter And How does TMB Work?</b><br>There are a lot of ways and methods to increase your twitter followers on Twitter. And Twitter Money Bot is a really glorious software that applies these Twitter Marketing methods “automatically”. When you try to do these tasks manually on Twitter, it becomes very boring and tiring. Our software will save lots of time for you.<br><br><b>What Kind Of Tasks Are We Talking About?</b><br>For example; Following Task. Following others is one of the best and fastest ways to get new followers on Twitter. If you follow people, some of them are definitely going to follow you back. You can try it manually on twitter and you’ll see that some of those people are going to follow you back especially if you followed some targeted group of people or people who related to your profile, interests and niche. However, as we said, after a while it’ll really become very tiring to do these kind of tasks with your hands one by one on Twitter. So guess what? You can’t do these tasks everyday manually and Twitter Money Bot will do all these tasks automatically with the click of a button! You better get this best Twitter marketing software!<br><br><b>How Can I Make Money With Twitter?</b><br>No matter what you do to make money from the inte.com but you will always need traffic and targeted visitors to promote your stuff (product as an affiliate, your own product, website, cpa offers etc.) on the inte.com. If there’s no traffic, no one is going to be interested in your offer or service or product, they won’t even notice your offer. And the social media, especially Twitter is a great traffic source for inte.com marketers. Twitter Money Bot will find and scrape targeted twitter users for you, and it’ll follow them automatically, some of them are going to follow you back and you’ll gain new followers on an autopilot. So you’ll be able to advertise your offer to your new followers. This is the main idea of Twitter Marketing.<br><br><b>Why You Should Get the Twitter Money Bot v3</b><br>Twitter is among the biggest social.comwork which millions of celebrities, clubs, businesses, news agencies, artists and marketers use daily. It is a platform used by these people to promote themselves, their products, gather fans and followers, share information, generate traffic, leads and much more.<br><br>You may initially think that Twitter is only good for tracking your favorite celebrities’ activities or swapping a few tweets with your friends but what you do not know is that fact that this popular social media platform can do a whole lot more. Several specialized services have actually tweaked it, turning ordinary Twitter accounts to carry on helpful tasks.<br><br>The Twitter Money Bot can check your stats for you, help you manage your own calendar and remind you of tweets. In short, it is not just your ordinary Twitter marketing software, the newest version also serves as an Inte.com Marketing Money Creator Robot.<br><br>The new Twitter Money Bot v3 comes with powerful options and features to help you boost Twitter marketing. It includes a mix of mass and automated features that can provide maximum flexibility to users. Do you want to know what Twitter Money Bot can do for you?<br><br>Below is a description for every built-in characteristic that Twitter Money Bot has to offer:<br><ul><li> When you begin running the new Twitter Money Bot v3, it will execute various customizable Twitter tasks for you. All you need to do is to run Twitter Bot in the background to perform these tasks – automatic random tweeting, automatic adding of targeted users, automatic following back, and so much more.<br></li><li> If you want to learn how to get followers on Twitter, Twitter Money Bot allows you to follow back new followers to leverage and expand your.comwork. Each time a new follower appears, Twitter Bot will automatically follow back for effective growth of potential prospects.<br></li><li> Aside from that, our Twitter automation software will subsequently unfollow Twitter users who are not following you back after a few days. In this way, we can help you avoid following individuals who cannot read your tweets. This is excellent for keeping your list of followers active and clean.<br></li><li> Do you need to spread certain information across your list of followers? The new Twitter Money Bot v3 has the capacity to send direct messages to all of them!<br></li><li> As every Twitter Marketing Software needs a search feature, users can now look for users and targeted tweets to follow with our Twitter Bot. The great thing about this is that the results are exportable to text editors.<br></li><li> The new V3 release enables users to work with multiple Twitter accounts. This feature is great if you want to load tweets, followers and friends coming from other profiles as you can easily import or export the data.<br></li><li> Another important tip, if you want to mass unfollow users from several accounts, Twitter Money Bot allows you to do so.<br></li><li> The new Twitter Money Bot v3 now has a local cache database which will help increase performance by huge margins and also avoid unneeded API connections. You can retrieve stored information with our software and the database will be consistently updated by the data sync service in order to make sure that your Twitter profile and Twitter Money Bot are synchronized.<br></li><li> Aggregate RSS feeds and real-time website content automatically as tweets and directly post them to your account.<br></li><li> Twitter Money Bot has a scheduler feature which allows you to set up tweets in advance. This will save you the time and effort and is effective as is starts the tasks on its own, according to the time frame you have set. You can schedule all your tweets through the Scheduler and you can watch all of them get posted without you having access to a mobile device or a computer. Experiment with different campaigns to find out which one works best for you.<br></li><li> A great feature of our Twitter bot is that it enables you to import tweets from certain third party tools like a text file. You also have the luxury of formulating tweets in advance from almost anywhere in just a single shot.<br></li><li> With all the features of our newest version of the Twitter Money Bot, it has everything that you need in order to grow your base of followers and promote anything at almost any time that you want to. There is no other tool that combines the powers of Twitter as a social media platform into just one software. This Twitter Bot is an automated and optimized version of Twitter that you can run seven days a week, 24 hours a day.<br></li></ul><br>Main Features Of Twitter Money Bot v3<br><ul><li> Auto follow users from search results or txt files<br></li><li> Follow other people’s followers or followings<br></li><li> Unfollow users who don’t follow you back<br></li><li> Mass Favorite And Mass Retweet<br></li><li> Tweet Poster<br></li><li> Reply And Mention Generator<br></li><li> Mass Account Statistics Checker<br></li><li> Twitter Account Creator<br></li><li> Direct Message Sender<br></li><li> Various Scrapers To Scrape Various Infos From Twitter<br></li><li> Multi Threaded – Now v3 can work with multiple accounts at the same time!<br></li><li> Proxy Support – Public And Private Proxies!<br></li><li> Scheduler – Just Set Up Your Campaign To The Task Table And Leave It To The Scheduler, It Will Start Your Tasks In The List Automatically<br></li><li> Random Delay Feature<br></li><li> Mass Twitter User ID / Username Converter<br></li><li> White List – The unfollower will never unfollow people who are in your white list…<br></li><li> DeathByCaptcha Auto Captcha Solver API Has Been Integrated For Account Creator<br></li><li> Able To Add Unlimited Twitter Accounts<br></li><li> Extra Helpful Modules And Tools For SEO And Inte.com Marketing<br></li><li> SERP Scraper – It Can Scrape Websites And URLs From Various Search Engines<br></li><li> Blog Comment Poster – It Can Post Your Comments To WP Blogs, So You Can Get Comment Backlinks<br></li><li> Article Scraper<br></li><li> Keyword Scraper<br></li><li> SEO / Website Analyzer<br></li><li> Keyword Analyzer<br></li><li> Mass Pinger<br></li><li> Fast Indexer<br></li><li> And More…<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://twittermoneybot.com/Screenshots/TMB-Main-GUI.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Twitter Money Bot 3.9.0 GOLD"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>TSupremacy 1.232 Ultimate</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1271-tsupremacy.html</link>
<description>Name : TSupremacy Version : 1.232 Ultimate OS : Windows Type : Twitter Marketing Tools Price : $80 Homepage : SalePage TSupremacy is Twitter marketing made easy. A sleek and clear design packed with tons of powerful features that are simple to use. It does not get any better than this. Simple. TSupremacy is a multi-threaded, proxy enabled Twitter account management tool. Boosting a huge array of features that makes automating Twitter marketing seamless. Sit back and relax while TSupremacy does the job for you!</description>
<category>Twitter Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="https://i.imgur.com/Nw66VEE.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2018 07:48:03 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Tweet Retweet Reply Mention Follow Unfollow Favorite Profile Photo / Bio / Header Account Creator Scraper Multi-Threaded Proxy Enabled Scheduler Auto Pilot Advanced Settings History Logs Task Reports Clear Design</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/T91maKbo-qk?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Tweet<br></li><li> Retweet<br></li><li> Reply<br></li><li> Mention<br></li><li> Follow<br></li><li> Unfollow<br></li><li> Favorite<br></li><li> Profile Photo / Bio / Header<br></li><li> Account Creator<br></li><li> Scraper<br></li><li> Multi-Threaded<br></li><li> Proxy Enabled<br></li><li> Scheduler<br></li><li> Auto Pilot<br></li><li> Advanced Settings<br></li><li> History Logs<br></li><li> Task Reports<br></li><li> Clear Design<br></li></ul><br><img src="https://i.imgur.com/Nw66VEE.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="TSupremacy 1.232 Ultimate"><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Twitter Laser 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4243-twitter-laser.html</link>
<description>Name : Twitter Laser Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Twitter Marketing Tool Price : $59 Homepage : SalePage Twitter Laser is a desktop application that allows uses to automatically tweet to users who have specific keywords in their tweets. For example if someone tweets &quot;excited for game of thrones&quot; then Twitter Laser can automatically send a tweet to this user saying something like &quot;@user Hi Ben, I&#039;m excited too! I wrote a cool post on this check it out&quot;. There is no limit on the amount of keywords that can be monitored or accounts that can be used.</description>
<category>Twitter Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 03:25:59 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Twitter Laser if used correctly can generate hundreds of laser targeted visitors per day. You simply have to know all the keywords your potential website visitors will be tweeting and customise the message you tweet at them for each one. Where else can you generate such targeted traffic from Twitter? Tips for max results - Don&#039;t post spammy links or you&#039;ll get your account and domain banned off Twitter pretty quickly. - Don&#039;t run other Twitter automation software on the same machine/IP. - Tweet useful things to users and don&#039;t annoy them. - Tweet from trusted and aged Twitter accounts. - Have a sensible delay between Tweeting messages to people. - Make your Tweets as targeted as possible so avoid many of the above. - As of 06/02/2018 this tool requires Chrome to be installed</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/gZT1ZmgniHE?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Twitter Laser if used correctly can generate hundreds of laser targeted visitors per day. You simply have to know all the keywords your potential website visitors will be tweeting and customise the message you tweet at them for each one. Where else can you generate such targeted traffic from Twitter?<br></li><li> Tips for max results<br></li><li> - Don't post spammy links or you'll get your account and domain banned off Twitter pretty quickly.<br></li><li> - Don't run other Twitter automation software on the same machine/IP.<br></li><li> - Tweet useful things to users and don't annoy them.<br></li><li> - Tweet from trusted and aged Twitter accounts.<br></li><li> - Have a sensible delay between Tweeting messages to people.<br></li><li> - Make your Tweets as targeted as possible so avoid many of the above.<br></li><li> - As of 06/02/2018 this tool requires Chrome to be installed<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Twitter Laser 1.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>TweetAttacksPro 4 Elite 7.5.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1280-tweetattackspro-4.html</link>
<description>Name : TweetAttacksPro 4 Version : Elite Version 7.5.0 Unlimited Accounts OS : Windows Type : Twitter Marketing Bot Price : $297 Homepage : SalePage The best twitter tool on the market! TweetAttacksPro 4 is designed to run thousands of twitter accounts at the same time 24/7 to auto-follow, unfollow, follow back, tweet, retweet, reply, favorite, and send messages to your new followers ..etc. Every account can have its own settings thus preventing twitter from becoming suspicious about the account, plus the software can simulate human operation perfectly!</description>
<category>Twitter Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.tweetattackspro.com/img/cut/TAPSettings.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 14:31:19 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Account Manager : Manage thousands of accounts and categories easily. Account Filter : Displays a list of following and followers of your account, and tells you which accounts you should unfollow, then unfollows them automatically. Basic Task Settings : Task black/white list settings, Desktop or mobile site selection and task run interval time etc... Auto Follow Task : Auto follow people by searching keywords, importing lists, others peoples&#039; followers..etc Auto Follow Back Task : Auto follow the people who follow you. Auto Unfollow Task : Auto unfollow people randomly or only unfollow the ones who don&#039;t follow you. There are many options you can select. Auto Tweet Task : Auto Tweet message in a list, txt file, rss etc... Auto Retweet Task : Auto Retweet others&#039; tweets by searching keywords, or by watching someone&#039;s tweet list. Auto Reply Task : This can watch tweets realtime based on your keywords and reply to them instantly. You also can search tweets to reply in a batch and you can set one reply message for the whole task, or set a different reply message for every account. Auto Favorite Task : Search keywords to find tweets to favorite, or watch other peoples&#039; tweets and favorite them in real time. This makes your account look active and gives your account more chance to get followed. Auto Send Message Task : Send messages to all your followers, or randomly send to some people, or send a message to new followers...etc. Advanced Task Settings : Set some advanced functions like auto-shift proxy when the current proxy has a problem, stop running a task when there is a.comwork problem, etc... Message Manager : Add/edit/manage your frequently-used messages, tweets, comments etc. ...You can manage them by category and import/use them in your task(s). SpinnerChief API Support : Spin your content to unique new content automatically. Proxy Support : Every account can use a different proxy to protect your account from being banned. Multi-Thread Support : Run thousands of accounts at the same time with multi-threads. Auto Captcha Support : Auto-Solving Captcha when there is a captcha needed. Auto Url Shorten Support : Auto shorten the url in your tweet, message, etc... Run tasks 24/7 Tweet Pictures : We can tweet images now, not just text. Send Message with Image : We can send message plus image now too. Global Black list Support : Set a global black list for follow, unfollow, retweet, reply, favorite and direct message functions. Then all tasks will use the black list when working. Auto Data Backup and Resume : Auto backup your data when the program is running. If your data is accidentally destroyed, you can resume it very easily. Much much more are not listed here...... - Unlimited accounts -</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/xVQgdq5FKBw?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><p><br></p><br><h3>Features</h3><br><p><br><ul><li> Account Manager : Manage thousands of accounts and categories easily.<br></li><li> Account Filter : Displays a list of following and followers of your account, and tells you which accounts you should unfollow, then unfollows them automatically. <br></li><li> Basic Task Settings : Task black/white list settings, Desktop or mobile site selection and task run interval time etc... <br></li><li> Auto Follow Task : Auto follow people by searching keywords, importing lists, others peoples' followers..etc <br></li><li> Auto Follow Back Task : Auto follow the people who follow you. <br></li><li> Auto Unfollow Task : Auto unfollow people randomly or only unfollow the ones who don't follow you. There are many options you can select. <br></li><li> Auto Tweet Task : Auto Tweet message in a list, txt file, rss etc... <br></li><li> Auto Retweet Task : Auto Retweet others' tweets by searching keywords, or by watching someone's tweet list. <br></li><li> Auto Reply Task : This can watch tweets realtime based on your keywords and reply to them instantly. You also can search tweets to reply in a batch and you can set one reply message for the whole task, or set a different reply message for every account. <br></li><li> Auto Favorite Task : Search keywords to find tweets to favorite, or watch other peoples' tweets and favorite them in real time. This makes your account look active and gives your account more chance to get followed. <br></li><li> Auto Send Message Task : Send messages to all your followers, or randomly send to some people, or send a message to new followers...etc. <br></li><li> Advanced Task Settings : Set some advanced functions like auto-shift proxy when the current proxy has a problem, stop running a task when there is a.comwork problem, etc... <br></li><li> Message Manager : Add/edit/manage your frequently-used messages, tweets, comments etc. ...You can manage them by category and import/use them in your task(s). <br></li><li> SpinnerChief API Support : Spin your content to unique new content automatically. <br></li><li> Proxy Support : Every account can use a different proxy to protect your account from being banned. <br></li><li> Multi-Thread Support : Run thousands of accounts at the same time with multi-threads. <br></li><li> Auto Captcha Support : Auto-Solving Captcha when there is a captcha needed. <br></li><li> Auto Url Shorten Support : Auto shorten the url in your tweet, message, etc... <br></li><li> Run tasks 24/7<br></li><li> Tweet Pictures : We can tweet images now, not just text. <br></li><li> Send Message with Image : We can send message plus image now too. <br></li><li> Global Black list Support : Set a global black list for follow, unfollow, retweet, reply, favorite and direct message functions. Then all tasks will use the black list when working. <br></li><li> Auto Data Backup and Resume : Auto backup your data when the program is running. If your data is accidentally destroyed, you can resume it very easily. <br></li><li> Much much more are not listed here......<br></li><li> - Unlimited accounts -<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://www.tweetattackspro.com/img/cut/TAPSettings.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="TweetAttacksPro 4 Elite 7.5.0"></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>TweetAttacksPro III Elite 6.4.0.2</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1071-tweetattackspro-iii.html</link>
<description>Name : TweetAttacksPro III Version : Unlimited accounts Elite Version 6.4.0.2 OS : Windows Type : Twitter Marketing Bot Price : $297 Homepage : SalePage The best twitter tool on the market! TweetAttacksPro 3 is designed to run thousands of twitter accounts at the same time 24/7 to auto-follow, unfollow, follow back, tweet, retweet, reply, favorite, and send messages to your new followers ..etc. Every account can have its own settings thus preventing twitter from becoming suspicious about the account, plus the software can simulate human operation perfectly!</description>
<category>Twitter Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.tweetattackspro.com/img/cut/RunTasks.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 14:31:17 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Account Manager : Manage thousands of accounts and categories easily. Account Filter : Displays a list of following and followers of your account, and tells you which accounts you should unfollow, then unfollows them automatically. Basic Task Settings : Task black/white list settings, Desktop or mobile site selection and task run interval time etc... Auto Follow Task : Auto follow people by searching keywords, importing lists, others peoples&#039; followers..etc Auto Follow Back Task : Auto follow the people who follow you. Auto Unfollow Task : Auto unfollow people randomly or only unfollow the ones who don&#039;t follow you. There are many options you can select. Auto Tweet Task : Auto Tweet message in a list, txt file, rss etc... Auto Retweet Task : Auto Retweet others&#039; tweets by searching keywords, or by watching someone&#039;s tweet list. Auto Reply Task : This can watch tweets realtime based on your keywords and reply to them instantly. You also can search tweets to reply in a batch and you can set one reply message for the whole task, or set a different reply message for every account. Auto Favorite Task : Search keywords to find tweets to favorite, or watch other peoples&#039; tweets and favorite them in real time. This makes your account look active and gives your account more chance to get followed. Auto Send Message Task : Send messages to all your followers, or randomly send to some people, or send a message to new followers...etc. Advanced Task Settings : Set some advanced functions like auto-shift proxy when the current proxy has a problem, stop running a task when there is a.comwork problem, etc... Message Manager : Add/edit/manage your frequently-used messages, tweets, comments etc. ...You can manage them by category and import/use them in your task(s). SpinnerChief API Support : Spin your content to unique new content automatically. Proxy Support : Every account can use a different proxy to protect your account from being banned. Multi-Thread Support : Run thousands of accounts at the same time with multi-threads. Auto Captcha Support : Auto-Solving Captcha when there is a captcha needed. Auto Url Shorten Support : Auto shorten the url in your tweet, message, etc... Run tasks 24/7 Tweet Pictures : We can tweet images now, not just text. Send Message with Image : We can send message plus image now too. Global Black list Support : Set a global black list for follow, unfollow, retweet, reply, favorite and direct message functions. Then all tasks will use the black list when working. Auto Data Backup and Resume : Auto backup your data when the program is running. If your data is accidentally destroyed, you can resume it very easily. Much much more are not listed here...... - Unlimited accounts -</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/xVQgdq5FKBw?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><p><br></p><br><h3>Features</h3><br><p><br><ul><li> Account Manager : Manage thousands of accounts and categories easily.<br></li><li> Account Filter : Displays a list of following and followers of your account, and tells you which accounts you should unfollow, then unfollows them automatically. <br></li><li> Basic Task Settings : Task black/white list settings, Desktop or mobile site selection and task run interval time etc... <br></li><li> Auto Follow Task : Auto follow people by searching keywords, importing lists, others peoples' followers..etc <br></li><li> Auto Follow Back Task : Auto follow the people who follow you. <br></li><li> Auto Unfollow Task : Auto unfollow people randomly or only unfollow the ones who don't follow you. There are many options you can select. <br></li><li> Auto Tweet Task : Auto Tweet message in a list, txt file, rss etc... <br></li><li> Auto Retweet Task : Auto Retweet others' tweets by searching keywords, or by watching someone's tweet list. <br></li><li> Auto Reply Task : This can watch tweets realtime based on your keywords and reply to them instantly. You also can search tweets to reply in a batch and you can set one reply message for the whole task, or set a different reply message for every account. <br></li><li> Auto Favorite Task : Search keywords to find tweets to favorite, or watch other peoples' tweets and favorite them in real time. This makes your account look active and gives your account more chance to get followed. <br></li><li> Auto Send Message Task : Send messages to all your followers, or randomly send to some people, or send a message to new followers...etc. <br></li><li> Advanced Task Settings : Set some advanced functions like auto-shift proxy when the current proxy has a problem, stop running a task when there is a.comwork problem, etc... <br></li><li> Message Manager : Add/edit/manage your frequently-used messages, tweets, comments etc. ...You can manage them by category and import/use them in your task(s). <br></li><li> SpinnerChief API Support : Spin your content to unique new content automatically. <br></li><li> Proxy Support : Every account can use a different proxy to protect your account from being banned. <br></li><li> Multi-Thread Support : Run thousands of accounts at the same time with multi-threads. <br></li><li> Auto Captcha Support : Auto-Solving Captcha when there is a captcha needed. <br></li><li> Auto Url Shorten Support : Auto shorten the url in your tweet, message, etc... <br></li><li> Run tasks 24/7<br></li><li> Tweet Pictures : We can tweet images now, not just text. <br></li><li> Send Message with Image : We can send message plus image now too. <br></li><li> Global Black list Support : Set a global black list for follow, unfollow, retweet, reply, favorite and direct message functions. Then all tasks will use the black list when working. <br></li><li> Auto Data Backup and Resume : Auto backup your data when the program is running. If your data is accidentally destroyed, you can resume it very easily. <br></li><li> Much much more are not listed here......<br></li><li> - Unlimited accounts -<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://www.tweetattackspro.com/img/cut/RunTasks.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="TweetAttacksPro III Elite 6.4.0.2"></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Twitter Account Manager Pro 2.9.0.2</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1067-twitter-account-manager.html</link>
<description>Name : Twitter Account Manager Version : Pro 2.9.0.2 OS : Windows Type : Twitter Marketing Bot Price : $147 Homepage : SalePage Create Hundreds of Twitter Account In Minutes, Confirm Register Email Automatically and Update Profile/Avatar/Design By One Click!</description>
<category>Twitter Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.tweetattackspro.com/Img/6confirm.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 10:58:26 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Account Register and Email Confirm Functions, Profile/Avatar/Design Update Functions</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/nFE4F5milRI?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><p><br></p><br><h3>Features</h3><br><p><br><ul><li> Account Register and Email Confirm Functions,<br></li><li> Profile/Avatar/Design Update Functions<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://www.tweetattackspro.com/Img/6confirm.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Twitter Account Manager Pro 2.9.0.2"></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Twitter Blue Bot 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3720-twitter-blue-bot.html</link>
<description>Name : Twitter Blue Bot Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Twitter Marketing Bot Price : $0 Homepage : SalePage Twitter Blue Bot automates many of you&#039;re daily twitter account activites for you. It can follow and unfollow people, tweet, pin, retweet and more. It can handle many many accounts and is only limited by the resources (RAM/CPU) you can allocate it.</description>
<category>Twitter Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 14:00:06 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>[media=https://youtu.be/14rjZF9zfu4] Features Why should I use Blue Bot Twitter is a fantastic source of traffic, while all social.comworks are great for driving traffic to your website few have the unique features that make Twitter really stand out for this task. For example few social.comworks allow you to amass an unlimited amount of contacts you may interact with. Linkedin, Facebook, Tumblr all have 5,000 limits in general. Twitter is also relatively bot friendly, as long as you are sharing good content and not spamming/annoying people you can follow a couple of hundred people per day without fear of your account being banned. How does Blue Bot work? You simply load your twitter accounts into Blue Bot then add any proxies you may need. Once all your accounts are loaded in you set up scheduled tasks that run at a set time or at set intervals to perform specific tasks such as tweeting a tweet from a pool of predefined tweets or following people who have just followed accounts related to your niche. With a healthy amount of accounts loaded in you can expect to gain 20,000+ followers after a month or so.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;">[media=https://youtu.be/14rjZF9zfu4]</div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br>Why should I use Blue Bot<br>Twitter is a fantastic source of traffic, while all social.comworks are great for driving traffic to your website few have the unique features that make Twitter really stand out for this task. For example few social.comworks allow you to amass an unlimited amount of contacts you may interact with. Linkedin, Facebook, Tumblr all have 5,000 limits in general. Twitter is also relatively bot friendly, as long as you are sharing good content and not spamming/annoying people you can follow a couple of hundred people per day without fear of your account being banned.<br><br>How does Blue Bot work?<br>You simply load your twitter accounts into Blue Bot then add any proxies you may need. Once all your accounts are loaded in you set up scheduled tasks that run at a set time or at set intervals to perform specific tasks such as tweeting a tweet from a pool of predefined tweets or following people who have just followed accounts related to your niche. With a healthy amount of accounts loaded in you can expect to gain 20,000+ followers after a month or so.<br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Twitter Blue Bot 1.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>RetweeThunder 1.2.8</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1653-retweethunder.html</link>
<description>Name : RetweeThunder Version : 1.2.8 OS : Windows Type : Twitter Marketing Bot Price : $79 Homepage : SalePage Auto Tweet Boot will help u retweet everydays Automatically monitoring the user’s latest tweet everyday and then using your own accounts to retweet.</description>
<category>Twitter Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://store.botchief.com/upload/img/pro/imgs/c182d955-98c0-481b-88a3-0103dd42cabe.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 14:30:17 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features 1. Proxy/useragent support to secure your accounts. 2. Available to set the minimum and maximum number of retweet. 3. Automatically verify your mail of your account. 4. Multiple thread support to improve the efficiency of work. 5. Very smart to judge if the account has been retweeted the same tweet again. 6. All the running log information will be shown clear. 7. Be very clear to show you the number of retweet of the account. 8. Running very fast and stable. Two ways to do the monitoring: 1. Monitoring account home page Tweet. 2. Monitoring account friend Tweet.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br>1. Proxy/useragent support to secure your accounts.<br>2. Available to set the minimum and maximum number of retweet.<br>3. Automatically verify your mail of your account.<br>4. Multiple thread support to improve the efficiency of work.<br>5. Very smart to judge if the account has been retweeted the same tweet again.<br>6. All the running log information will be shown clear.<br>7. Be very clear to show you the number of retweet of the account. <br>8. Running very fast and stable.<br><br>Two ways to do the monitoring:<br>1. Monitoring account home page Tweet.<br>2. Monitoring account friend Tweet.<br><img src="http://store.botchief.com/upload/img/pro/imgs/c182d955-98c0-481b-88a3-0103dd42cabe.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="RetweeThunder 1.2.8"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>