<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>GB Graphic Kits - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>GB Graphic Kits - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>JumboVID + OTOs [Instant Deliver]</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4505-junbovid-otos.html</link>
<description>GB Name : JumboVID + OTOs Version : Last OS : Anything Type : PPT VIDEO TEMPLATES GB Price : $27(FE) + $47(OTO1) = $64 GB Cost : 10$/6 Peoples + 1.8$ Fee GB Joined : 5/6 Peoples GB Status : Delivered Homepage : SalePage Our graphic products is the most easy to edit. All you need to do is EDIT, CLICK, and EXPORT. This pack also offer 395+ video marketing templates in various niche for business or personal need that no-One ever provide video templates like we do.</description>
<category>GB Graphic Kits</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 05:26:48 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FE - JunboVID - $27 135 Video Templates 1. Business Presentation (total 5) 2. Animated Explainer (total 10) 3. Welcome Video (total 10) 4. Promotion Video (total 10) 5. Logo Opener (total 20) 6. Video Outro (total 20) 7. Video Explainer (total 20) 8. Social Media (total 20) 9. Facebook Cover (total 20) Commersial License OTO1 - PLATINUM - $47 260 Video Templates 1. Business Presentation (total 15) 2. Animated Explainer (total 15) 3. Welcome Video (total 15) 4. Promotion Video (total 15) 5. Logo Opener (total 40) 6. Video Outro (total 40) 7. Video Explainer (total 40) 8. Social Media (total 40) 9. Facebook Cover (total 40) More niche Commersial License on All Packages OTO2 - VIDEO-X - $57 OTO3 - BUNDLE - $87</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br><a href="https://arseniomedia.com/astroblu/jumbovidjv" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>FE - JunboVID - </b></a><br><ul><li> 135 Video Templates <br></li><li> 1. Business Presentation (total 5)<br></li><li> 2. Animated Explainer (total 10)<br></li><li> 3. Welcome Video (total 10)<br></li><li> 4. Promotion Video (total 10)<br></li><li> 5. Logo Opener (total 20)<br></li><li> 6. Video Outro (total 20)<br></li><li> 7. Video Explainer (total 20)<br></li><li> 8. Social Media (total 20)<br></li><li> 9. Facebook Cover (total 20)<br>Commersial License<br></li></ul><br><a href="https://arseniomedia.com/astroblu/jumbovidjv" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO1 - PLATINUM - </b></a><br><ul><li> 260 Video Templates<br></li><li> 1. Business Presentation (total 15)<br></li><li> 2. Animated Explainer (total 15)<br></li><li> 3. Welcome Video (total 15)<br></li><li> 4. Promotion Video (total 15)<br></li><li> 5. Logo Opener (total 40)<br></li><li> 6. Video Outro (total 40)<br></li><li> 7. Video Explainer (total 40)<br></li><li> 8. Social Media (total 40)<br></li><li> 9. Facebook Cover (total 40)<br></li><li> More niche<br></li><li> Commersial License on All Packages<br></li></ul><br><a href="https://arseniomedia.com/astroblu/jumbovidjv" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO2 - VIDEO-X - </b></a><br><ul><li> <br></li></ul><br><a href="https://arseniomedia.com/astroblu/jumbovidjv" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO3 - BUNDLE - </b></a><br><ul><li> <br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="JumboVID + OTOs [Instant Deliver]"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>TheMovid + OTOs [Instant Deliver]</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4509-themovid-otos.html</link>
<description>GB Name : TheMovid + OTOs Version : Last OS : Anything Type : Creative Video + Graphic Templates GB Price : $19.43(FE) + $34(OTO1) + $57(OTO2) = $110.43 GB Cost : 11.5$/10 Peoples + 1$ Fee GB Joined : 8/10 Peoples GB Status : Delivered Homepage : SalePage TheMovid is a brand new fresh breakthrough and creative video or graphic templates. All template created from Powerpoint, without additional complicated video software. There is also No additional plugin needed, No technology skills required and No need</description>
<category>GB Graphic Kits</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 05:26:36 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FE - TheMovid - $19.43 NO Copyright Music No need to buy extra additional music. All templates in TheMovid include no copyright music, so you don&#039;t need to buy extra additional music. NO Complicated Video Software You only need Powerpoint, without need Adobe After Effects, Adobe Premiere or Vegas Pro and No Additional Plugin Required. No Need to Try from Scratch Stop wasting your time and money trying to create High-quality video or graphic design. You only need edit &amp;amp; replace! Free Royalty Images or Video All image or video in TheMovid is included. So you don&#039;t need to buy the image or video again, and you can use for your projects. Powerful Colouring All templates in TheMovid are made by the experts, thus it will certainly making your video looks like made by professional using colouring video. Your video will definitely get people jealous. ALL in One Bundle It&#039;s the Most Comprehensive Bundle ever Designed. INSTANT! You can create Professional Videos and Graphics without any have Experience and Design Skills. Module 1: Movie Style Video Templates Module 2: Explainer Video Templates Module 3: Instagram Video Templates Module 4: Social Story Video Templates Module 5: Facebook Cover Video Templates Module 6: Instagram Banner Templates Module 7: Premium Flyer/Poster Design Templates OTO1 - TheMovid Pro Upgrade + Developer License - $34 TheMovid Pro Upgrade is a Additional Mega Bundle Video and Graphic Templates with Developer/commercial License that will help you create engaging and professional to creating Video and Graphics Templates for your clients.. EXCLUSIVE FOR NEW CUSTOMER ONLY All contents inside TheMovid Pro Version are exclusive for new customer only, so you can expect super UNIQUE &amp;amp; FRESH contents that make your video or graphics stand out from the crowd MORE TEMPLATES READY TO USE Once you upgrade to PRO version, you’ll get more powerpoint templates in various niches as well as new effects. This surely will help you to create even more high quality video or graphics. EASY MONEY BY SELLING VIDEOS TO CLIENTS Video or graphic creation service is in a HOT Demand right now. With commercial license included in the PRO Version, you can easily charge anywhere between $400 – $1,500 per video you make for a client. OTO2 - All Bundle Creativid Templates - $57 Creativid is a Mega bundle of brand new creative video templates. Yes, now anyone can make a creative video with easy-to-use powerpoint without additional complicated video editor. There is also no special plugin needed and no technology skills required.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ZjYsfrmCI5s?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><a href="https://themovid.com/live-bestdeal/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>FE - TheMovid - .43</b></a><br><ul><li> NO Copyright Music<br></li><li> No need to buy extra additional music. All templates in TheMovid include no copyright music, so you don't need to buy extra additional music.<br></li><li> NO Complicated Video Software<br></li><li> You only need Powerpoint, without need Adobe After Effects, Adobe Premiere or Vegas Pro and No Additional Plugin Required.<br></li><li> No Need to Try from Scratch<br></li><li> Stop wasting your time and money trying to create High-quality video or graphic design. You only need edit &amp; replace!<br></li><li> Free Royalty Images or Video<br></li><li> All image or video in TheMovid is included. So you don't need to buy the image or video again, and you can use for your projects.<br></li><li> Powerful Colouring<br></li><li> All templates in TheMovid are made by the experts, thus it will certainly making your video looks like made by professional using colouring video. Your video will definitely get people jealous.<br></li><li> ALL in One Bundle<br></li><li> It's the Most Comprehensive Bundle ever Designed. INSTANT! You can create Professional Videos and Graphics without any have Experience and Design Skills.<br></li><li> Module 1: Movie Style Video Templates<br></li><li> Module 2: Explainer Video Templates<br></li><li> Module 3: Instagram Video Templates<br></li><li> Module 4: Social Story Video Templates<br></li><li> Module 5: Facebook Cover Video Templates<br></li><li> Module 6: Instagram Banner Templates<br></li><li> Module 7: Premium Flyer/Poster Design Templates<br></li></ul><br><a href="https://themovid.com/pro-upgrade/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO1 - TheMovid Pro Upgrade + Developer License - </b></a><br><ul><li> TheMovid Pro Upgrade is a Additional Mega Bundle Video and Graphic Templates with Developer/commercial License that will help you create engaging and professional to creating Video and Graphics Templates for your clients..<br></li><li> EXCLUSIVE FOR NEW CUSTOMER ONLY<br></li><li> All contents inside TheMovid Pro Version are exclusive for new customer only, so you can expect super UNIQUE &amp; FRESH contents that make your video or graphics stand out from the crowd<br></li><li> MORE TEMPLATES READY TO USE<br></li><li> Once you upgrade to PRO version, you’ll get more powerpoint templates in various niches as well as new effects. This surely will help you to create even more high quality video or graphics.<br></li><li> EASY MONEY BY SELLING VIDEOS TO CLIENTS<br></li><li> Video or graphic creation service is in a HOT Demand right now. With commercial license included in the PRO Version, you can easily charge anywhere between 0 – ,500 per video you make for a client.<br></li></ul><br><a href="https://themovid.com/super-discount-member-only/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO2 - All Bundle Creativid Templates - </b></a><br><ul><li> Creativid is a Mega bundle of brand new creative video templates. Yes, now anyone can make a creative video with easy-to-use powerpoint without additional complicated video editor. There is also no special plugin needed and no technology skills required.<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="TheMovid + OTOs [Instant Deliver]"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>AudioBlocks Annual</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3993-audioblocks.html</link>
<description>GB Name : AudioBlocks Annual Version : Last OS : Anything Type : Stock Audio Download GB Price : $150/y GB Cost : 15$/10 Peoples + 1.5$ Fee GB Joined : 6/10 Peoples GB Status : Going Homepage : SalePage Find the Royalty-free Stock Audio You Need. Fast. Ready to get started? Select the audio type you need today: - Music - Sound Effects - Loops</description>
<category>GB Graphic Kits</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 27 May 2018 11:30:24 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FE - AudioBlocks - $100/y Unlimited Downloads You will have unlimited access to the library- including more than 100,000 tracks. There are no download caps, so you can download and use as much as you want. 100% Royalty-Free All tracks provided on Audioblocks come with the right to use them royalty free for personal or commercial projects. There are absolutely no hidden fees. Continuously Updated New content is continually added to Audioblocks, so there is always something fresh. Enjoy unlimited access to all new content as a benefit of your membership.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/NUFJ50OZLPY?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><a href="https://www.audioblocks.com/join"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer"><b>FE - AudioBlocks  - 0/y</b></a><br><ul><li> Unlimited Downloads<br></li><li> You will have unlimited access to the library- including more than 100,000 tracks. There are no download caps, so you can download and use as </li><li> </li><li> much as you want.<br></li><li> 100% Royalty-Free<br></li><li> All tracks provided on Audioblocks come with the right to use them royalty free for personal or commercial projects. There are absolutely no hidden fees.<br></li><li> Continuously Updated<br></li><li> New content is continually added to Audioblocks, so there is always something fresh. Enjoy unlimited access to all new content as a benefit of your membership.<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="AudioBlocks Annual"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>GraphicStock Annual</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4351-graphicstock-otos.html</link>
<description>GB Name : GraphicStock Annual Version : Last OS : Anything Type : Images, Photos, Vectors &amp;amp; Graphics Download GB Price : $100/y GB Cost : 15$/6 Peoples + 1.5$ Fee GB Joined : 6/6 Peoples GB Status : Going Homepage : SalePage Be Brilliant on a Budget. Become a Member and Save on Millions of High-Quality Stock Photos, Vectors, and Illustrations.</description>
<category>GB Graphic Kits</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 08:57:56 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FE - Graphicstock - $100/y Unlimited 400,000 images included Your subscription includes unlimited downloads from our Member Library at no additional cost. New Marketplace Save 60% on millions of images sold by artists in our new Marketplace. Royalty-free license Every image you download is yours to keep and use forever—royalty-free.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/i2YerpQYG0A?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe><br><h3>Features</h3><br><a href="https://www.graphicstock.com"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer"><b>FE - Graphicstock - 0/y</b></a><br><ul><li> Unlimited<br></li><li> 400,000 images included<br></li><li> Your subscription includes unlimited downloads from our Member Library at no additional cost.<br></li><li> New Marketplace<br></li><li> Save 60% on millions of images sold by artists in our new Marketplace.<br></li><li> Royalty-free license<br></li><li> Every image you download is yours to keep and use forever—royalty-free.<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="GraphicStock Annual"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>PicMonkey Annual</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4479-picmonkey-annual.html</link>
<description>GB Name : PicMonkey Annual Version : Last OS : Anything Type : Photo Editing + Collage Making + Graphic Design GB Price : $119.88/y GB Cost : 12$/10 Peoples + 1$ Fee GB Joined : 6/10 Peoples GB Status : Going Homepage : SalePage Everything you need to make your ideas come to life—photo editing, collage making, graphic design—PicMonkey&#039;s got it. It&#039;s never been easier to feed your creative beast.</description>
<category>GB Graphic Kits</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 08:09:59 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FE - PicMonkey Annual - $119.88/y Unlimited Hub storage Organize Hub with Collections Save, Export, Share Advanced touch up tools Primo effects, overlays, fonts Re-editable images, in Hub Top-shelf templates No ads</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/7E65KA_Z5JM?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><a href="https://www.picmonkey.com/pricing"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer"><b>FE - PicMonkey Annual  - 9.88/y</b></a><br><ul><li> Unlimited Hub storage<br></li><li> Organize Hub with Collections<br></li><li> Save, Export, Share<br></li><li> Advanced touch up tools<br></li><li> Primo effects, overlays, fonts<br></li><li> Re-editable images, in Hub<br></li><li> Top-shelf templates<br></li><li> No ads<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="PicMonkey Annual"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Pinguino + OTOs [Delivering]</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4492-pinguino-otos.html</link>
<description>GB Name : Pinguino + OTOs Version : Last OS : Anything Type : Product Mockup Generator GB Price : $37(FE) + $47(OTO1) + $239.4/y(OTO2) = $323.4 GB Cost : 16.5$/20 Peoples + 2$ Fee GB Joined : 16/20 Peoples GB Status : Going Homepage : SalePage Pinguino is a product mockup generator. It allows you to build any product in a matter of minutes. And the best part about this tool is that it does not require you to have any prior understanding of graphic design.</description>
<category>GB Graphic Kits</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 04:57:57 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FE - Pinguino - $37 100+ cutting-edge templates Pinguino offers push-button mockup designs, which will reduce a great deal of time for the manual tasks. Moreover, you can easily drag and drop any image and make your own templates in seconds. It thus saves a lot of time and money for outsourcing. As a result, it allows you to diversify your resources more efficiently. Automatic generation This tool has hundreds of product mockups that are compatible with almost all devices. With just a press of a button, you will have a ready-to-sell material at your fingertips. Pinguino has made designing so easy that even a complete newbie can start using it without any hassle. And this feature is what my Pinguino Review really wants to capitalize on. I believe drag-and-drop design will soon be a trend. Unlimited commercial license You do not only create the products, you can also sell them anytime you want. Additionally, you can set them at any price of your choice. With the commercial license, users can actually make profits from what they created. It also means that you will be both the product creator and the graphic designer at the same time. And there will be no extra payment for any third party. Highly responsive support As you need any help from the support team, you can contact them spontaneously. Among all digital products I ever experienced, Pinguino is one of those with the best support. Cloud-based system With Pinguino, there is no such term as “complicated download” or “installment”. You can work with it anywhere and at any time. Once you log in to its platform, you can freely use all the features. OTO1 - Pinguino Pro - $47 Export Super Sized Transparent Images in Ultra High Quality Print Ready Formats Additional Pro Only Templates OTO2 - Pinguino Club - $239.4/y Access To All Templates 15 Exclusive, Professionally Designed Templates added every single month</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/HyMKWMtOXVw?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><a href="http://www.ezmagicvideo.com/jv/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>FE - Pinguino - </b></a><br><ul><li> 100+ cutting-edge templates<br></li><li> Pinguino offers push-button mockup designs, which will reduce a great deal of time for the manual tasks. Moreover, you can easily drag and drop any image and make your own templates in seconds.<br></li><li> It thus saves a lot of time and money for outsourcing. As a result, it allows you to diversify your resources more efficiently. <br></li><li> Automatic generation<br></li><li> This tool has hundreds of product mockups that are compatible with almost all devices. With just a press of a button, you will have a ready-to-sell material at your fingertips.<br></li><li> Pinguino has made designing so easy that even a complete newbie can start using it without any hassle. And this feature is what my Pinguino Review really wants to capitalize on. I believe drag-and-drop design will soon be a trend.<br></li><li> Unlimited commercial license<br></li><li> You do not only create the products, you can also sell them anytime you want. Additionally, you can set them at any price of your choice. With the commercial license, users can actually make profits from what they created.<br></li><li> It also means that you will be both the product creator and the graphic designer at the same time. And there will be no extra payment for any third party. <br></li><li> Highly responsive support<br></li><li> As you need any help from the support team, you can contact them spontaneously. Among all digital products I ever experienced, Pinguino is one of those with the best support.<br></li><li> Cloud-based system<br></li><li> With Pinguino, there is no such term as “complicated download” or “installment”. You can work with it anywhere and at any time. Once you log in to its platform, you can freely use all the features.<br></li></ul><br><a href="https://pinguino.pw/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO1 - Pinguino Pro - </b></a><br><ul><li> Export Super Sized Transparent Images in Ultra High Quality Print Ready Formats<br></li><li> Additional Pro Only Templates<br></li></ul><br><a href="https://pinguino.pw/templateclub" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO2 - Pinguino Club - 9.4/y</b></a><br><ul><li> Access To All Templates<br></li><li> 15 Exclusive, Professionally Designed Templates added every single month<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Pinguino + OTOs [Delivering]"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Video Kedavra Prestige + OTOs [Instant Deliver]</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4475-video-kedavra-prestige-otos.html</link>
<description>GB Name : Video Kedavra Prestige + OTOs Version : Last OS : Anything Type : Package of Presentation Graphics GB Price : $27(FE) + $37(OTO1) + $59(OTO2) = $123 GB Cost : 12.3$/10 Peoples + 1$ Fee GB Joined : 8/10 Peoples GB Status : Delivered Homepage : SalePage Video Kedavra Prestige is a package of presentation graphics. It offers everything you need to create a stunning, professional presentation. The vendor team also adds a lot of necessary elements so that you can win a pitch as fast as you can. This PowerPoint-based package is built to help you win pitches. It is created with the same formula as many start-up founders have done to raise millions. - More than 600 creative slides - Created with Slide Master - No need to use Photoshop - Customizable - Image placeholder ready - Totally animated - Drag and drop Please do not mistake that this is a plugin, a software or a WP theme. Video Kedavra is only a package of PowerPoint video templates that have been pre-made for you. To customize, you need to install the latest version of Microsoft. I highly recommend the latest version as in some cases, the old versions cannot fully display all the effects.x</description>
<category>GB Graphic Kits</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 12 May 2018 08:11:45 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FE - Video Kedavra Prestigee - $27 In this part of the Video Kedavra Prestige Review, I am going to show you some elements you can get from Video Kedavra Prestige, let’s see what they are: More than 1800 slides - More than 600 slides in the front-end version and more than 1200 in the upsell 60 color themes - 20 color themes in the front-end version and 40 color themes in the upsell Is that just it? No, you also receive some extra modules as follows: Extra module 1: Prestige Promotional Video Template Extra module 2: Prestige Opener Video Template Extra module 3: Business Card Template Extra module 4: CV Business Template Extra module 5: Poster Prestige Template One little reminder from me in this Video Kedavra Prestige Review is that the product can only be used for personal projects. You can use it for unlimited projects of yours but you cannot resell or modify to make profits from it. OTO1 - Video Kedavra Prestige Platinum - $37 Platinum package 1200+ Slides Developer Commercial License for your Kedavra prestige + Kedavra Prestige Platinum plus EXTRA MODULE OTO2 - Kedavra MEGA - $59 EXCLUSIVE FOR NEW CUSTOMER ONLY All contents inside Presentation Warrior Platinum are exclusive for new customer only, so you can expect super UNIQUE contents that make your videos stand out from the crowd MORE TEMPLATES TO CHOOSE FROM Once you upgrade to PLATINUM version, you&#039;ll get more powerpoint templates in various niches as well as new cinematic effects. This surely will help you to create even more high quality videos. EASY MONEY BY SELLING VIDEOS TO CLIENTS Video creation service is in a HOT Demand right now. With commercial license included in the Platinum Version, you can easily charge anywhere between $400 - $1,500 per video you make for a client.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/SNo9gF3jFbw?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><a href="http://prestige.videokedavra.com/live/bestdeal/"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer"><b>FE - Video Kedavra Prestigee - </b></a><br><ul><li> In this part of the Video Kedavra Prestige Review, I am going to show you some elements you can get from Video Kedavra Prestige, let’s see what they are:<br></li><li> More than 1800 slides<br></li><li>  - More than 600 slides in the front-end version and more than 1200 in the upsell<br></li><li> 60 color themes<br></li><li>  - 20 color themes in the front-end version and 40 color themes in the upsell<br></li><li> Is that just it? No, you also receive some extra modules as follows:<br></li><li> Extra module 1: Prestige Promotional Video Template<br></li><li> Extra module 2: Prestige Opener Video Template<br></li><li> Extra module 3: Business Card Template<br></li><li> Extra module 4: CV Business Template<br></li><li> Extra module 5: Poster Prestige Template<br></li><li> One little reminder from me in this Video Kedavra Prestige Review is that the product can only be used for personal projects. You can use it for unlimited projects of yours but you cannot resell or modify to make profits from it.<br></li></ul><br><a href="http://www.prestige.videokedavra.com/.comimeoffer1/"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer"><b>OTO1 - Video Kedavra Prestige Platinum - </b></a><br><ul><li> Platinum package<br></li><li> 1200+ Slides<br></li><li> Developer Commercial License for your Kedavra prestige + Kedavra Prestige Platinum plus EXTRA MODULE<br></li></ul><br><a href="http://www.videokedavra.com/videokedavra-platinum/"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer"><b>OTO2 - Kedavra MEGA - </b></a><br><ul><li> EXCLUSIVE FOR NEW CUSTOMER ONLY<br></li><li> All contents inside Presentation Warrior Platinum are exclusive for new customer only, so you can expect super UNIQUE contents that make your videos stand out from the crowd<br></li><li> MORE TEMPLATES TO CHOOSE FROM<br></li><li> Once you upgrade to PLATINUM version, you'll get more powerpoint templates in various niches as well as new cinematic effects. This surely will help you to create even more high quality videos. <br></li><li> EASY MONEY BY SELLING VIDEOS TO CLIENTS<br></li><li> Video creation service is in a HOT Demand right now. With commercial license included in the Platinum Version, you can easily charge anywhere between 0 - ,500 per video you make for a client.<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Video Kedavra Prestige + OTOs [Instant Deliver]"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Lifetime Studio FX + OTOs [Instant Deliver]</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4023-lifetime-studio-fx-otos.html</link>
<description>GB Name : Lifetime Studio FX + OTOs Version : Last OS : Anything Type : eCovers Box Creator, Social Viral Content Creator GB Price : $97(FE) + $97(OTO1) + $97(OTO2) + $197(OTO3) = $488 GB Cost : 33$/15 Peoples + 2$ Fee GB Joined : 13/15 Peoples GB Status : Delivered Homepage : SalePage Lifetime Studio FX, a Lifetime Bundled Version of both Pixel Studio FX (called as PSFX) and Social Studio FX (called as SSFX). Pixel Studio FX is an online service which allows people to create the professional, high converting eCovers and box art in only 60 seconds or less. There have about 13,000 members who have created more than 190,000 eCovers. Pixel Studio FX is the world’s easiest-to-use design tool for eBooks with more than 8,000 stock images, 28,000 unique designs, 6,000 web icons, and 650 more professional templates. Social Studio FX, which is known as an online service which allows people to create beautiful, highly-engaging designs for the social media &amp;amp; advertising in only three simple steps. It allows you to design more than 66 different platforms and sizes, from Facebook to Twitter or Instagram and even some popular website banners; they always have the perfect size for your projects which is trusted by over 3,000 members.</description>
<category>GB Graphic Kits</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 03:29:16 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FE - PSFX &amp;amp; SSFX - $97 Do It Yourself Tools -This is known as one of The Highest Niches on JVZoo. Even the smallest business owners, now they can afford to outsource their graphics. It allows you to generate the perfect looking eCovers, Box Art, Online Advertisements, Social Media Images and more with none of the experience. Proven Products. -This is not a start up which have just presented to the market. It has Over 15,000 Units Sold for $950,000. Pixel Studio FX, Pixel Studio FX 2 and Social Studio FX has got almost $1,000,000 on the JVZoo.comwork for only two years. Paying affiliates over $500,000 in three previous launches. This bundle Lifetime Studio FX is expected to make a huge bang to this industry. Lifetime Hosting &amp;amp; Lifetime Stock Video -Their sales is selling over $1,000,000 in about 14 months. The Lifetime brand products, which have launched since August 2016, have sold more than 20,000 units for over $1,000,000. In Average, it’s more than $35,000 monthly to our affiliates -Lifetime Access to Pixel Studio FX -12 eCover Styles, 250 Done-for-You Templates -14,000 Unique Designs, 180+ Web Fonts -8,000+ Stock Images, 6,000+ Web Icons -Lifetime Access to Social Studio FX -66 Social Media Styles, 200 Done -for-you Templates -30 Bonus Template Club exclusive templates -Lifetime IM.Tools Academy, Marketers Dozen Bundle, Social Media Income OTO1 - Enterprise/Pro - $97 400 Additional done-for-you eCovers Templates 18 Additional eCover Designs 180 Additional Web Fonts 50 mb Additional Storage for Pixel Studio FX 50 mb Additional Storage for Social Studio FX Ability to Create 40 Different and Unique 3D Bundle Groupshots 1,000 Royalty Free Images YouTube Marketing, YouTube Ads &amp;amp; Social Marketing Advantage Enterprise License with Developer Rights OTO2 - 1-Pay PSFX Club - $97 12 Months of Pixel Studio FX Template Club 360 Exclusive Templates OTO3 - Reseller - $197 300 Lifetime Studio FX Memberships to Sell Your Cost: $0.66 Per Membership Resell 2 Memberships to Recover Todays Investment We Do All The Work We Do All The Support We Provide the Software We Pay All The Infrastructure You Resell For Between $23,100 - $29,100 We Share All Upsell Revenue With You You Earn 70%</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/htCeHKYKQ7w?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><a href="http://static.lifetimestudiofx.com/special/offer/"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer"><b>FE - PSFX &amp; SSFX - </b></a><br><ul><li> Do It Yourself Tools<br></li><li> -This is known as one of The Highest Niches on JVZoo. Even the smallest business owners, now they can afford to outsource their graphics. It allows you to generate the perfect looking eCovers, Box Art, Online Advertisements, Social Media Images and more with none of the experience.<br></li><li> Proven Products.<br></li><li> -This is not a start up which have just presented to the market. It has Over 15,000 Units Sold for 0,000. Pixel Studio FX, Pixel Studio FX 2 and Social Studio FX  has got almost ,000,000 on the JVZoo.comwork for only two years. Paying affiliates over 0,000 in three previous launches.  This bundle Lifetime Studio FX is expected to make a huge bang to this industry.<br></li><li> Lifetime Hosting &amp; Lifetime Stock Video<br></li><li> -Their sales is selling over ,000,000 in about 14 months. The Lifetime brand products, which have launched since August 2016, have sold more than 20,000 units for over ,000,000.  In Average, it’s more than ,000 monthly to our affiliates<br></li><li> -Lifetime Access to Pixel Studio FX<br></li><li> -12 eCover Styles, 250 Done-for-You Templates<br></li><li> -14,000 Unique Designs, 180+ Web Fonts<br></li><li> -8,000+ Stock Images, 6,000+ Web Icons<br></li><li> -Lifetime Access to Social Studio FX<br></li><li> -66 Social Media Styles, 200 Done -for-you Templates<br></li><li> -30 Bonus Template Club exclusive templates<br></li><li> -Lifetime IM.Tools Academy, Marketers Dozen Bundle, Social Media Income<br></li></ul><br><a href="http://static.lifetimestudiofx.com/special/enterprise/"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer"><b>OTO1 - Enterprise/Pro - </b></a><br><ul><li> 400 Additional done-for-you eCovers Templates<br></li><li> 18 Additional eCover Designs<br></li><li> 180 Additional Web Fonts<br></li><li> 50 mb Additional Storage for Pixel Studio FX<br></li><li> 50 mb Additional Storage for Social Studio FX <br></li><li> Ability to Create 40 Different and Unique 3D Bundle Groupshots <br></li><li> 1,000 Royalty Free Images<br></li><li> YouTube Marketing, YouTube Ads &amp; Social Marketing Advantage<br></li><li> Enterprise License with Developer Rights <br></li></ul><br><a href="http://static.lifetimestudiofx.com/special/templateclub/"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer"><b>OTO2 - 1-Pay PSFX Club - </b></a><br><ul><li> 12 Months of Pixel Studio FX Template Club<br></li><li> 360 Exclusive Templates<br></li></ul><br><a href="http://static.lifetimestudiofx.com/special/reseller/"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer"><b>OTO3 - Reseller - 7</b></a><br><ul><li> 300 Lifetime Studio FX<br></li><li> Memberships to Sell<br></li><li> Your Cost:<br></li><li> <![CDATA[Features FE - PSFX &amp;amp; SSFX - $97 Do It Yourself Tools -This is known as one of The Highest Niches on JVZoo. Even the smallest business owners, now they can afford to outsource their graphics. It allows you to generate the perfect looking eCovers, Box Art, Online Advertisements, Social Media Images and more with none of the experience. Proven Products. -This is not a start up which have just presented to the market. It has Over 15,000 Units Sold for $950,000. Pixel Studio FX, Pixel Studio FX 2 and Social Studio FX has got almost $1,000,000 on the JVZoo.comwork for only two years. Paying affiliates over $500,000 in three previous launches. This bundle Lifetime Studio FX is expected to make a huge bang to this industry. Lifetime Hosting &amp;amp; Lifetime Stock Video -Their sales is selling over $1,000,000 in about 14 months. The Lifetime brand products, which have launched since August 2016, have sold more than 20,000 units for over $1,000,000. In Average, it’s more than $35,000 monthly to our affiliates -Lifetime Access to Pixel Studio FX -12 eCover Styles, 250 Done-for-You Templates -14,000 Unique Designs, 180+ Web Fonts -8,000+ Stock Images, 6,000+ Web Icons -Lifetime Access to Social Studio FX -66 Social Media Styles, 200 Done -for-you Templates -30 Bonus Template Club exclusive templates -Lifetime IM.Tools Academy, Marketers Dozen Bundle, Social Media Income OTO1 - Enterprise/Pro - $97 400 Additional done-for-you eCovers Templates 18 Additional eCover Designs 180 Additional Web Fonts 50 mb Additional Storage for Pixel Studio FX 50 mb Additional Storage for Social Studio FX Ability to Create 40 Different and Unique 3D Bundle Groupshots 1,000 Royalty Free Images YouTube Marketing, YouTube Ads &amp;amp; Social Marketing Advantage Enterprise License with Developer Rights OTO2 - 1-Pay PSFX Club - $97 12 Months of Pixel Studio FX Template Club 360 Exclusive Templates OTO3 - Reseller - $197 300 Lifetime Studio FX Memberships to Sell Your Cost: $0.66 Per Membership Resell 2 Memberships to Recover Todays Investment We Do All The Work We Do All The Support We Provide the Software We Pay All The Infrastructure You Resell For Between $23,100 - $29,100 We Share All Upsell Revenue With You You Earn 70%]]>.66 Per Membership<br></li><li> Resell 2 Memberships to<br></li><li> Recover Todays Investment<br></li><li> We Do All The Work<br></li><li> We Do All The Support<br></li><li> We Provide the Software<br></li><li> We Pay All The Infrastructure<br></li><li> You Resell For<br></li><li> Between ,100 - ,100<br></li><li> We Share All Upsell Revenue With You<br></li><li> You Earn 70%<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Lifetime Studio FX + OTOs [Instant Deliver]"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>FreePik Premium</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4462-freepik-premium.html</link>
<description>GB Name : FreePik Premium Version : Last OS : Anything Type : 304,042 Premium vectors GB Price : $89.99/y(FE) = $89.99 GB Cost : 10$/10 Peoples + 1.5$ Fee GB Joined : 6/10 Peoples GB Status : Going Homepage : SalePage 304,042 Premium vectors Premium vectors for personal and commercial use. Download in AI and EPS format.</description>
<category>GB Graphic Kits</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 13:12:24 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FE - FreePik Premium - $89.99/y 535,500+ resources (80,000+ every month) 221,500 Stock photos 824,500+ Premium resources No linking required in Selection Unlimited downloads (more info) No ads</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br><a href="https://www.freepik.com/freepik-premium-vectors"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer"><b>FE - FreePik Premium - .99/y</b></a><br><ul><li> 535,500+ resources (80,000+ every month)		<br></li><li> 221,500 Stock photos		<br></li><li> 824,500+ Premium resources		<br></li><li> No linking required in Selection		<br></li><li> Unlimited downloads (more info)		<br></li><li> No ads<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="FreePik Premium"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Motion Animation Pro + OTOs [Instant Deliver]</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3669-motion-animation-pro-otos.html</link>
<description>GB Name : Motion Animation Pro + OTOs Version : Last OS : Anything Type : Video Library GB Price : $37 (FE) + $37(OTO1) + $17x2(OTO2) = 108$ GB Cost : 9.8$/10 Peoples +1$ Fee GB Joined : 9/10 Peoples GB Status : Delivered Homepage : SalePage Motion Animation Pro is brand new giant bundle of cutting edge motion animations and motion transitions that anyone can use to add instant spectacular effects to any of their video or other project.</description>
<category>GB Graphic Kits</category>
<enclosure url="http://motionanimationpro.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/04/Compability.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 28 Apr 2018 04:39:55 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FE - $37 1000+ Motion Animations : An Immense Collection of more than 1000 High Definition Motion Animations that you can add instant alluring effects to any of your video, presentation, graphic or any project! 500+ Motion Transitions : A Vast Selection of more than 500 high impact motion transitions that you can turn any of your video, slideshow, presentation or project into an eye catching master piece! Motion Animation Pro is Super Versatile! All the files in the Motion Animation Pro Bundle are included with MOV (Encoded With alpha channel transparent background), MP4 (With chroma key that you can key out easily), Animated GIF (Transparent background), FLV and SWF files that give you total flexibility. You can drop these files into almost all major video, presentation or graphic software and turn your dull project into a stunner! Motion Animation Pro is Compatible with Almost all Video, Presentation &amp;amp; Graphic Software:And Many More! Special Extra: Motion Sales Video Templates.These gorgeous motion sales video templates are enchanted with alluring spectacular effects making them absolutely stunning. Best of all these video templates can be easily edited with just PowerPoint! Special Extra: Motion Video Templates.These general themed video templates are paired with mouth-watering animation effects that make them absolutely gorgeous. All these video templates are designed with general theme and you can use them to create video for any niche and they are all editable with PowerPoint. OTO1 - $37 Super Size with 1250 more Motion Animations 660+ Motion Transitions and 500+ High Definition Motion Effects. Developer Rights so you can use these Cutting Edge Contents in your Customer’s Project. OTO2 - $17/m Create Award Winning Videos, Presentation &amp;amp; Other Creative Materials!Easily create awesome videos, presentations and digital creative materials that will boost your conversion and make a lasting impact to your viewers with our mammoth collection of animated PowerPoint slides and various different templates. Unbeatable Values.With our membership model, you can literally save thousands if not hundreds of dollars. Our membership gives you unlimited access and downloads to all our premium PowerPoint templates for an unbeatable. Regular Updates.We regularly add new contents to our website to keep pace with the ever changing demand of the market so you never run out of fresh contents to use for your nxt project. Professional Quality.All our PowerPoint video templates, animated slides and presentation templates are crafted by professional designers to meet the highest industry standard and meet all your taste bud. Make Boat Loads of Money!When you join SuperPowerPPT membership you will also receive free developer license, we don’t make you pay extra for this, with commercial license our membership opens up countless money making opportunity, you can use our contents to create amazing videos and other creative materials that you can sell to your customers and make unlimited profits.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/80vC-bvHjZc?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><a href="http://motionanimationpro.com/live/"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer"><b>FE - </b></a><br><ul><li> 1000+ Motion Animations : An Immense Collection of more than 1000 High Definition Motion Animations that you can add instant alluring effects to any of your video, presentation, graphic or any project!<br></li><li> 500+ Motion Transitions : A Vast Selection of more than 500 high impact motion transitions that you can turn any of your video, slideshow, presentation or project into an eye catching master piece!<br></li><li> Motion Animation Pro is Super Versatile! All the files in the Motion Animation Pro Bundle are included with MOV (Encoded With alpha channel transparent background), MP4 (With chroma key that you can key out easily), Animated GIF (Transparent background), FLV and SWF files that give you total flexibility. You can drop these files into almost all major video, presentation or graphic software and turn your dull project into a stunner!<br></li><li> Motion Animation Pro is Compatible with Almost all Video, Presentation &amp; Graphic Software:And Many More!<br></li><li> <img src="http://motionanimationpro.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/04/Compability.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Motion Animation Pro + OTOs [Instant Deliver]"><br></li><li> Special Extra: Motion Sales Video Templates.These gorgeous motion sales video templates are enchanted with alluring spectacular effects making them absolutely stunning. Best of all these video templates can be easily edited with just PowerPoint!<br></li><li> Special Extra: Motion Video Templates.These general themed video templates are paired with mouth-watering animation effects that make them absolutely gorgeous. All these video templates are designed with general theme and you can use them to create video for any niche and they are all editable with PowerPoint.<br></li></ul><br><a href="http://motionanimationpro.com/live/oto/"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer"><b>OTO1 - </b></a><br><ul><li> Super Size with 1250 more Motion Animations <br></li><li> 660+ Motion Transitions and <br></li><li> 500+ High Definition Motion Effects.<br></li><li> Developer Rights so you can use these Cutting Edge Contents in your Customer’s Project.<br></li></ul><br><a href="http://www.superpowerppt.com/special-oto-offer/"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer"><b>OTO2 - /m</b></a><br><ul><li> Create Award Winning Videos, Presentation &amp; Other Creative Materials!Easily create awesome videos, presentations and digital creative materials that will boost your conversion and make a lasting impact to your viewers with our mammoth collection of animated PowerPoint slides and various different templates.<br></li><li> Unbeatable Values.With our membership model, you can literally save thousands if not hundreds of dollars. Our membership gives you unlimited access and downloads to all our premium PowerPoint templates for an unbeatable.<br></li><li> Regular Updates.We regularly add new contents to our website to keep pace with the ever changing demand of the market so you never run out of fresh contents to use for your nxt project.<br></li><li> Professional Quality.All our PowerPoint video templates, animated slides and presentation templates are crafted by professional designers to meet the highest industry standard and meet all your taste bud.<br></li><li> Make Boat Loads of Money!When you join SuperPowerPPT membership you will also receive free developer license, we don’t make you pay extra for this, with commercial license our membership opens up countless money making opportunity, you can use our contents to create amazing videos and other creative materials that you can sell to your customers and make unlimited profits.<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>