<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Social Ads Tools - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Social Ads Tools - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>Social Page Analyzer 1.0.12</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/941-social-page-analyzer.html</link>
<description>Name : Social Page Analyzer Version : 1.0.12 OS : Windows Type : FB Fanpage Tool Price : $354.95 Homepage : SalePage The NEW Social Page Analyzer, an extremely powerful Mac/PC software that analyzes facebook pages, posts, and comments helping you uncover the top marketing content and strategies for your own social marketing campaigns! A new powerful tool for analyzing Facebook fanpages, fanpage posts and post comments with 5 built-in tools for uncovering the secrets behind any successful fanpage in just seconds!</description>
<category>Social Ads Tools</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2018 13:31:47 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Search thousands of fanpages by keyword or paste in as many facebook page you links want to analyze Check fanpage names for Facebook ad interest keywords for your ad campaigns Generate VERY detailed page score reports for optimizing your fanpages for high natural organic traffic! Get 27 different data metrics for every fanpage Extract emails &amp;amp; websites for fanpages! Contact page owners to build valuable marketing relationships to skyrocket your Facebook marketing success! Works on both Mac and PC computers Get 1000&#039;s of fanpages using sophisticated search features that no other software has! Generate sophisticated page scores for all pages to get the &quot;REAL&quot; sense of the true page value! Extract 1000&#039;s of posts from ANY fanpage in just seconds! Sort by shares, comments, likes, or any other data metric to uncover the content with the best engagement! Preview the top posts in a beautiful post layout preview window! Extract thousands of comments from ANY fanpage post in just seconds! Reveal powerful information using the cutting-edge &quot;Word Analyzer&quot; tool to instantly uncover all the most common word-combinations across thousands of user comments or page posts! Uncover product ideas that are hiding inside your competitors user comments! Use built-in blazing fast filters and custom filters to get the data you really need!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/245289125?app_id=122963" width="425" height="239" frameborder="0" title="Social Page Analyzer - Facebook Fanpage Research Software" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Search thousands of fanpages by keyword or paste in as many facebook page you links want to analyze<br></li><li> Check fanpage names for Facebook ad interest keywords for your ad campaigns<br></li><li> Generate VERY detailed page score reports for optimizing your fanpages for high natural organic traffic!<br></li><li> Get 27 different data metrics for every fanpage<br></li><li> Extract emails &amp; websites for fanpages! Contact page owners to build valuable marketing relationships to skyrocket your Facebook marketing success!<br></li><li> Works on both Mac and PC computers<br></li><li> Get 1000's of fanpages using sophisticated search features that no other software has!<br></li><li> Generate sophisticated page scores for all pages to get the "REAL" sense of the true page value!<br></li><li> Extract 1000's of posts from ANY fanpage in just seconds! Sort by shares, comments, likes, or any other data metric to uncover the content with the best engagement!<br></li><li> Preview the top posts in a beautiful post layout preview window!<br></li><li> Extract thousands of comments from ANY fanpage post in just seconds!<br></li><li> Reveal powerful information using the cutting-edge "Word Analyzer" tool to instantly uncover all the most common word-combinations across thousands of user comments or page posts!<br></li><li> Uncover product ideas that are hiding inside your competitors user comments!<br></li><li> Use built-in blazing fast filters and custom filters to get the data you really need!<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Social Page Analyzer 1.0.12"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Simpel Audiens X Pro 5.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3746-simpel-audiens.html</link>
<description>Name : SIMPEL AUDIENS X Version : 5.0 OS : Windows Type : FB Target Extract Price : $497 Homepage : SalePage How To Instant Dig Millions of Potential Consumer Data from Facebook in Just Minutes You Can Get Millions of Potential Targeted Potential Buyers from Facebook, With Just 3 Easy Steps!</description>
<category>Social Ads Tools</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 22:46:44 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features With a simple audience you can explore potential personal data of potential customers by facebook group, FansPage and based on keywords that match your products or services you marketed. Next you can do the Promotion very easily, Want to choose a free reply or paid no problem anymore</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/KV306Ei9UAw?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><br>With a simple audience you can explore potential personal data of potential customers by facebook group, FansPage and based on keywords that match your products or services you marketed.<br><br>Next you can do the Promotion very easily, Want to choose a free reply or paid no problem anymore<br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Simpel Audiens X Pro 5.0"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Interest Architect 1.0.1.8</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/991-interest-architect.html</link>
<description>Name : Interest Architect Version : 1.0.1.8 OS : Windows Type : Facebook Research,Alexa Research, IMDB Research,Wikipedia Research, Amazon Research,Google books Research Price : $147 Homepage : SalePage The brand NEW Interest Architect is an extremely powerful Mac/PC software tool that helps you save 100&#039;s of hours of research time .. by uncovering thousands of profitable interest keyword phrases used for Facebook ad campaigns</description>
<category>Social Ads Tools</category>
<enclosure url="http://interestarchitect.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/features2.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://interestarchitect.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/slider-images-2.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://interestarchitect.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/slider-images-3.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://interestarchitect.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/slider-images-4.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://interestarchitect.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/slider-images-5.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://interestarchitect.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/slider-images-6.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://interestarchitect.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/slider-images-7.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://interestarchitect.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/slider-images-8.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 09:30:50 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><div class="dlevideoplayer" style="width:100%;max-width:425px;">
			<ul data-theme="default" data-preload="metadata">
				<li data-title="main-salesvideo-project-main-1" data-type="m4v" data-url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/appbreed/interestarchitect/videos/main-salesvideo-project-main-1.mp4" ></li>
			</ul>
		</div></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><img src="http://interestarchitect.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/features2.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Interest Architect 1.0.1.8"><br><img src="http://interestarchitect.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/slider-images-2.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><img src="http://interestarchitect.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/slider-images-3.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><img src="http://interestarchitect.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/slider-images-4.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><img src="http://interestarchitect.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/slider-images-5.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><img src="http://interestarchitect.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/slider-images-6.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><img src="http://interestarchitect.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/slider-images-7.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><img src="http://interestarchitect.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/slider-images-8.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Audience Analyzer 1.0.15</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3655-audience-analyzer.html</link>
<description>Name : Audience Analyzer Version : 1.0.15 OS : Windows/MAC Type : Facebook Ads Tools Price : $147 Homepage : SalePage A powerful 7-in-1 software used to find profitable audience targets for your facebook ad campaigns! New Software Uncovers Thousands of Hidden Targeting Keywords &amp;amp; Millions of New Buyers for Your Facebook Ad Campaigns, in just Seconds ... The NEW Audience Analyzer, an extremely powerful Mac/PC software tool that helps you save 100&#039;s of hours of research time by uncovering thousands of profitable interest keyword phrases directly from the Facebook internal keywords database!</description>
<category>Social Ads Tools</category>
<enclosure url="http://audienceanalyzer.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/step1.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://audienceanalyzer.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/step2.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://audienceanalyzer.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/step3.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://audienceanalyzer.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/category-targets-tool.gif" type="image/gif" />
<enclosure url="http://audienceanalyzer.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/filters2.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://audienceanalyzer.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/04/aa-box-set-3.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2018 12:14:49 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Facebook Interests Tool : Uncover thousands of interest keyword phrases directly from Facebook&#039;s internal database through their marketing API! Wikipedia Tool : Instantly pull thousands of keywords from Wikipedia for ANY niche imaginable, and then verify if the keywords are facebook interests at a click of a button! Movies Tool : Search movie titles and actor/actress names to uncover super-targeted interest keywords! Books Tool : Instantly search book &amp;amp; magazine titles directly from Google book&#039;s internal database! Sites Tool : Find thousands of web site names to use as highly-targeted interest keyword phrases! Brands Tool : Target brand name interest keywords for ultra-targeted results! Search Engine Tool : Quickly expand your keyword spread by extracted thousands of more keyword phrases from the top search engines and top ecommerce search engines! Targets Manager Tool : Quickly manage all your Facebook interest keywords in one easy-to-use target manager tool! Built-in Category Targets Browser Tool!This &quot;Never-Seen-Before&quot; unique tool allows you to instantly browse into the 1,000+ built-in category targets that facebook provides you! BUT, the big problem is having an easy way to view what you REALLY need! Dial-In Your Research using Filters for Getting the Exact Data You REALLY Need!Use the blazing-fast quick-filters from the top of the columns or use the integrated filter window for creating more customized filters to fit all your needs!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/222903066?app_id=122963" width="425" height="239" frameborder="0" title="Audience Analyzer - Facebook Ad Marketing Software" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><br><ul><li> Facebook Interests Tool : Uncover thousands of interest keyword phrases directly from Facebook's internal database through their marketing API!<br></li><li> Wikipedia Tool : Instantly pull thousands of keywords from Wikipedia for ANY niche imaginable, and then verify if the keywords are facebook interests at a click of a button!<br></li><li> Movies Tool : Search movie titles and actor/actress names to uncover super-targeted interest keywords!<br></li><li> Books Tool : Instantly search book &amp; magazine titles directly from Google book's internal database!<br></li><li> Sites Tool : Find thousands of web site names to use as highly-targeted interest keyword phrases!<br></li><li> Brands Tool : Target brand name interest keywords for ultra-targeted results!<br></li><li> Search Engine Tool : Quickly expand your keyword spread by extracted thousands of more keyword phrases from the top search engines and top ecommerce search engines!<br></li><li> Targets Manager Tool : Quickly manage all your Facebook interest keywords in one easy-to-use target manager tool!<br></li><li> Built-in Category Targets Browser Tool!This "Never-Seen-Before" unique tool allows you to instantly browse into the 1,000+ built-in category targets that facebook provides you! BUT, the big problem is having an easy way to view what you REALLY need!<br></li><li> Dial-In Your Research using Filters for Getting the Exact Data You REALLY Need!Use the blazing-fast quick-filters from the top of the columns or use the integrated filter window for creating more customized filters to fit all your needs!<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://audienceanalyzer.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/step1.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Audience Analyzer 1.0.15"><br><img src="http://audienceanalyzer.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/step2.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><img src="http://audienceanalyzer.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/step3.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><img src="http://audienceanalyzer.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/category-targets-tool.gif" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><img src="http://audienceanalyzer.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/filters2.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><br><img src="http://audienceanalyzer.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/04/aa-box-set-3.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>IInterests 4.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4402-iinterests.html</link>
<description>Name : iinterests Version : 4.0 OS : Windows/MAC/Linux Type : Interests Extractor Price : $0 Homepage : SalePage iinterests is a small chrome utility that will take the most important interests you get from Facebook Audience insights into one clean easy to upload file for Your Facebook ADV Campaign</description>
<category>Social Ads Tools</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 08:48:44 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Sort By Affinity Fast and effective Completely Free For MAC + PC Ease of Use | Video Tutorial</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ac4UxBmZ1_o?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Sort By Affinity  <br></li><li> Fast and effective   <br></li><li> Completely Free     <br></li><li> For MAC + PC     <br></li><li> Ease of Use | Video Tutorial<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="IInterests 4.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Target Generator 1.0.0.8</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/989-target-generator.html</link>
<description>Name : Target Generator Version : 1.0.0.8 OS : Windows Type : Facebook Marketing, Facebook Research Price : $197 Homepage : SalePage Powerful Software for Generating Highly-Targeted &quot;Interest Keywords&quot; for your Facebook ad Campaigns!</description>
<category>Social Ads Tools</category>
<enclosure url="http://tabfu.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/09/target-generator-4.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 06:34:10 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Uncover thousands of hidden Facebook interests you would have never thought existed! Expand your Facebook ad campaign audience for squeezing more profits from your campaigns! Use &quot;Power keywords&quot; to get the MOST profitable interest targets for any niche imaginable! Fully Facebook compliant, Target Generator does NOT violate any terms of service. So you can be confident when using our software! Extract the number of likes &amp;amp; the number of people talking about each page target Instantly know all the targets that have the most engagement using the Affinity data! Search with multiple keyword phrases, and use the handy &quot;power words&quot; button to append all power words with a single click! Never lose your data .. save all your targets to external files in text, csv, and project files!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/5che5wGDZys?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Uncover thousands of hidden Facebook interests you would have never thought existed!<br></li><li> Expand your Facebook ad campaign audience for squeezing more profits from your campaigns!<br></li><li> Use "Power keywords" to get the MOST profitable interest targets for any niche imaginable!<br></li><li> Fully Facebook compliant, Target Generator does NOT violate any terms of service. So you can be confident when using our software!<br></li><li> Extract the number of likes &amp; the number of people talking about each page target<br></li><li> Instantly know all the targets that have the most engagement using the Affinity data!<br></li><li> Search with multiple keyword phrases, and use the handy "power words" button to append all power words with a single click!<br></li><li> Never lose your data .. save all your targets to external files in text, csv, and project files!<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://tabfu.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/09/target-generator-4.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Target Generator 1.0.0.8"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Interests Explorer 8.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1820-interests-explorer.html</link>
<description>Name : Interests Explorer 2018 Version : 8.0 OS : Windows/MAC/Linux Type : Facebook Lead Tools Price : $67 Homepage : SalePage Uncover thousands of hidden &amp;amp; High-Converting Facebook interests you would have never thought existed! Interests Explorer - The World&#039;s first Facebook Real Interests Cloud Engine Interests Explorer Minimize Risk Of Failure By Providing High Converting &amp;amp; Targeted Interests Set For Each Campaign To Make Sure Your Facebook Campaign Yield Good ROI</description>
<category>Social Ads Tools</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.interestsexplorer.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/06/3steps.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 06:31:32 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features World’s Most Powerful &amp;amp; Smartest Interests Explorer The World’s First Native Facebook Interests Engine ! Target your Facebook campaigns more precisely ! Discover the Most Profitable Interests on FB High conversions Interests with super targeted visitors Creating a Real &quot;Interests Cloud&quot; of Your Core Interests Multi license - You can install on up to 3 computers! For Windows, Mac, Chromebook &amp;amp; Linux Newbie &amp;amp; Pro Friendly Enviroment Step-by-Step &quot;how to&quot; Tutorial. Interests Explorer is one of the simplest and most intuitive IM software you will ever use and you probably will not have any questions... But just in case you do, each and every feature is covered in full detail, in the help section. Our goal is that you are completely satisfied with your purchase. If for any reason you aren&#039;t satisfied we will be at your service please let us know by: Emailing a request to support@interestsexplorer.com Handcrafted by experts! Interests Explorer ( IE ) was built by professionals with more than ten years of software Dev. experience. With IE, we have used our experience from countless IM software projects and designed a tool that fits perfectly into the workflow of both professionals and novices Optimized for speed and Accurate IE contains the fastest process mining algorithms, and the most efficient Interests search engine framework In The Market . On top of that, you get an obsessively streamlined user experience allowing you to move fast. Because what counts is performance from start to finish. There are no upsells, no backend one-time-offers and no recurring payments. This a one-time payment for lifetime access. The Must have tool for any Facebook Marketers &amp;amp; Advertisers The most reliable and accurate Interests Cloud engine in the market. in fact the only one ... :-)</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ZMJowoL_3Qs?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> World’s Most Powerful &amp; Smartest Interests Explorer<br></li><li> The World’s First Native Facebook Interests Engine !<br></li><li> Target your Facebook campaigns more precisely !<br></li><li> Discover the Most Profitable Interests on FB<br></li><li> High conversions Interests with super targeted visitors<br></li><li> Creating a Real "Interests Cloud" of Your Core Interests<br></li><li> Multi license - You can install  on up to 3 computers!<br></li><li> For Windows,  Mac,  Chromebook &amp; Linux<br></li><li> Newbie &amp; Pro Friendly  Enviroment<br></li><li> Step-by-Step "how to" Tutorial. Interests Explorer is one of the simplest and most intuitive IM software you will ever use and you probably will not have any questions... But just in case you do, each and every feature is covered in full detail, in the help section.<br></li><li> Our goal is that you are completely satisfied with your purchase. If for any reason you aren't satisfied we will be at your service please let us know by: Emailing a request to support@interestsexplorer.com <br></li><li> Handcrafted by experts! Interests Explorer ( IE ) was built by professionals with more than ten years of software Dev. experience. With IE, we have used our experience from countless IM software projects and designed a tool that fits perfectly into the workflow of both professionals and novices<br></li><li> Optimized for speed and Accurate IE contains the fastest process mining algorithms, and the most efficient Interests search engine framework In The Market . On top of that, you get an obsessively streamlined user experience allowing you to move fast. Because what counts is performance from start to finish.<br></li><li> There are no upsells, no backend one-time-offers  and no recurring payments. This a one-time payment for lifetime access.<br></li><li> The Must have tool for any Facebook Marketers &amp; Advertisers<br></li><li> The most reliable and accurate Interests Cloud engine in the  market. in fact the only one ...  :-)<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://www.interestsexplorer.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/06/3steps.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Interests Explorer 8.0"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Social Ad Creator 1.8</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4188-social-ad-creator.html</link>
<description>Name : Social Ad Creator Version : 1.0.8 OS : Windows Type : FB Ads Creator Price : $354.95 Homepage : SalePage A graphic designer for creating facebook image ads. It comes with over 1000+ built-in graphics elements and 800+ facebook ad templates across 8 different image ad sizes!</description>
<category>Social Ads Tools</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 15:26:28 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Easily create eye catching, clickable, high converting Facebook ad graphics for every ad type and size in just minutes! Generate ads for page post engagement, clicks to website, optimize for conversions, app installs, page post engagements, video view thumbnails, and carousel ad images Get over 800+ templates based on winning ad designs and reverse engineered niche research Easily edit any element object of any template with an easy-to-use drag and drop editor Save your best designs to your own built-in library for easy re-use in future ad campaigns Get a HUGE library of over 1,000+ royalty free graphics organized into 8 easy-to-navigate categories! Insert &amp;amp; edit text from a huge built-in list of fonts and upload your own images to build up your own customized library of graphics. Also get the built-in text space checker to stay below the 20% text and within Facebook&#039;s terms &amp;amp; services. Export high-quality JPEG or PNG image formats for full high-resolution image ads! Use the &quot;Size Swap&quot; feature to duplicate your design for other ad sizes helping you create fast split-tests for your fb ads. Get an additional EXTRA 500+ Facebook ad templates that are optimized for high-converting ad campaigns. Stop wasting money and waiting days for expensive freelance designers to deliver your ad designs! See which ads convert best with your target audience by effortlessly and scientifically split-testing your ad images! Instantly revive tired ad campaigns with fresh, high converting ad creatives to keep the clicks, conversions and sales rolling in daily.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/251728701" width="425" height="239" frameborder="0" title="Social Ad Creator - Easily Create Unlimited Facebook Ads in Just Minutes - BONUS Facebook Software" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Easily create eye catching, clickable, high converting Facebook ad graphics for every ad type and size in just minutes!<br></li><li> Generate ads for page post engagement, clicks to website, optimize for conversions, app installs, page post engagements, video view thumbnails, and carousel ad images<br></li><li> Get over 800+ templates based on winning ad designs and reverse engineered niche research<br></li><li> Easily edit any element object of any template with an easy-to-use drag and drop editor<br></li><li> Save your best designs to your own built-in library for easy re-use in future ad campaigns<br></li><li> Get a HUGE library of over 1,000+ royalty free graphics organized into 8 easy-to-navigate categories!<br></li><li> Insert &amp; edit text from a huge built-in list of fonts and upload your own images to build up your own customized library of graphics.<br></li><li> Also get the built-in text space checker to stay below the 20% text and within Facebook's terms &amp; services.<br></li><li> Export high-quality JPEG or PNG image formats for full high-resolution image ads!<br></li><li> Use the "Size Swap" feature to duplicate your design for other ad sizes helping you create fast split-tests for your fb ads.<br></li><li> Get an additional EXTRA 500+ Facebook ad templates that are optimized for high-converting ad campaigns.<br></li><li> Stop wasting money and waiting days for expensive freelance designers to deliver your ad designs!<br></li><li> See which ads convert best with your target audience by effortlessly and scientifically split-testing your ad images!<br></li><li> Instantly revive tired ad campaigns with fresh, high converting ad creatives to keep the clicks, conversions and sales rolling in daily.<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Social Ad Creator 1.8"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Hash Lighter 4.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1405-hash-lighter.html</link>
<description>Name : Hash Lighter Premium Version : 4.0 OS : Windows/MAC/Linux Type : Facebook Lead Tools Price : $67 Homepage : SalePage Hashlighter has automatic pilot which you can turn off at any time. You can control the settings and if to scrape all hashtags or just the top 40. No need for an activation code: you pay and get an immediate account access. Hashlighter will improve your Social Media Marketing (SMM) effort, it highlights hashtags on your screen as you browse, scrapes and exports leading hashtags, scrape social media followers from influencers pages, scrape the top 40 hashtags from all pages, automatic pilot of hashtags scraper and much more Hashlighter can scrape the full list of all followers of Twitter personas what allows you to market directly to those followers in your niche market! Hashlighter is working on all platforms: Instagram, Twitter, Facebook, Google+, Google search, CNN,... you just name it - it will work on it.</description>
<category>Social Ads Tools</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 21:23:48 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Highlight all #hashtags Highlight all @tags Your set the highlight color Can turn on/off with one click No hassles, improves productivity</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/dOKDN7ppMHU?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Highlight all #hashtags<br></li><li> Highlight all @tags<br></li><li> Your set the highlight color<br></li><li> Can turn on/off with one click<br></li><li> No hassles, improves productivity <br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Hash Lighter 4.0"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>AD RESPARK 2.4.7 Pro</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1526-ad-respark.html</link>
<description>Name : AD RESPARK Version : 2.4.7 Monthly Pro OS : Windows Type : Ad Creator Tools Price : $50/monthly Homepage : SalePage The Most Trusted Brand In eCommerce Is Here To Bring You The Most Requested Software Of 2016 The Software Every Small Online Business Needs... Don&#039;t Believe Us? Watch The Video Below Tons Of Easily Customizable Ad Templates WITH Tweakable Copy We&#039;re back to bring you Ad Respark... The software every small online business NEEDS. When it comes to creating ads, small businesses just don&#039;t have many options; whether it be due to lack of capital, lack of artistic ability, or lack of copy skills. They could hire a professional, but that would take away from their budget for running ads. They can hire someone on Fiverr.. and those designs look okay, but will they get any results? They can try designing their ads themselves.. But then they can come out looking.. Well, not so great. That&#039;s why we created Ad Respark, the MUST have tool for ad creation</description>
<category>Social Ads Tools</category>
<enclosure url="http://ad-respark.co/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/AdRespark.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2016 17:50:10 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features The Ad Creation Tool you&#039;ve always wanted needed Proven To Convert Ad Templates : We&#039;ve taken ads used in our own businesses &amp;amp; from million dollar brands and turned them into easily customized &amp;amp; editable ads.. Allowing your customer to create PROVEN to work ads in just seconds using our proprietary AdRespark software! Built For EVERY Ad Platform : We don&#039;t want to limit your customers to just one advertising platform... That&#039;s why AdRespark covers them ALL... Instantly create ads for BUT NOT LIMITED TO websites such as... Facebook, YouTube, Instagram, Pinterest, Twitter, Google Display Network &amp;amp; more... Intuitive Adaptive Size Technology : Our adaptive size technology makes ad creation simpler than ever before. Create your ad in one size &amp;amp; it automatically adapts and creates the same ad in every other size... So if you create an ad for Facebook... You&#039;ll also automatically have a high quality ad for Pinterest, YouTube, Instagram, etc, etc.. Create one &amp;amp; you&#039;re done As Simple OR Customizable As You Need : Just want to change the text in our proven to convert ads and go? Fine, it can be that simple! Want to fully customize your ad &amp;amp; turn it into your own personally branded version of our proven template? We&#039;ve allowed customers to either keep it simple, or customize as much as they want to! No Advanced Computer Skills? No Problem : Our software was designed with ease of use &amp;amp; customer experience in mind.. The goal is to ensure anyone, no matter their age or technical skill can easily pick up the software and have their own ads made in just minutes... Our wizard &amp;amp; training videos leave nothing to the imagination, everything is covered &amp;amp; easy to do. Smart Integrations For Unlimited Variations : We&#039;ve integrated with multiple APIs to ensure your ad creation experience is as enjoyable AND easy as possible... With things such as background removers, Stock Photos &amp;amp; more built directly into the software... You&#039;ve got every tool you need in one place, making your customers lives easier than ever ScreenShot</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><div class="dlevideoplayer" style="width:100%;max-width:425px;"><ul data-theme="default" data-preload="metadata"><li data-title="" data-type="youtube" data-url="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jTBhjZcrkGA"></li></ul></div></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> The Ad Creation Tool you've always wanted needed<br></li><li> Proven To Convert Ad Templates : We've taken ads used in our own businesses &amp; from million dollar brands and turned them into easily customized &amp; editable ads.. Allowing your customer to create PROVEN to work ads in just seconds using our proprietary AdRespark software!<br></li><li> Built For EVERY Ad Platform : We don't want to limit your customers to just one advertising platform... That's why AdRespark covers them ALL... Instantly create ads for BUT NOT LIMITED TO websites such as... Facebook, YouTube, Instagram, Pinterest, Twitter, Google Display Network &amp; more...<br></li><li> Intuitive Adaptive Size Technology : Our adaptive size technology makes ad creation simpler than ever before. Create your ad in one size &amp; it automatically adapts and creates the same ad in every other size... So if you create an ad for Facebook... You'll also automatically have a high quality ad for Pinterest, YouTube, Instagram, etc, etc.. Create one &amp; you're done<br></li><li> As Simple OR Customizable As You Need : Just want to change the text in our proven to convert ads and go? Fine, it can be that simple! Want to fully customize your ad &amp; turn it into your own personally branded version of our proven template? We've allowed customers to either keep it simple, or customize as much as they want to!<br></li><li> No Advanced Computer Skills? No Problem : Our software was designed with ease of use &amp; customer experience in mind.. The goal is to ensure anyone, no matter their age or technical skill can easily pick up the software and have their own ads made in just minutes... Our wizard &amp; training videos leave nothing to the imagination, everything is covered &amp; easy to do.<br></li><li> Smart Integrations For Unlimited Variations : We've integrated with multiple APIs to ensure your ad creation experience is as enjoyable AND easy as possible... With things such as background removers, Stock Photos &amp; more built directly into the software... You've got every tool you need in one place, making your customers lives easier than ever<br><br></li></ul><br><h3>ScreenShot</h3><br><img src="http://ad-respark.co/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/AdRespark.png" alt="AD RESPARK 2.4.7 Pro"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>