<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Video Creator - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Video Creator - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>Adobe Character Animator CC 2018 1.5</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4488-adobe-character-animator.html</link>
<description>Name : Adobe Character Animator CC 2018 Version : 1.5 OS : Windows Type : 2D Creator Price : $53/m Homepage : SalePage Create a 2D character and make it come alive. Character Animator CC copies your facial movements so your characters act — and react — realistically.</description>
<category>Video Creator</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 12 May 2018 05:46:12 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Start with a character. Build your character from scratch in Illustrator or Photoshop — or start with one of the puppets already available in Character Animator. Animations with legs — and arms and heads. Getting your character to move doesn’t take a lot of work. Control gestures like waving with your keyboard or MIDI device. Movements can be saved as buttons, sliders, or knobs so they’re easier to remember than key commands. And you can smooth transitions between facial poses for a hand-animated look. Put your best face forward. Character Animator tracks your facial expressions — from raised eyebrows to moving lips — in real time and records your motion and voice using your webcam and microphone. So when you look surprised, happy, or angry, your character does, too. It’s showtime. Send your character out into the world. Go live on Facebook or TV. Amuse your friends on social media. Or send it to Adobe Premiere Pro CC or After Effects CC to include in bigger projects like a movie or cartoon.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/lmPo0_WZyPU?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Start with a character.<br></li><li> Build your character from scratch in Illustrator or Photoshop — or start with one of the puppets already available in Character Animator.<br></li><li> Animations with legs — and arms and heads.<br></li><li> Getting your character to move doesn’t take a lot of work. Control gestures like waving with your keyboard or MIDI device. Movements can be saved as buttons, sliders, or knobs so they’re easier to remember than key commands. And you can smooth transitions between facial poses for a hand-animated look.<br></li><li> Put your best face forward.<br></li><li> Character Animator tracks your facial expressions — from raised eyebrows to moving lips — in real time and records your motion and voice using your webcam and microphone. So when you look surprised, happy, or angry, your character does, too.<br></li><li> It’s showtime.<br></li><li> Send your character out into the world. Go live on Facebook or TV. Amuse your friends on social media. Or send it to Adobe Premiere Pro CC or After Effects CC to include in bigger projects like a movie or cartoon.<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Adobe Character Animator CC 2018 1.5"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Adobe After Effects CC 2018 15.1.0.166</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3504-adobe-after-effects.html</link>
<description>Name : Adobe After Effects CC 2018 Version : 15.1.0.166 OS : Windows Type : Video Editor Price : $239 Homepage : SalePage Create incredible motion graphics and visual effects. The industry-standard animation and creative compositing app lets you design and deliver professional motion graphics and visual effects for film, TV, video, and web.</description>
<category>Video Creator</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 15:56:50 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Can deliver convincing visual impacts. Bound together and adaptable perspectives rearranged. Audits have been continuous. Enhanced client interface. The overhaul board tab. RED and overhauling OpenEXR merchants. More responsive interface. Quick picture storing. Include face following technique. Adobe After Effects Animator Character introduced.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/F1ezwdhbYnc?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><p><br></p><br><h3>Features</h3><br><p><br><ul><li> Can deliver convincing visual impacts.<br></li><li> Bound together and adaptable perspectives rearranged.<br></li><li> Audits have been continuous.<br></li><li> Enhanced client interface.<br></li><li> The overhaul board tab.<br></li><li> RED and overhauling OpenEXR merchants.<br></li><li> More responsive interface.<br></li><li> Quick picture storing.<br></li><li> Include face following technique.<br></li><li> Adobe After Effects Animator Character introduced.<br></li></ul></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Adobe After Effects CC 2018 15.1.0.166"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Photodex ProShow Producer 9.0.3793 Final</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3930-photodex-proshow-producer.html</link>
<description>Name : Photodex ProShow Producer Version : 9.0.3793 Final + Gold OS : Windows Type : Video Slider marker Price : $200 Homepage : SalePage ProShow Producer is a software solution that allows you to create and edit videos in a professional manner.</description>
<category>Video Creator</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 06:40:45 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features ProShow Producer is a software solution that allows you to create and edit videos in a professional manner. The interface of the program is intuitive. Users can follow three simple steps - add photos, video and music, use &quot;Slide Options&quot; to customize slides, and then create the output files in several formats. So, you can use the file browser to search for media files and add them to the timeline by using the &quot;drag and drop&quot; method. Furthermore, you can add from hundreds of transitions (basic, blocks, fly in and out, image adjustments, page, patterns, shapes, simulations, slides and pushes, themed, two-sided, wipes). You can also create layers, configure video settings, edit the video (e.g. contrast, brightness, sharpen, blur, hue, opacity, red-eye reduction), adjust motion and adjustment effects, change caption settings and caption motion, as well as configure sound effects. In addition, you can toggle between the timeline and slide list, import music from an audio CD, use text on captions, manage the soundtrack, import and export templates, add watermarks, use the &quot;Undo&quot; and &quot;Redo&quot; functions, enable full screen playback, and much more. Once your project is complete, you can create an output for televisions (DVD, Blu-ray), social media, web shows, computers (PC executable, video files, autorun CD), and others (e.g. send via email, use as screensaver). The program uses a high amount of resources (evidently) and comes with a very well-drawn help file, as well as a &quot;New project&quot; wizard for rookies. The downside is that certain functions take a long time to load (e.g. when ProShow Producer is reading transitions). Although the program aims to teach novices how to use its features, it has some advanced functions that are only accessible to expert users. The bottom line is that we recommend ProShow Producer for personal use while keeping in mind that it needs a lot of system memory.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> ProShow Producer is a software solution that allows you to create and edit videos in a professional manner.<br></li><li> The interface of the program is intuitive. Users can follow three simple steps - add photos, video and music, use "Slide Options" to customize slides, and then create the output files in several formats.<br></li><li> <br></li><li> So, you can use the file browser to search for media files and add them to the timeline by using the "drag and drop" method.<br></li><li> <br></li><li> Furthermore, you can add from hundreds of transitions (basic, blocks, fly in and out, image adjustments, page, patterns, shapes, simulations, slides and pushes, themed, two-sided, wipes).<br></li><li> <br></li><li> You can also create layers, configure video settings, edit the video (e.g. contrast, brightness, sharpen, blur, hue, opacity, red-eye reduction), adjust motion and adjustment effects, change caption settings and caption motion, as well as configure sound effects.<br></li><li> <br></li><li> In addition, you can toggle between the timeline and slide list, import music from an audio CD, use text on captions, manage the soundtrack, import and export templates, add watermarks, use the "Undo" and "Redo" functions, enable full screen playback, and much more.<br></li><li> <br></li><li> Once your project is complete, you can create an output for televisions (DVD, Blu-ray), social media, web shows, computers (PC executable, video files, autorun CD), and others (e.g. send via email, use as screensaver).<br></li><li> <br></li><li> The program uses a high amount of resources (evidently) and comes with a very well-drawn help file, as well as a "New project" wizard for rookies. The downside is that certain functions take a long time to load (e.g. when ProShow Producer is reading transitions).<br></li><li> <br></li><li> Although the program aims to teach novices how to use its features, it has some advanced functions that are only accessible to expert users. The bottom line is that we recommend ProShow Producer for personal use while keeping in mind that it needs a lot of system memory.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Photodex ProShow Producer 9.0.3793 Final"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>VideoSpinn 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1763-videospinn.html</link>
<description>Name : VideoSpinn Version : 1.0 Build 20160415 OS : Windows Type : Video Spin Tools Price : $37 Homepage : SalePage &quot;Push Button Video Creator Helps 64 Year Old Former Flight Attendant From Florida Crank Out Up To 100 Unique Keyword Optimized Videos In Mere Minutes!&quot; Are you searching for more knowledge about Video Spinn? Please read through my honest reviews about Video Spinn before selecting it, to evaluate the weaknesses and strengths of it. Can it be worth your time and effort and cash? Video Spinn is an innovative desktop app (for both Windows &amp;amp; Mac) that allows you to create hundreds — even thousands — of unique videos with just a few mouse clicks. It can easily create randomized slideshow videos using folders of video clips and/or images. These are perfect for SEO, YouTube domination, offline client commercials, video personalization, affiliate marketing via video, video branding, keyword targeting, and more! We’re finding new uses every day.</description>
<category>Video Creator</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.jvzoowsoreview.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/05/Video-Spinn-Review-and-bonus-compressed-e1463469092699-765x909.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://i.imgur.com/9HdzELQ.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2018 07:46:22 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Fast Bulk Video Creation – it can easily create up to 100 unique videos just by entering a few simple fields &amp;amp; spinning a few dials. You will now have plenty of unique videos to insert as ‘related videos’ to your YouTube channels… so your videos rank higher for their keywords Optional Intro And Final Image/Clip – Brand your videos with optional intro &amp;amp; final clips… insert your logo or contact info to make your video more memorable to the viewer Video Transitions – Engage your viewers longer with pro level effects to stay glued to the screen – Video Spinn has a full range of transition options, including cross dissolve; fade to white; fade to black; slide from right/left/top/bottom; &amp;amp; zoom from or to center. Optional Audio Clips – Select from the Continuous option, which pulls one of your audio clip from the Music Folder per video &amp;amp; loops it for the duration of the video… or select the Random option, which randomly pulls music files &amp;amp; inserts them into your videos for you. Supported Video Formats – Video Spinn supports inserting .MP4 .MPG .AVI .MOV .FLV &amp;amp; .WMV clips to your finished videos Supported Image Formats – Images in .JPG .PNG .GIF .BMP. TIFF file formats are supported by Video Spinn Select Your Own Filenames – The ability to enter your own file names is a large advantage, because you can easily enter your keywords as your file names… which means higher ranking &amp;amp; free traffic Spin Option – Select this option to let the software randomly add the exact number of images &amp;amp; clips you want… for unlimited &amp;amp; unique videos on demand Join Option – Creates a single video from all the images or videos in the Resource Folder, joined together alphabetically, to effortlessly create ‘authority videos’ which build your brand &amp;amp; reputation. Watermark Option – Protect your videos from being ripped off by other marketers Supported Audio Formats – .MP3 .WMA .WAV .ACC audio files are supported by Video Spinn PC &amp;amp; Mac Compatible – Video Spinn is compatible with both types of machines… simply select the best option for your needs Includes Quick Start Guide &amp;amp; Video Walkthrough – We have included a simple-to-follow Quick Start Guide in order to get your 1st project set up in just minutes from now. Of course, because we want to ensure your success, we have also included a video walkthrough Video Spinn. Watch along as you see a campaign set up in real time.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/TU2YvCfyHoo?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Fast Bulk Video Creation – it can easily create up to 100 unique videos just by entering a few simple fields &amp; spinning a few dials. You will now have plenty of unique videos to insert as ‘related videos’ to your YouTube channels… so your videos rank higher for their keywords<br></li><li> Optional Intro And Final Image/Clip – Brand your videos with optional intro &amp; final clips… insert your logo or contact info to make your video more memorable to the viewer<br></li><li> Video Transitions – Engage your viewers longer with pro level effects to stay glued to the screen – Video Spinn has a full range of transition options, including cross dissolve; fade to white; fade to black; slide from right/left/top/bottom; &amp; zoom from or to center.<br></li><li> Optional Audio Clips – Select from the Continuous option, which pulls one of your audio clip from the Music Folder per video &amp; loops it for the duration of the video… or select the Random option, which randomly pulls music files &amp; inserts them into your videos for you.<br></li><li> Supported Video Formats – Video Spinn supports inserting .MP4 .MPG .AVI .MOV .FLV &amp; .WMV clips to your finished videos<br></li><li> Supported Image Formats – Images in .JPG .PNG .GIF .BMP. TIFF file formats are supported by Video Spinn<br></li><li> Select Your Own Filenames – The ability to enter your own file names is a large advantage, because you can easily enter your keywords as your file names… which means higher ranking &amp; free traffic<br></li><li> Spin Option – Select this option to let the software randomly add the exact number of images &amp; clips you want… for unlimited &amp; unique videos on demand<br></li><li> Join Option – Creates a single video from all the images or videos in the Resource Folder, joined together alphabetically, to effortlessly create ‘authority videos’ which build your brand &amp; reputation.<br></li><li> Watermark Option – Protect your videos from being ripped off by other marketers<br></li><li> Supported Audio Formats – .MP3 .WMA .WAV .ACC audio files are supported by Video Spinn<br></li><li> PC &amp; Mac Compatible – Video Spinn is compatible with both types of machines… simply select the best option for your needs<br></li><li> Includes Quick Start Guide &amp; Video Walkthrough – We have included a simple-to-follow Quick Start Guide in order to get your 1st project set up in just minutes from now. Of course, because we want to ensure your success, we have also included a video walkthrough Video Spinn. Watch along as you see a campaign set up in real time.<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://www.jvzoowsoreview.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/05/Video-Spinn-Review-and-bonus-compressed-e1463469092699-765x909.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt="VideoSpinn 1.0"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Video Spin Blaster 2.29 Pro Plus</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/960-video-spin-blaster-pro.html</link>
<description>Name :Video Spin Blaster Version : 2.29 Pro Plus OS : Windows Type : Video Marketing Price : $37 Homepage : SalePage Create Video Slideshows In Seconds : Create videos from images, adding transitions and audio EASY VIDEO CREATOR : Generating videos has never been easier! You can download images from google or add them from your local PC and start generating hundreds of videos by randomizing the pictures. VSB Pro also supports downloading copyright-free audio files from Soundcloud that you can then add to your videos. Another great feature is the option to add custom text to every slide, and turn the text to audio, with one click. EASY VIDEO EDITOR : If you already have videos on your PC and want to edit them, then Video Spin Blaster Pro will help you. It&#039;s easy to add audio, image or text watermark, cut time from start or end of your existing videos. Video Spin Blaster Pro has a powerful algorithm that allows you to generate multiple unique copies of the same video. You can then upload this videos on YouTube without him knowing that the same video is uploaded multiple times (avoid duplicate content filter).</description>
<category>Video Creator</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/glass-button.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 08:44:37 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Fast mode allows you to generate a video in seconds Download images from google or add form PC Transform text to audio and add it to slides Support for Video sldies. Combine Images &amp;amp; Videos Randomize pictures before generating a video Compatible with Windows Xp Sp3/Vista/7/8 and all Server Editions Individual watermark for every slide with custom position Add text to every slide or to multiple slides at a time Auto download articles and split them between slides Download copyright free images automatically Download copyright free music automatically Randomize slides Set custom slide duration Automatically select thumbnail for YouTube Support for multiple video lists Live preview changes you make to slides Select output quality of video Randomly select an audio background from folder Turn text to audio and add it to final video Generate videos fast (without transitions), 10 minute HD video in less than 10 seconds Randomize slides to obtain hundreds of videos with 1 click Spin existing videos to make them unique for YouTube and others Add image or text watermark to existing videos Cut random time from start or end of existing videos Change audio from file or random file from directory for existing videos Generate up to 1000 unique video copies from an existing video by adding random pixel watermark Version 2: Human Text To Speech voice added Version 2: Add video slides and image slides. Combine images &amp;amp; Videos with ease Version 2: Convert existing videos to different formats Version 2: Append intro video to existing videos from your PC Version 2: 15 New transitions added Version 2: Align text of videos to left, center or rigt :::Free Members ::: http://mir.cr/1ZLF3K9F Password : www.tgmember.com :::ViP Only:::</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/TrreIWCagjk?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><p><br></p><br><h3>Features</h3><br><p><br><ul><li> Fast mode allows you to generate a video in seconds<br></li><li> Download images from google or add form PC<br></li><li> Transform text to audio and add it to slides<br></li><li> Support for Video sldies. Combine Images &amp; Videos<br></li><li> Randomize pictures before generating a video<br></li><li> Compatible with Windows Xp Sp3/Vista/7/8 and all Server Editions<br></li><li> Individual watermark for every slide with custom position<br></li><li> Add text to every slide or to multiple slides at a time<br></li><li> Auto download articles and split them between slides <br></li><li> Download copyright free images automatically <br></li><li> Download copyright free music automatically <br></li><li> Randomize slides<br></li><li> Set custom slide duration<br></li><li> Automatically select thumbnail for YouTube<br></li><li> Support for multiple video lists<br></li><li> Live preview changes you make to slides<br></li><li> Select output quality of video <br></li><li> Randomly select an audio background from folder <br></li><li> Turn text to audio and add it to final video<br></li><li> Generate videos fast (without transitions), 10 minute HD video in less than 10 seconds <br></li><li> Randomize slides to obtain hundreds of videos with 1 click <br></li><li> Spin existing videos to make them unique for YouTube and others <br></li><li> Add image or text watermark to existing videos <br></li><li> Cut random time from start or end of existing videos <br></li><li> Change audio from file or random file from directory for existing videos <br></li><li> Generate up to 1000 unique video copies from an existing video by adding random pixel watermark <br></li><li> Version 2: Human Text To Speech voice added<br></li><li> Version 2: Add video slides and image slides. Combine images &amp; Videos with ease<br></li><li> Version 2: Convert existing videos to different formats<br></li><li> Version 2: Append intro video to existing videos from your PC<br></li><li> Version 2: 15 New transitions added<br></li><li> Version 2: Align text of videos to left, center or rigt<br></li></ul></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><span style="font-size:12pt;"><b><span style="color:#006600;">:::Free Members :::</span></b></span><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/glass-button.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Video Spin Blaster 2.29 Pro Plus"><br><div class="quote"><br><a href="http://mir.cr/1ZLF3K9F"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer"><a href="http://mir.cr/1ZLF3K9F" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><a href="http://mir.cr/1ZLF3K9F"  target="_blank">http://mir.cr/1ZLF3K9F</a></a></a><br>Password : www.tgmember.com<br></div></div><br><p><br><br></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><span style="font-size:12pt;"><b><span style="color:#ff0000;">:::ViP Only:::</span></b></span><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>HitFilm 7.1.7427.37708</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4369-hitfilm.html</link>
<description>Name : HitFilm Version : 7.1.7427.37708 OS : Windows Type : Video Editing, Compositing and VFX Software Price : $0 Homepage : SalePage Professional video editing, compositing and VFX software.</description>
<category>Video Creator</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 08:32:02 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Create breakout content and stunning VFX with one souped-up software: HitFilm Pro. This latest release comes jam-packed with a professional editor, compositor, 800+ VFX and presets, and new built-in animation tools! 12 months of free updates and support. No subscription.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Create breakout content and stunning VFX with one souped-up software: HitFilm Pro. This latest release comes jam-packed with a professional editor, compositor, 800+ VFX and presets, and new built-in animation tools!<br></li><li> 12 months of free updates and support. No subscription.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="HitFilm 7.1.7427.37708"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Video Tweeter 1.1.5.1 Elite</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3749-video-tweeter.html</link>
<description>Name : Video Tweeter Version : 1.1.5.1 Elite OS : Windows Type : Video Creation Price : $299 Homepage : SalePage CREATE, SPIN AND UPLOAD VIDEOS! So Easy with Content Samurai Pro evolutionary Tools For Video Marketing! With VideoTweeter, you can generate a professional video from a script in seconds. It&#039;s very much easy to become a video producer. Unlike traditional video-making softwares, you do not have to spend months in order to learn VideoTweeter. It&#039;s interface is easy to understand and anyone can master it in just a few minutes. VideoTweeter is not only a fast video creating software, it is also a video mass downloander, spinner and uploader. So it is not only very usefull for video creator, but also for video marketers. You can download other’s videos from any site by VideoTweeter, and you can convert/spin existent video to thousands of different videos by few clicks.</description>
<category>Video Creator</category>
<enclosure url="http://i.imgur.com/y9HPc3h.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 10:38:04 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Fast Video Creator : Fast Video Creator is to to automatically convert an article to a slideshow. You can do a little modification for the sideshow, then program will convert the slideshow to video. Video Download : YouTube, Vimeo, Dailymotion.....you only need a website link, then you can download the website’s videos. Video Spin : Insert photo, watermarks, text, subtitles, audio, and TTS for the existing videos, and all these operations can be done in bulk Add text : Input text or import the text from a file. These texts will be added as a watermark to the video. The location for the text can be ramdom Add watermark : Add watermark for the video. You can define the watermark, or randomly select from a batch of watermarks. The location of the watermark can be random Add subtitles : Select a video file and a subtitle file (.ass, .srt). The subtitle file will be embedded in the video Add audio : Add a piece of audio for the video as background music. The insert time point can be defined or randomly Text To Speech (TTS) : Convert the text to audio, and then add it to any section of the video Flexible task management : Create multiple different types of tasks, and then flexible set the start time and loop method for upload task Account management : Manage each video site account via this program. You can manage them by group or bulk check if your account is available Video Upload : Select a number of accounts and a group of video, then do some simple settings for these accounts, and these accounts will upload these videos on the defined time Flexible video upload settings : Here are multiple upload videos settings provided by us. You can set the settings to batch upload the videos. And select one of the video to upload to one of the websites. Save multiple upload default settings : Each site can save multiple video upload settings. Create the default settings for it, and it will use the default settings automatically when you do the upload video operation. Custom module management : Use your own module created by BotChief to check your accounts and upload videos. You can manage these modules via this program. Customize website add : Add custom website, and manage them which are not developed by this program.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/fRaVo5r0rb0?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Fast Video Creator : Fast Video Creator is to to automatically convert an article to a slideshow. You can do a little modification for the sideshow, then program will convert the slideshow to video.<br></li><li> Video Download : YouTube, Vimeo, Dailymotion.....you only need a website link, then you can download the website’s videos.<br></li><li> Video Spin : Insert photo, watermarks, text, subtitles, audio, and TTS for the existing videos, and all these operations can be done in bulk<br></li><li> Add text : Input text or import the text from a file. These texts will be added as a watermark to the video. The location for the text can be ramdom<br></li><li> Add watermark : Add watermark for the video. You can define the watermark, or randomly select from a batch of watermarks. The location of the watermark can be random<br></li><li> Add subtitles : Select a video file and a subtitle file (.ass, .srt). The subtitle file will be embedded in the video<br></li><li> Add audio : Add a piece of audio for the video as background music. The insert time point can be defined or randomly<br></li><li> Text To Speech (TTS) : Convert the text to audio, and then add it to any section of the video<br></li><li> Flexible task management : Create multiple different types of tasks, and then flexible set the start time and loop method for upload task<br></li><li> Account management : Manage each video site account via this program. You can manage them by group or bulk check if your account is available<br></li><li> Video Upload : Select a number of accounts and a group of video, then do some simple settings for these accounts, and these accounts will upload these videos on the defined time<br></li><li> Flexible video upload settings : Here are multiple upload videos settings provided by us. You can set the settings to batch upload the videos. And select one of the video to upload to one of the websites.<br></li><li> Save multiple upload default settings : Each site can save multiple video upload settings. Create the default settings for it, and it will use the default settings automatically when you do the upload video operation.<br></li><li> Custom module management : Use your own module created by BotChief to check your accounts and upload videos. You can manage these modules via this program.<br></li><li> Customize website add : Add custom website, and manage them which are not developed by this program.<br></li></ul><br><br><img src="http://i.imgur.com/y9HPc3h.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Video Tweeter 1.1.5.1 Elite"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Viral Video Curator Pro 1.7.7</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1093-viral-video-curator-pro.html</link>
<description>Name : Viral Video Curator Pro Version : Unlimited 1.7.7 OS : Windows Type : Video Marketing Tools Price : $99 Homepage : SalePage What’s the most important thing for an online presence, blog, or e-commerce website? Traffic and online presence. And what’s the best way to engage viewers? Video! Video engages your viewers and enhances your on-page time significantly. And the laser-targeted content you can find with VVC Pro is extremely effective at pulling great SEO results – these traffic stats are typical of the kind of traffic increase you can achieve from curating videos – the traffic indicated in the following chart was true organic traffic, achieved from nothing but curating videos with VVC Pro and the proper blog setup: Viral Video Curator Pro has built-in templating that you can use, or not use, according to your preference. The templating is designed to enhance your on-page SEO by channeling your content by keyword. And it really works!</description>
<category>Video Creator</category>
<enclosure url="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/5SOYfrD4EOM/hqdefault.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/VVCProSR/wso-fe-files/slice_03.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 22:57:03 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Ru_ZGMTNG5A?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><img src="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/5SOYfrD4EOM/hqdefault.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Viral Video Curator Pro 1.7.7"><br><br><img src="https://s3.amazonaws.com/VVCProSR/wso-fe-files/slice_03.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Explaindio Video Creator Platinum 3.047</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1170-explaindio-video-creator-pro.html</link>
<description>Name : Explaindio Video Creator Version : Pro Platinum 2.109 + 3.047 OS : Windows/MAC Type : Video Marketing Tools Price : $47 Homepage : SalePage The #1 Animation, Doodle Sketch, and Motion Video Creation Software. How To Create Attention-Grabbing Professional-Looking Marketing, Explainer &amp;amp; Training Videos in Just Minutes! Explaindio enables people to do amazing things, and for many people it&#039;s the most important creative tool they use. This is why we really love making it better. Explaindio 2.0 is built on a foundation of features that Explaindio 1.0 video creators know and love; these include animation, doodle sketch, the full motion video, and an impressive ease of use. Now, we&#039;ve added more features than any other business video creation software in the world, and we&#039;ve given it a completely new user interface for even more advanced and rapid video creation.</description>
<category>Video Creator</category>
<enclosure url="http://i.imgur.com/a7YwBNC.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 11:36:53 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Sketch to Video : Sketch the first frame of the video and then make amazing transition to live video. Sketch to Animation : Sketch the first frame of the animation and then make smooth transition to animation. Fully Animated Moving Motion Objects : Make multi-step, sprite like, moving animation of any objects including video, animation, image, and doodle. Green Screen : Create &quot;green screen&quot; video and replace any color with animation, live video, doogle sketch or image.. Font Import &amp;amp; International Characters : Import any TTF font in any language. Draw or animate text with any characters. Filled Line Text Drawing : Draw beautifully looking text characters with solid line. Dynamic Zoom : Set multiple zoom in &amp;amp; out actions for video, animation, image, and doodle sketch image. Set independent action time for each part of zoom sequence. ScreenShot :::Free Members ::: Download Now Password : www.tgmember.com :::v3 Platinum ViP Only::: :::Bonus::: :::Explaindio for Professionals::: :::AWESOME Slides::: :::Bonuses from Johnn Reviews:::</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/3Mo4umTukb0?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><p><br></p><br><h3>Features</h3><br><p><br><ul><li> Sketch to Video : Sketch the first frame of the video and then make amazing transition to live video.<br></li><li> Sketch to Animation : Sketch the first frame of the animation and then make smooth transition to animation.<br></li><li> Fully Animated Moving Motion Objects : Make multi-step, sprite like, moving animation of any objects including video, animation, image, and doodle.<br></li><li> Green Screen : Create "green screen" video and replace any color with animation, live video, doogle sketch or image..<br></li><li> Font Import &amp; International Characters : Import any TTF font in any language. Draw or animate text with any characters.<br></li><li> Filled Line Text Drawing : Draw beautifully looking text characters with solid line.<br></li><li> Dynamic Zoom : Set multiple zoom in &amp; out actions for video, animation, image, and doodle sketch image. Set independent action time for each part of zoom sequence.<br></li></ul></p><br><h3>ScreenShot</h3><br><p><br><img src="http://i.imgur.com/a7YwBNC.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Explaindio Video Creator Platinum 3.047"></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><span style="font-size:12pt;"><b><span style="color:#006600;">:::Free Members :::</span></b></span><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><a href="http://31.220.48.156/engine/go.php?url=aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9jbG91ZGRyaXZlL3NoYXJlL0lCZnF3c0YzNnF2V1VKSk5xWC1VT25kRGNra2tweUdZeXJQdG9HZ3pQQW8%3D"  target="_blank">Download Now</a><br>Password : www.tgmember.com<br></div></div><br><p><br><br></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><span style="font-size:12pt;"><b><span style="color:#ff0000;">:::v3 Platinum ViP Only:::</span></b></span><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br><br><br><span style="font-size:12pt;"><b><span style="color:#ff0000;">:::Bonus:::</span></b></span><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br><br><span style="font-size:12pt;"><b><span style="color:#ff0000;">:::Explaindio for Professionals:::</span></b></span><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br><br><span style="font-size:12pt;"><b><span style="color:#ff0000;">:::AWESOME Slides:::</span></b></span><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br><br><span style="font-size:12pt;"><b><span style="color:#ff0000;">:::Bonuses from Johnn Reviews:::</span></b></span><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Easy VSL Platinum 3.4.3</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1407-easy-vsl-platinum.html</link>
<description>Name : Easy VSL Version : Platinum 3.4.3 OS : Windows/MAC Type : Video Creator Software Price : $97 Homepage : SalePage In just 9 Months, EasyVSL has become The #1 Video Sales Letter (VSL) Creator and Sales Converting Video Software Online! The World’s Most Engaging Sales Machine. Now Enhanced By The World’s Most Powerful VSL Creation Features!</description>
<category>Video Creator</category>
<enclosure url="http://easyvsl.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/10/video-creation.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://i.imgur.com/q0dl7lj.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 00:13:12 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Premium Background Themes Speech to Text Video Creation Automatic Slide Creation Animated Transition Effects Premium Custom Fonts Instant Audio Syncing High Quality MP4 Video Production One-Click Language Translator ... and much more!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/nGquYA-1En4?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" gesture="media" allow="encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Premium Background Themes<br></li><li> Speech to Text Video Creation<br></li><li> Automatic Slide Creation<br></li><li> Animated Transition Effects<br></li><li> Premium Custom Fonts<br></li><li> Instant Audio Syncing<br></li><li> High Quality MP4 Video Production<br></li><li> One-Click Language Translator<br></li><li> ... and much more!<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://easyvsl.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/10/video-creation.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Easy VSL Platinum 3.4.3"><br><img src="http://i.imgur.com/q0dl7lj.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>