<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Vine Marketing - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Vine Marketing - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>Viny Bot 3.0.1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/964-viny-bot.html</link>
<description>Name : Viny Bot Version : 3.0.1.0 OS : Windows Type : Vine Marketing, Social Marketing Price : $97 VinyBot is a software tool that I&#039;ve created to naturally grow my Vine following, faster and more effectively than ever before. In just a few minutes, VinyBot can perform a multitude of research and implementation tasks that would take several hours to perform manually... By failing to utilise Vine, you&#039;re not only leaving a lot of money on the table, you&#039;re also giving the edge to your competition... By using VinyBot, you&#039;ll be able to use Vine to its full potential, and grow your following at a rate that your competition could only dream of...</description>
<category>Vine Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://xorbots.com/images/vinybot.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2016 03:25:26 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Enhanced winsock technology Free lifetime automatic update Multi-Threading that further speeds up Proxy support with built-in downloader Easy to use layout Instant download CAPTCHA support Delay functionality User-Agent changer Multiple account support Account statistics Mass account checker Mass follow/unfollow tool Mass reviner Mass liker Mass comment with spinning capability Mass vine downloader Mass vine uploader with unique video creation Scrape usernames from search results, followers, following, tags, channels and many more Scrape vines from tags, channels, on the rise and many more Account creator Loops increaser</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/22iWjMwwugA?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Enhanced winsock technology<br></li><li> Free lifetime automatic update<br></li><li> Multi-Threading that further speeds up<br></li><li> Proxy support with built-in downloader<br></li><li> Easy to use layout<br></li><li> Instant download<br></li><li> CAPTCHA support<br></li><li> Delay functionality<br></li><li> User-Agent changer<br></li><li> Multiple account support<br></li><li> Account statistics<br></li><li> Mass account checker<br></li><li> Mass follow/unfollow tool<br></li><li> Mass reviner<br></li><li> Mass liker<br></li><li> Mass comment with spinning capability<br></li><li> Mass vine downloader<br></li><li> Mass vine uploader with unique video creation<br></li><li> Scrape usernames from search results, followers, following, tags, channels and many more<br></li><li> Scrape vines from tags, channels, on the rise and many more<br></li><li> Account creator<br></li><li> Loops increaser<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://xorbots.com/images/vinybot.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Viny Bot 3.0.1.0"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>6Sec Blaster 1.9</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/860-6sec-blaster.html</link>
<description>Name :6Sec Blaster Version : 1.9 OS : Windows Type : Social Marketing, Video Marketing, Vine Marketing Price : $37 Homepage : SalePage Best Vine Compilation Maker : Find And Download Vines With 1 Click, Then Generate Your Compilation Find Viral Vines : With the help of 6Sec Blaster you can search for vines from 4 different sources: twitter, custom link, vine.co based on keyword or search on vine.co popular page. Downloading is done almost instant, and after that, you have various options that will allow you to select only the viral vines. For every vine downloaded you will see the number of likes, Facebook shares and Twitter likes. Generate Vine Compilations : Once you finished downloading and sorting through the vines, you can start generating your video. Before every vine you can add an intro slide. The intro slide can be displayed for a custom amount of time. This intro slide can contain information about the vine, a cool background and also, if you want, credits to the original author of the vine. The best part is that 6Sec Blaster also generates a description and tags for you, so you can instantly upload the video on YouTube or any other video sharing website.</description>
<category>Vine Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://blastersuite.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2015/07/6sec2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2016 04:40:18 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Generate Vine compilations on the fly Download hundreds of videos in minutes Search for viral vines on 4 different sources View the vines popularity and keep what&#039;s viral Option to give credits to original author Compatible with Windows Xp Sp3/Vista/7/8 and all Server Editions Download vines from 4 different sources (vine, twitter, popular page, custom link) Custom templates for intro slides of vines Preview slide modifications Duplicate vines (so you can show a vine multiple times in your compilation) Auto generate SEO optimized description/tags for your video Sort the list of vines based on number of likes, shares or tweets Set custom length to intro slides Auto-update system so 6Sec Blaster is always up to date Free For All http://mir.cr/0PVKYVTK</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/FXbQe5b9fOk?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Generate Vine compilations on the fly<br /></li><li> Download hundreds of videos in minutes<br /></li><li> Search for viral vines on 4 different sources<br /></li><li> View the vines popularity and keep what's viral<br /></li><li> Option to give credits to original author<br /></li><li> Compatible with Windows Xp Sp3/Vista/7/8 and all Server Editions<br /></li><li> Download vines from 4 different sources (vine, twitter, popular page, custom link)<br /></li><li> Custom templates for intro slides of vines<br /></li><li> Preview slide modifications<br /></li><li> Duplicate vines (so you can show a vine multiple times in your compilation)<br /></li><li> Auto generate SEO optimized description/tags for your video<br /></li><li> Sort the list of vines based on number of likes, shares or tweets<br /></li><li> Set custom length to intro slides<br /></li><li> Auto-update system so 6Sec Blaster is always up to date<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://blastersuite.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2015/07/6sec2.jpg" alt="6Sec Blaster 1.9" title="6Sec Blaster 1.9"  /><br /><div class="quote">Free For All<br /><a href="http://mir.cr/0PVKYVTK"  target="_blank">http://mir.cr/0PVKYVTK</a> <br /></div><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="6Sec Blaster 1.9" title="6Sec Blaster 1.9"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Vine Demon 1.3</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1191-vinedemon.html</link>
<description>Name :Vine Demon – The Ultimate VINE Bot Version : 1.3 OS : Windows Type : Vine Marketing Bot Price : $299 Homepage : SalePage Vine Demon is designed to help users get rid of all difficulties when using Vine for online marketing. Vine Demon allows users to save lots of time and money by offering automatic functions such as mass account checker, mass following/unfollowing, mass liker, mass reviner, and much more. All are done automatically and systematically. Vine Demon has user-friendly interface and ease of use that allow users to manage the whole process easily. Vine Demon, a cost-effective tool, is indispensable to your arsenal in online marketing tool kits.</description>
<category>Vine Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://smmbots.com/screenshots/vine/vd.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://smmbots.com/screenshots/vine/account-creator.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2016 01:24:52 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Modules Follow/Unfollow Modules Liker Modules Commenter Modules Revine Modules Mass Promoter Modules Scraper Modules Account Creator Modules Edit Avatar Modules Edit Profile Modules Account Statistic Modules Captcha Sloving Modules Proxies</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/VT0TRPV3OOw?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Modules Follow/Unfollow<br /></li><li> Modules Liker<br /></li><li> Modules Commenter<br /></li><li> Modules Revine<br /></li><li> Modules Mass Promoter<br /></li><li> Modules Scraper<br /></li><li> Modules Account Creator<br /></li><li> Modules Edit Avatar<br /></li><li> Modules Edit Profile<br /></li><li> Modules Account Statistic<br /></li><li> Modules Captcha Sloving<br /></li><li> Modules Proxies<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://smmbots.com/screenshots/vine/vd.png" alt="Vine Demon 1.3" title="Vine Demon 1.3"  /><br /><img src="http://smmbots.com/screenshots/vine/account-creator.png" alt="Vine Demon 1.3" title="Vine Demon 1.3"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Vine Demon 1.3" title="Vine Demon 1.3"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>