<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Marketing Tools - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Marketing Tools - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>Orion 1.0.30</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1158-orion.html</link>
<description>Name : Orion Version : 1.0.30 OS : Windows/MAC Type : Lead Marketing, Ebay Marketing Price : $1250 Homepage : SalePage Orion and it helps business owners to find unlimited amounts of leads and customers. The software has 8 tools inside it to help any business owners to get more exposure, which means there will be more traffic and leads and sales. Some of the tools inside will help you make leads by finding buyers that are looking and asking to buy stuff that you maybe selling.</description>
<category>Ebay Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 11:18:09 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Ad forge – It will create Ad’s with pictures for you. Auction Pro – Is a tool that has Buyers and Sellers on action to classified price Excavator – Helps get you leads Get leads – Find leads for you Get Traffic – Finds all websites on products that are promoting the same or slightly different products to you that are on pages 1-3 in search engines like Google. Then you can leave a reply on that site to drive more traffic to your site. Middle Man Accelerator – gives you help with door to door selling of a product, by selling them a service. Like building them a top ranking website for their business. Post Master – It will post on web forms for you. Siphon competition – Shows you how to siphon the customers from your competitors by placing comments on others blogs.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/6cfBHa00OGM?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Ad forge – It will create Ad’s with pictures for you.<br></li><li> Auction Pro –  Is a tool that has Buyers and Sellers on action to classified price<br></li><li> Excavator – Helps get you leads<br></li><li> Get leads – Find leads for you<br></li><li> Get Traffic – Finds all websites on products that are promoting the same or slightly different products to you that are on pages 1-3 in search engines like Google. Then you can leave a reply on that site to drive more traffic to your site.<br></li><li> Middle Man Accelerator – gives you help with door to door selling of a product, by selling them a service. Like building them a top ranking website for their business.<br></li><li> Post Master – It will post on web forms for you.<br></li><li> Siphon competition – Shows you how to siphon the customers from your competitors by placing comments on others blogs.<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Orion 1.0.30"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Jungle Scout 4.1.4 + Pro 2.1.6</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1169-jungle-scout.html</link>
<description>Name : Jungle Scout Lite + Jungle Scout Pro Version : 4.1.4 + Pro 2.1.6 OS : Windows Type : Amazon Research Tools, Amazon Seller Tools Price : $87 + $147 Homepage : SalePage Jungle Scout integrates into your Google Chrome browser, streamlining your product research. Extract rank, sales volume, estimated revenue and more without ever exiting your browser or entering an Amazon product page. Amazon product research made easy. Save hours uncovering product ideas and sales information.</description>
<category>Amazon Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-07/thumbs/1437434033_jungles.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 08:33:04 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Quickly See Best Seller Ranks : One click of the Jungle Scout favicon neatly lists all the best seller ranks and pertinent categories. Estimate Monthly Revenue : Using proprietary sales information, monthly unit sales and revenue are estimated for each product. Works with Mac and PC : One click seamless installation into your Chrome browser means it works with any operating system and runs lean. Uncover Product Review Stats : Product review statistics, including number of reviews and the average star rating are neatly displayed. Free Updates : Team members work tirelessly to improve Jungle Scout. Unlimited product updates are included for the next year at no extra cost. Export Results : With one click of a button you can export all your data to a .csv file. Proof Tester</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/WvYkxqzhz2g?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><p><br></p><br><h3>Features</h3><br><p><br><ul><li> Quickly See Best Seller Ranks : One click of the Jungle Scout favicon neatly lists all the best seller ranks and pertinent categories. <br></li><li> Estimate Monthly Revenue : Using proprietary sales information, monthly unit sales and revenue are estimated for each product. <br></li><li> Works with Mac and PC : One click seamless installation into your Chrome browser means it works with any operating system and runs lean. <br></li><li> Uncover Product Review Stats : Product review statistics, including number of reviews and the average star rating are neatly displayed. <br></li><li> Free Updates : Team members work tirelessly to improve Jungle Scout. Unlimited product updates are included for the next year at no extra cost. <br></li><li> Export Results : With one click of a button you can export all your data to a .csv file.<br></li></ul></p><br><h3>Proof Tester</h3><br><p><br><a href="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-07/1437434033_jungles.png" class="highslide" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-07/thumbs/1437434033_jungles.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=''></a></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Jungle Scout 4.1.4 + Pro 2.1.6"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>ASINspector 2.4.1 + Pro 2.4.12</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1233-asinspector.html</link>
<description>Name : ASINspector Version : 2.4.1 + Pro 2.4.12 OS : Windows/MAC/Linux Type : Amazon Marketing Tools Price : $127 + 97$/yearly Homepage : SalePage ASINspector Amazon Search Tool Researching Amazon Just Got A Whole Lot Easier! ASINspector integrates into your Google Chrome browser as an extension, streamlining your product research. Extract rank, sales volume, estimated revenue, find out where it is being sold on other sites, source product and more without ever exiting your browser. Simply type a product in on Amazon and instantly get results and do this in multiple countries. If you are selling, know someone who is selling products on Amazon you will not want to do it without this tool. This will save you hours of work and allow you to be able easily beat your competition. You can find niche products to easily rank on Amazon.</description>
<category>Amazon Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://asinspector.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/10/mobile_scanning_asinpro.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://asinspector.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/10/asin_tracker_pro.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://asinspector.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/07/ss.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 08:32:38 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Estimate Monthly Revenue Find Niche products quickly and easily Know what your competition is doing volume wise instantly Works in multiple countries Find the product on other sources and compare such as Alibaba, Ebay (co,uk, ca, fr), Walmart, Target, Etc Categories and Nodes where you will want your product coming up! Graph with history pricing! Easy to use with any screen size! Extract your data to Excel/CSV, no limit to the amount you can extract! Use the tool right from AMZ product page, category page and seller page Allows you to alter the pricing to see how the numbers will change based on different scenarios! Much, Much, More... Allows you to sort by any keyword, product, category and find what is selling the most on Amazon You can ethically “spy” on your Competition by Quickly gathering whatever Data You Choose Works with Mac or PC - One click seamless installation into your Chrome browser means it works with any operating system and runs lean. Works with any country you may be in. Allows you to see what other competing sites such as Ebay, Walmart, Etc to see what pricing they are offering if at all. Easily source it on Alibaba and Aliexpress to see what price you might get the product at. Find out instantly what the monthly revenue is for any product you want. Quickly sort by most revenue made with one click Know instantly what rank, reviews, ratings, price of any product, niche, category you want. Know instantly every keyword the product is listed under Pro Version Spy on your competitor with our keyword search and find too Mobile - Yes scan any item anywhere from any store on your ISO/Android device Effortlessly filter any category and or column and drill down to find exactly the parameters you are looking for ASINspector Product Tracker - Track pricing, margins, inventory, and so much more - $80/mo value Easily find sponsored link products Brainstorm - Not sure what to search click our magic light bulb and let ASINspector Pro find it for you Simply store and save your most favorite searches to easily with one click find them again. Import unlimited amount of ASIN&#039;s at once, then let ASIN Pro research them all (with filters as well) Easily get other related keywords for any product in Google + Google Trends Easily reverse search sites like WalMart and have ASIN pull the results. ...much, MUCH more! Screen Pro Version Screen Nomal Version Walk Through</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/133793653?app_id=122963" width="425" height="484" frameborder="0" title="ASINspector Chrome Extension" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><p><br></p><br><h3>Features</h3><br><p><br><ul><li> Estimate Monthly Revenue<br></li><li> Find Niche products quickly and easily<br></li><li> Know what your competition is doing volume wise instantly<br></li><li> Works in multiple countries<br></li><li> Find the product on other sources and compare such as Alibaba, Ebay (co,uk, ca, fr), Walmart, Target, Etc<br></li><li> Categories and Nodes where you will want your product coming up!<br></li><li> Graph with history pricing!<br></li><li> Easy to use with any screen size!<br></li><li> Extract your data to Excel/CSV, no limit to the amount you can extract!<br></li><li> Use the tool right from AMZ product page, category page and seller page<br></li><li> Allows you to alter the pricing to see how the numbers will change based on different scenarios!<br></li><li> Much, Much, More...<br></li><li> Allows you to sort by any keyword, product, category and find what is selling the most on Amazon<br></li><li> You can ethically “spy” on your Competition by Quickly gathering whatever Data You Choose<br></li><li> Works with Mac or PC - One click seamless installation into your Chrome browser means it works with any operating system and runs lean.<br></li><li> Works with any country you may be in.<br></li><li> Allows you to see what other competing sites such as Ebay, Walmart, Etc to see what pricing they are offering if at all.<br></li><li> Easily source it on Alibaba and Aliexpress to see what price you might get the product at.<br></li><li> Find out instantly what the monthly revenue is for any product you want.<br></li><li> Quickly sort by most revenue made with one click<br></li><li> Know instantly what rank, reviews, ratings, price of any product, niche, category you want.<br></li><li> Know instantly every keyword the product is listed under<br></li></ul></p><br><h3>Pro Version</h3><br><p><br><ul><li> Spy on your competitor with our keyword search and find too<br></li><li> Mobile - Yes scan any item anywhere from any store on your ISO/Android device<br></li><li> Effortlessly filter any category and or column and drill down to find exactly the parameters you are looking for<br></li><li> ASINspector Product Tracker - Track pricing, margins, inventory, and so much more - /mo value<br></li><li> Easily find sponsored link products<br></li><li> Brainstorm - Not sure what to search click our magic light bulb and let ASINspector Pro find it for you<br></li><li> Simply store and save your most favorite searches to easily with one click find them again.<br></li><li> Import unlimited amount of ASIN's at once, then let ASIN Pro research them all (with filters as well)<br></li><li> Easily get other related keywords for any product in Google + Google Trends<br></li><li> Easily reverse search sites like WalMart and have ASIN pull the results.<br></li><li> ...much, MUCH more!<br></li></ul></p><br><h3>Screen Pro Version</h3><br><p><br><img src="http://asinspector.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/10/mobile_scanning_asinpro.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="ASINspector 2.4.1 + Pro 2.4.12"><br><img src="http://asinspector.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/10/asin_tracker_pro.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""></p><br><h3>Screen Nomal Version</h3><br><p><br><img src="http://asinspector.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/07/ss.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><br></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br>Walk Through<br><div class="dlevideoplayer" style="width:100%;max-width:425px;">
			<ul data-theme="default" data-preload="metadata">
				<li data-title="conv_35uu3ipxixd6v" data-type="m4v" data-url="https://vidhosting-files.s3.amazonaws.com/conv_35uu3ipxixd6v.mp4" ></li>
			</ul>
		</div><br><div class="dlevideoplayer" style="width:100%;max-width:425px;">
			<ul data-theme="default" data-preload="metadata">
				<li data-title="user_3_de7c29a8ba060897438bc0940ff026e4c685dba5" data-type="m4v" data-url="https://www.vidhostingonline.com/_members/_video_files/converted/media_124/user_3_de7c29a8ba060897438bc0940ff026e4c685dba5.mp4" ></li>
			</ul>
		</div><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>SellerHacks 10 in 1 2.5</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4340-sellerhacks.html</link>
<description>Name : SellerHacks 10 in 1 Version : 2.5 OS : Windows/MAC/Linux Type : Amazon FB Tools Price : $2997 Homepage : SalePage We believe that following a live, real case study is the best way for YOU to learn and implement the hacks and strategies we&#039;re successfully using in our Amazon business</description>
<category>Amazon Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 06:22:28 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Everything in PREMIUM Plus... Instead of 3 months, you get 6 months of free access to SellerHacks Insiders - our monthly coaching program. (6 x $397 = $2,382 real value) Instead of 3 months of Software Access, you get free acess to all our software for the entire duration of the case study, which is at least 12 months! ($11,964+ real value) Exclusive access to our Ultimate Review Hacks program - 3 different strategies for getting more reviews. Consisting of 3 different live training webinars, along with 3 Q&amp;amp;A live webinars and 3 different software tools that make the 3 strategies easy to implement and use. These hacks are not available anywhere else and this is the only way to get access to these 3 super powerful hacks. If you need more, high quality reviews - you need to get this. ($1,997 real value)</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/RTxey-UP_l0?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Everything in PREMIUM Plus...<br></li><li> Instead of 3 months, you get 6 months of free access to SellerHacks Insiders - our monthly coaching program. (6 x 7 = ,382 real value)<br></li><li> Instead of 3 months of Software Access, you get free acess to all our software for the entire duration of the case study, which is at least 12 months! (,964+ real value)<br></li><li> Exclusive access to our Ultimate Review Hacks program - 3 different strategies for getting more reviews. Consisting of 3 different live training webinars, along with 3 Q&amp;A live webinars and 3 different software tools that make the 3 strategies easy to implement and use. These hacks are not available anywhere else and this is the only way to get access to these 3 super powerful hacks. If you need more, high quality reviews - you need to get this. (,997 real value)<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="SellerHacks 10 in 1 2.5"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Amasuite 5.0.1.4</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/992-amasuite-4.html</link>
<description>Name : Amasuite (Ama Keyword Generator + Ama Top Product Analyzer+ Ama Search Analyzer + Ama Review Analyzer) Version : 5.0.1.4 (5.0.1.1 + 5.0.1.4 + 5.0.1.1 + 5.0.0.9) OS : Windows/MAC Type : Amazon Marketing Price : $297 Homepage : SalePage AmaSuite 5 is the collection of five powerful software tools designed to help solve some of the most important aspects of succeeding on Amazon. A totally re-invented version of AmaSuite with more powerful features than ever before</description>
<category>Amazon Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://20028-presscdn.pagely.comdna-cdn.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/top-product-analyzer-boxset-1.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://20028-presscdn.pagely.comdna-cdn.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/search-analyzer-boxset-3.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://20028-presscdn.pagely.comdna-cdn.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/keyword-generator-boxset-1.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://20028-presscdn.pagely.comdna-cdn.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/review-analyzer-boxset-1.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://20028-presscdn.pagely.comdna-cdn.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/ali-inspector-box-combo-2.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://20028-presscdn.pagely.comdna-cdn.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/sellers-training-course-set-600.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://20028-presscdn.pagely.comdna-cdn.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/affiliate-training-course-set-600.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 18:45:59 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Amasuite Top Product Analyzer Find hidden profitable niches to avoid the worry to releasing unsuccessful products Find hot selling items that you know will convert well when people click over to Amazon Amasuite Search Analyzer Go beyond the top 100 and take advantage of competitive info, like massively discounted productsAmasuite 5 Search Analyzer Amasuite Keyword Generator Out do the competition by finding what people are actually searching for when wanting to buy Find the perfect keywords for your product listing to show up and sell moreAmaSuite 5 Review Amasuite Review Analyzer Differentiate your product from the competition to increase sales &amp;amp; conversions Find new product ideas to private label on AmazonAmasuite 5 Review Analyzer Ali Inspector Find dropship products you can test on Amazon &amp;amp; then private label for your own business Analyze thousands of products on AliExpress in just minutes Amazon Sellers Training Course Module 1 – Introduction to selling on Amazon Module 2 – How to pick the right product to sell Module 3 – How to find a supplier Module 4 – How to get sales on Amazon Module 5 – How to get reviews on Amazon Module 6 – How to scale your from one product to many Module 7 – Customer Q&amp;amp;A – December 2016 Amazon Affiliate Training Course Module 1 – How To Research An Amazon Niche Module 2 – How to setup an Amazon web-site Module 3 – Should you build niche or authority web-sites Module 4 – Why Amazon review web-sites work the best Module 5 – How to write content for an Amazon web-site Module 6 – How to use AmaSync to cut down content creation times Module 7 – How to make Cash with Amazon websites Module 8 – How to get traffic to an Amazon web-site Module 9 – How to buy Amazon web-sites</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/y2bVeIXXlbo?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><img src="http://20028-presscdn.pagely.comdna-cdn.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/top-product-analyzer-boxset-1.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Amasuite 5.0.1.4"><br><b>Amasuite Top Product Analyzer</b><br><ul><li> Find hidden profitable niches to avoid the worry to releasing unsuccessful products<br></li><li> Find hot selling items that you know will convert well when people click over to Amazon<br></li></ul><br><br><img src="http://20028-presscdn.pagely.comdna-cdn.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/search-analyzer-boxset-3.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><b>Amasuite Search Analyzer</b><br><ul><li> Go beyond the top 100 and take advantage of competitive info, like massively discounted productsAmasuite 5 Search Analyzer<br></li></ul><br><br><img src="http://20028-presscdn.pagely.comdna-cdn.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/keyword-generator-boxset-1.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><b>Amasuite Keyword Generator</b><br><ul><li> Out do the competition by finding what people are actually searching for when wanting to buy<br></li><li> Find the perfect keywords for your product listing to show up and sell moreAmaSuite 5 Review<br></li></ul><br><br><img src="http://20028-presscdn.pagely.comdna-cdn.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/review-analyzer-boxset-1.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><b>Amasuite Review Analyzer</b><br><ul><li> Differentiate your product from the competition to increase sales &amp; conversions<br></li><li> Find new product ideas to private label on AmazonAmasuite 5 Review Analyzer<br></li></ul><br><br><img src="http://20028-presscdn.pagely.comdna-cdn.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/ali-inspector-box-combo-2.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><b>Ali Inspector</b><br><ul><li> Find dropship products you can test on Amazon &amp; then private label for your own business<br></li><li> Analyze thousands of products on AliExpress in just minutes<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://20028-presscdn.pagely.comdna-cdn.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/sellers-training-course-set-600.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><br><b>Amazon Sellers Training Course</b><br><ul><li> Module 1 – Introduction to selling on Amazon<br></li><li> Module 2 – How to pick the right product to sell<br></li><li> Module 3 – How to find a supplier<br></li><li> Module 4 – How to get sales on Amazon<br></li><li> Module 5 – How to get reviews on Amazon<br></li><li> Module 6 – How to scale your from one product to many<br></li><li> Module 7 – Customer Q&amp;A – December 2016<br></li></ul><br><br><img src="http://20028-presscdn.pagely.comdna-cdn.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/affiliate-training-course-set-600.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><b>Amazon Affiliate Training Course</b><br><ul><li> Module 1 – How To Research An Amazon Niche<br></li><li> Module 2 – How to setup an Amazon web-site<br></li><li> Module 3 – Should you build niche or authority web-sites<br></li><li> Module 4 – Why Amazon review web-sites work the best<br></li><li> Module 5 – How to write content for an Amazon web-site<br></li><li> Module 6 – How to use AmaSync to cut down content creation times<br></li><li> Module 7 – How to make Cash with Amazon websites<br></li><li> Module 8 – How to get traffic to an Amazon web-site<br></li><li> Module 9 – How to buy Amazon web-sites<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Amazon Keyword Generator 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3996-amazon-keyword-generator.html</link>
<description>Name : Amazon Keyword Generator Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Amazon Keyword Tool Price : $59 Homepage : SalePage Amazon Keyword Tool is a keyword software tool that allows users to generate unlimited long tail keywords from Amazon auto search suggest. Amazon auto search suggest keywords are generated when an Amazon user enters any characters. For example if they enter cooking then a list of auto complete suggestions will be generated.</description>
<category>Amazon Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 03:19:40 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features The tool simply fires requests off to Amazon in the background and scrapes the results to automatically to find long tail variants of your niches keywords that Amazon users are searching for when buying items from Amazon. You simply enter your inital niches keyword(s) then configure the depth of long tails you want to generate and click start.. For example if your niche/main keyword is gaming, you would simply enter gaming and click generate long tails and the software would bring back hundreds of gaming related long tail keywords to give you a better insight into what Amazon customers in your niche are searching for. This will also help you optimise your Amazon listings so they appear higher up in Amazon search results.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/CYEnR1xeFh4?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> The tool simply fires requests off to Amazon in the background and scrapes the results to automatically to find long tail variants of your niches keywords that Amazon users are searching for when buying items from Amazon. You simply enter your inital niches keyword(s) then configure the depth of long tails you want to generate and click start.. For example if your niche/main keyword is gaming, you would simply enter gaming and click generate long tails and the software would bring back hundreds of gaming related long tail keywords to give you a better insight into what Amazon customers in your niche are searching for. This will also help you optimise your Amazon listings so they appear higher up in Amazon search results.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Amazon Keyword Generator 1.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>AU Black Label Edition  5.3</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/868-arbitrage-underdog-reloaded.html</link>
<description>Name : Arbitrage Underdog RELOADED Black Label Edition + OTO1 + OTO2 Version : 5.3 OS : Windows Type : Fiverr Marketing, Craigslist Marketing,Elance Marketing, Odesk Marketing and Gumtree Marketing Price : $97 Homepage : SalePage Turn $5 Into $100-$1000...over and over with the most Successful, PROVEN Software of its kind! Arbitrage Underdog RELOADED is a business in a box; a career-making tool that has turned countless marketers, including newbies, into accomplished business owners. It also lends itself perfectly to outsourcing, making it ideal for advanced marketers looking to add another business to their bottom line. Since 2013, Arbitrage Underdog has given thousands of marketers an unfair advantage with Craigslist and Fiverr. Now updated for speed and 2014 changes, it has gone from powerful to industry-leading when it comes to online arbitrage. Arbitrage Underdog RELOADED is the only software of its kind that pulls results directly from Craigslist&#039;s database, producing leads in real time as they are posted on Craigslist. Within seconds Arbitrage Underdog RELOADED produces fresh, paying leads on one side of the screen, while matching those leads up with top rated sellers willing to do the job for $5 on the other side of the screen, eliminating hours of manual detective work. This allows you the user to be the middle-man, profiting handsomely every time!</description>
<category>Fiverr Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.arbitrageunderdogreloaded.com/jv/assets/img/softwarebox.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://antigurus.com/images/page4.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 04:06:50 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Quickly arbitrages suppliers on Fiverr with buyers on Craigslist FRESH leads DIRECTLY from Craigslist mainframe Uses Proprietary Smart Bot Technology Produces hundreds of FRESH leads in minutes Highly effective for both arbitrage and job search Doubles as the ultimate automated Fiverr, and Craigslist search tool The Ultimate All-In-One Arbitrage &amp;amp; Search Interface AU Black Label Edition (OTO) All the features of the Front End product, plus: Produces THOUSANDS of leads instead of hundreds, dramatically increasing profitability Searches all US states plus Canada, UK &amp;amp; Australia simultaneously, at the click of one button 50+ times faster search results Prevents duplicate emails Built in fully customizable email templates Also pulls leads from Elance, Odesk and Gumtree</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ttlJcCElUmU?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><p><br></p><br><h3>Features</h3><br><p><br><ul><li> Quickly arbitrages suppliers on Fiverr with buyers on Craigslist<br></li><li> FRESH leads DIRECTLY from Craigslist mainframe<br></li><li> Uses Proprietary Smart Bot Technology<br></li><li> Produces hundreds of FRESH leads in minutes<br></li><li> Highly effective for both arbitrage and job search<br></li><li> Doubles as the ultimate automated Fiverr, and Craigslist search tool<br></li><li> The Ultimate All-In-One Arbitrage &amp; Search Interface<br></li></ul><br>AU Black Label Edition (OTO)<br><ul><li> All the features of the Front End product, plus:<br></li><li> Produces THOUSANDS of leads instead of hundreds, dramatically increasing profitability<br></li><li> Searches all US states plus Canada, UK &amp; Australia simultaneously, at the click of one button<br></li><li> 50+ times faster search results<br></li><li> Prevents duplicate emails<br></li><li> Built in fully customizable email templates<br></li><li> Also pulls leads from Elance, Odesk and Gumtree<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://www.arbitrageunderdogreloaded.com/jv/assets/img/softwarebox.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="AU Black Label Edition  5.3"><br><img src="http://antigurus.com/images/page4.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Ali Inspector 1.41</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1970-ali-inspector.html</link>
<description>Name : Ali Inspector Version : 1.41 OS : Windows Type : AliExpress Spy Tools Price : $50 Homepage : SalePage Powerful 3-in-1 AliExpress Product Research Software that Generates Niche Keywords, Analyzes Bestsellers, and Uncovers Top Performing Dropship Products for Your eCommerce Store in just Minutes!</description>
<category>Market Spy Tools</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.appbreed.com/apps/aliinspector/images/aliinspector-header.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://aliinspector.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/09/ali-inspector-box-combo-2.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 11:42:42 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Keyword Generator Tool : Instantly generate thousands of highly targeted niche keywords in just seconds using the built-in keyword generator tool. Best Sellers Tool : Analyze all the best sellers on AliExpress in any category to instantly uncover the top selling products for your own eCommerce store! Keyword Search Tool : Quickly search AliExpress for any keyword using powerful search options to see the exact top selling products you need for your own eCommerce store!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/182916663?app_id=122963" width="425" height="239" frameborder="0" title="Dave Guindon&#039;s Shopy Spy Bonus - Ali Inspector" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><p><br></p><br><h3>Features</h3><br><p><br><ul><li> Keyword Generator Tool : Instantly generate thousands of highly targeted niche keywords in just seconds using the built-in keyword generator tool.<br></li><li> Best Sellers Tool : Analyze all the best sellers on AliExpress in any category to instantly uncover the top selling products for your own eCommerce store!<br></li><li> Keyword Search Tool : Quickly search AliExpress for any keyword using powerful search options to see the exact top selling products you need for your own eCommerce store!<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://www.appbreed.com/apps/aliinspector/images/aliinspector-header.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Ali Inspector 1.41"><br><img src="http://aliinspector.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/09/ali-inspector-box-combo-2.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Amazon Link Checker 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4133-amazon-link-checker.html</link>
<description>Name : Amazon Link Checker Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Amazon Check Link Tool Price : $50 Homepage : SalePage Amazon Link Checker is a desktop tool that will crawl your Amazon affiliate website checking all your outbound links to Amazon for out of stock, unavailable, 404, missing affiliate tracking IDs and more. You simply enter your website&#039;s address and click &quot;Start check&quot; and it will check every webpage on your website for Amazon affiliate links with any issues.</description>
<category>Amazon Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 06:17:23 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Using advanced crawling technology you don&#039;t need to tell this tool about every page on your website you simply enter your homepage and it will go page to page searching for outbound links to Amazon. Once it finds one it can check for any of the following issues. - Check product score - You may write an amazon review for a newly launched product that you think is going to be amazing but once people get hold of it they may give it negative reviews. This check will tell you if the average review score is below a certain threshold. With that information you can switch products you are promoting or stop promoting that product with negative reviews. - Out of stock - This simple check will tell you if an Amazon product is out of stock. - Check for affiliate code - This mode will check if your tracking ID (affiliate code) is present in the link to the Amazon product. - Check for 404 - This mode will check for pages you are linking to that no longer exist (or maybe didn&#039;t ever) by checking the server HTTP response code. Examples of server HTTP response codes that will cause issues with your links are 404 (page not found) and 500 (internal server error). - Check for unavailable - This mode will check if the product you are linking to is still available and actually being sold.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/UHHRLRWfnjY?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Using advanced crawling technology you don't need to tell this tool about every page on your website you simply enter your homepage and it will go page to page searching for outbound links to Amazon. Once it finds one it can check for any of the following issues.<br></li><li> - Check product score - You may write an amazon review for a newly launched product that you think is going to be amazing but once people get hold of it they may give it negative reviews. This check will tell you if the average review score is below a certain threshold. With that information you can switch products you are promoting or stop promoting that product with negative reviews.<br></li><li> - Out of stock - This simple check will tell you if an Amazon product is out of stock.<br></li><li> - Check for affiliate code - This mode will check if your tracking ID (affiliate code) is present in the link to the Amazon product.<br></li><li> - Check for 404 - This mode will check for pages you are linking to that no longer exist (or maybe didn't ever) by checking the server HTTP response code. Examples of server HTTP response codes that will cause issues with your links are 404 (page not found) and 500 (internal server error).<br></li><li> - Check for unavailable - This mode will check if the product you are linking to is still available and actually being sold.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Amazon Link Checker 1.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Ebay Keyword Generator 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3954-ebay-keyword-generator.html</link>
<description>Name : Ebay Keyword Generator Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Ebay Keyword Tool Price : $200 Homepage : SalePage eBay Keyword Tool is a keyword software tool for eBay that allows users to generate unlimited long tail keywords from eBay auto search suggest. eBay auto search suggest keywords are generated when an eBay user enters any characters. For example if they enter gaming then a list of auto complete suggestions will be generated. Such as</description>
<category>Ebay Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 06:13:54 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features The tool simply fires requests off to eBay in the background automatically then scrapes the auto suggest results to find long tail variants of your niches keywords that eBay users are searching for when buying items from Ebay. You simply enter your inital niches keyword(s) then configure the depth of long tails you want to generate and click start.. For example if your niche/main keyword is gaming, you would simply enter gaming and click generate long tails and eBay Keyword Tool would bring back hundreds of gaming related long tail keywords to give you a better insight into what Ebay customers in your niche are searching for. This will also help you optimise your eBay listings so they appear higher up in eBay search results. If generates these long tails by mining the auto suggest, it will enter gaming a then gaming b and so on. Eg. gaming a will return the below... - gaming accessories - gaming armchair - gaming art - gaming atx case</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/vWHcz9yR_3U?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> The tool simply fires requests off to eBay in the background automatically then scrapes the auto suggest results to find long tail variants of your niches keywords that eBay users are searching for when buying items from Ebay. You simply enter your inital niches keyword(s) then configure the depth of long tails you want to generate and click start.. For example if your niche/main keyword is gaming, you would simply enter gaming and click generate long tails and eBay Keyword Tool would bring back hundreds of gaming related long tail keywords to give you a better insight into what Ebay customers in your niche are searching for. This will also help you optimise your eBay listings so they appear higher up in eBay search results. If generates these long tails by mining the auto suggest, it will enter gaming a then gaming b and so on.  <br></li><li> Eg. gaming a will return the below...<br></li><li>  - gaming accessories<br></li><li>  - gaming armchair<br></li><li>  - gaming art<br></li><li>  - gaming atx case<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Ebay Keyword Generator 1.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>