<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Directory Submission - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Directory Submission - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>Forum Traffic Generator 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4009-forum-traffic-generator.html</link>
<description>Name : Forum Traffic Generator Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Forum Manager Price : $59 Homepage : SalePage Forum Traffic Generator is a desktop application that will monitor your favorite forums for new threads that contain your niche&#039;s keywords. Allowing you to get the first reply and most exposure of your link or signature helping you generate a flood of targeted traffic to your website.</description>
<category>Directory Submission</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2018 04:20:28 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features If the forum you want to monitor makes use of squential thread ID&#039;s in the URL then this software is compatible. To test this simply browse to your chosen forum(s) open a thread and see if there is an ID in the URL. Here are some examples. As you can see these forums use sequential ID&#039;s to identify and load the different threads so they will most likely be compatible with this software tool. Once you have entered a recent thread from your chosen forum(s) the software will try loading higher thread ID&#039;s to find the latest thread. It will now periodically check for new threads at your chosen interval and then check the contents of the post to see if it matches any of your chosen keywords. If it does you will be instantly notified via the title of the thread showing in the tool or a notification balloon popup. This allows you to get the first reply on that niche related thread meaning your link or signature gets maximum exposure to all the threads visitors.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/dODhvOq33ZM?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> If the forum you want to monitor makes use of squential thread ID's in the URL then this software is compatible. To test this simply browse to your chosen forum(s) open a thread and see if there is an ID in the URL. Here are some examples. <br></li><li> As you can see these forums use sequential ID's to identify and load the different threads so they will most likely be compatible with this software tool. <br></li><li> Once you have entered a recent thread from your chosen forum(s) the software will try loading higher thread ID's to find the latest thread. It will now periodically check for new threads at your chosen interval and then check the contents of the post to see if it matches any of your chosen keywords. If it does you will be instantly notified via the title of the thread showing in the tool or a notification balloon popup. This allows you to get the first reply on that niche related thread meaning your link or signature gets maximum exposure to all the threads visitors.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Forum Traffic Generator 1.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>SliQ Submitter Plus 3.7.1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1810-sliq-submitter-plus.html</link>
<description>Name : SliQ Submitter Plus Version : 3.7.1.0 OS : Windows Type : Directory Submitter Price : $97 Homepage : SalePage SliQ Submitter Plus is a professional software application whose purpose is to help you manage submissions to web directories for one or multiple websites.</description>
<category>Directory Submission</category>
<enclosure url="http://i1-win.softpedia-static.com/screenshots/SliQ-Submitter-Plus_1.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2016 00:03:31 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features [list] - Over 2000 directories. - Captcha decoding for fully automatic directory submission. - 3 month license - submit as many websites as you like. - Add your own directories for use in the Fast Submitter with fully automatic submission. - Unlimited website titles and descriptions. - Learns directory categories to improve accuracy. - Remain in control of the submission process. - Submit as many or as few per day as you like. - Change titles and descriptions at any time. - Records which directories have been submitted. - Export submission reports to Excel.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/OtVb-p3BN0Q?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br />[list]<br />- Over 2000 directories.<br />- Captcha decoding for fully automatic directory submission.<br />- 3 month license - submit as many websites as you like.<br />- Add your own directories for use in the Fast Submitter with fully automatic submission.<br />- Unlimited website titles and descriptions.<br />- Learns directory categories to improve accuracy.<br />- Remain in control of the submission process.<br />- Submit as many or as few per day as you like.<br />- Change titles and descriptions at any time.<br />- Records which directories have been submitted.<br />- Export submission reports to Excel.<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://i1-win.softpedia-static.com/screenshots/SliQ-Submitter-Plus_1.png" alt="SliQ Submitter Plus 3.7.1.0" title="SliQ Submitter Plus 3.7.1.0"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="SliQ Submitter Plus 3.7.1.0" title="SliQ Submitter Plus 3.7.1.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>GSA Auto Website Submitter 5.14</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1028-gsa-auto-website-submitter.html</link>
<description>The GSA Auto Website Submitter is a program designed to submit your web page to thousands of search engines like google and web directories. It will save you lots of time and also money since it&#039;s fully automated. You just enter some details about your web page and the program takes care of the rest.</description>
<category>Directory Submission</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-05/1431542544_1zf7i83.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-05/1431542806_gsa-ser-extension.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-05/1431542756_gsa-trial-reset.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2015 22:56:27 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Promoting your own website has never been easier. Search engine ranking More people are using search engines like Google and MSN than ever before. An investigation showed that more than 75% of all traffic is coming from search engines. It is important that the website is not only listed on them, but that it is listed at the first pages since almost no one will go beyond web page 10 of the search engine results. You really have to make sure many other websites link to your web page to get your website listed at the first result pages within a inte.com search engine. This is usually the primary criteria for search engines to rank a site. GSA Website Submitter will make this happen while submitting your website to a large number of directories and search engines. Automated web site submission Unlike some other programs it will accomplish this not semi-automated but almost fully automated. Filling out categories and a description is all you need to do. It is also possible to fill up Captchas immediately either by analyzing the image codes by the software or by using self-proclaimed captcha services for a small fee (e.g. 6 USD for 1000 captchas). Make your website known to other people If you are not listed in these search engines, web users won&#039;t even know you exist. It is simple to list your site with all of the search engines and directories by utilizing GSA Website Submitter. Backlinks One of the most essential tools for increasing your ranking in search engines are generally inbound links. GSA Website Submitter helps you gain these important links by automatically submitting you to directories along with search engines. Every directory you are listed in gives you a one way link. Updates The program is getting updated several times per month to make sure that all of the integrated submission sites (over thousand directories and search engines) are still working. Save yourself a lot of time, money and other resources To submit your own website to every single search engine and directory supplied by GSA Website Submitter would probably take a person several weeks or even months of work. You can now submit all of your websites in a matter of hours. Take your time back simply by automating the submission procedure, so you can improve your productivity in working your business. Avoid high website marketing costs and start posting your website today. Details for Website Submitter - Increasing the traffic of search engines to your website - Automated submitting is saving you time and energy - Increase inbound links through directory submissions - Regular updates with new directories and search engines almost once per week - E-Mail validation tool (logs into your E-Mail account and automatically clicks the verification links - Automated decaptcher with DeCaptcher, DeathByCaptcha, or even BypassCaptcha. - Usage of spin syntax - Multiple proxy usage (auto find new proxies) - Link report tool</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<b>Promoting your own website has never been easier.<br /></b><b>Search engine ranking<br /></b>More people are using search engines like Google and MSN than ever before. An investigation showed that more than 75% of all traffic is coming from search engines.<br />It is important that the website is not only listed on them, but that it is listed at the first pages since almost no one will go beyond web page 10 of the search engine results.<br /><br />You really have to make sure many other websites link to your web page to get your website listed at the first result pages within a inte.com search engine. This is usually the primary criteria for search engines to rank a site.<br />GSA Website Submitter will make this happen while submitting your website to a large number of directories and search engines.<br /><b>Automated web site submission<br /></b>Unlike some other programs it will accomplish this not semi-automated but almost fully automated. Filling out categories and a description is all you need to do. It is also possible to fill up Captchas immediately either by analyzing the image codes by the software or by using self-proclaimed captcha services for a small fee (e.g. 6 USD for 1000 captchas).<br /><b>Make your website known to other people<br /></b>If you are not listed in these search engines, web users won't even know you exist.<br />It is simple to list your site with all of the search engines and directories by utilizing GSA Website Submitter.<br /><b>Backlinks</b><br />One of the most essential tools for increasing your ranking in search engines are generally inbound links.<br />GSA Website Submitter helps you gain these important links by automatically submitting you to directories along with search engines.<br />Every directory you are listed in gives you a one way link.<br /><b>Updates</b><br />The program is getting updated several times per month to make sure that all of the integrated submission sites (over thousand directories and search engines) are still working.<br /><b>Save yourself a lot of time, money and other resources<br /></b>To submit your own website to every single search engine and directory supplied by GSA Website Submitter would probably take a person several weeks or even months of work.<br />You can now submit all of your websites in a matter of hours. Take your time back simply by automating the submission procedure, so you can improve your productivity in working your business.<br />Avoid high website marketing costs and start posting your website today.<br /><b>Details for Website Submitter<br /></b>- Increasing the traffic of search engines to your website<br />- Automated submitting is saving you time and energy<br />- Increase inbound links through directory submissions<br />- Regular updates with new directories and search engines almost once per week<br />- E-Mail validation tool (logs into your E-Mail account and automatically clicks the verification links<br />- Automated decaptcher with DeCaptcher, DeathByCaptcha, or even BypassCaptcha.<br />- Usage of spin syntax<br />- Multiple proxy usage (auto find new proxies)<br />- Link report tool<br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="GSA Auto Website Submitter 5.14" title="GSA Auto Website Submitter 5.14"  /></div><br /><div class="quote"><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>