<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Media Plugin - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Media Plugin - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>Media File Renamer 3.5.6 PRO</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2029-media-file-renamer.html</link>
<description>Name : Media File Renamer Version : 3.5.6 PRO OS : Linux Type : Media Plugin Price : $400 Homepage : SalePage The Media File Renamer is a WordPress plugin that physically renames media files nicely for a cleaner system and for a better SEO. Please read the description as it contains important information.</description>
<category>Media Plugin</category>
<enclosure url="https://meowapps.com/wp-content/uploads/media-file-renaming-mode.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="https://meowapps.com/wp-content/uploads/Media-File-Renamer-1024x727.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2017 02:52:11 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features The Pro users are given a few more features like manual renaming, renaming depending on the post the media is attached to, logging of SQL queries and a few more options. With the Pro, a good process is to actually let the plugin do the renaming automatically (like in the free version) and to do manual renaming for the files that require fine tuning.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br>The Pro users are given a few more features like manual renaming, renaming depending on the post the media is attached to, logging of SQL queries and a few more options. With the Pro, a good process is to actually let the plugin do the renaming automatically (like in the free version) and to do manual renaming for the files that require fine tuning.<br><br><img src="https://meowapps.com/wp-content/uploads/media-file-renaming-mode.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Media File Renamer 3.5.6 PRO"><br><img src="https://meowapps.com/wp-content/uploads/Media-File-Renamer-1024x727.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Simple Video Management System 5.7</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2163-simple-video-management-system.html</link>
<description>Name : Simple Video Management System Version : 5.7 Type : Media Plugin Price : $97 Homepage : SalePage You Are About To Be Handed The Opportunity To Grab The Exact Video Software Used To Power A 7-Figure Online Business...What Will You Do With It? Power Your Own Business Using Video! You Can Have The Coolest Videos In The World, But What Good Is It If The Videos Don’t Display Consistently For Your Target Market? Congratulations! You are about to end your video management worries for good!</description>
<category>Media Plugin</category>
<enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/svmslaunch/salescopyimages/svms-works-with-software-small.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2017 03:34:05 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Play the video in any browser Make it intuitive and user friendly Organize videos logically Create Page / Video Index Add HTML / buy buttons &quot;Magic Video Sales Letter” Autoplay options Toggle video controls Automatic Redirecting to a link of Your Choice</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/QVrSagn6Vt0?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Play the video in any browser<br></li><li> Make it intuitive and user friendly<br></li><li> Organize videos logically<br></li><li> Create Page / Video Index<br></li><li> Add HTML / buy buttons<br></li><li> "Magic Video Sales Letter”<br></li><li> Autoplay options<br></li><li> Toggle video controls<br></li><li> Automatic Redirecting to a link of Your Choice<br></li></ul><br><img src="https://s3.amazonaws.com/svmslaunch/salescopyimages/svms-works-with-software-small.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Simple Video Management System 5.7"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>WP Video Ace 1.1.3 Pro</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3648-wp-video-ace.html</link>
<description>Name : WP Video Ace Pro Version : 1.1.3 Type : Media Player Plugins Price : $250 Homepage : SalePage With all the great features of WP Video Ace, you can custom video in your own way. You can select any screen corner for fixed thumbnail playback or lock custom content to appear between any start and end point of video playback by anything. WP Video Ace is a brand new unique WordPress plugin which allows you to create the fantastic custom video players and apply them anywhere in your WordPress website. With this software, You can take complete control of your WordPress video marketing, by applying cool “engagement effects” to any video (it works on Youtube, Local Video Uploads, OR any Video URL). .</description>
<category>Media Plugin</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2017 03:29:05 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Can create custom video players for youtube, video URL (amazon for example), or local wordpress media upload. Can force fullscreen mode between any start and end point in the playback of video. Can have the video go to a ‘fixed thumbnail playback’ when visitor scrolls on page. Can select any screen corner, (top left or right, bottom left or right) for ‘fixed thumbnail playback’. All players have custom control for width in percentage (fluid mobile responsive, or fixed playback) All players can specify aspect ratio and video playback quality (so can force HD mode for youtube for example) Player can ‘lock’ custom content to appear between any start and end point in video playback ‘locked custom content’ can by anything (text, image, buy button, opt in form, or even entire post) ‘Locked custom content’ can appear above, below, to the left or right of video ‘Locked custom content’ can also appear in shortcode anywhere on post or page.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/fp5Me0xsvLE?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Can create custom video players for youtube, video URL (amazon for example), or local wordpress media upload.<br></li><li> Can force fullscreen mode between any start and end point in the playback of video.<br></li><li> Can have the video go to a ‘fixed thumbnail playback’ when visitor scrolls on page.<br></li><li> Can select any screen corner, (top left or right, bottom left or right) for ‘fixed thumbnail playback’.<br></li><li> All players have custom control for width in percentage (fluid mobile responsive, or fixed playback)<br></li><li> All players can specify aspect ratio and video playback quality (so can force HD mode for youtube for example)<br></li><li> Player can ‘lock’ custom content to appear between any start and end point in video playback ‘locked custom content’ can by anything (text, image, buy button, opt in form, or even entire post)<br></li><li> ‘Locked custom content’ can appear above, below, to the left or right of video<br></li><li> ‘Locked custom content’ can also appear in shortcode anywhere on post or page.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="WP Video Ace 1.1.3 Pro"><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>