<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Ebay Marketing - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Ebay Marketing - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>Orion 1.0.30</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1158-orion.html</link>
<description>Name : Orion Version : 1.0.30 OS : Windows/MAC Type : Lead Marketing, Ebay Marketing Price : $1250 Homepage : SalePage Orion and it helps business owners to find unlimited amounts of leads and customers. The software has 8 tools inside it to help any business owners to get more exposure, which means there will be more traffic and leads and sales. Some of the tools inside will help you make leads by finding buyers that are looking and asking to buy stuff that you maybe selling.</description>
<category>Ebay Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 11:18:09 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Ad forge – It will create Ad’s with pictures for you. Auction Pro – Is a tool that has Buyers and Sellers on action to classified price Excavator – Helps get you leads Get leads – Find leads for you Get Traffic – Finds all websites on products that are promoting the same or slightly different products to you that are on pages 1-3 in search engines like Google. Then you can leave a reply on that site to drive more traffic to your site. Middle Man Accelerator – gives you help with door to door selling of a product, by selling them a service. Like building them a top ranking website for their business. Post Master – It will post on web forms for you. Siphon competition – Shows you how to siphon the customers from your competitors by placing comments on others blogs.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/6cfBHa00OGM?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Ad forge – It will create Ad’s with pictures for you.<br></li><li> Auction Pro –  Is a tool that has Buyers and Sellers on action to classified price<br></li><li> Excavator – Helps get you leads<br></li><li> Get leads – Find leads for you<br></li><li> Get Traffic – Finds all websites on products that are promoting the same or slightly different products to you that are on pages 1-3 in search engines like Google. Then you can leave a reply on that site to drive more traffic to your site.<br></li><li> Middle Man Accelerator – gives you help with door to door selling of a product, by selling them a service. Like building them a top ranking website for their business.<br></li><li> Post Master – It will post on web forms for you.<br></li><li> Siphon competition – Shows you how to siphon the customers from your competitors by placing comments on others blogs.<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Orion 1.0.30"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Ebay Keyword Generator 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3954-ebay-keyword-generator.html</link>
<description>Name : Ebay Keyword Generator Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Ebay Keyword Tool Price : $200 Homepage : SalePage eBay Keyword Tool is a keyword software tool for eBay that allows users to generate unlimited long tail keywords from eBay auto search suggest. eBay auto search suggest keywords are generated when an eBay user enters any characters. For example if they enter gaming then a list of auto complete suggestions will be generated. Such as</description>
<category>Ebay Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 06:13:54 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features The tool simply fires requests off to eBay in the background automatically then scrapes the auto suggest results to find long tail variants of your niches keywords that eBay users are searching for when buying items from Ebay. You simply enter your inital niches keyword(s) then configure the depth of long tails you want to generate and click start.. For example if your niche/main keyword is gaming, you would simply enter gaming and click generate long tails and eBay Keyword Tool would bring back hundreds of gaming related long tail keywords to give you a better insight into what Ebay customers in your niche are searching for. This will also help you optimise your eBay listings so they appear higher up in eBay search results. If generates these long tails by mining the auto suggest, it will enter gaming a then gaming b and so on. Eg. gaming a will return the below... - gaming accessories - gaming armchair - gaming art - gaming atx case</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/vWHcz9yR_3U?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> The tool simply fires requests off to eBay in the background automatically then scrapes the auto suggest results to find long tail variants of your niches keywords that eBay users are searching for when buying items from Ebay. You simply enter your inital niches keyword(s) then configure the depth of long tails you want to generate and click start.. For example if your niche/main keyword is gaming, you would simply enter gaming and click generate long tails and eBay Keyword Tool would bring back hundreds of gaming related long tail keywords to give you a better insight into what Ebay customers in your niche are searching for. This will also help you optimise your eBay listings so they appear higher up in eBay search results. If generates these long tails by mining the auto suggest, it will enter gaming a then gaming b and so on.  <br></li><li> Eg. gaming a will return the below...<br></li><li>  - gaming accessories<br></li><li>  - gaming armchair<br></li><li>  - gaming art<br></li><li>  - gaming atx case<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Ebay Keyword Generator 1.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Aura Profit Hunter 1.6.5.1</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1765-aura-profit-hunter.html</link>
<description>Name : Aura Profit Hunter Version : 1.6.5.1 OS : Windows Type : Ebay Marketing, Amazon Marketing Price : $169 Homepage : SalePage Find Profitable Items for Sale in Minutes! FAST, EASY-TO-USE, &amp; NO LIMITATION Start Your Own Profitable Business! FIND BEST &amp; PROFITABLE AMAZON ARBITRAGE OPPORTUNITIES WITH AURA PROFIT HUNTER</description>
<category>Ebay Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="https://auraprofithunter.com/assets/img/head1.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="https://auraprofithunter.com/assets/img/screenshot2.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2016 00:42:21 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features USA &amp; UK : Search, find &amp; get full details either U.S or UK Amazon and eBay Sites. HIGH-PERFORMANCE : Find only profitable matches and get details within seconds with multi-thread support! PROXY SUPPORT : Aura Profit Hunter comes with Public and Private proxy support! No one can stop you! EXPORT : Export your list with all item details into a detailed .CSV file. EXPORT TO EBAY TURBO LISTER 2 : Aura Profit Hunter will export your items with full item details, calculated price, full description and automatically detected category name to eBay&#039;s official Turbo Lister 2 CVS format with one click! Cool, right? LIFETIME FREE UPDATES : We stand behind our awesome Aura Profit Hunter! You will get all updates and new features FOR FREE! SEARCH BY SELLER ID : You can scrape eBay Sellers&#039; &quot;Complete&quot; or &quot;Sold List&quot; quickly! If you wish, you can set the price range too! SEARCH BY KEYWORD(S) ...Or maybe you want to find the products in your niche. No problem! Just write your keyword(s) and click on the Start button! SAVE RESULT INTO DB : You can also keep all items with their details included database of Aura Profit Hunter! You will not lose good opportunities. Time Saver! SET YOUR PROFIT : Set your minimum profit target for each search! You decide how much you want to earn! AMAZON PRIME : Search only Amazon Prime Items. Just like on Amazon marketplace! But Of course, Aura Profit Hunter can check the items and list Prime Eligible &amp; Not Prime Eligible for you! ITEMS ON YOUR E-COMMERCE SITE : ...Well, maybe you wish to build up your own website and sell eBay items on your own e-Commerce Website. Aura Profit Hunter will also help you with this process! After listing items from eBay, you can get the item list only for this work!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/LtcgfBGvueU?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> USA & UK : Search, find & get full details either U.S or UK Amazon and eBay Sites.<br /></li><li> HIGH-PERFORMANCE : Find only profitable matches and get details within seconds with multi-thread support!<br /></li><li> PROXY SUPPORT : Aura Profit Hunter comes with Public and Private proxy support! No one can stop you!<br /></li><li> EXPORT : Export your list with all item details into a detailed .CSV file.<br /></li><li> EXPORT TO EBAY TURBO LISTER 2 : Aura Profit Hunter will export your items with full item details, calculated price, full description and automatically detected category name to eBay's official Turbo Lister 2 CVS format with one click! Cool, right?<br /></li><li> LIFETIME FREE UPDATES : We stand behind our awesome Aura Profit Hunter! You will get all updates and new features FOR FREE!<br /></li><li> SEARCH BY SELLER ID : You can scrape eBay Sellers' "Complete" or "Sold List" quickly! If you wish, you can set the price range too!<br /></li><li> SEARCH BY KEYWORD(S) ...Or maybe you want to find the products in your niche. No problem! Just write your keyword(s) and click on the Start button!<br /></li><li> SAVE RESULT INTO DB : You can also keep all items with their details included database of Aura Profit Hunter! You will not lose good opportunities. Time Saver!<br /></li><li> SET YOUR PROFIT : Set your minimum profit target for each search! You decide how much you want to earn!<br /></li><li> AMAZON PRIME : Search only Amazon Prime Items. Just like on Amazon marketplace! But Of course, Aura Profit Hunter can check the items and list Prime Eligible & Not Prime Eligible for you!<br /></li><li> ITEMS ON YOUR E-COMMERCE SITE : ...Well, maybe you wish to build up your own website and sell eBay items on your own e-Commerce Website. Aura Profit Hunter will also help you with this process! After listing items from eBay, you can get the item list only for this work!<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="https://auraprofithunter.com/assets/img/head1.png" alt="Aura Profit Hunter 1.6.5.1" title="Aura Profit Hunter 1.6.5.1"  /><br /><img src="https://auraprofithunter.com/assets/img/screenshot2.png" alt="Aura Profit Hunter 1.6.5.1" title="Aura Profit Hunter 1.6.5.1"  /><br /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Aura Profit Hunter 1.6.5.1" title="Aura Profit Hunter 1.6.5.1"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>E-Prospector 1.1</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1257-e-prospector.html</link>
<description>Name :E-Prospector Version : 1.1 OS : Windows/MAC Type : Ebay Marketing Price : $57 Homepage : SalePage E-Prospector Software : this software tells you what the hottest selling products are on ebay sau you can exploit this ecommerce giant for more profits for yourself. You will have in your hands the keys to finding important information on the hottest selling and trending products on the ebay platform. Being able to digg deep into their records is huge, and the fact that you can get this information in seconds is even better. Reverse engineer the ebay database, so you can uncover even more hot potential niches on ebay.Know extracly what to sel, and with this software at your disposal you can get multiple income streams by selling the same products on both amazon and ebay! Don&#039;t spend another minute without this tool in your back of tricks</description>
<category>Ebay Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/ecomexposed/eprospector.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 22:04:25 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Feature #1: Category Search : Quickly get an idea of what products are hot based on their category. This software is setup with all the main Ebay categories so you can rest assured that you are research bases are completely covered! Feature #2: Clear Button : Software includes a “Clear” button so you can start over. Just like the old Nintendo systems with the reset button, you have a chance to reset your search without having to open the software up! Feature #4: Price : Sorting by price enables you to determine what products are selling at different price ranges, so you can better determine what product to sell. Feature #5: Offers : On Ebay there can be several different sellers of the exact same product. E-Prospector allows you to see how different businesses are selling the same products, so you can see demand and also view if the product you are looking at would have a lower competition. Feature #6: Reviews : On Ebay a product with a high number of reviews is almost all the time a product that is getting a pile of sales. This is one of the favorite parts of this software. You can use the 8 different sorting options for reviews to uncover those hidden gems that you can start to grow your business around. Feature #7: Keyword Research : If you have already settled on your niche market, or just want to sort through products using a certain keyword this software gives you that ability! You can run searches for any type of product and use the results to validate that you are going in the correct direction. With this keyword research option it opens up the capabilities of this software big time!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/t4J8XShRLGA?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Feature #1: Category Search : Quickly get an idea of what products are hot based on their category. This software is setup with all the main Ebay categories so you can rest assured that you are research bases are completely covered! 	 <br /></li><li> Feature #2: Clear Button : Software includes a “Clear” button so you can start over. Just like the old Nintendo systems with the reset button, you have a chance to reset your search without having to open the software up! <br /></li><li> Feature #4: Price : Sorting by price enables you to determine what products are selling at different price ranges, so you can better determine what product to sell. 	  <br /></li><li> Feature #5: Offers : On Ebay there can be several different sellers of the exact same product. E-Prospector allows you to see how different businesses are selling the same products, so you can see demand and also view if the product you are looking at would have a lower competition. 	   <br /></li><li> Feature #6: Reviews : On Ebay a product with a high number of reviews is almost all the time a product that is getting a pile of sales. This is one of the favorite parts of this software. You can use the 8 different sorting options for reviews to uncover those hidden gems that you can start to grow your business around. 	   <br /></li><li> Feature #7: Keyword Research : If you have already settled on your niche market, or just want to sort through products using a certain keyword this software gives you that ability! You can run searches for any type of product and use the results to validate that you are going in the correct direction. With this keyword research option it opens up the capabilities of this software big time! 	 <br /></li></ul><br /><img src="https://s3.amazonaws.com/ecomexposed/eprospector.png" alt="E-Prospector 1.1" title="E-Prospector 1.1"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="E-Prospector 1.1" title="E-Prospector 1.1"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Paypal Payment Manager 1.24</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1461-paypal-payment-manager.html</link>
<description>Name : Rodney&#039;s Paypal Payment Manager Version : 1.24 OS : Windows Type : Bussiness Marketing Tools Price : $100 Homepage : SalePage Tired of Manually Collecting Recurring Payments? This is a software that was designed for marketers or business owners who are looking to collect outstanding balances in bulk via PayPal. This software is very easy to use as you see in the video but it has a lot of value because it will literally save you tons of time and effort. This will allow you to completely automate this process and use your time to take care of more important aspects of your business!</description>
<category>Ebay Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-12/thumbs/1451510351_mc12m0a_paypal1.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2015 01:34:54 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Completely get full access to the founder software and video training Expressly Getting Start quickly up to 7 days and you could use all the techniques there to go ahead and start earning from your first few campaigns Using the best way you utilize the $1 trial and 100% YOU get paid And then you’ll give back for the founder helping you out Then After the 7 days and 100% you will get tons of money there is only 1 payment of $54 And that’s Fair enough Just use for action takers who will actually DO something with this goldmine of a software and BANK ON IT and who will take action and get results quickly</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/sNrmZGqj7Kc?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Completely get full access to the founder software and video training Expressly<br /></li><li> Getting Start quickly up to 7 days and you could use all the techniques there to go ahead and start earning from your first few campaigns<br /></li><li> Using the best way you utilize the  trial and 100% YOU get paid<br /></li><li> And then you’ll give back for the founder helping you out<br /></li><li> Then After the 7 days and 100% you will get tons of money there is only 1 payment of <br /></li><li> And that’s Fair enough<br /></li><li> Just use for action takers who will actually DO something with this goldmine of a software and BANK ON IT and who will take action and get results quickly<br /></li></ul><br /><a href="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-12/1451510351_mc12m0a_paypal1.png" rel="highslide" class="highslide"><img src="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-12/thumbs/1451510351_mc12m0a_paypal1.png" alt='Paypal Payment Manager 1.24' title='Paypal Payment Manager 1.24'  /></a><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Paypal Payment Manager 1.24" title="Paypal Payment Manager 1.24"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Hot Item Finder 2.1.20</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/987-hot-item-finder.html</link>
<description>Name : Hot Item Finder Version : 2.1.20 OS : Windows Type : Ebay Marketing, Market Research, Ebay Research Price : $164 Homepage : SalePage Your ultimate all-in-one auction research software One of the best ebay Research tools of all time, total ebay Domination</description>
<category>Ebay Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.hotitemfinder.com/images2/benefits.gif" type="image/gif" />
<enclosure url="http://www.hotitemfinder.com/images2/tools-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="http://www.hotitemfinder.com/images2/tools-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="http://www.hotitemfinder.com/images2/tools-3.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="http://www.hotitemfinder.com/images2/tools-4.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="http://www.hotitemfinder.com/images2/tools-5.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="http://www.hotitemfinder.com/images2/tools-6.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="http://www.hotitemfinder.com/images2/tools-7.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2015 15:15:54 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><video width="640" height="480" preload="metadata" controls="controls">
				<source src="https://s3.amazonaws.com/appbreed/hotitemfinder/help/hif-intro.mp4"></source>
				</video></div><br /><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><img src="http://www.hotitemfinder.com/images2/benefits.gif" alt="Hot Item Finder 2.1.20" title="Hot Item Finder 2.1.20"  /><br /><img src="http://www.hotitemfinder.com/images2/tools-1.jpg" alt="Hot Item Finder 2.1.20" title="Hot Item Finder 2.1.20"  /><br /><img src="http://www.hotitemfinder.com/images2/tools-2.jpg" alt="Hot Item Finder 2.1.20" title="Hot Item Finder 2.1.20"  /><br /><img src="http://www.hotitemfinder.com/images2/tools-3.jpg" alt="Hot Item Finder 2.1.20" title="Hot Item Finder 2.1.20"  /><br /><img src="http://www.hotitemfinder.com/images2/tools-4.jpg" alt="Hot Item Finder 2.1.20" title="Hot Item Finder 2.1.20"  /><br /><img src="http://www.hotitemfinder.com/images2/tools-5.jpg" alt="Hot Item Finder 2.1.20" title="Hot Item Finder 2.1.20"  /><br /><img src="http://www.hotitemfinder.com/images2/tools-6.jpg" alt="Hot Item Finder 2.1.20" title="Hot Item Finder 2.1.20"  /><br /><img src="http://www.hotitemfinder.com/images2/tools-7.jpg" alt="Hot Item Finder 2.1.20" title="Hot Item Finder 2.1.20"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Hot Item Finder 2.1.20" title="Hot Item Finder 2.1.20"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Feedback Analyzer Pro 2.1.0.5</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/986-feedback-analyzer-pro.html</link>
<description>Name : Feedback Analyzer Pro Version : 2.1.0.5 OS : Windows Type : Ebay Marketing, Market Research Price : $47 Homepage : SalePage Research ebay sellers before you buy &amp; instantly increase your ebay auction sales with Powerful Feedback Ads</description>
<category>Ebay Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.hotitemfinder.com/images2/bonus-software-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2015 15:15:02 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features create feedback ads for your auctions Sorting and filtering feedback comment lists Saving and loading feedback comments extract feedback comments from an ebay member</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><video width="640" height="480" preload="metadata" poster="rss.xml" controls="controls">
						<source type="video/mp4" src="https://s3.amazonaws.com/appbreed/feedbackanalyzerpro/fba-video-1.mp4"></source>
						</video></div><br /><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li>create feedback ads for your auctions<br /></li><li>Sorting and filtering feedback comment lists<br /></li><li>Saving and loading feedback comments<br /></li><li>extract feedback comments from an ebay member<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://www.hotitemfinder.com/images2/bonus-software-2.jpg" alt="Feedback Analyzer Pro 2.1.0.5" title="Feedback Analyzer Pro 2.1.0.5"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Feedback Analyzer Pro 2.1.0.5" title="Feedback Analyzer Pro 2.1.0.5"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>