<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Content Marketing - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Content Marketing - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>SEO Content Machine 4.18.4.30</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1476-seo-content-machine.html</link>
<description>Name : SEO Content Machine Version : 4.18.4.30 OS : Windows Type : Content Marketing Tools Price : $237$/yearly Homepage : SalePage Change The Way You Create Content The first multi-language content creator program. You can also generate content specific to your local region. Trouble Creating Content?SEO Content Machine takes the pain out of creating SEO Content.</description>
<category>Content Creator</category>
<enclosure url="http://seocontentmachine.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/SCM-Monitor-Copy-e1408635573145.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2018 09:04:12 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Accelerate Your Link Building Manage Your PBNs : Draft &amp;amp; post to WordPress/Blogger or any site that supports post by email. Schedule drip feed content and keep your blog.comwork fresh indefinitely. Content Toolbag : Get your content tools. Scrape Google Suggest, create Tier 1 Content, create About Me’s. Roll your own content with an Article Downloader, Translator &amp;amp; Content Combiner. Content In Any Language : This program is a multi-language content scraper &amp;amp; generator. Supports all western languages. Create SEO content in Spanish, French, German and more. You can also generate content specific to your local region. Custom Content Sources : Find and download 100s of pages of content on any topic on any site. Customizable content sources means you don’t get caught scraping the same over-used sites as everyone else. Linkbuilding Content Generation : Make the most of your link building programs. Generate keyword targeted articles for unlimited content submissions. Supports popular programs directly such as GSA SER, Senuke &amp;amp; Ultimate Demon. Creates Readable + Keyword Relevant Articles : Special filtering algorithms remove spammy and irrelevant content automatically. This program will individually rank content against your keyword for relevancy before it is used to generate articles. Simple Content Generation : You don’t need proxies, VPS installs or other special tools. A Content Wizard mode for beginners lets you create content in less than 10 clicks. Online help + video tutorials at your finger tips. 100% Automated Content Generation : Create articles with images, videos and links. Translate or re-write articles using spinners to generate 100% unique content. 100% task automation with the option of scheduling it to repeat for as long as you like. http://direct.seocontentmachine.com/download/changelog.txt</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/f1bx-q2dudk?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Accelerate Your Link Building<br></li><li> Manage Your PBNs : Draft &amp; post to WordPress/Blogger or any site that supports post by email.  Schedule drip feed content and keep your blog.comwork fresh indefinitely.<br></li><li> Content Toolbag : Get your content tools. Scrape Google Suggest, create Tier 1 Content, create About Me’s.  Roll your own content with an Article Downloader, Translator &amp; Content Combiner. <br></li><li> Content In Any Language : This program is a multi-language content scraper &amp; generator.  Supports all western languages. Create SEO content in Spanish, French, German and more.  You can also generate content specific to your local region. <br></li><li> Custom Content Sources : Find and download 100s of pages of content on any topic on any site.  Customizable content sources means you don’t get caught scraping the same over-used sites as everyone else.  <br></li><li> Linkbuilding Content Generation : Make the most of your link building programs. Generate keyword targeted articles for  unlimited content submissions.  Supports popular programs directly such as GSA SER, Senuke &amp; Ultimate Demon.  <br></li><li> Creates Readable + Keyword Relevant Articles : Special filtering algorithms remove spammy and irrelevant content automatically.  This program will individually rank content against your keyword for relevancy before it is used to generate articles. <br></li><li> Simple Content Generation : You don’t need proxies, VPS installs or other special tools.  A Content Wizard mode for beginners lets you create content in less than 10 clicks.  Online help + video tutorials at your finger tips.<br></li><li> 100% Automated Content Generation : Create articles with images, videos and links.  Translate or re-write articles using spinners to generate 100% unique content.  100% task automation with the option of scheduling it to repeat for as long as you like.<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://seocontentmachine.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/SCM-Monitor-Copy-e1408635573145.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="SEO Content Machine 4.18.4.30"><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><a href="http://direct.seocontentmachine.com/download/changelog.txt"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">http://direct.seocontentmachine.com/download/changelog.txt</a><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>ContentBomb Elite 1.1.1</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1069-content-bomb.html</link>
<description>Name : ContentBomb Version : Elite 1.1.1 OS : Windows Type : Content Marketing Tools Price : $297 Homepage : SalePage Scrape, Convert, Output and Submit - All in One! ContentBomb is designed to be very smart, allowing you to scrape anything and convert it into any format of new content, then you can save the new content in any custom format or submit it to your blog or website. Get Started Now !</description>
<category>Content Creator</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.contentbomb.com/img/mobile.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 07:44:55 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Scrape Content From Any Source Manage Unlimited Blog/Site Accounts And Run Unlimited AutoBlog Tasks! Plenty of Content Sources Content Mix Rule and Templates Create New Content, Download Articles, Images and Videos etc.... Submit Content to Blog/Site and Ping</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/OB7DlPrkqiA?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Scrape Content From Any Source<br></li><li> Manage Unlimited Blog/Site Accounts And Run Unlimited AutoBlog Tasks!<br></li><li> Plenty of Content Sources<br></li><li> Content Mix Rule and Templates<br></li><li> Create New Content, Download Articles, Images and Videos etc....<br></li><li> Submit Content to Blog/Site and Ping<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://www.contentbomb.com/img/mobile.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="ContentBomb Elite 1.1.1"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Fresh Title 1.0.0.7</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1274-fresh-title.html</link>
<description>Name : Fresh Title Version : 1.0.0.7 OS : Windows Type : Content Marketing Tools, Content Title Generator Price : $47 Homepage : SalePage Instantly Create Hundreds of Highly Responsive Titles &amp;amp; Headlines for ANY Content you Want!</description>
<category>Title Optimizer</category>
<enclosure url="http://freshtitle.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/09/freshtitle-boxset-3.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://freshtitle.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/09/freshtitle-set-1.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2018 12:06:07 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features One-Click Software Gives You INSTANT Access to Thousands Of The BEST HEADLINES! Generate Content Title by Keyword Advande Search Content Title By Keyword Many Mores you can check on video</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/136407674?app_id=122963" width="425" height="319" frameborder="0" title="freshtitle-quickstart" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> One-Click Software Gives You INSTANT Access to Thousands Of The BEST HEADLINES! <br></li><li> Generate Content Title by Keyword Advande<br></li><li> Search Content Title By Keyword<br></li><li> Many Mores you can check on video<br></li></ul><br><br><img src="http://freshtitle.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/09/freshtitle-boxset-3.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Fresh Title 1.0.0.7"><br><img src="http://freshtitle.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/09/freshtitle-set-1.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Content Creator 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3992-content-creator.html</link>
<description>Name : Content Creator Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Creator Content Tool Price : $59 Homepage : SalePage Content Creator is a software tool that will search Google for your keyword and download all related content from Google&#039;s results for that keyword. You can then use this content in a Blackhat or Whitehat way. The Blackhat way will spin the content and shuffles all sentances allowing you to use this unique spun content in your links to your money website. The Whitehat way is an option to bring back all the h1 and h2 tags, the results of this is a list of all the topics that the top 100 articles for that keyword have covered.</description>
<category>Content Creator</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2018 21:53:30 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Content Creator scrapes the top 100 results from Google for your keyword then extracts all p tag contents and h2/h2 tags. Content and topic headings are then generated from this.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/hyalcLjL0uE?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Content Creator scrapes the top 100 results from Google for your keyword then extracts all p tag contents and h2/h2 tags. Content and topic headings are then generated from this.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Content Creator 1.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>SEO Plagiarism Checker 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4236-seo-plagiarism-checker.html</link>
<description>Name : SEO Plagiarism Checker Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : SEO Tools Price : $50 Homepage : SalePage SEO Plagiarism Checker is a desktop tool that will crawl your website checking every page&#039;s content to see if that content is elsewhere on the inte.com.</description>
<category>Plagiarism Checker</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 06:18:51 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features If another website is stealing your websites content then this is one of the fastest ways you can be notified of it. There are several reasons plagiarism can damage your website... - SEO damage - Although Google has repeatedly said there is no &quot;Duplicate content penalty&quot;, it has said it will filter out duplicate content. Imagine how frustrating it would be if you spent weeks working on an article only to publish it and have someone else copy it, then request Google to index it on their website through Google webmaster tools before the Google bot found the article on your website. Your brand new amazing article may be filtered out of Google&#039;s search results. - Brand damage - If someone copies your content then claims it&#039;s theirs this can greatly damage your brand. How do you prove you wrote it if they copy it straight away before Google indexes it? - Free backlinks - If someone has quoted/cited your content this can often be a great opportunity to get a backlink by reaching out to them and asking them to link to your in return for allowing them to use your content.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ho7L18g2Pno?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> If another website is stealing your websites content then this is one of the fastest ways you can be notified of it. There are several reasons plagiarism can damage your website...<br></li><li> - SEO damage - Although Google has repeatedly said there is no "Duplicate content penalty", it has said it will filter out duplicate content. Imagine how frustrating it would be if you spent weeks working on an article only to publish it and have someone else copy it, then request Google to index it on their website through Google webmaster tools before the Google bot found the article on your website. Your brand new amazing article may be filtered out of Google's search results.<br></li><li> - Brand damage - If someone copies your content then claims it's theirs this can greatly damage your brand. How do you prove you wrote it if they copy it straight away before Google indexes it?<br></li><li> - Free backlinks - If someone has quoted/cited your content this can often be a great opportunity to get a backlink by reaching out to them and asking them to link to your in return for allowing them to use your content.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="SEO Plagiarism Checker 1.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Spun By Google Content Spinner 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4233-spun-by-google-content-spinner.html</link>
<description>Name : Spun By Google Content Spinner Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Article Spinner Price : $0 Homepage : SalePage Spun By Google Article Spinner is an article spinner software tool that uses Google translate to spin your content so you know the result is grammatically correct well formed content in the eyes of Google. This free content spinning tool simply throws your content in and out of Google translate. There are different options for how many times you want it spun and how hard you want it spun. The content it generates is perfect for lower tires in tired link building campaigns and even expired web 2.0s. NOTE: Please do not use spun content on your main/money website it is against Google webmaster terms and can result in your website being deindexed.</description>
<category>Article Spinners</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 06:18:21 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features By throwing your content back and forth through Google translate it changes but is always kept gramatically correct due to Google&#039;s excellent translation service. You can spin the content up to 10 times and spin soft, medium or hard. You can also shuffle the sentances.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Dq1kGb3p7rY?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> By throwing your content back and forth through Google translate it changes but is always kept gramatically correct due to Google's excellent translation service. You can spin the content up to 10 times and spin soft, medium or hard. You can also shuffle the sentances.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Spun By Google Content Spinner 1.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Elite Content Creator 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4101-elite-content-creator.html</link>
<description>Name : Elite Content Creator Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Content Creator Price : $200 Homepage : SalePage Elite Content Creator is a windows desktop application that is capable of generating an unlimited amount of niche related high quality content for your website. You simply give it your keyword then sit back and let the unique high quality content be generated.</description>
<category>Content Creator</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 06:16:27 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features When you enter your keyword into Elite Content Creator it simply scrapes YouTube for videos related to your keyword (there are several filters so you can find just what you are looking for) for every video it finds it will rip/scrape the subtitles from. This content is not indexed by Google so you can use it freely without worry of duplicate content issues. This tool even has a built in uniqueness checker just to be sure no one else has used this tool on the same video and uploaded the content to their website or the YouTube uploader has a transcript of the video on their website. This tool will even punctuate the content for you, producing excellent high quality articles for your website. This tool is perfect for people who either want a high quaility content and articles for their white hat websites or people who want quality keyword and LSI rich content for the web 2.0s or PBNs. The quality of the content it produces is so good its also Adsense and Amazon safe. Writing quality content takes time and with this tool you can make use of the inte.coms largest gold mine of unindexed high quality content...YouTube.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/bdxaQ9WMMCA?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> When you enter your keyword into Elite Content Creator it simply scrapes YouTube for videos related to your keyword (there are several filters so you can find just what you are looking for) for every video it finds it will rip/scrape the subtitles from. This content is not indexed by Google so you can use it freely without worry of duplicate content issues. This tool even has a built in uniqueness checker just to be sure no one else has used this tool on the same video and uploaded the content to their website or the YouTube uploader has a transcript of the video on their website. This tool will even punctuate the content for you, producing excellent high quality articles for your website.<br></li><li> This tool is perfect for people who either want a high quaility content and articles for their white hat websites or people who want quality keyword and LSI rich content for the web 2.0s or PBNs. The quality of the content it produces is so good its also Adsense and Amazon safe. Writing quality content takes time and with this tool you can make use of the inte.coms largest gold mine of unindexed high quality content...YouTube.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Elite Content Creator 1.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Plagiarism Detector Pro 1.92</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4386-plagiarism-detector-pro.html</link>
<description>Name : Plagiarism Detector Pro Version : 1.0.92 OS : Windows Type : Software to Detect Plagiarism Price : $0 Homepage : SalePage Plagiarism Detector - is a Software to detect Plagiarism in online and offline documents: - Plagiarism Detector - is a Plagiarism Detection Software to check for Plagiarism in text documents. It is a fast and reliable Plagiarism Checker! - - Plagiarism Detector is a Microsoft Windows 10 (XP,Vista,7,8 etc.) desktop application to check sets of documents against the major search engines databases trying to locate the possible sources and define the exact amount of shared information. - - Plagiarism Detector&#039;s main task is the automated detection of digital plagiarism (that is unauthorized copy-paste of textual material) that originated from the world wide web. It was designed to use the biggest digital publicly open database in the world - that of the search engines. - - Plagiarism Detector has lots of features (see next page) that cover all possible situations when it comes to text comparison and search! - - Plagiarism Detector has won multiple Plagiarism Detection competitions in multiple countries. It has been recognized as one of the best available solutions for Plagiarism Detection and Prevention! - - Plagiarism Detector was built with KISS principle: structural complexity with functional simplicity!</description>
<category>Plagiarism Checker</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 08:11:33 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Plagiarism Detector honors your privacy: 1. Checked Documents do not leave your computer! 2. Reports are strictly private! 3. Checked Documents are not stored in any database! Plagiarism Detector works efficiently: 4. Works fast - less than 2 minutes per average document! 5. Your documents are checked immediately - no waiting in queue! 6. Checks are done against more than 7 billion on-line sources! Plagiarism Detector integrates easily with Microsoft products: 7. Microsoft WordPowerPoint &#039;single click&#039; plagiarism check. 8. Microsoft Word Integration. 9. Microsoft PowerPoint Integration. Plagiarism Detector has cool reporting capabilities: 10. State-of-art Advanced Report Viewer. 11. Extended Source Tracing Mechanism. 12. On-the-Fly Original to Source comparison with dynamic statistics. Plagiarism Detector supports multiple document formats: 11. *.pdf, *.doc, *.docx, *.html, *.txt, *.rtf, *.odt. 12. Microsoft Word versions from 2000 to 2017 (*.docx). 13. Microsoft PowerPoint versions from 2000 to 2017 (*.pptx). 14. Native PDF support - no 3rd party software required. 15. Multiple text extraction engines available to ensure correctness. 16. Automatic encoding detection. 17. Multiple encoding support for plain text documents. Plagiarism Detector has advanced functions: 18. 97% Effectiveness - No False Positives. 19. Automatic Reference Detection and processing. 20. Multiple documents processing. 21. Quotes detection algorithms. 22. PDF reports online converter. 23. Online Report Sharing. 24. Robust functions to run plagiarism checks easy and effective!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Plagiarism Detector honors your privacy:<br></li><li> 1. Checked Documents do not leave your computer!<br></li><li> 2. Reports are strictly private!<br></li><li> 3. Checked Documents are not stored in any database!<br></li><li> Plagiarism Detector works efficiently:<br></li><li> 4. Works fast - less than 2 minutes per average document!<br></li><li> 5. Your documents are checked immediately - no waiting in queue!<br></li><li> 6. Checks are done against more than 7 billion on-line sources!<br></li><li> Plagiarism Detector integrates easily with Microsoft products:<br></li><li> 7. Microsoft WordPowerPoint 'single click' plagiarism check.<br></li><li> 8. Microsoft Word Integration.<br></li><li> 9. Microsoft PowerPoint Integration.<br></li><li> Plagiarism Detector has cool reporting capabilities:<br></li><li> 10. State-of-art Advanced Report Viewer.<br></li><li> 11. Extended Source Tracing Mechanism.<br></li><li> 12. On-the-Fly Original to Source comparison with dynamic statistics.<br></li><li> Plagiarism Detector supports multiple document formats:<br></li><li> 11. *.pdf, *.doc, *.docx, *.html, *.txt, *.rtf, *.odt.<br></li><li> 12. Microsoft Word versions from 2000 to 2017 (*.docx).<br></li><li> 13. Microsoft PowerPoint versions from 2000 to 2017 (*.pptx).<br></li><li> 14. Native PDF support - no 3rd party software required.<br></li><li> 15. Multiple text extraction engines available to ensure correctness.<br></li><li> 16. Automatic encoding detection.<br></li><li> 17. Multiple encoding support for plain text documents. Plagiarism Detector has advanced functions:<br></li><li> 18. 97% Effectiveness - No False Positives.<br></li><li> 19. Automatic Reference Detection and processing.<br></li><li> 20. Multiple documents processing.<br></li><li> 21. Quotes detection algorithms.<br></li><li> 22. PDF reports online converter.<br></li><li> 23. Online Report Sharing.<br></li><li> 24. Robust functions to run plagiarism checks easy and effective!<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Plagiarism Detector Pro 1.92"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>The Journal 7.0.0.1099</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3932-the-journal.html</link>
<description>Name : The Journal Version : 7.0.0.1099 OS : Windows Type : Diary Software Price : $995 Homepage : SalePage You want to keep a diary. You want to write every day. With The Journal, you can! Whatever your journaling or writing needs, The Journal gives you unmatched convenience, flexibility, security, and reliability. The Journal is always available when you need it, and lets you make entries with text, photos, images, and just about anything else. Plus, The Journal’s optional password-protection and encryption ensure that your secrets remain secret. The Journal runs on any PC, laptop, notebook or tablet with Windows 10, Windows 8, Windows 7, Windows Vista, or Windows XP. Plus, with The Journal’s “Household License” you can use The Journal on any computer you own.</description>
<category>Content Creator</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 00:05:41 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features The Journal is Incredibly Easy to Use! - Make new entries easily! - Make entries on any date, at any time! - Review past entries with just a click on the calendar! - Runs on nearly all versions of Windows! - Search for anything, anywhere in your journal! The Journal is Both Powerful and Flexible! - Store anything! (text, digital photographs, videos, files…) - Doodle in your entries, or even edit photographs! - Print your entries for binding or sharing! - Set reminders for appointments, events, tasks &amp;amp; special days! - Be as organized as you want to be! The Journal is Secure! - Keep your secrets secret! - Be as secure as you want to be! - Full password protection! (But only if you want it.) - Want more than the default level of security? The Journals’ Extended Security features are also available to lock your journal up as tight as possible. The Journal is Reliable! - Your entries are automatically saved as you make them! - Built-in backup and restore! - Easily move The Journal to a new computer!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> The Journal is Incredibly Easy to Use!<br></li><li>  - Make new entries easily!<br></li><li>  - Make entries on any date, at any time!<br></li><li>  - Review past entries with just a click on the calendar!<br></li><li>  - Runs on nearly all versions of Windows!<br></li><li>  - Search for anything, anywhere in your journal!<br></li><li> The Journal is Both Powerful and Flexible!<br></li><li>  - Store anything! (text, digital photographs, videos, files…)<br></li><li>  - Doodle in your entries, or even edit photographs!<br></li><li>  - Print your entries for binding or sharing!<br></li><li>  - Set reminders for appointments, events, tasks &amp; special days!<br></li><li>  - Be as organized as you want to be!<br></li><li> The Journal is Secure!<br></li><li>  - Keep your secrets secret!<br></li><li>  - Be as secure as you want to be!<br></li><li>  - Full password protection! (But only if you want it.)<br></li><li>  - Want more than the default level of security? The Journals’ Extended Security features are also available to lock your journal up as tight as possible.<br></li><li> The Journal is Reliable!<br></li><li>  - Your entries are automatically saved as you make them!<br></li><li>  - Built-in backup and restore!<br></li><li>  - Easily move The Journal to a new computer!<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="The Journal 7.0.0.1099"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Dom Recovery 1.0.34.0 Pro</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1651-domrecovery.html</link>
<description>Name : Dom Recovery Version : 1.0.34.0 Pro OS : Windows Type : Keyword Research, Price : $97 Homepage : SalePage Ideal for PBN Domains Quickly and Easily build out PBN Domains for next level SEO In 2016 there is no alternative for a niche related PBN built with expired domains. With DomRecovery you can build out your PBN domains with relevant content within minutes instead of spending lots of time and money on new content and designs for each domain. Get aged unique content with minimal effort and time. DomRecovery is simple to use yet incredibly powerful software that can recover any website from the Wayback Machine making filling out your PBN websites quicker than it ever could be before. DomRecovery is an innovative new software that can be used to recover any website from the Inte.com Archive’s Wayback Machine* so that it can be re-uploaded and used again. The Wayback Machine* contains perfect copies of most websites online today and in the past so it is a great resource for checking what a website used to look like. This makes it perfect for recovering old versions of a website or for recovering past instances of a website. DomRecovery is the only tool capable of downloading websites from the Wayback Machine* in their entirety including layout, styles, content and images and any other media that has been archived with it.</description>
<category>Content Creator</category>
<enclosure url="http://domrecovery.com/assets/img/carousel-screeny.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 07:50:18 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Easy yet Customisable : Can recover a website by entering the domain but also offers lots of optional controls if required Very Fast : DomRecovery uses thread and sockets which means it is very fast to recover websites Unlimited Recoveries : Recover as many of your old websites as you need with no limits. Regular Upgrades : DomRecovery is regularly updated to add features and ensure smooth running. Professional Website Recovery : Download any website from Wayback Machine - Downloads all content from the wayback machine - Get all images, JS and stylesheets - Works for any website in the Wayback Machine - Fastest known method to save you time - Works for any website in the Wayback Machine Very Easy to Use Wizard Driven for Simplicity - Wizard makes everything as simple as possible - Optional controls for extra power - Can edit content for use on other domains - Maintains look and feel of original website</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ZbEuYqrp3FY?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><p><br></p><br><h3>Features</h3><br><p><br><ul><li> Easy yet Customisable : Can recover a website by entering the domain but also offers lots of optional controls if required<br></li><li> Very Fast : DomRecovery uses thread and sockets which means it is very fast to recover websites<br></li><li> Unlimited Recoveries : Recover as many of your old websites as you need with no limits.<br></li><li> Regular Upgrades : DomRecovery is regularly updated to add features and ensure smooth running.<br></li><li> Professional Website Recovery : Download any website from Wayback Machine<br></li><li> - Downloads all content from the wayback machine<br></li><li> - Get all images, JS and stylesheets<br></li><li> - Works for any website in the Wayback Machine<br></li><li> - Fastest known method to save you time<br></li><li> - Works for any website in the Wayback Machine<br></li><li> Very Easy to Use<br></li><li> Wizard Driven for Simplicity<br></li><li> - Wizard makes everything as simple as possible<br></li><li> - Optional controls for extra power<br></li><li> - Can edit content for use on other domains<br></li><li> - Maintains look and feel of original website<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://domrecovery.com/assets/img/carousel-screeny.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Dom Recovery 1.0.34.0 Pro"></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>