<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>SEO Script - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>SEO Script - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>ProRank 2.1.1</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2133-prorank.html</link>
<description>Name : ProRank - Analyzer stats website Version : 2.1.1 Type : Onpage SEO Script Price : $29 Homepage : Salepage Prorank Script is a tool to analyze websites to find weaknesses related to competition and make a suggestions to improve your website rankings. It also has a module for analysis of technologies used on the website. Prorank Script allows you to create a website in less than 5 minutes.</description>
<category>SEO Script</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 18:58:50 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Domain Authority Google Pagespeed Bounce Rate Meta Tags Analyzer Google Preview Estimation traffic and earnings * Unique visitors * Unique page views * Traffic statistics * Technologies analyzer Google, Yahoo and Bing index checker Speed and optimization tips Broken link checker Alexa rank with map Website score Social login Bookmark for register users Dashboard Panel Administrator Panel Responsive design Filter bad words Multi languages support (With auto translation Yandex) Ads Support Disqus comment on customs pages support Quick and easy installation Custom pages support SEO Friendly URL’s reCaptcha ready Some values are estimated with a professional algorithm</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<b>Features</b><br><ul><li> Domain Authority<br></li><li> Google Pagespeed<br></li><li> Bounce Rate<br></li><li> Meta Tags Analyzer<br></li><li> Google Preview<br></li><li> Estimation traffic and earnings *<br></li><li> Unique visitors *<br></li><li> Unique page views *<br></li><li> Traffic statistics *<br></li><li> Technologies analyzer<br></li><li> Google, Yahoo and Bing index checker<br></li><li> Speed and optimization tips<br></li><li> Broken link checker<br></li><li> Alexa rank with map<br></li><li> Website score<br></li><li> Social login<br></li><li> Bookmark for register users<br></li><li> Dashboard Panel<br></li><li> Administrator Panel<br></li><li> Responsive design<br></li><li> Filter bad words<br></li><li> Multi languages support (With auto translation Yandex)<br></li><li> Ads Support<br></li><li> Disqus comment on customs pages support<br></li><li> Quick and easy installation<br></li><li> Custom pages support<br></li><li> SEO Friendly URL’s<br></li><li> reCaptcha ready<br></li><li> Some values are estimated with a professional algorithm<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="ProRank 2.1.1"><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>SocioQuiz 2.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2138-socioquiz.html</link>
<description>Name : SocioQuiz - Viral Quiz website with Facebook login Version : 2.0 Type : Social Networking Script Price : $44 Homepage : Salepage SocioQuiz is a Viral Quiz website script that has full image/video and custom HTML support. It has more features than the quizzes on Playbuzz, Buzzfeed or other sites out there.</description>
<category>SEO Script</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 00:53:31 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<b>Features</b><br><img src="https://d1a6a9r46cnyll.cloudfront.com/cc55db06718129d19836bf8a4d4dc2d19a6c74d1/687474703a2f2f626f726e736f63696f2e636f6d2f6173736574732f736f63696f2d7175697a2f31302e706e67" style="max-width:100%;" alt="SocioQuiz 2.0"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""> <br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Social Ninja 2.8</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1571-social-ninja.html</link>
<description>Name : Social Ninja Version : 2.8 OS : Windows Type : Social Networking Script Price : $29 Homepage : SalePage Social Ninja - Facebook Twitter Youtube Campaigner Social Ninja is an app that can be used to schedule campaigns and create contents for your Facebook, Twitter and Youtube accounts. It offers a tool to upload contents in bulk in an organized fashion and schedule them to be posted later on your social profiles. Content creator will help you to create rich contents, edit photos and videos, download images and videos from inte.com to be used in your campaigns. Social Ninja is also capable of sorting out posts with negative feedbacks from your fans and automatically delete them based on your preferences.</description>
<category>SEO Script</category>
<enclosure url="https://1c5582f73d3fe9689a6e85f684ebae73d35c2d20.googledrive.com/host/0B34QQcRSxhm2X3VNN0ZETDZSbEU/showcase.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="https://1c5582f73d3fe9689a6e85f684ebae73d35c2d20.googledrive.com/host/0B34QQcRSxhm2X3VNN0ZETDZSbEU/banner1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2017 17:34:51 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<br><h3>Features</h3><br><img src="https://1c5582f73d3fe9689a6e85f684ebae73d35c2d20.googledrive.com/host/0B34QQcRSxhm2X3VNN0ZETDZSbEU/showcase.png" alt="Social Ninja 2.8"><br><img src="https://1c5582f73d3fe9689a6e85f684ebae73d35c2d20.googledrive.com/host/0B34QQcRSxhm2X3VNN0ZETDZSbEU/banner1.jpg" alt=""><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Facebook Business Scraper &amp; Page Analytics 2.2</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2132-facebook-business-scraper-page-analytics.html</link>
<description>Name : Facebook Business Scraper &amp;amp; Page Analytics Version : 2.2 Type : Facebook Search Script Price : $19 Homepage : Salepage A powerful facebook scraper to get facebook data such as page data by keyword, page data by location, group data, event data and user data. You will get major data including email (you will only get email in page search by keyword &amp;amp; group search). It has introduced facebook page insight (multi-page) feature from v2.0 It has built in support for 11 languages and you can add any language easily. It’s a multi-user SaaS application means you can resell the Software as a Service. PayPal &amp;amp; Stripe is integrated so that you can receive payment from your end users. If you want to use the SaaS features and charge your end user for using the service you have to buy extended license. Awesome website will be provided as a package with page search (Custom limit by you) feature, so that your visitors can test the system and system can collect emails of your visitors. Mailchimp is also integrated. Recently we have added advertise areas to front-end and advertise control in admin panel.</description>
<category>SEO Script</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2017 23:30:29 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Facebook page search by keyword Facebook page search by keyword, location and distance Facebook group search by keyword Facebook event search by keyword Facebook user search by keyword Facebook page insight (multi-page) page storytellers by story type page storytellers by user country page impression paid vs non-paid page impression organic page impression by user country page impression by user city page storyteller by user city page engaged users page consumption by type page positive feedback by type page negative feedback by type page fans online per day page fans by like source page likes vs unlikes page posts impressions page posts impressions paid vs organic page tab views page views by external referral Multilingual support (built-in support for 11 languages) Multi-user SaaS pack, membership package setting PayPal / Stripe integration and payment dashboard Lead collection and Mailchimp integration Responsive front-end and back-end Awesome dashboard Page search widget (embed HTML to your other websites) Advertise ready</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<b>Features</b><br><ul><li> Facebook page search by keyword<br></li><li> Facebook page search by keyword, location and distance<br></li><li> Facebook group search by keyword<br></li><li> Facebook event search by keyword<br></li><li> Facebook user search by keyword<br></li><li> Facebook page insight (multi-page)<br></li><li> page storytellers by story type<br></li><li> page storytellers by user country<br></li><li> page impression paid vs non-paid<br></li><li> page impression organic<br></li><li> page impression by user country<br></li><li> page impression by user city<br></li><li> page storyteller by user city<br></li><li> page engaged users<br></li><li> page consumption by type<br></li><li> page positive feedback by type<br></li><li> page negative feedback by type<br></li><li> page fans online per day<br></li><li> page fans by like source<br></li><li> page likes vs unlikes<br></li><li> page posts impressions<br></li><li> page posts impressions paid vs organic<br></li><li> page tab views<br></li><li> page views by external referral<br></li><li> Multilingual support (built-in support for 11 languages)<br></li><li> Multi-user SaaS pack, membership package setting<br></li><li> PayPal / Stripe integration and payment dashboard<br></li><li> Lead collection and Mailchimp integration<br></li><li> Responsive front-end and back-end<br></li><li> Awesome dashboard<br></li><li> Page search widget (embed HTML to your other websites)<br></li><li> Advertise ready<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Facebook Business Scraper &amp; Page Analytics 2.2"><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>AdLinkFly 3.5.2</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2131-adlinkfly.html</link>
<description>Name : AdLinkFly - M.comized URL Shortener Version : 3.5.2 Type : Short URL Script Price : $29 Homepage : Salepage Earn money by starting your own m.comized link shortening service, just like adf.ly adfly clone, ouo.io clone, linkshrink.com clone or shorte.st clone! Allow members to shorten links &amp;amp; earn money, and keep a share of the profit. AdLinkFly includes a complete publisher and advertiser system, campaigns, referrals, withdrawals, API, translation ready, PayPal, Payza, Bitcoin, Webmoney &amp;amp; Bank Transfer integration, reCAPTCHA integration and much more!</description>
<category>Clone Script</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2017 15:40:18 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features PUBLISHERS Publishers and you can earn money by showing ads when users click on shortened links Ability to change the CPM (Cost Per Mille, thousands) for each country Different ad types Interstitial ? Full page ad Banner ? 728?90, 468?60 &amp;amp; 336?280 No ad ? will work as redirect servise like bit.ly Publishers have access to a powerful dashboard Statistics sorted by Month &amp;amp; Year Auto-generated line graphs Can view, edit, and hide links ADVERTISER SYSTEM Each visitor you will purchase will meet the following criteria: Unique within a 24 hour time frame They are not using Adblocker extenstions They will have j&amp;#097;vascript enabled They will have Cookies enabled Must view your website for at least 5 seconds Advertisers can create campaigns for the below adertisments: Interstitial ? Full page ad Banner ? 728?90, 468?60 &amp;amp; 336?280 Pop Up Advertisers can select campaigns target sources like Desktop Mobile/tablests All sources Advertisers can pause, resume and monitor their campaigns PAYMENT GATEWAYS PayPal with sandbox support Payza Bitcoin WebMoney Bank Transfer And more is coming …. WITHDRAWAL SYSTEM Publishers can withdraw their earned profits using PayPal or Payza Turn off withdrawals if funds are low REFERRALS SYSTEM The AdLinkFly referral program is a great way to spread the word of this great service and to earn even more money with your short links! Refer friends and receive 20% of their earnings for life! MEMBERS SYSTEM visitors can sign up and activation e-mails will be sent out reCAPTCHA verification on reset password and signup pages Allow users to reset their passwords Allow users to change their email address Users can add add their billing information like first name, last name, address, country, city, state and phone number API TOOLS Quick Link: Everyone can use the shortest way to shorten links with AdLinkFly. Mass Shrinker: Enter up to 20 URLs (one per line) to be shrunk and added to your account Full Page Script: If you have a website with 100’s or 1000’s of links you want to change over to short then tool will be helpful for you. Developers API: For developers AdLinkFly prepared API which returns responses in JSON format. CAPTCHA SYSTEM Enable/Disable Captcha Enable/Disable on Short Links Page Enable/Disable on Signup Form Enable/Disable on Forgot Password Form TRANSLATION READY Easliy translate AdLinkFly to the language of your choice. MULTILINGUAL READY Visitors can choose ftheir language from the dropdown. PAGES You can add unlimited pages with the ability to edit and delete. GENERAL Multi domains for short links Testimonials system Support form for member area AdLinkFly includes two themes: Classic and Modern Ajax contact form. Copy button(No flash required anymore) for shotned links ADMINISTRATION PANEL Easily accessible &amp;amp; make users admins View site statistics on the dashboard Change website name &amp;amp; description Change default site language and timezone Add your website logo in two versions Enable/Disable Account Activation by Email Enable/Disable advertising features Change Referral Percentage earning Ability to add Head Code into front area pages Ability to add Head Code into Auth pages like signin, sinup, forgot password pages Ability to add Head Code into member area Ability to add Head Code into admin area Disallow certain domains from be shortened Change alias min length &amp;amp; max length Enable/Disable Interstitial Advertisement Enable/Disable Banner Advertisement Enable/Disable No Advert Set default advertisement type for anonymous and members Set counter value into short links pages Set Mass Shrinker Limit Admin can ads into various positions like: Member Area Captcha page Interstitial Page Ad: This ad will be displayed between logo and counter. Banner 728?90 Banner 468?60 Banner 336?280 Ability to change currency code Ability to change Currency symbol Ability to ad Facebook Page URL Ability to ad Twitter Profile URL Ability to ad Google Plus URL SMTP email support Ability to filter campaigns Ability to filter users Ability to filter links</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<b>Features</b><br><br><br>PUBLISHERS<br><br>Publishers and you can earn money by showing ads when users click on shortened links<br>Ability to change the CPM (Cost Per Mille, thousands) for each country<br>Different ad types<br>Interstitial ? Full page ad<br>Banner ? 728?90, 468?60 &amp; 336?280<br>No ad ? will work as redirect servise like bit.ly<br>Publishers have access to a powerful dashboard<br>Statistics sorted by Month &amp; Year<br>Auto-generated line graphs<br>Can view, edit, and hide links<br>ADVERTISER SYSTEM<br><br>Each visitor you will purchase will meet the following criteria:<br>Unique within a 24 hour time frame<br>They are not using Adblocker extenstions<br>They will have j&#097;vascript enabled<br>They will have Cookies enabled<br>Must view your website for at least 5 seconds<br>Advertisers can create campaigns for the below adertisments:<br>Interstitial ? Full page ad<br>Banner ? 728?90, 468?60 &amp; 336?280<br>Pop Up<br>Advertisers can select campaigns target sources like<br>Desktop<br>Mobile/tablests<br>All sources<br>Advertisers can pause, resume and monitor their campaigns<br>PAYMENT GATEWAYS<br><br>PayPal with sandbox support<br>Payza<br>Bitcoin<br>WebMoney<br>Bank Transfer<br>And more is coming ….<br>WITHDRAWAL SYSTEM<br><br>Publishers can withdraw their earned profits using PayPal or Payza<br>Turn off withdrawals if funds are low<br>REFERRALS SYSTEM<br><br>The AdLinkFly referral program is a great way to spread the word of this great service and to earn even more money with your short links! Refer friends and receive 20% of their earnings for life!<br><br>MEMBERS SYSTEM<br><br>visitors can sign up and activation e-mails will be sent out<br>reCAPTCHA verification on reset password and signup pages<br>Allow users to reset their passwords<br>Allow users to change their email address<br>Users can add add their billing information like first name, last name, address, country, city, state and phone number<br>API TOOLS<br><br>Quick Link: Everyone can use the shortest way to shorten links with AdLinkFly.<br>Mass Shrinker: Enter up to 20 URLs (one per line) to be shrunk and added to your account<br>Full Page Script: If you have a website with 100’s or 1000’s of links you want to change over to short then tool will be helpful for you.<br>Developers API: For developers AdLinkFly prepared API which returns responses in JSON format.<br>CAPTCHA SYSTEM<br><br>Enable/Disable Captcha<br>Enable/Disable on Short Links Page<br>Enable/Disable on Signup Form<br>Enable/Disable on Forgot Password Form<br>TRANSLATION READY<br><br>Easliy translate AdLinkFly to the language of your choice.<br><br>MULTILINGUAL READY<br><br>Visitors can choose ftheir language from the dropdown.<br><br>PAGES<br><br>You can add unlimited pages with the ability to edit and delete.<br><br>GENERAL<br><br>Multi domains for short links<br>Testimonials system<br>Support form for member area<br>AdLinkFly includes two themes: Classic and Modern<br>Ajax contact form.<br>Copy button(No flash required anymore) for shotned links<br>ADMINISTRATION PANEL<br><br>Easily accessible &amp; make users admins<br>View site statistics on the dashboard<br>Change website name &amp; description<br>Change default site language and timezone<br>Add your website logo in two versions<br>Enable/Disable Account Activation by Email<br>Enable/Disable advertising features<br>Change Referral Percentage earning<br>Ability to add Head Code into front area pages<br>Ability to add Head Code into Auth pages like signin, sinup, forgot password pages<br>Ability to add Head Code into member area<br>Ability to add Head Code into admin area<br>Disallow certain domains from be shortened<br>Change alias min length &amp; max length<br>Enable/Disable Interstitial Advertisement<br>Enable/Disable Banner Advertisement<br>Enable/Disable No Advert<br>Set default advertisement type for anonymous and members<br>Set counter value into short links pages<br>Set Mass Shrinker Limit<br>Admin can ads into various positions like:<br>Member Area<br>Captcha page<br>Interstitial Page Ad: This ad will be displayed between logo and counter.<br>Banner 728?90<br>Banner 468?60<br>Banner 336?280<br>Ability to change currency code<br>Ability to change Currency symbol<br>Ability to ad Facebook Page URL<br>Ability to ad Twitter Profile URL<br>Ability to ad Google Plus URL<br>SMTP email support<br>Ability to filter campaigns<br>Ability to filter users<br>Ability to filter links<br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="AdLinkFly 3.5.2"><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Twitter Manager Standalone Script 3.01</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2141-twitter-manager-standalone-script.html</link>
<description>Name : Twitter Manager Standalone Script Version : 3.01 Type : Social Networking Script Price : $19 Homepage : Salepage Get ready to skyrocket your twitter followers. This php script developed for php/mysql based hostining account takes keywords, hashtags and Twitter ID’s you enter and gets you the most targeted followers imaginable. All of this happens automatically after you take 30 minutes to install and setup the module. Just think, 24 hours a day this module goes out and and finds you followers.</description>
<category>SEO Script</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 19:24:38 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Automatically follow twitter users Automatically unfollow people who do not follow you Find twitter users by keyword, hashtag or snipe users from competitors Watch your twitter follower growth in real time. The Twitter Manager script Logs section allows you to see the history of follows and unfollows for a specific account. Additionally you can view the activity of your cronjob and see how your twitter account (following vs. followers) look over time in line chart form. Below is a sample snapshot from a real Twitter Manager report. Longterm results you can count on When you build a follower base you need long term retention. The user targeting capabilities of the Twitter Manager Script allows you to find your exact target market and build your folower base from that group. Lets take a dieting website as an example. We can enter diet, dieting, #diet, #dieting in this module, it will run every time you set it up to run, and it will find people who are posting tweets based on diet, dieting or with the hashtags. It then follows those users. Those users then follow you back. You can gain 10’s, Hundreds and in cases thousands of followers every day using our Twitter Manager. That is just the beginning, The twitter Manager manages the people who do not follow you back, lets you search twitter directly from the module, shows logs of all activity and much more. Our success is based on our customer satisfaction. Our support team is dedicated to helping clients solve any issues they might experience. We are long time developers with an impeccable record of developing enterprise applications for clients around the world. The products we have here are time tested by us and are used on a daily basis by all our direct clients.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<b>Features</b><br><ul><li> Automatically follow twitter users<br></li><li> Automatically unfollow people who do not follow you<br></li><li> Find twitter users by keyword, hashtag or snipe users from competitors<br></li><li> Watch your twitter follower growth in real time. The Twitter Manager script Logs section allows you to see the history of follows and unfollows for a specific account. Additionally you can view the activity of your cronjob and see how your twitter account (following vs. followers) look over time in line chart form. Below is a sample snapshot from a real Twitter Manager report.<br></li><li> Longterm results you can count on<br></li><li> When you build a follower base you need long term retention. The user targeting capabilities of the Twitter Manager Script allows you to find your exact target market and build your folower base from that group.<br></li><li> Lets take a dieting website as an example. We can enter diet, dieting, #diet, #dieting in this module, it will run every time you set it up to run, and it will find people who are posting tweets based on diet, dieting or with the hashtags. It then follows those users. Those users then follow you back. You can gain 10’s, Hundreds and in cases thousands of followers every day using our Twitter Manager. That is just the beginning, The twitter Manager manages the people who do not follow you back, lets you search twitter directly from the module, shows logs of all activity and much more.<br></li><li> Our success is based on our customer satisfaction. Our support team is dedicated to helping clients solve any issues they might experience. We are long time developers with an impeccable record of developing enterprise applications for clients around the world. The products we have here are time tested by us and are used on a daily basis by all our direct clients.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Twitter Manager Standalone Script 3.01"> <br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Twitter Analytics Multi Accounts 1.1</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2140-twitter-analytics-multi-accounts.html</link>
<description>Name : Twitter Analytics Multi Accounts Version : 1.1 Type : Social Networking Script Price : $19 Homepage : Salepage You’re statistically analyze your twitter account. Twitter Analytics Multi Accounts will help you this. To help you have a clearer view of your account and opponents to take measures to promote more efficient. Moreover if you manage multiple accounts Twitter Analytics Multi Accounts will help you in a simple way and without having to log in multiple times.</description>
<category>SEO Script</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 19:23:42 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features ANALYTICS TWEETS – Tweet history: Statistics of tweets by day. – Users most retweeted: Top 10 users most retweeted. – Users most mentioned: Top 10 users most mentioned. – Hashtags most used: Top 10 hashtags most used. – Days of the week and Hours of the day: Statistics tweets per day and hours of the day – Platforms most tweeted from: Statistics tweets per day and hours of the day. ANALYTICS MENTIONS – Mentions: Twitter users who mentioned you in their tweets. – Most influential users: Users with the highest number of followers. – Most engaging users: Top users by number of favorites generated by their tweets mentioning you. – Most active users: Top 10 hashtags most used. – Top hashtags: The hashtags most often used in tweets mentioning you. – Days of the week: Day of the week people mentioned you the most. – Hours of the day: Time of the day people mentioned you the most. ANALYTICS RETWEETS – Retweets: Your tweets retweeted by other Twitter users. – Have been favorite: Proportion of retweeted tweets that have been favorited. – Are repliess: Proportion of retweeted tweets that are replies. – Include mentions: Proportion of retweeted tweets that include at least one mention. – Include links: Proportion of retweeted tweets that include at least one link. – Include hashtags: Proportion of retweeted tweets that include at least one hashtag. ANALYTICS FOLLOWERS Browse, search, filter, get insights on the people who follow you ANALYTICS RETWEETS Browse, search, filter and get insights on the people you are following</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<b>Features</b><br>ANALYTICS TWEETS<br><br>– Tweet history: Statistics of tweets by day.<br>– Users most retweeted: Top 10 users most retweeted.<br>– Users most mentioned: Top 10 users most mentioned.<br>– Hashtags most used: Top 10 hashtags most used.<br>– Days of the week and Hours of the day: Statistics tweets per day and hours of the day<br>– Platforms most tweeted from: Statistics tweets per day and hours of the day.<br>ANALYTICS MENTIONS<br><br>– Mentions: Twitter users who mentioned you in their tweets.<br>– Most influential users: Users with the highest number of followers.<br>– Most engaging users: Top users by number of favorites generated by their tweets mentioning you.<br>– Most active users: Top 10 hashtags most used.<br>– Top hashtags: The hashtags most often used in tweets mentioning you.<br>– Days of the week: Day of the week people mentioned you the most.<br>– Hours of the day: Time of the day people mentioned you the most.<br>ANALYTICS RETWEETS<br><br>– Retweets: Your tweets retweeted by other Twitter users.<br>– Have been favorite: Proportion of retweeted tweets that have been favorited.<br>– Are repliess: Proportion of retweeted tweets that are replies.<br>– Include mentions: Proportion of retweeted tweets that include at least one mention.<br>– Include links: Proportion of retweeted tweets that include at least one link.<br>– Include hashtags: Proportion of retweeted tweets that include at least one hashtag.<br>ANALYTICS FOLLOWERS<br><br>Browse, search, filter, get insights on the people who follow you<br>ANALYTICS RETWEETS<br><br>Browse, search, filter and get insights on the people you are following<br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Twitter Analytics Multi Accounts 1.1"> <br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Turbo Spinner 1.4</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2139-turbo-spinner.html</link>
<description>Name : Turbo Spinner: Article Rewriter Version : 1.4 Type : Article Rewriter Script Price : $20 Homepage : Salepage Turbo Spinner is a advanced automatic article spinner can instantly rewrite any data into SEO friendly unique content. Helps to avoid duplicate content penalties from search engines. It comes with API Access, Therefore you can generate unlimited SEO friendly unique content from any platform. Sell your API keys to your client and manage via admin panel. Mostly turbo spinner rewrite text can be human readable text and 100% unique from other services. So, very useful for mass posting blog and web services.</description>
<category>SEO Script</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 19:22:50 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features - Built in synonyms database - Spintax Support. - 6 languages Support [English, Dutch, French, Spanish, Germany, Turkish]. - Limit the homepage spin per visitors. - API Access Support - Rewrite from any where using API - Unlimited spinned articles - Secure captcha protection system - Support HTML document and produce HTML output - Human readable output - API Sample’s included (C# and PHP) - API credit checker - Full control over synonyms databases - Add your own synonyms to database - Full tracking of API Access - Create unlimited custom pages - Contact page for visitors - Powerful admin control panel - Clean and responsive design layout - One-Click Ads integration - and many more included….</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<b>Features</b><br>- Built in synonyms database<br>- Spintax Support. <br>- 6 languages Support [English, Dutch, French, Spanish, Germany, Turkish].<br>- Limit the homepage spin per visitors.<br>- API Access Support <br>- Rewrite from any where using API<br>- Unlimited spinned articles<br>- Secure captcha protection system<br>- Support HTML document and produce HTML output<br>- Human readable output<br>- API Sample’s included (C# and PHP)<br>- API credit checker<br>- Full control over synonyms databases<br>- Add your own synonyms to database<br>- Full tracking of API Access<br>- Create unlimited custom pages<br>- Contact page for visitors<br>- Powerful admin control panel<br>- Clean and responsive design layout<br>- One-Click Ads integration <br>- and many more included….<br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Turbo Spinner 1.4"> <br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>SiteSpy 3.3</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2137-sitespy.html</link>
<description>Name : SiteSpy - Complete Visitor &amp;amp; SEO Analytics Version : 3.3 Type : SEO Script, Ratings and Charts Price : $30 Homepage : Salepage Complete visitor and SEO anlytics package including visitor analytics (unique visitor, page view, bounce rate, average stay time, average visit, traffic analysis, top refferer, new &amp;amp; returning visitor, content overview, country &amp;amp; browser report, os &amp;amp; device report etc.) , web analytics (alexa data,similarWeb data, whois data, social media data, moz check, dmoz check, search engine index, google page rank, IP analysis, malware check ) , SEO tools (link analysis, keyword position analysis, auto keyword suggestion,page status check, backlink creation/search, website ping, google adword scraper etc.) You will also get several bonus utility tools such as email encoder/decoder, metatag generator, ogtag generator, plgiarism check, valid email check, duplicate email filter, url encode/decode, robot code generator etc. It?s a multi-user SaaS application means you can resell the Software as a Service. PayPal &amp;amp; Stripe are integrated so that you can receive payment from your end users. If you want to use the SaaS features and charge your end user for using the service you have to buy extended license. It has native API by which developers can integrate it’s facilities with another app. Nice colorful widgets are available. You can simply copy &amp;amp; paste some line of codes to any page you want and can display site information.</description>
<category>Clone Script</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 19:21:02 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Visitor Analytics : own site Unique Visitor Page View Bounce Rate Average Stay Time Average Visit Traffic Analysis Top Refferer New &amp;amp; Returning Visitor Content Overview Country &amp;amp; Browser Report OS &amp;amp; Device Report Website Analytics : any site (pdf report) Whois Info MOZ Info, DMOZ Listing Google Back Link IP Info Malware Scan Report Search Engine Index Social Network Traffic Keyword &amp;amp; Meta Info Alexa Info SimilarWeb Info Mobile Friendly Check Social Network Analysis (SEO Tool) Facebook Like, Share, Comment Google+ Comment LinkedIn, Xing, Buffer Share Reddit Score, Up, Down Pinterest Pin StumbleUpon List,View, Like, Comment Rank &amp;amp; Index Analysis (SEO Tool) Alexa Rank/Data SimilarWeb Rank &amp;amp; Data MOZ Check Google Index Yahoo Index Bing Index Domain Analysis (SEO Tool) Whois Search Data DMOZ Directory Listing Expired (Auction) Domain List IP Analysis (SEO Tool) What is my IP Domain IP Information Sites in Same IP IPv6 Compatibility Check Keyword Analysis (SEO Tool) Keyword Analyzer Keyword Position &amp;amp; Suggestion Correlated Trending Keywords Backlink &amp;amp; Ping (SEO Tool) Google Backlink Search Backlink Generator Website/Blog Ping Malware Scan (SEO Tool) Google Safe Browser Norton,McAfee,AVG Link Analysis (SEO Tool) Link Analyzer Page Status Check Google Adwords Scraper (SEO Tool) get paid google adwards links Google URL Shortener (SEO Tool) Google URL Shortener (bulk) Shortened URL Analytics (graphical) Code Minifier (SEO Tool) HTML Minifer CSS Minifier j&amp;#097;vascript Minifier Bonus Utilities (Utility Tool) Email Encoder/ Decoder URL Encoder/ Decoder Meta Tag Generator Robot Code Generator Plagiarism Check (unicode support) Valid Email Check Duplicate Email Filter Native API (25 APIs) + Native Widget (3 Widgets) Use our awesome native APIS And Widgets Responsive design Social login (Google + Facebook) Dashboard of Recent Activities Multilingual Use awesome services in your own language Multi-user, SaaS Pack, PayPal + Stripe Create packages, resell awesome services, setup your business and receive payment via PayPal / Stripe.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<b>Features</b><br><ul><li> Visitor Analytics : own site<br></li><li> Unique Visitor<br></li><li> Page View<br></li><li> Bounce Rate<br></li><li> Average Stay Time<br></li><li> Average Visit<br></li><li> Traffic Analysis<br></li><li> Top Refferer<br></li><li> New &amp; Returning Visitor<br></li><li> Content Overview<br></li><li> Country &amp; Browser Report<br></li><li> OS &amp; Device Report<br></li><li> <br></li><li> Website Analytics : any site (pdf report)<br></li><li> Whois Info<br></li><li> MOZ Info, DMOZ Listing<br></li><li> Google Back Link<br></li><li> IP Info<br></li><li> Malware Scan Report<br></li><li> Search Engine Index<br></li><li> Social Network Traffic<br></li><li> Keyword &amp; Meta Info<br></li><li> Alexa Info<br></li><li> SimilarWeb Info<br></li><li> Mobile Friendly Check<br></li><li> <br></li><li> Social Network Analysis (SEO Tool)<br></li><li> Facebook Like, Share, Comment<br></li><li> Google+ Comment<br></li><li> LinkedIn, Xing, Buffer Share<br></li><li> Reddit Score, Up, Down<br></li><li> Pinterest Pin<br></li><li> StumbleUpon List,View, Like, Comment<br></li><li> <br></li><li> Rank &amp; Index Analysis (SEO Tool)<br></li><li> Alexa Rank/Data<br></li><li> SimilarWeb Rank &amp; Data<br></li><li> MOZ Check<br></li><li> Google Index<br></li><li> Yahoo Index<br></li><li> Bing Index<br></li><li> <br></li><li> Domain Analysis (SEO Tool)<br></li><li> Whois Search Data<br></li><li> DMOZ Directory Listing<br></li><li> Expired (Auction) Domain List<br></li><li> <br></li><li> IP Analysis (SEO Tool)<br></li><li> What is my IP<br></li><li> Domain IP Information<br></li><li> Sites in Same IP<br></li><li> IPv6 Compatibility Check<br></li><li> <br></li><li> Keyword Analysis (SEO Tool)<br></li><li> Keyword Analyzer<br></li><li> Keyword Position &amp; Suggestion<br></li><li> Correlated Trending Keywords<br></li><li> <br></li><li> Backlink &amp; Ping (SEO Tool)<br></li><li> Google Backlink Search<br></li><li> Backlink Generator<br></li><li> Website/Blog Ping<br></li><li> <br></li><li> Malware Scan (SEO Tool)<br></li><li> Google Safe Browser<br></li><li> Norton,McAfee,AVG<br></li><li> <br></li><li> Link Analysis (SEO Tool)<br></li><li> Link Analyzer<br></li><li> Page Status Check<br></li><li> <br></li><li> Google Adwords Scraper (SEO Tool)<br></li><li> get paid google adwards links<br></li><li> Google URL Shortener (SEO Tool)<br></li><li> Google URL Shortener (bulk)<br></li><li> Shortened URL Analytics (graphical)<br></li><li> <br></li><li> Code Minifier (SEO Tool)<br></li><li> HTML Minifer<br></li><li> CSS Minifier<br></li><li> j&#097;vascript Minifier<br></li><li> <br></li><li> Bonus Utilities (Utility Tool)<br></li><li> Email Encoder/ Decoder<br></li><li> URL Encoder/ Decoder<br></li><li> Meta Tag Generator<br></li><li> Robot Code Generator<br></li><li> Plagiarism Check (unicode support)<br></li><li> Valid Email Check<br></li><li> Duplicate Email Filter<br></li><li> <br></li><li> Native API (25 APIs) + Native Widget (3 Widgets)<br></li><li> Use our awesome native APIS And Widgets <br></li><li> <br></li><li> Responsive design <br></li><li> <br></li><li> Social login (Google + Facebook) <br></li><li> <br></li><li> Dashboard of Recent Activities <br></li><li> <br></li><li> Multilingual<br></li><li> Use awesome services in your own language <br></li><li> <br></li><li> Multi-user, SaaS Pack, PayPal + Stripe<br></li><li> Create packages, resell awesome services, setup your business and receive payment via PayPal / Stripe.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="SiteSpy 3.3"> <br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>SiteDoctor 1.2</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2136-sitedoctor.html</link>
<description>Name : SiteDoctor - website health checker Version : 1.2 Type : Onpage SEO Script Price : $19 Homepage : Salepage SideDoctor can check your website’s health status within a minute. Follow the suggestion provided by the SiteDoctor and make your site more SEO friendly. SiteDoctor will analysis all metrics of your website such as title, description, keyword, tag, page size, page speed, server status, compression status, mobile friendly status, image/css/javacript status and many more other important metrics of your website. It has built in support for 11 languages and you can add any language easily. Awesome website will be provided and system collects emails of your visitors. Mailchimp is also integrated.</description>
<category>Clone Script</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 19:17:55 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Website health checker Google page speed insight Google mobile ready Website health comparison PDF report generation (own branding) Lead collection and Mailchimp integration Advertise ready Multilingual Powerful dashboard with visitor info Unique visitor Page view Average stay time Average visit Bounce rate Traffic source Visitor type Country-wise report Browser report OS report Device report 100% responsive design and many more Health check metrics Page title Page meta keyword Page meta description Keyword usage Text/HTML ratio robot.txt Sitemap Internal vs external links NoIndex, noFollow, doFollow links SEO friendly link Favicon Image alt text Doc type Depreciated HTML tag HTML page size Inline CSS Internal CSS Micro data scheme test IP &amp;amp; DNS report IP canonicalization test URL canonicalization test Plain text email test cURL response Mobile friendly check Page speed Usability score Avoid install interstitials that hide content Avoid plugins Configure viewport Size content to viewport Size tap target Landing page redirects GZIP compression Leverage browsing caching Server reponse time Minify CSS Minify HTML Minify j&amp;#097;vascript Render-blocking j&amp;#097;vascript &amp;amp; CSS Optimize Images Priotirize visible content</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<b>Features</b><br><ul><li> Website health checker<br></li><li> Google page speed insight<br></li><li> Google mobile ready<br></li><li> Website health comparison<br></li><li> PDF report generation (own branding)<br></li><li> Lead collection and Mailchimp integration<br></li><li> Advertise ready<br></li><li> Multilingual<br></li><li> Powerful dashboard with visitor info<br></li><li> Unique visitor<br></li><li> Page view<br></li><li> Average stay time<br></li><li> Average visit<br></li><li> Bounce rate<br></li><li> Traffic source<br></li><li> Visitor type<br></li><li> Country-wise report<br></li><li> Browser report<br></li><li> OS report<br></li><li> Device report<br></li><li> 100% responsive design and many more<br></li></ul><br>Health check metrics<br><ul><li> Page title<br></li><li> Page meta keyword<br></li><li> Page meta description<br></li><li> Keyword usage<br></li><li> Text/HTML ratio<br></li><li> robot.txt<br></li><li> Sitemap<br></li><li> Internal vs external links<br></li><li> NoIndex, noFollow, doFollow links<br></li><li> SEO friendly link<br></li><li> Favicon<br></li><li> Image alt text<br></li><li> Doc type<br></li><li> Depreciated HTML tag<br></li><li> HTML page size<br></li><li> Inline CSS<br></li><li> Internal CSS<br></li><li> Micro data scheme test<br></li><li> IP &amp; DNS report<br></li><li> IP canonicalization test<br></li><li> URL canonicalization test<br></li><li> Plain text email test<br></li><li> cURL response<br></li><li> Mobile friendly check<br></li><li> Page speed<br></li><li> Usability score<br></li><li> Avoid install interstitials that hide  content<br></li><li> Avoid plugins<br></li><li> Configure viewport<br></li><li> Size content to viewport<br></li><li> Size tap target<br></li><li> Landing page redirects<br></li><li> GZIP compression<br></li><li> Leverage browsing caching<br></li><li> Server reponse time<br></li><li> Minify CSS<br></li><li> Minify HTML<br></li><li> Minify j&#097;vascript<br></li><li> Render-blocking j&#097;vascript &amp; CSS<br></li><li> Optimize Images<br></li><li> Priotirize visible content<br><br></li></ul><br><img src="https://d1a6a9r46cnyll.cloudfront.com/1971b04b7f7fbc240e841be9a56c28b048071398/687474703a2f2f7865726f6e6569742e6e65742f64656d6f2f73697465646f635f656e7661746f5f696d6167652f707265766965772e706e67" alt="SiteDoctor 1.2"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>