<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Group Buy - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Group Buy - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>Keyword Tool.io (Pro+) Annual</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4150-keyword-toolio-pro-annual.html</link>
<description>GB Name : Keyword Tool.io (Pro+) Annual Version : Last OS : Anything Type : Keyword Research Tools GB Price : $845/Y GB Cost : 42$/20 Peoples + 4$ Fee GB Joined : 15/20 Peoples GB Status : Going Homepage : SalePage Keyword Tool Pro Is The Fastest Way To Discover Thousands Of Keywords Hidden By Google Keyword Planner And Research Using Search Volume, Competition Level And Cost-Per-Click Data.</description>
<category>GB Spy Tools</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 23:47:00 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Search Volume Data Cost-Per-Click Data AdWords Competition Data 2 Times More Keywords Competitor Keyword Analysis Bulk Search Volume Analysis</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/wCj3U823MSY?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Search Volume Data 			<br></li><li> Cost-Per-Click Data 			<br></li><li> AdWords Competition Data 			<br></li><li> 2 Times More Keywords 			<br></li><li> Competitor Keyword Analysis 			<br></li><li> Bulk Search Volume Analysis <br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Keyword Tool.io (Pro+) Annual"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Go by VideoRemix + OTOs [Delivering]</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4332-videoremix.html</link>
<description>GB Name : Go by VideoRemix - Smart video 2 + OTOs Version : Last OS : Anything Type : Personalized Video Creator GB Price : $47 (FE) + $444(OTO1) + $27(OTO2) + $97(OTO3) + $197(OTO4) = $812 GB Cost : 54.1$/15 Peoples + 4.4$ Fee GB Joined : 10/15 Peoples GB Status : Going Homepage : SalePage Go by VideoRemix makes personalized video marketing easier than ever. Utilizing a simplified editor and robust DFY templates, you can quickly and easily create personalized campaigns to boost conversions, engagement, and sales. No need to fuss with complex timelines or messy merge tokens. Instead,</description>
<category>GB App Tools</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 03:27:16 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FE - VideoRemix - $47 You already know that VideoRemix stands for quality QUALITY. The second you see how easy GO is to use, you’ll know for certain that this is going to be one of your most profitable launches EVER. And we’re throwing EVERYTHING in (including over $35,000 in NO MINIMUMS prizes!) to make sure that on the 5th of June, we will be putting more money in your pocket than any other launch around. [Funnel Graphic] OTO#1: Go by VideoRemix Template Generator - $37/m With Over 450+ Pure Quality Base Level Videos Over 70+ Different Niche Scripts Over 50+ Different Audio Tracks OTO#2: Go by VideoRemix CTA Library - $27 Prominent. So that they receive maximum attention and visual focus. Recognizable. So that your message doesn’t get lost in a fog of creativity and your CTAs are instantly recognizable as something viewers are meant to click on. Well-Defined. With plenty of ‘breathing room’ (or ‘negative space if we’re going to be all technical), stark outlines, shadows and contrasting colors to define and add appeal. Striking. Your CTA must stand out; it should call out “Hey, I’m here, you know you wanna’ click me!” to the user. Appealing. Our designers have done the hard work, so you don’t have to.Your CTA’s will draw people to them. Colors, image and typeface are expertly mixed together to create appeal. Clear. Every CTA in our library has an obvious thrust. The user wants — needs — to know what will happen if he or she clicks your CTA button. Your CTAs will perfectly match what your visitors anticipate. Use active verbs. Your CTAs are powerful and motion-oriented. It’s a call to ACTION, after all. Communicate Value. You’re asking users to act, so your CTAs make your visitors understand that they’ll get something worthwhile in return. Any action online is an investment of time and effort, so the ROI must be apparent. Provide Assurance. Building trust is a MASSIVE part of conversions. Trust signals are just as important in CTAs as they are in VSL scripts and copy. OTO#3: Go by VideoRemix Complete Done-For-You Fast Track To Success - $97 Your Professionally Designed To Convert, Ready-to-Go Website And Landing Pages: $1997 3 Personalized And Editable Video Commercials Designed Especially For You To Sell GO. $1997 White Label Webinar $2,997 and a LOT of extra sales! A whole Suite Of Upload and Print-Ready Graphics $1497 High Converting Killer Powerpoint Presentation &amp;amp; Proposal. $997 Ready-To-Mail E-Mail Autoresponder Series (With Maximum Click-ability). $997 Ready Made Social Media Posts: FB, Twitter and Instagram $297 Pimped-to-Sell Telemarketing Scripts $997 (And Invaluable To Your Business!) A carbon copy of the ready to use proposal that one of our clients used to close over $45,000 in deals. (AND a step by step guide to how he did it). OTO#4: Go by VideoRemix Masterclass Coaching Call - $197 YOUR PERSONAL GUIDE TO TOP LEVEL SUCCESS WITH GO THE RESULTS AND PROFITS ARE YOURS TO GAIN. Set You On Your Perfect Path To Secure Your Very First Client In Just 7 Days</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ivCJBltvYUc?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><a href="https://secure.videoremix.io/go/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>FE - VideoRemix - </b></a><br><ul><li> You already know that VideoRemix stands for quality QUALITY. The second you see how easy GO is to use, you’ll know for certain that this is going to be one of your most profitable launches EVER. <br></li><li> And we’re throwing EVERYTHING in (including over ,000 in NO MINIMUMS prizes!) to make sure that on the 5th of June, we will be putting more money in your pocket than any other launch around. [Funnel Graphic] <br></li></ul><br><a href="https://secure.videoremix.io/gooto1/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO#1: Go by VideoRemix Template Generator - /m</b></a><br><ul><li> With Over 450+ Pure Quality Base Level Videos <br></li><li> Over 70+ Different Niche Scripts<br></li><li> Over 50+ Different Audio Tracks <br></li></ul><br><a href="https://secure.videoremix.io/gooto2/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO#2: Go by VideoRemix CTA Library - </b></a><br><ul><li> Prominent. So that they receive maximum attention and visual focus.  <br></li><li> Recognizable. So that your message doesn’t get lost in a fog of creativity and your CTAs are instantly recognizable as something viewers are meant to click on.  <br></li><li> Well-Defined. With plenty of ‘breathing room’ (or ‘negative space if we’re going to be all technical), stark outlines, shadows and contrasting colors to define and add appeal.   <br></li><li> Striking. Your CTA must stand out; it should call out “Hey, I’m here, you know you wanna’ click me!” to the user.  <br></li><li> Appealing. Our designers have done the hard work, so you don’t have to.Your CTA’s will draw people to them. Colors, image and typeface are expertly mixed together to create appeal.  <br></li><li> Clear. Every CTA in our library has an obvious thrust. The user wants — needs — to know what will happen if he or she clicks your CTA button. Your CTAs will perfectly match what your visitors anticipate. <br></li><li> Use active verbs. Your CTAs are powerful and motion-oriented. It’s a call to ACTION, after all.  <br></li><li> Communicate Value. You’re asking users to act, so your CTAs make your visitors understand that they’ll get something worthwhile in return. Any action online is an investment of time and effort, so the ROI must be apparent.  <br></li><li> Provide Assurance. Building trust is a MASSIVE part of conversions. Trust signals are just as important in CTAs as they are in VSL scripts and copy. <br></li></ul><br><a href="https://secure.videoremix.io/gooto3/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO#3: Go by VideoRemix Complete Done-For-You Fast Track To Success - </b></a><br><ul><li> Your Professionally Designed To Convert, Ready-to-Go Website And Landing Pages:	97<br></li><li> 3 Personalized And Editable Video Commercials Designed Especially For You To Sell GO.	97<br></li><li> White Label Webinar	,997 and a LOT of extra sales!<br></li><li> A whole Suite Of Upload and Print-Ready Graphics	97<br></li><li> High Converting Killer Powerpoint Presentation &amp; Proposal.	7<br></li><li> Ready-To-Mail E-Mail Autoresponder Series (With Maximum Click-ability).	7<br></li><li> Ready Made Social Media Posts: FB, Twitter and Instagram	7<br></li><li> Pimped-to-Sell Telemarketing Scripts	7 (And Invaluable To Your Business!)<br></li><li> A carbon copy of the ready to use proposal that one of our clients used to close over ,000 in deals. (AND a step by step guide to how he did it).<br><br></li></ul><br><a href="https://secure.videoremix.io/gooto4/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO#4: Go by VideoRemix Masterclass Coaching Call - 7</b></a><br><ul><li> YOUR PERSONAL GUIDE TO TOP LEVEL SUCCESS WITH GO<br></li><li> THE RESULTS AND PROFITS ARE YOURS TO GAIN. <br></li><li> Set You On Your Perfect Path To Secure Your Very First Client In Just 7 Days<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Go by VideoRemix + OTOs [Delivering]"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>LeadPrimo + OTOs</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4532-leadprimo-otos.html</link>
<description>GB Name : LeadPrimo + OTOs Version : Last OS : Anything Type : Email Marketing Software GB Price : $47(FE) + $77(OTO1) + $97(OTO2) + $97(OTO3) + $324/y(OTO4) = $642 GB Cost : 32.4$/20 peoples + 2.6$ Fee GB Joined : 10/20 Peoples GB Status : Going Homepage : SalePage LeadPrimo is a All-In-One Email Marketing Software that makes everything simple and easy, you can enjoy maximum delivery, capture and import unlimited lists and make use of all other features that our IM space needs as it creates high converting lead pages, boost leads, commissions, webinar registrations and ultimately get more profits on complete autopilot. It is completely newbie friendly and enable your subscribers to get THOUSANDS of Leads, send UNLIMITED emails, as well as follow-up with all the leads automatically and manage them without any complex issues. They can also see the complete real-time activity of subscribers, and find out which particular campaigns are giving best results. So, provide your subscribers with the untapped power to turn leads into buyers to get best results from the Email Marketing activities. With LeadPrimo, it is a SIMPLE and EASY 3 step method that goes like this-</description>
<category>GB Requests</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 03:24:11 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FE - LeadPrimo Pro - $47 1. 20 eye-catchy templates to create high converting lead pages. 2. Get direct views and leads from Facebook by adding your page as page tab. 3. By default, 1 list – All Subscribers. 4. Add subscribers. 5. Subscriber management. 6. Newsletter. 7. 1 email template. 8. Google, Yahoo, Hotmail - FREE mailing. 9. SMTP Mailing - SMTP mailing setup allowed. 10. 5 web-form templates with editor – inline editor. 11. 1 Sub-Domain / Business only. 12. Unlimited mailing per month. 13. Stats and Much More. OTO1 - LeadPrimo Elite - $77 1. Get 30 extra, Inbuilt eye-catching lead page templates to maximize lead generation. 2. Multiple List. 3. Advanced Subscriber management – suppression list, message wise, bounce wise, export, create custom fields. 4. 20 email templates. 5. Advanced messages management – use message again. 6. 10 form templates with editor. 7. Integrations – Webinars. 8. API – Integrate with any software. 9. Media Library. OTO2 - LeadPrimo Enterprise - $97 1. Complete lead Page real time statistics. 2. Autoresponder. 3. Advance Statistics. 4. Bounce management. 5. Advanced List management. 6. Advance Subscriber management – copy &amp;amp; move contacts. 7. Integrations – CRM. 8. Team management up-to 5 members. 9. 30 email templates. 10. 15 form templates with editor. OTO3 - LeadPrimo Reseller - $97 This is a mind-blowing deal as we are providing RESELLER license to LeadPrimo, and now your subscribers can SELL LeadPrimo to anyone they want &amp;amp; they get to KEEP 100% of the PROFITS. They don&#039;t have to do anything, just collect their 100% profit and find a way to spend it. OTO4 - Premium Membership - $324/y 1. 5 Brand New Lead-Page Templates Every Month. 2. 10 brand new eye- catchy &amp;amp; premium email templates delivered every month. 3. 5 web form templates with editor each month. 4. Create Multiple autoresponders for multiple businesses. 5. Ultra-Fast Servers for faster mail delivery. 6. Premium support. 7. Regular Updates. 8. Unlimited members team management. 9. Library with UNLIMITED Hosting on FAST servers &amp;amp; 200GB bandwidth per month.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br><a href="https://www.leadprimo.com/jv/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>FE - LeadPrimo Pro - </b></a><br><ul><li> 1. 20 eye-catchy templates to create high converting lead pages.<br></li><li> 2. Get direct views and leads from Facebook by adding your page as page tab.<br></li><li> 3. By default, 1 list – All Subscribers.<br></li><li> 4. Add subscribers.<br></li><li> 5. Subscriber management.<br></li><li> 6. Newsletter.<br></li><li> 7. 1 email template.<br></li><li> 8. Google, Yahoo, Hotmail - FREE mailing.<br></li><li> 9. SMTP Mailing - SMTP mailing setup allowed.<br></li><li> 10. 5 web-form templates with editor – inline editor.<br></li><li> 11. 1 Sub-Domain / Business only.<br></li><li> 12. Unlimited mailing per month.<br></li><li> 13. Stats and Much More.<br></li></ul><br><a href="https://www.leadprimo.com/jv/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO1 - LeadPrimo Elite - </b></a><br><ul><li> 1. Get 30 extra, Inbuilt eye-catching lead page templates to maximize lead generation.<br></li><li> 2. Multiple List.<br></li><li> 3. Advanced Subscriber management – suppression list, message wise, bounce wise, export, create custom fields.<br></li><li> 4. 20 email templates.<br></li><li> 5. Advanced messages management – use message again.<br></li><li> 6. 10 form templates with editor.<br></li><li> 7. Integrations – Webinars.<br></li><li> 8. API – Integrate with any software.<br></li><li> 9. Media Library.<br></li></ul><br><a href="https://www.leadprimo.com/jv/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO2 - LeadPrimo Enterprise - </b></a><br><ul><li> 1. Complete lead Page real time statistics.<br></li><li> 2. Autoresponder. <br></li><li> 3. Advance Statistics.<br></li><li> 4. Bounce management.<br></li><li> 5. Advanced List management.<br></li><li> 6. Advance Subscriber management – copy &amp; move contacts.<br></li><li> 7. Integrations – CRM.<br></li><li> 8. Team management up-to 5 members.<br></li><li> 9. 30 email templates.<br></li><li> 10. 15 form templates with editor.<br></li></ul><br><a href="https://www.leadprimo.com/jv/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO3 - LeadPrimo Reseller - </b></a><br><ul><li> This is a mind-blowing deal as we are providing RESELLER license to LeadPrimo, and now your subscribers can SELL LeadPrimo to anyone they want &amp; they get to KEEP 100% of the PROFITS. They don't have to do anything, just collect their 100% profit and find a way to spend it.<br></li></ul><br><a href="https://www.leadprimo.com/jv/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO4 - Premium Membership - 4/y</b></a><br><ul><li> 1. 5 Brand New Lead-Page Templates Every Month.<br></li><li> 2. 10 brand new eye- catchy &amp; premium email templates delivered every month.<br></li><li> 3. 5 web form templates with editor each month.<br></li><li> 4. Create Multiple autoresponders for multiple businesses.<br></li><li> 5. Ultra-Fast Servers for faster mail delivery.<br></li><li> 6. Premium support.<br></li><li> 7. Regular Updates.<br></li><li> 8. Unlimited members team management.<br></li><li> 9. Library with UNLIMITED Hosting on FAST servers &amp; 200GB bandwidth per month.<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="LeadPrimo + OTOs"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>LetSlotio + OTOs</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4529-letslotio-otos.html</link>
<description>GB Name : LetSlotio + OTOs Version : Last OS : Anything Type : SaaS Web App GB Price : $47(FE) + $67(OTO1) + $67(OTO2) + $77(OTO3) = $258 GB Cost : 17.5$/15 peoples + 1.5$ Fee GB Joined : 10/15 Peoples GB Status : Going Homepage : SalePage Just like LetSpin.io, LetSlot.io is a Full Featured Lead Generation Platform (SaaS Web App) that Leverages the Power of Gamification to Use the Inherent Human Curiosity of Playing &amp;amp; Winning Gifts in a Slot Machine.</description>
<category>GB Requests</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 03:23:56 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FE - LetSlotio Elite - $47 Outcome Weightage (Intelligent Wheel) Fully Customizable Slot Machine Shopify Plugin Wordpress Plugin Express Shopify Checkout Plugin AutoResponders Integration Webinars Integration Basic Email Validation Customisable Form Builder Scarcity Bar and Countdown Timer 5 Domain License Unlimited Optins Built in Library Youzign Integration Zapier Integration Campaign Level Integration Slot Icon Pack Live Campaign/ Slot Machine Preview Advance Show up Conditions (On Page Load, On Exit, X Time on Page, X Percentage of Scroll) Display URL Targeting Mobile Optimised Slot Machine Multiple Action Types on Win (Redirect URL, Close Popup, Reirect URL in New Tab, Copy Coupon) Leads Export as CSV File In Depth Training Sound and Basic Animation GDPR Complaint OTO1 - LetSlotio Platinum - $67 Outsourcer License with Unlimited Users &amp;amp; Access Level Roles Reminder Widget Follow Up Widget Advanced Show Up Conditions for Desktop (After X Time on Page, After X % Scroll, Load Up Widget) Advanced Show Up Conditions for Mobile (After X Time on Page, After X % Scroll, Load Up Widget) Advanced Display URL Targeting (Exclude URL &amp;amp; Referral URL conditions) Detailed Reporting (Export as CSV and PDF) Show LetSlot Machine on Click and Load Up Widget Customizable Floating Widget One Click Clone Campaigns Campaign Specific Multi Action Automations Slot Machine Animations Daily/Weekly Email Reports Repeat Show up Conditions Lead Generation Masterclass OTO2 - LetSlotio Booster - $67 Lander Win on Multiple Spins Detailed Reporting and Stats (Booster) Social Share User Card Add any Retargeting Pixel OTO3 - LetSlotio Jacker - $77 Run LetSlot Campaigns on Any Third Party Website WhitelabelDomain Name Detailed Reporting and Stats (Jacker) Detailed Reporting and Stats (Jacker) Commercial License Unlimited Domain License Removable Branding FullContact Integration Facebook &amp;amp; other Social Media Sharing Customizable Emoji Integration Done for you Lead Ma.com Vault</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/73VKreV2S4Y?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><a href="http://jvpartners.letx.co/letslotio/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>FE - LetSlotio Elite - </b></a><br><ul><li> Outcome Weightage (Intelligent Wheel) <br></li><li> Fully Customizable Slot Machine<br></li><li> Shopify Plugin<br></li><li> Wordpress Plugin<br></li><li> Express Shopify Checkout Plugin<br></li><li> AutoResponders Integration<br></li><li> Webinars Integration<br></li><li> Basic Email Validation <br></li><li> Customisable Form Builder<br></li><li> Scarcity Bar and Countdown Timer<br></li><li> 5 Domain License<br></li><li> Unlimited Optins<br></li><li> Built in Library<br></li><li> Youzign Integration<br></li><li> Zapier Integration <br></li><li> Campaign Level Integration <br></li><li> Slot Icon Pack <br></li><li> Live Campaign/ Slot Machine Preview <br></li><li> Advance Show up Conditions (On Page Load, On Exit, X Time on Page, X Percentage of Scroll)<br></li><li> Display URL Targeting<br></li><li> Mobile Optimised Slot Machine<br></li><li> Multiple Action Types on Win (Redirect URL, Close Popup, Reirect URL in New Tab, Copy Coupon) <br></li><li> Leads Export as CSV File <br></li><li> In Depth Training<br></li><li> Sound and Basic Animation  <br></li><li> GDPR Complaint <br></li></ul><br><a href="http://jvpartners.letx.co/letslotio/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO1 - LetSlotio Platinum - </b></a><br><ul><li> Outsourcer License with Unlimited Users &amp; Access Level Roles<br></li><li> Reminder Widget<br></li><li> Follow Up Widget <br></li><li>  Advanced Show Up Conditions for Desktop (After X Time on Page, After X % Scroll, Load Up Widget)<br></li><li>  Advanced Show Up Conditions for Mobile (After X Time on Page, After X % Scroll, Load Up Widget)<br></li><li> Advanced Display URL Targeting (Exclude URL &amp; Referral URL conditions) <br></li><li> Detailed Reporting (Export as CSV and PDF) <br></li><li> Show LetSlot Machine on Click and Load Up Widget <br></li><li> Customizable Floating Widget<br></li><li> One Click Clone Campaigns<br></li><li> Campaign Specific Multi Action Automations <br></li><li>  Slot Machine Animations<br></li><li> Daily/Weekly Email Reports <br></li><li> Repeat Show up Conditions <br></li><li> Lead Generation Masterclass<br></li></ul><br><a href="http://jvpartners.letx.co/letslotio/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO2 - LetSlotio Booster - </b></a><br><ul><li> Lander <br></li><li> Win on Multiple Spins<br></li><li> Detailed Reporting and Stats (Booster)  <br></li><li> Social Share<br></li><li> User Card<br></li><li> Add any Retargeting Pixel<br></li></ul><br><a href="http://jvpartners.letx.co/letslotio/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO3 - LetSlotio Jacker - </b></a><br><ul><li> Run LetSlot Campaigns on Any Third Party Website <br></li><li> WhitelabelDomain Name  <br></li><li> Detailed Reporting and Stats (Jacker) <br></li><li> Detailed Reporting and Stats (Jacker) <br></li><li> Commercial License <br></li><li> Unlimited Domain License <br></li><li> Removable Branding  <br></li><li> FullContact Integration <br></li><li> Facebook &amp; other Social Media Sharing Customizable  <br></li><li> Emoji Integration  <br></li><li> Done for you Lead Ma.com Vault<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="LetSlotio + OTOs"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Links Robot + OTOs [Instant Deliver]</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4251-links-robot-otos.html</link>
<description>GB Name : Links Robot + OTOs Version : Last OS : Anything Type : SEO Tools (301 Redirector, Directory Submit, Social BookMark) GB Price : $67(FE) + $97(OTO1) + $47(OTO4) = $211 GB Cost : 21.1$/10 Peoples + 1.9$ Fee GB Joined : 8/10 Peoples GB Status : Delivered Homepage : SalePage LinksRobot creates 500+ redirect backlinks within 3 clicks for Unlimited number of websites, videos, and URLs.</description>
<category>GB App Tools</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 15:17:08 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FE - Links Robot - $77 500+ Authority Backlinks Automated 1-Click Link Builder Permanent &amp;amp; Dofollow Links Add Unlimited Projects Built-in Pinger No Captchas or Proxies! Whitelabel Reports Web-based SEO Software OTO1 - Social Ranker - $97 Social Backlinks - 200+ Unique Websites! Unlimited Campaigns - NO LIMITS! Whitelabel Reports - For Yourself &amp;amp; Clients! 95% Success Rate - For literally ANY URL! Drip Feed - Safe &amp;amp; Natural Link Building Built-in Pinger - Click &amp;amp; Done! 100% Automated - No Captchas, No Proxies! OTO2 - 301 Ranker Pro - $47 Social Backlinks - 200+ Unique Websites! Unlimited Campaigns - NO LIMITS! Whitelabel Reports - For Yourself &amp;amp; Clients! 95% Success Rate - For literally ANY URL! Drip Feed - Safe &amp;amp; Natural Link Building Built-in Pinger - Click &amp;amp; Done! 100% Automated - No Captchas, No Proxies! OTO3 - LinkIndexr - $47 Social Backlinks - 200+ Unique Websites! Unlimited Campaigns - NO LIMITS! Whitelabel Reports - For Yourself &amp;amp; Clients! 95% Success Rate - For literally ANY URL! Drip Feed - Safe &amp;amp; Natural Link Building Built-in Pinger - Click &amp;amp; Done! 100% Automated - No Captchas, No Proxies! OTO4 - Directory Submiter - $47 Members area 1 Click submission Instant reports Approval emails 300+ Directories Higher rankings</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/T_EG271ZQkU?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><a href="http://linksrobot.co/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>FE  - Links Robot - </b></a><br><ul><li> 500+ Authority Backlinks<br></li><li> Automated 1-Click Link Builder<br></li><li> Permanent &amp; Dofollow Links<br></li><li> Add Unlimited Projects<br></li><li> Built-in Pinger<br></li><li> No Captchas or Proxies!<br></li><li> Whitelabel Reports<br></li><li> Web-based SEO Software<br></li></ul><br><a href="http://linksrobot.co/special/oto.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO1 - Social Ranker - </b></a><br><ul><li> Social Backlinks - 200+ Unique Websites!<br></li><li> Unlimited Campaigns - NO LIMITS!<br></li><li> Whitelabel Reports - For Yourself &amp; Clients!<br></li><li> 95% Success Rate - For literally ANY URL!<br></li><li> Drip Feed - Safe &amp; Natural Link Building<br></li><li> Built-in Pinger - Click &amp; Done!<br></li><li> 100% Automated - No Captchas, No Proxies!<br></li></ul><br><a href="http://linksrobot.co/special/otospecial.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO2 - 301 Ranker Pro - </b></a><br><ul><li> Social Backlinks - 200+ Unique Websites!<br></li><li> Unlimited Campaigns - NO LIMITS!<br></li><li> Whitelabel Reports - For Yourself &amp; Clients!<br></li><li> 95% Success Rate - For literally ANY URL!<br></li><li> Drip Feed - Safe &amp; Natural Link Building<br></li><li> Built-in Pinger - Click &amp; Done!<br></li><li> 100% Automated - No Captchas, No Proxies!<br></li></ul><br><a href="http://linksrobot.co/special/oto2.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO3 - LinkIndexr - </b></a><br><ul><li> Social Backlinks - 200+ Unique Websites!<br></li><li> Unlimited Campaigns - NO LIMITS!<br></li><li> Whitelabel Reports - For Yourself &amp; Clients!<br></li><li> 95% Success Rate - For literally ANY URL!<br></li><li> Drip Feed - Safe &amp; Natural Link Building<br></li><li> Built-in Pinger - Click &amp; Done!<br></li><li> 100% Automated - No Captchas, No Proxies!<br></li></ul><br><br><a href="http://directorysubmiter.com/special.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO4 - Directory Submiter - </b></a><br><ul><li> Members area<br></li><li> 1 Click submission<br></li><li> Instant reports<br></li><li> Approval emails<br></li><li> 300+ Directories<br></li><li> Higher rankings<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Links Robot + OTOs [Instant Deliver]"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Article Genie + OTOs [Delivering]</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4092-article-genie-otos.html</link>
<description>GB Name : Article Genie + OTOs Version : Last OS : Anything Type : Create Content Software GB Price : $16.93(FE) + $37(OTO1) + $47(OTO2) + $127(OTO3) = $227.93 GB Cost : 11.5$/20 Peoples + 1$ Fee GB Joined : 16/20 Peoples GB Status : Going Homepage : SalePage Article Genie is a powerful software that enables your customers and subscribers to create unique content that they can sell on sites like Freelancer, Upwork, Fiverr &amp;amp; Many More! On top of all that, they can use to their own advantage, in their owns sites and online businesses!</description>
<category>GB App Tools</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 06:01:50 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FE - Article Genie - $16.93 Article Genie Software - Enables them to create unique content with the push of a button! OTO1 - Article Genie Upgrade - $37 A full training and extra features that will take Article Genie to the next level! OTO2 - Article Genie Club - $47 1,900 HD &amp;amp; 4K Stock Videos that they can sell for huge profits! OTO3 - Article Genie Reseller License - $127 Reseller Rights to Article Genie</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/KHluCtsp-bE?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><a href="https://offer.getarticlegenie.com/jv/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>FE - Article Genie - .93</b></a><br><ul><li> Article Genie Software - Enables them to create unique content with the push of a button!<br></li></ul><br><a href="https://offer.getarticlegenie.com/jv/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO1 - Article Genie Upgrade - </b></a><br><ul><li> A full training and extra features that will take Article Genie to the next level! <br></li></ul><br><a href="https://offer.getarticlegenie.com/jv/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO2 - Article Genie Club - </b></a><br><ul><li> 1,900 HD &amp; 4K Stock Videos that they can sell for huge profits! <br></li></ul><br><a href="https://offer.getarticlegenie.com/jv/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO3 - Article Genie Reseller License - 7</b></a><br><ul><li> Reseller Rights to Article Genie<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Article Genie + OTOs [Delivering]"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Stop Motion Creator + OTOs</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4517-stopmotioncreator-otos.html</link>
<description>GB Name : Stop Motion Creator + OTOs Version : Last OS : Anything Type : Video Creater Tool GB Price : $67(FE) + $67(OTO1) + $67(OTO2) + $67(OTO3) = $268 GB Cost : 26.8$/10 Peoples + 2.2$ Fee GB Joined : 6/10 Peoples GB Status : Going Homepage : SalePage EyeCatching &quot;Stop Motion&quot; Videos in 3 Simple Steps With The World&#039;s First Automated Stop Motion Video Creator</description>
<category>GB App Tools</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 05:57:58 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FE - Stop Motion Creator - $57 Quality product Our team is known for producing quality software. This software is no different and that is very same devs who coded our other great software Customer Support We now have 6 full time support team which is helping customers of our product so you known your buyers are in the good hands Attractive Audience This is the very same target andience as for a few other launch with combined over $3m sales Huge Commissions As will all our launches we are looking for above $11 across the funnel OTO1 - Stop Motion Creator Pro - $67 Fully control every second of each video and add stop motions to the parts of the video that you want. And do it as many times as you want! Full Pro Level Editing At Your Fingertips! OTO2 - Stop Motion Creater Pro Templates - $67 3,000 hand-selected marketing videos 100 markets and categories covered 100% Royalty-Free use them as much as you want. $25 worth each with unlimited use license 100% HD Quality in all the videos included. OTO3 - Stop Motion Traffic - $67 POST : Publish directly to up to 17 Social Media Networks at a time for instant traffic SCHEDULE : Schedule Your automated traffic for continous unlimited free traffic PREVIEW : Post text, links, and your StopMotionVideo for each social.comwork LIVE DATA : Count each and every click, comment and visitor from each and every post AUTOMATIC : The more you automate, the more traffic you get. Let StopMotionCreator Traffic get you traffic. UNLIMITED : There is NO LIMITS to the number of posts and accounts you can connect.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/mkqKMkhf4m0?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><a href="http://jv.stopmotioncreator.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>FE - Stop Motion Creator - </b></a><br><ul><li> Quality product<br></li><li> Our team is known for producing quality software. This software is no different and that is very same devs who coded our other great software<br></li><li> Customer Support<br></li><li> We now have 6 full time support team which is helping customers of our product so you known your buyers are in the good hands<br></li><li> Attractive Audience<br></li><li> This is the very same target andience as for a few other launch with combined over m sales<br></li><li> Huge Commissions<br></li><li> As will all our launches we are looking for above  across the funnel<br></li></ul><br><a href="http://jv.stopmotioncreator.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO1 - Stop Motion Creator Pro - </b></a><br><ul><li> Fully control every second of each video and add stop motions to the parts of the video that you want.<br></li><li> And do it as many times as you want!<br></li><li> Full Pro Level Editing At Your Fingertips!<br></li></ul><br><a href="http://jv.stopmotioncreator.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO2 - Stop Motion Creater Pro Templates - </b></a><br><ul><li> 3,000 hand-selected marketing videos <br></li><li> 100 markets and categories covered<br></li><li> 100% Royalty-Free use them as much as you want.<br></li><li>  worth each with unlimited use license<br></li><li> 100% HD Quality in all the videos included.<br></li></ul><br><a href="http://jv.stopmotioncreator.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO3 - Stop Motion Traffic - </b></a><br><ul><li> </li><li> POST : Publish directly to up to 17 Social Media Networks at a time for instant traffic  <br></li><li> SCHEDULE : Schedule Your automated traffic for continous unlimited free traffic <br></li><li> PREVIEW : Post text, links, and your StopMotionVideo for each social.comwork  <br></li><li> LIVE DATA : Count each and every click, comment and visitor from each and every post  <br></li><li> AUTOMATIC : The more you automate, the more traffic you get. Let StopMotionCreator Traffic get you traffic. <br></li><li> UNLIMITED : There is NO LIMITS to the number of posts and accounts you can connect.<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Stop Motion Creator + OTOs"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>BuddyAd Native Annual</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4523-buddyad-native.html</link>
<description>GB Name : BuddyAd Native Version : Last OS : Anything Type : Native Ads Spy GB Price : $1359/y GB Cost : 94$/15 Peoples + 8$ Fee GB Joined : 10/15 Peoples GB Status : Going Homepage : SalePage #1 Widget-Based Spy Tool with Native, Pop and Adult Widget/Site ID Finder since 2016</description>
<category>GB Spy Tools</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 05:57:48 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FE - BuddyAd Native - $1359/y Native Spy Tool (widget based) All the features that you would expect from a spy tool.. and more! Widget IDs on Adult, Pop and Native Traffic BuddyAd is the only tool that can match a widget or site ID with the relative publisher IF it is on our db. We are constantly scanning the web for more placements, as well as constantly adding more.comworks and geos to our platform. Native Real Time Scan Not sure that your native campaign is properly running? Monitor your campaign and check if your banners are running on a particular website or widget ID (if we have it on our database) using our Real Time Scan. Get rid of bad placements. Content Recommendation Networks display your ads on thousands of websites. BuddyAd lets you discover premium placements with great quality of traffic so that you can avoid having your ads running on poor websites. We support BIG traffic sources.. and a few super-vertical ones! At BuddyAd we believe in traffic. That&#039;s why we included some of the major traffic sources and content recommendation.comworks out there including RevContent, Taboola, OutBrain, AdNow, Content.ad, MGID, Yahoo Gemini, ExoClick, PropellerAds, Reporo, Popcash and more.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/PdN-eXUWXvU?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><a href="http://buddyad.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>FE - BuddyAd Native  - 59/y</b></a><br><ul><li> Native Spy Tool (widget based)<br></li><li> All the features that you would expect from a spy tool.. and more!<br></li><li> Widget IDs on Adult, Pop and Native Traffic<br></li><li> BuddyAd is the only tool that can match a widget or site ID with the relative publisher IF it is on our db. We are constantly scanning the web for more placements, as well as constantly adding more.comworks and geos to our platform.<br></li><li> Native Real Time Scan<br></li><li> Not sure that your native campaign is properly running? Monitor your campaign and check if your banners are running on a particular website or widget ID (if we have it on our database) using our Real Time Scan.<br></li><li> Get rid of bad placements.<br></li><li> Content Recommendation Networks display your ads on thousands of websites. BuddyAd lets you discover premium placements with great quality of traffic so that you can avoid having your ads running on poor websites.<br></li><li> We support BIG traffic sources..<br></li><li> and a few super-vertical ones!<br></li><li> At BuddyAd we believe in traffic. That's why we included some of the major traffic sources and content recommendation.comworks out there including RevContent, Taboola, OutBrain, AdNow, Content.ad, MGID, Yahoo Gemini, ExoClick, PropellerAds, Reporo, Popcash and more. <br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="BuddyAd Native Annual"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Pintra + OTOs</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4525-pintra-otos.html</link>
<description>GB Name : Pintra + OTOs Version : Last OS : Anything Type : Pinterest Wordpress Software GB Price : $27(FE) + $32(OTO1) + $37(OTO2) + $27(OTO3) + $97(OTO4) = $220 GB Cost : 11$/20 peoples + 1$ Fee GB Joined : 0/20 Peoples GB Status : Going Homepage : SalePage Inside Pintra we show you a way to get Free traffic by posting content that is relevant to your niche and help you generate leads and sales, using our software and over the shoulder&#039;s training, in 3 easy steps. Instead of slaving away trying to manually post new content to your new niche blog, or to create a high-traffic Pinterest account, or even spending a small fortune on paid ads… We&#039;ve developed a fully Automated &quot;One Click&quot; Pinterest Wordpress Software. We have also included inside exclusive Video Training To Maximize your Profits With Pinterest and Wordpress, Quickly &amp;amp; Easily by Finding Great Content Online and Posting it in Seconds! Our Software will Post Images, ,Full Blog Posts, Certain Features and More With One Click!</description>
<category>GB WordPress</category>
<enclosure url="https://i.imgur.com/OmmYCST.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="https://i.imgur.com/kJy8kQl.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="https://i.imgur.com/egJHecV.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="https://i.imgur.com/vfT9KFE.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 05:57:31 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>[mdeia=https://youtu.be/MEPbPsvfqpw] Features FE - Pintra Empire - $27 You can also Create Proper Links that &quot;Source Back&quot; to the original content taken! We also show you how to copywrite your content to Avoid the dreaded Google Slap! We take you by the hand and show you how you can Easily Generate Your Own Niche Blog With Amazing Content You Can M.comize! This means more Targeted Traffic to Your Ecom Store, Affiliate Offers, or Create More Leads! Our Easy To Follow “Over The Shoulder” Training That Covers Everything You’ll Need! Anyone can do this, easily, and effortlessly. This is for the experienced, advanced and newbie in mind. You can get started without any experience, but it&#039;s also made for the advanced user too. As a marketer, blogger or ecommerce website owner you want to be able to generate the most targeted traffic you can, as well as the most ideal content, FAST &amp;amp; EASILY. Luckily for you, we’ve taken all the headaches and hassles out of tapping into the traffic and content goldmine that is and simplified the entire process for you… Perfect for: eCom, CPA Marketing, Affiliate Marketing, List building. You can create a sustainable income depending on the work you put out and the content you bring out should be consistent and persistent. OTO1 - Pintra Scheduler - $32 OTO2 - Pintra Expansion - $37 OTO3 - Pintra Robo - $27 OTO4 - Pintra Fusion - $97</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;">[mdeia=https://youtu.be/MEPbPsvfqpw]</div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><a href="https://www.d-papa.com/pintrajvs" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>FE - Pintra Empire - </b></a><br><ul><li> You can also Create Proper Links that "Source Back" to the original content taken!  <br></li><li> We also  show you how to copywrite your content  to Avoid the dreaded Google Slap!    We take you by the hand and show you how you can Easily Generate Your Own Niche Blog With Amazing Content You Can M.comize!  <br></li><li> This means more  Targeted Traffic to Your Ecom Store, Affiliate Offers, or Create More Leads!<br></li><li> Our Easy To Follow “Over The Shoulder” Training That Covers Everything You’ll Need!<br></li><li> Anyone can do this, easily, and effortlessly.<br></li><li> This is for the experienced, advanced and newbie in mind.<br></li><li> You can get started without any experience, but it's also made for the advanced user too.  <br></li><li> As a marketer, blogger or ecommerce website owner you want to be able to generate the most targeted traffic you can, as well as the most ideal content,  FAST &amp; EASILY.<br></li><li> Luckily for you, we’ve taken all the headaches and hassles out of tapping into the traffic and content goldmine that is and simplified the entire process for you… <br></li><li> Perfect for: eCom, CPA Marketing, Affiliate Marketing, List building.  <br></li><li> You can create a sustainable income depending on the work you put out and the content you bring out should be consistent and persistent.    <br></li></ul><br><a href="https://www.d-papa.com/pintrajvs" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO1 - Pintra Scheduler - </b></a><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="https://i.imgur.com/OmmYCST.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Pintra + OTOs"></div><br><br><a href="https://www.d-papa.com/pintrajvs" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO2 - Pintra Expansion - </b></a><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="https://i.imgur.com/kJy8kQl.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""></div><br><br><a href="https://www.d-papa.com/pintrajvs" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO3 - Pintra Robo - </b></a><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="https://i.imgur.com/egJHecV.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""></div><br><br><a href="https://www.d-papa.com/pintrajvs" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO4 - Pintra Fusion - </b></a><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="https://i.imgur.com/vfT9KFE.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""></div><br><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Dropified Unlimited Annual</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4513-dropified-unlimited.html</link>
<description>GB Name : Dropified Unlimited Version : Last OS : Anything Type : Product Hunter GB Price : $1188 GB Cost : 80$/15 Peoples + 8$ Fee GB Joined : 10/15 Peoples GB Status : Going Homepage : SalePage Dropified’s ecosystem is leading the way in making normal ecommerce users become highly profitable power users. Our software suites will allow you as a distributor to find the best deals with the best margins for the best return on your dollar as an ecommerce supplier.</description>
<category>GB Spy Tools</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 05:57:06 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FE - Dropified Unlimited - $1188 Unlimited Store connections All Features Included Special Bonus Tools</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/159628928?app_id=122963" width="425" height="239" frameborder="0" title="Dropified App Unlimited" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><a href="https://www.dropified.com/pricing/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>FE - Dropified Unlimited  - 88</b></a><br><ul><li> Unlimited Store connections<br></li><li> All Features Included<br></li><li> Special Bonus Tools<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Dropified Unlimited Annual"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>