<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>List Managers - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>List Managers - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>Email List Cleaner 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4207-email-list-cleaner.html</link>
<description>list] Name : Email List Cleaner Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Email Marketing Tool Price : $59 Homepage : SalePage Email List Cleaner is a software tool that allows users to import their email lists then each email address will be filtered through up to 10 different rules to determine if its a real valid email address that is worth sending emails to.</description>
<category>List Managers</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2018 21:55:36 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Here is the list of filters that are applied to each email address. - SMTP check - We will connect to the server (so if the email address is alex@gmail.com we connect to gmail.com MX records) mailbox then ask the mail server if the mailbox exists. While this works perfectly for gmail from any IP address some other mail servers such as hotmail will not allow this check from a residential IP address as rDNS must be setup. However as we only mark the email address as invalid if we receive a mailbox does not exist error we eliminate any false positives. - Gibberish check - We check each email address for mixes of letters and numbers that contain few unique letters and numbers. For example abcde@gmail.com would pass but aaaa@gmail.com would fail the list clean. - Rude word check - Swear words and words that are not commonly in email addresses cause these emails to be filtered out. - Valid email (loose check) - Checks email address to see if they contain only letters and numbers, - _ and @ - Valid email (loose check) - Checks email address to see if they conform to the RFC 5322 standard. - Known temp disposable email domain - Checks to see if the email contains a known temp disposable email domain from the softwares internal database of known temp disposable email domains - Suspected temp disposable email domain - At the start of the run this settings will search Google for keywords such as &quot;disposable email address&quot;. Then it will crawl all the results extracting and validating all the domains it can find on these disposable email address websites, while being careful not to exclude known good email domains. - Email domain DNS resolves - Checks to see if the domain on the email has DNS that successfully resolves. - Check if domain has MX records - Checks the email domain to see if it has MX records set. - Duplicate check - Checks to see if email address is a duplicate and already in imported email list.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/GDYb4mfsRGc?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Here is the list of filters that are applied to each email address. <br></li><li> - SMTP check - We will connect to the server (so if the email address is alex@gmail.com we connect to gmail.com MX records) mailbox then ask the mail server if the mailbox exists. While this works perfectly for gmail from any IP address some other mail servers such as hotmail will not allow this check from a residential IP address as rDNS must be setup. However as we only mark the email address as invalid if we receive a mailbox does not exist error we eliminate any false positives.<br></li><li> - Gibberish check - We check each email address for mixes of letters and numbers that contain few unique letters and numbers. For example abcde@gmail.com would pass but aaaa@gmail.com would fail the list clean.<br></li><li> - Rude word check - Swear words and words that are not commonly in email addresses cause these emails to be filtered out.<br></li><li> - Valid email (loose check) - Checks email address to see if they contain only letters and numbers, - _ and @<br></li><li> - Valid email (loose check) - Checks email address to see if they conform to the RFC 5322 standard.<br></li><li> - Known temp disposable email domain - Checks to see if the email contains a known temp disposable email domain from the softwares internal database of known temp disposable email domains<br></li><li> - Suspected temp disposable email domain - At the start of the run this settings will search Google for keywords such as "disposable email address". Then it will crawl all the results extracting and validating all the domains it can find on these disposable email address websites, while being careful not to exclude known good email domains.<br></li><li> - Email domain DNS resolves - Checks to see if the domain on the email has DNS that successfully resolves.<br></li><li> - Check if domain has MX records - Checks the email domain to see if it has MX records set.<br></li><li> - Duplicate check - Checks to see if email address is a duplicate and already in imported email list.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Email List Cleaner 1.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>List Janitor Agency 1.4.3</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3666-list-janitor.html</link>
<description>Name : List Janitor Agency Version : 1.4.3 OS : Windows Type : Email List Manager Price : $483 Homepage : SalePage Boost Email Deliverability with this Powerful List Cleaning And Management Tool Powerful desktop software helps you clean your list on your desktop computer itself. You won’t have to pay a hefty fees to get your list cleaned, and you won’t have to pay a recurring. Use it for as long as you want, and as often as you want. List Janitor also has ultra-powerful list management and segmentation features that will help you create sub-lists targeting specific user groups. You can’t get this even from expensive list-cleaning services. Like all our products, List Janitor is field-tested, proven and well-maintained. Multi Language Support : List Janitor’s interface is available in English, Spanish, German &amp;amp; Portuguese.</description>
<category>List Managers</category>
<enclosure url="http://listjanitor.in/Content/jvimg/product1.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 10:40:06 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Bring dead lists to life Import your lists easier into autoresponders Reduce your email marketing costs Improves your email delivery Get a higher open rate Segment your lists easily Combine two lists into one Super Easy To Use Import any list and clean it in a matter of seconds. Removes invalid addresses, role addresses, spam-traps etc. from your lists. Works with CSVs or simple list of email addresses. Advanced list management &amp;amp; analysis features help you get the most from your list. Bring back your old and dying list to life by purifying it. Every Inte.com marketer needs this product. Must have if you want to import your lists into an autoresponder (Autoresponders do not import unclean lists). Improves your deliverability and reduces your expense.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/B584YKZAI14?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><br><ul><li> Bring dead lists to life<br></li><li> Import your lists easier into autoresponders<br></li><li> Reduce your email marketing costs<br></li><li> Improves your email delivery<br></li><li> Get a higher open rate<br></li><li> Segment your lists easily<br></li><li> Combine two lists into one<br></li><li> Super Easy To Use<br></li><li> Import any list and clean it in a matter of seconds.<br></li><li> Removes invalid addresses, role addresses, spam-traps etc. from your lists.<br></li><li> Works with CSVs or simple list of email addresses.<br></li><li> Advanced list management &amp; analysis features help you get the most from your list.<br></li><li> Bring back your old and dying list to life by purifying it.<br></li><li> Every Inte.com marketer needs this product.<br></li><li> Must have if you want to import your lists into an autoresponder (Autoresponders do not import unclean lists).<br></li><li> Improves your deliverability and reduces your expense.<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://listjanitor.in/Content/jvimg/product1.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="List Janitor Agency 1.4.3"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>MailWasher Pro 7.11.5</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4104-mailwasher-pro.html</link>
<description>Name : MailWasher Pro Version : 7.11.5 OS : Windows Type : Anti-Spam Email Tool Price : $0 Homepage : SalePage MAILWASHER PRO STOPS SPAMBLOCK ALL SPAM BEFORE IT GETS TO YOUR COMPUTER Install MailWasher today to screen all your email accounts in one place and allow only the email you want in your inbox. MailWasher lets you preview all your email before it gets to your computer or mobile device, enabling you to read all your email securely, and instantly delete any unwanted or suspicious email. Your remaining good email is downloaded to your PC or mobile device, so you avoid any spam or email viruses in your PC.</description>
<category>List Managers</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 00:18:22 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features WHEN YOU USE MAILWASHER, THE BENEFITS BECOME OBVIOUS. • Zero spam in your computer or mobile device. • Inspect any email before it gets to your computer or mobile device. • Never lose an email because you can’t afford to. • Intelligent spam tools ensure spam is caught and good email is not. With over 8 million users, 22 languages and featured on both BBC World and CNN you can be confident that using MailWasher is one of the easiest ways to get rid of spam.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br>WHEN YOU USE MAILWASHER, THE BENEFITS BECOME OBVIOUS.<br><br>• Zero spam in your computer or mobile device.<br>• Inspect any email before it gets to your computer or mobile device.<br>• Never lose an email because you can’t afford to.<br>• Intelligent spam tools ensure spam is caught and good email is not.<br><br>With over 8 million users, 22 languages and featured on both BBC World and CNN you can be confident that using MailWasher is one of the easiest ways to get rid of spam.<br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="MailWasher Pro 7.11.5"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Automatic Email Processor 1.4.4</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2104-automatic-email-processor.html</link>
<description>Name : Automatic Email Processor Version : 1.4.4 OS : Windows Type : Outlook List Manager Price : $69 Homepage : SalePage AUTOMATICALLY PROCESS EMAILS AND EMAIL ATTACHMENTS IN OUTLOOK ACCORDING TO INDIVIDUAL RULES Automatic Email Processor is the complete solution for Outlook to store and print incoming emails and their attachments automatically. For this, various filters, flexible configuration options, such as individually definable storage folders and the possibility of subsequent processing are available. For example, the path of the location where you want Automatic Email Processor to save certain emails or email attachments, can be assembled dynamically from individual properties of an email. For storing email messages, inter alia, the output format can be specified (for example, PDF, RTF, or HTML). The program supports the creation of an unlimited number of profiles to allow separate settings for different email accounts. Profiles can be additionally applied to emails of a specific time period or to any previously received emails of an Outlook folder.</description>
<category>List Managers</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.automatic-email-processor.com/images/outlook-print-emails.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 12:07:36 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Automatically store respectively archive email attachments Save emails automatically (as PDF file or in the original format) Automatically print emails and email attachments (PDF files, Office documents etc.) Monitor an unlimited number of Outlook folders Create custom profiles for different tasks Filter by subject, sender, recipient, attachment file name ... Receive information about the processing status via email Create storage folders dynamically from properties of an email Perform subsequent actions such as start a program with parameters, mark the message as read, or move the email into another Outlook folder Re-process all emails (with certain criteria) of an Outlook folder</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/xsi9wPnxJnQ?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Automatically store respectively archive email attachments<br /></li><li> Save emails automatically (as PDF file or in the original format)<br /></li><li> Automatically print emails and email attachments (PDF files, Office documents etc.)<br /></li><li> Monitor an unlimited number of Outlook folders<br /></li><li> Create custom profiles for different tasks<br /></li><li> Filter by subject, sender, recipient, attachment file name ...<br /></li><li> Receive information about the processing status via email<br /></li><li> Create storage folders dynamically from properties of an email<br /></li><li> Perform subsequent actions such as start a program with parameters, mark the message as read, or move the email into another Outlook folder<br /></li><li> Re-process all emails (with certain criteria) of an Outlook folder<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://www.automatic-email-processor.com/images/outlook-print-emails.png" alt="Automatic Email Processor 1.4.4" title="Automatic Email Processor 1.4.4"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Automatic Email Processor 1.4.4" title="Automatic Email Processor 1.4.4"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Total Mail Converter 5.1.174</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2103-total-mail-converter.html</link>
<description>Name : Total Mail Converter Version : 5.1.174 OS : Windows Type : List Manager Price : $59 Homepage : SalePage Convert Emails (MSG, EML) to PDF, TXT, DOC, PST in batch via user interface or command line. Total Mail Converter helps you manage your emails outside of your email client (Outlook, Thunderbird, and more) in the same way you would work with PDF, DOC or RTF files. Loaded with unique options,</description>
<category>List Managers</category>
<enclosure url="https://www.coolutils.com/screenshots/TotalMailConverterPro/MailProMain16.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 12:02:47 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Convert MSG or EML to PDF, PDF/A, DOC, XLS, XPS, HTML, XHTML, TXT, TIFF, EML, MSG, PST files. Attached files can be extracted and placed into the same or a new folder. Or embedded as clickable links to output files. To convert attachments to DOC, PDF, TIFF, JPEG, HTML, TXT . Perfect for eDiscovery and Freedom Of Information requests. Convert emails via the friendly user interface or directly through the command line. We even offer a server version without the GUI or any messages for silent server operations. Selectively export the email fields of your choosing: Sender, Recipient, Date, Subject, or Body. More unique options..</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/e6TIFY4NKmQ?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Convert MSG or EML to PDF, PDF/A, DOC, XLS, XPS, HTML, XHTML, TXT, TIFF, EML, MSG, PST files.<br /></li><li> Attached files can be extracted and placed into the same or a new folder. Or embedded as clickable links to output files. To convert attachments to DOC, PDF, TIFF, JPEG, HTML, TXT .<br /></li><li> Perfect for eDiscovery and Freedom Of Information requests.<br /></li><li> Convert emails via the friendly user interface or directly through the command line. We even offer a server version without the GUI or any messages for silent server operations.<br /></li><li> Selectively export the email fields of your choosing: Sender, Recipient, Date, Subject, or Body. More unique options..<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="https://www.coolutils.com/screenshots/TotalMailConverterPro/MailProMain16.png" alt="Total Mail Converter 5.1.174" title="Total Mail Converter 5.1.174"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Total Mail Converter 5.1.174" title="Total Mail Converter 5.1.174"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Email List Splitter 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1733-email-list-splitter.html</link>
<description>Name : Email List Splitter Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Email Marketing Tools Price : $0 Homepage : SalePage Email List Splitter -Splits big email lists into smaller ones If you find yourself with a large list of email addresses and need to split them into smaller more managable files, NCRlistSplitter will do the job!</description>
<category>List Managers</category>
<enclosure url="http://adultvideoblaster.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2-Side-Box_small_transp.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://adultvideoblaster.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/features-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2016 11:12:50 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>[media=https://player.vimeo.com/video/161022535] Features Multiple account support : AVB supports multiple accounts for the top 5 adult video directories. Track views and position : Manage your video lists with ease. Track the current views and search positions for all uploaded videos. Built-in video editor : Automatically add watermark or append an intro video. No more wasting time editing videos the old way! Multiple tube sites : 1 Click and start uploading to pornhub, xhamster, xvideos, txxx, youporn, spankwire, redtube and more… Mass Upload On All Major Tube Sites With Ease! BULK WATERMARK AND EDIT VIDEOS! Easy import and upload</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;">[media=https://player.vimeo.com/video/161022535]</div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Multiple account support : AVB supports multiple accounts for the top 5 adult video directories.<br /></li><li> Track views and position : Manage your video lists with ease. Track the current views and search positions for all uploaded videos.<br /></li><li> Built-in video editor : Automatically add watermark or append an intro video. No more wasting time editing videos the old way!<br /></li><li> Multiple tube sites : 1 Click and start uploading to pornhub, xhamster, xvideos, txxx, youporn, spankwire, redtube and more…<br /></li><li> Mass Upload On All Major Tube Sites With Ease!<br /></li><li> BULK WATERMARK AND EDIT VIDEOS!<br /></li><li> Easy import and upload<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://adultvideoblaster.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2-Side-Box_small_transp.png" alt="Email List Splitter 1.0" title="Email List Splitter 1.0"  /><br /><img src="http://adultvideoblaster.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/features-1.jpg" alt="Email List Splitter 1.0" title="Email List Splitter 1.0"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Email List Splitter 1.0" title="Email List Splitter 1.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Email List Cleaner 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1732-email-list-cleaner.html</link>
<description>Name : Email List Cleaner Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Email Marketing Tools Price : $0 Homepage : SalePage Email List Cleaner -Quickly Cleans Your Lists Have a list of email addresses but it&#039;s too big to manually clean? This email list cleaner will remove all duplicates and all mal-formed email addresses leaving you with a cleaned list ready to go!</description>
<category>List Managers</category>
<enclosure url="http://adultvideoblaster.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2-Side-Box_small_transp.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://adultvideoblaster.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/features-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2016 11:11:07 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>[media=https://player.vimeo.com/video/161022535] Features Multiple account support : AVB supports multiple accounts for the top 5 adult video directories. Track views and position : Manage your video lists with ease. Track the current views and search positions for all uploaded videos. Built-in video editor : Automatically add watermark or append an intro video. No more wasting time editing videos the old way! Multiple tube sites : 1 Click and start uploading to pornhub, xhamster, xvideos, txxx, youporn, spankwire, redtube and more… Mass Upload On All Major Tube Sites With Ease! BULK WATERMARK AND EDIT VIDEOS! Easy import and upload</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;">[media=https://player.vimeo.com/video/161022535]</div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Multiple account support : AVB supports multiple accounts for the top 5 adult video directories.<br /></li><li> Track views and position : Manage your video lists with ease. Track the current views and search positions for all uploaded videos.<br /></li><li> Built-in video editor : Automatically add watermark or append an intro video. No more wasting time editing videos the old way!<br /></li><li> Multiple tube sites : 1 Click and start uploading to pornhub, xhamster, xvideos, txxx, youporn, spankwire, redtube and more…<br /></li><li> Mass Upload On All Major Tube Sites With Ease!<br /></li><li> BULK WATERMARK AND EDIT VIDEOS!<br /></li><li> Easy import and upload<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://adultvideoblaster.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2-Side-Box_small_transp.png" alt="Email List Cleaner 1.0" title="Email List Cleaner 1.0"  /><br /><img src="http://adultvideoblaster.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/features-1.jpg" alt="Email List Cleaner 1.0" title="Email List Cleaner 1.0"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Email List Cleaner 1.0" title="Email List Cleaner 1.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Elite List Puller 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1713-elite-list-puller.html</link>
<description>Name : Elite List Puller Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : List Tools Price : $39 Homepage : SalePage Elite List Puller is a powerful tool that helps small business owners and.comwork marketing professionals</description>
<category>List Managers</category>
<enclosure url="http://s2.dmcdn.com/BU530/1280x720-wYk.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2016 20:14:05 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features GET UNLIMITED EMAIL LEADS IN REAL TIME! GET UNLIMITED GMAIL,HOTMAIL,MSN, AND YAHOO EMAILS! USE ANY KEYWORD FOR MORE DIRECT EMAIL NICHES! RUN MULTIPLE INSTANCES OF THE SOFTWARE NEVER PAY FOR EMAIL LEADS EVER AGAIN!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/h2xxm_dj9R0?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> GET UNLIMITED EMAIL LEADS IN REAL TIME!<br /></li><li> GET UNLIMITED GMAIL,HOTMAIL,MSN, AND YAHOO EMAILS!<br /></li><li> USE ANY KEYWORD FOR MORE DIRECT EMAIL NICHES!<br /></li><li> RUN MULTIPLE INSTANCES OF THE SOFTWARE<br /></li><li> NEVER PAY FOR EMAIL LEADS EVER AGAIN!<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://s2.dmcdn.com/BU530/1280x720-wYk.jpg" alt="Elite List Puller 1.0" title="Elite List Puller 1.0"  /><br /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Elite List Puller 1.0" title="Elite List Puller 1.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Prospective 2016 v9.13</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1680-prospective.html</link>
<description>Name : Prospective Version : 2016 v9.13 OS : Windows Type : List Manage Price : $399 Homepage : SalePage Prospective! contact management serving the SOHO / SME ... P?r?nisez and consolidate your business by having a thorough knowledge of your customers and prospects: General information and relevant to your criteria, monitoring, marketing actions ... You want to quickly and easily manage your contacts? Your contact base will be created in minutes! However, for a more punctilious management, each contact has a thirty fields with ten fully customizable. The contact cards also feature a &quot;notepad&quot; and a maximum of 10 attachments (accounting documents, text files, images ...). Prospective 2011 frees your mind by recording all important information of all your contacts. Agenda, emailing, project management, Annalyse ... All the tools to develop your sales!</description>
<category>List Managers</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.prospective-fr.com/img/top-bg2.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2016 20:38:18 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features contact management Customizable contact sheets Geolocation contacts on a map of France Sending email from the contact card Access the website Contact Access social.comworks of contact (Facebook, Viadeo) Knowing the financial health of your contact (Manageo) Bloc general and priority rating Integration of photo, logos History of all activity (task, appointment...) Project management Adding attachments related to the contact General functions simple and effective Intuitive Search contacts collaborative Agenda Sorting and Searching Analysis of the activity graph Import / Export Assistant (Excel, Outlook, Access) professional direct mail professional emailing Administration Password database protection Management of user rights Read-only mode automated backups compatible with Windows 2000, XP, Vista, Seven Up to 15,000 contacts database sharing.comwork database Number of database Unlimited Managing multi-activity Remote synchronization via VPN</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><div class="dlevideoplayer" style="width:100%;max-width:425px;"><ul data-theme="default" data-preload="metadata"><li data-title="" data-type="youtube" data-url="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ow4osYybWC4"></li></ul></div></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> contact management	 	 <br></li><li> Customizable contact sheets	<br></li><li> Geolocation contacts on a map of France<br></li><li> Sending email from the contact card	<br></li><li> Access the website Contact	<br></li><li> Access social.comworks of contact (Facebook, Viadeo)	<br></li><li> Knowing the financial health of your contact (Manageo)	<br></li><li> Bloc general and priority rating	<br></li><li> Integration of photo, logos	<br></li><li> History of all activity (task, appointment...)	<br></li><li> Project management	<br></li><li> Adding attachments related to the contact	<br></li><li> General functions	 	 <br></li><li> simple and effective	<br></li><li> Intuitive Search contacts	<br></li><li> collaborative Agenda	 	<br></li><li> Sorting and Searching	<br></li><li> Analysis of the activity graph	<br></li><li> Import / Export Assistant (Excel, Outlook, Access)	<br></li><li> professional direct mail	<br></li><li> professional emailing	<br></li><li> Administration	 	 <br></li><li> Password database protection	<br></li><li> Management of user rights	 	<br></li><li> Read-only mode	<br></li><li> automated backups	<br></li><li> compatible with Windows 2000, XP, Vista, Seven	<br></li><li> Up to 15,000 contacts database	<br></li><li> sharing.comwork database	 	<br></li><li> Number of database Unlimited<br></li><li> Managing multi-activity	 	<br></li><li> Remote synchronization via VPN<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://www.prospective-fr.com/img/top-bg2.png" alt="Prospective 2016 v9.13"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Emails Generator 15.11.11.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1441-emails-generator.html</link>
<description>Name : Emails Generator Version : 15.11.11.0 OS : Windows Type : Emails Marketing Tools Price : $8 Homepage : SalePage Emails Generator Software is a marketing tool software, it creates automatic bulk email list in really short time. The Database include about 100k name list.</description>
<category>List Managers</category>
<enclosure url="https://dl.dropboxusercontent.com/u/57468883/EmailGenerator/Pics/English/Campain.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2015 18:46:38 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Running in Background : Emails Generator Software doesn’t need you to generate a large email list, just set the number of emails you need and let Email Generator run in the background, and it will not affect you to do something else. Promote Your Business Faster : The program will bulid a consumer mailing list for e-mail marketing and advertising campaigns. If you want your business to start being recognized in the world of the Web, be sure to download the application that will surely assist you effectively in the difficult task of creating a brand. These randomly generated email addresses can be useful for online marketing activities. Simple to use : The program’s user interface is easy to understand and only a few steps are required to start generating the email addresses. Now more and more webmasters, bloggers and affiliate using this software increase their income. Most of them have been successful.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/5FByJRwHes0?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Running in Background : Emails Generator Software doesn’t need you to generate a large email list, just set the number of emails you need and let Email Generator run in the background, and it will not affect you to do something else.<br /></li><li> Promote Your Business Faster : The program will bulid a consumer mailing list for e-mail marketing and advertising campaigns. If you want your business to start being recognized in the world of the Web, be sure to download the application that will surely assist you effectively in the difficult task of creating a brand. These randomly generated email addresses can be useful for online marketing activities.<br /></li><li> Simple to use : The program’s user interface is easy to understand and only a few steps are required to start generating the email addresses. Now more and more webmasters, bloggers and affiliate using this software increase their income. Most of them have been successful.<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="https://dl.dropboxusercontent.com/u/57468883/EmailGenerator/Pics/English/Campain.png" alt="Emails Generator 15.11.11.0" title="Emails Generator 15.11.11.0"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Emails Generator 15.11.11.0" title="Emails Generator 15.11.11.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>