<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Pinterest Marketing - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Pinterest Marketing - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>Ninja Pinner 5.7.4</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1024-ninjapinner.html</link>
<description>Name : NinjaPinner Version : 5.7.4 OS : Windows Type : Pinterest Marketing Bot Price : $27 Homepage : SalePage NinjaPinner is a powerful software which can be used to automate the process of pinning, following, liking and commenting on Pinterest. The software has a built-in browser which is used to navigate the Pinterest website. You can perform searches, browsing, along with gathering ID’s. When you get to a list of members on Pinterest that you would like to follow, you click the “Gather Friends” button. The program automatically goes page by page gathering all friends in the list. At this point, you can then begin auto-following, sending comments, liking posts, or re-pinning images.</description>
<category>Pinterest Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 12:54:32 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Target your market based specific keyword. Gather friend(s) id’s from comment threads, pin-boards, people or any other search area of Pinterest Filter Pinterest users by follower / following count as well as by recent login activity Auto Follow feature that allows you to mass follow other users fast, gaining you thousands of followers back Auto Unfollow function that allows you to mass unfollow users that don’t follow you Choose to exclude people you’ve followed ___ days ago so you can give Pinterest users time to respond before unfollowing them Schedule your follows, unfollows, likes, repins, comments and invites to automatically be sent at a specified time and at specified intervals. Auto Pin feature that allows you to mass re-pin other images on autopilot getting you exposure Re-pin URL swap function allowing you to substitute YOUR links when you re-pin content Auto Commenter feature that allows you to send out comments to all others users. Auto Comment rotation which allows you to send comments from a list of different pre-written comments. Queue up as many variations as you like. Import and export featured comments The ability to use Spintax in comments and pin captions Invite others to follow your boards Auto like feature that allows you to mass like pins, boards, etc. Create a “Black List” for ID’s you don’t want to send to. Use unlimited Pinterest.com accounts (unlimited licence only) When commenting, you can skip pins from any user you have already commented on in the last ___ days When repinning you can change the caption of the pin, keep the current caption, or add to the current caption Comes with a NinjaPinner News Bulletin to keep you up to date with the latest news. Free product updates, support and technical assistance for LIFE.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/cb720Fn1Cak?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><br><ul><li> Target your market based specific keyword.<br></li><li> Gather friend(s) id’s from comment threads, pin-boards, people or any other search area of Pinterest<br></li><li> Filter Pinterest users by follower / following count as well as by recent login activity<br></li><li> Auto Follow feature that allows you to mass follow other users fast, gaining you thousands of followers back<br></li><li> Auto Unfollow function that allows you to mass unfollow users that don’t follow you<br></li><li> Choose to exclude people you’ve followed ___ days ago so you can give Pinterest users time to respond before unfollowing them<br></li><li> Schedule your follows, unfollows, likes, repins, comments and invites to automatically be sent at a specified time and at specified intervals.<br></li><li> Auto Pin feature that allows you to mass re-pin other images on autopilot getting you exposure<br></li><li> Re-pin URL swap function allowing you to substitute YOUR links when you re-pin content<br></li><li> Auto Commenter feature that allows you to send out comments to all others users.<br></li><li> Auto Comment rotation which allows you to send comments from a list of different pre-written comments. Queue up as many variations as you like.<br></li><li> Import and export featured comments<br></li><li> The ability to use Spintax in comments and pin captions<br></li><li> Invite others to follow your boards<br></li><li> Auto like feature that allows you to mass like pins, boards, etc.<br></li><li> Create a “Black List” for ID’s you don’t want to send to.<br></li><li> Use unlimited Pinterest.com accounts (unlimited licence only)<br></li><li> When commenting, you can skip pins from any user you have already commented on in the last ___ days<br></li><li> When repinning you can change the caption of the pin, keep the current caption, or add to the current caption<br></li><li> Comes with a NinjaPinner News Bulletin to keep you up to date with the latest news.<br></li><li> Free product updates, support and technical assistance for LIFE.<br></li></ul><br><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Ninja Pinner 5.7.4"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>PinDominator 3.5.0.22</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/912-pindominator.html</link>
<description>Name :PinDominator Agency Version : 3.5.0.22 OS : Windows Type : Pinterest Marketing Price : $1499 Homepage : SalePage PinDominator: Your All-in-one Pinterest Marketing Tool PinDominator lets you target with precision, connect directly with your audience, spread your Images throughout the day and do much more to make sure you achieve your marketing goals. PinDominator is the most efficient pinterest marketing software in the market. Use our pinterest software to automatically create pinterest accounts, repin, ...</description>
<category>Pinterest Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 07:02:29 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Repin Module Comment Module Like Module Follow/Unfollow Module Board Module Invite Module User To Board Account Checker User Scraper New Pin</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/21ChjNh9l4A?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Repin Module<br></li><li> Comment Module<br></li><li> Like Module<br></li><li> Follow/Unfollow Module<br></li><li> Board Module<br></li><li> Invite Module<br></li><li> User To Board<br></li><li> Account Checker<br></li><li> User Scraper<br></li><li> New Pin<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="PinDominator 3.5.0.22"><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>PinFlux Agency 1.9</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3711-pinflux.html</link>
<description>Name : PinFlux Agency + OTOs Version : 1.9 OS : Windows Type : Pinterest Marketing Bot Price : $515 Homepage : SalePage Powerful Pinterest Automation Software Does Everything On Your Desktop Computer Pinterest is the fastest growing traffic source for e-commerce, brands, bloggers and even social media marketers. With nearly 200 million monthly active users , a high presence of female users, and a big percentage of buyers, this platform is vital for any online marketer’s success. Till now Pinterest lay untapped for automation because there was no effective automation software that unlocked every feature of Pinterest. Pinflux is the first such software.</description>
<category>Pinterest Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 09:56:49 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Work with multiple boards across multiple IDs. Automates pinning of fresh content. Search and automatically finds powerful content from Pinterest. Finds pins in any niche and repins them to your boards. Automatically follows niche targeted profiles. Unfollow automation for profiles that did not follow you back. Like &amp;amp; activity automation. 100% support for manual actions. You can do everything from within Pinflux OTO1 - Pinflux Pro Enhanced and supercharged version of Pinflux unlocks more powerful automation features and also supports more number of accounts and boards. Perfect for professional Pinterest marketers. OTO2 - Pinflux Agency The agency version of Pinflux unlocks all features, and also supports Unlimited accounts and Unlimited boards. Perfect for professional marketers who want to do Pinterest marketers for others as well as themselves. OTO3 - VidPush + Video Jeet Powerful content automation software for Facebook and for blogging. This in combination with Pinflux lets your users create a three pronged automation strategy that covers 1) Pinterest, 2) Facebook, 3) Blogging. OTO4 - Pinflux WhiteLabel An opportunity to sell Pinterest and keep 100% of the profits using two powerful options. Reseller that lets you sell using our setup and get 100% on the front-end and Whitelabel which gives you 100% custom created version of Pinflux that you can sell yourself.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Py93crc3n4E?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Work with multiple boards across multiple IDs.<br></li><li> Automates pinning of fresh content.<br></li><li> Search and automatically finds powerful content from Pinterest.<br></li><li> Finds pins in any niche and repins them to your boards.<br></li><li> Automatically follows niche targeted profiles.<br></li><li> Unfollow automation for profiles that did not follow you back.<br></li><li> Like &amp; activity automation.<br></li><li> 100% support for manual actions. You can do everything from within Pinflux<br></li></ul><br>OTO1 - Pinflux Pro<br><ul><li> Enhanced and supercharged version of Pinflux unlocks more powerful automation features and also supports more number of accounts and boards. Perfect for professional Pinterest marketers.<br></li></ul><br>OTO2 - Pinflux Agency<br><ul><li> The agency version of Pinflux unlocks all features, and also supports Unlimited accounts and Unlimited boards. Perfect for professional marketers who want to do Pinterest marketers for others as well as themselves.<br></li></ul><br>OTO3 - VidPush + Video Jeet<br><ul><li> Powerful content automation software for Facebook and for blogging. This in combination with Pinflux lets your users create a three pronged automation strategy that covers 1) Pinterest, 2) Facebook, 3) Blogging.<br></li></ul><br>OTO4 - Pinflux WhiteLabel<br><ul><li> An opportunity to sell Pinterest and keep 100% of the profits using two powerful options. Reseller that lets you sell using our setup and get 100% on the front-end and Whitelabel which gives you 100% custom created version of Pinflux that you can sell yourself.<br></li></ul><br><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="PinFlux Agency 1.9"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Pin Blaster 2.84 Exclusive Edition</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1122-pin-blaster.html</link>
<description>Name : Pin Blaster + Pin Grabber 1.33 Version : 2.84 Exclusive Edition OS : Windows Type : Pinterest Marketing Bot Price : $67 Homepage : SalePage World’s Best Pinterest Automation Software! What used to take hours to do, Pin Blaster does in minutes - Multiple accounts &amp;amp; proxy support - Easy scrape and follow users - Multi threaded actions - Pin, like, comment repin with 1 click - Auto post content on your blog</description>
<category>Pinterest Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2018 18:50:22 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Multiple account support Create boards – multi threaded board creation in different categories Check if accounts are still valid or not Add board co creators (who can pin in your board) Delete boards from accounts View number of boards, followers and following for every account Private and public proxy support (both ipv4 and ipv6) 100% Http Requests making it very fast and reliable Auto unblock accounts by connecting to the email associated with the account Follow and Unfollow users Scrape users from category, keyword, user or location (geo target) Add users manually 1 by 1 or mass import from file Follow users with all accounts or with a single account. You have the option to follow X users / account than switch to next account + tons of other options Find all people you follow so you can unfollow them Find fake friends (users that YOU FOLLOW but that do not follow you back) Unfollow fake friends (works with 1 account or all your accounts) Export users/followers Pin Actions module (gather pins and like/repin/comment the pins) Search for pins from a specific category, keyword or account filter pins (gather pins that have minimum X likes or minimum Y repins) Multi threaded like/repin/comment all the gathered pins Change repin links Use random boards or default boards when repinning Content Poster (pin your own pins, add them to your blog Add images manually directly from your PC Import pins from Pin Grabber Upload images on your blog and then pin on pinterest Pin images directly on Pinterest Enter custom repin links Scedule actions so you can set and forget Spyntax support Mass like or comment your own pins Multiple campaign support (multiple lists) View pin preview (so you can see how it will look on Pinterest) Shuffle or export pins Pin Grabber – Scrape Pins Download images from Pinterest based on category, keyword or account Download images from 9Gag.com Set custom text before or after original description Export directly for Pin Blaster Other settings Multi threaded for all functions Custom delays on all actions you do (random between 2 values) Private and public proxy support Log reports (on screen log reporting, you can track the status of your current action, see errors etc… Auto watermark the images before you upload them Do actions on 1 account or on a group of accounts at a time Randomize accounts before doing actions</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/39042983" width="425" height="239" frameborder="0" title="Pin Blaster" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><p><br></p><br><h3>Features</h3><br><p><br><br>Multiple account support<br><ul><li> Create boards – multi threaded board creation in different categories<br></li><li> Check if accounts are still valid or not<br></li><li> Add board co creators (who can pin in your board)<br></li><li> Delete boards from accounts<br></li><li> View number of boards, followers and following for every account<br></li><li> Private and public proxy support (both ipv4 and ipv6)<br></li><li> 100% Http Requests making it very fast and reliable<br></li><li> Auto unblock accounts by connecting to the email associated with the account<br></li></ul><br>Follow and Unfollow users<br><ul><li> Scrape users from category, keyword, user or location (geo target)<br></li><li> Add users manually 1 by 1 or mass import from file<br></li><li> Follow users with all accounts or with a single account. You have the option to follow X users / account than switch to next account + tons of other options<br></li><li> Find all people you follow so you can unfollow them<br></li><li> Find fake friends (users that YOU FOLLOW but that do not follow you back)<br></li><li> Unfollow fake friends (works with 1 account or all your accounts)<br></li><li> Export users/followers<br></li></ul><br>Pin Actions module (gather pins and like/repin/comment the pins)<br><ul><li> Search for pins from a specific category, keyword or account<br></li><li> filter pins (gather pins that have minimum X likes or minimum Y repins)<br></li><li> Multi threaded like/repin/comment all the gathered pins<br></li><li> Change repin links<br></li><li> Use random boards or default boards when repinning<br></li></ul><br>Content Poster (pin your own pins, add them to your blog<br><ul><li> Add images manually directly from your PC<br></li><li> Import pins from Pin Grabber<br></li><li> Upload images on your blog and then pin on pinterest<br></li><li> Pin images directly on Pinterest<br></li><li> Enter custom repin links<br></li><li> Scedule actions so you can set and forget<br></li><li> Spyntax support<br></li><li> Mass like or comment your own pins<br></li><li> Multiple campaign support (multiple lists)<br></li><li> View pin preview (so you can see how it will look on Pinterest)<br></li><li> Shuffle or export pins<br></li></ul><br>Pin Grabber – Scrape Pins<br><ul><li> Download images from Pinterest based on category, keyword or account<br></li><li> Download images from 9Gag.com<br></li><li> Set custom text before or after original description<br></li><li> Export directly for Pin Blaster<br></li></ul><br>Other settings<br><ul><li> Multi threaded for all functions<br></li><li> Custom delays on all actions you do (random between 2 values)<br></li><li> Private and public proxy support<br></li><li> Log reports (on screen log reporting, you can track the status of your current action, see errors etc…<br></li><li> Auto watermark the images before you upload them<br></li><li> Do actions on 1 account or on a group of accounts at a time<br></li><li> Randomize accounts before doing actions<br></li></ul></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Pin Blaster 2.84 Exclusive Edition"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Social Multiplier 2.1972</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1392-social-multiplier.html</link>
<description>Name : Social Multiplier Version : 1.135 + 2.1972 OS : Windows Type : Pinterest Marketing Bot Tools Price : $130 Homepage : SalePage Drive Instant, High-Quality Traffic from Pinterest, on auto-pilot! Instant, Quality Traffic Social Multiplier regularly drives thousands of visitors to user sites on auto-pilot. This traffic often has better bounce rates and longer time on site than even Google traffic! Multiply Pinterest Followers Social Multiplier can increase the number of followers you have on Pinterest to up to 15,000 users! That&#039;s the maximum number of followers Pinterest allows and SocialMultiplier can get you there FAST. Amazing Social Proof Since Social Multiplier pins your URL on Pinterest (among other things) social share numbers shown in social sharing plugins on your site will show thousands, even TENS of thousands, of shares!</description>
<category>Pinterest Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://learnfromjon.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/06/sp.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2017 20:28:31 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>[media=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HvvGJ4hvYG0] Features Social Multiplier Grows Your Followers Faster Than You EVER Could Manually : Want a loyal following of people hungry to see your products, visit your site and buy what you&#039;re selling? Social Multiplier grows that audience for you ON AUTO-PILOT!Your fan base literally grows while you sleep! Social Multiplier Gets OTHER PEOPLE To Do The Heavy Lifting For You : Social Multiplier can invite other people to post to one or more of your boards. When those people post to your board, their own follows often follow YOUR board. When YOU pin to that board, ALL of the followers will see your pins, resulting in more traffic and revenue! It&#039;s viral traffic generation at its best. Your Followers Will SHARE What Social Multiplier Pins = More Traffic! This is no spam tool, that&#039;s for sure! Look at all of the interaction our followers have with our pins! Liking and repinning the pins with their own followers -- resulting in even more traffic.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;">[media=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HvvGJ4hvYG0]</div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Social Multiplier Grows Your Followers Faster Than You EVER Could Manually : Want a loyal following of people hungry to see your products, visit your site and buy what you're selling? Social Multiplier grows that audience for you ON AUTO-PILOT!Your fan base literally grows while you sleep!<br></li><li> Social Multiplier Gets OTHER PEOPLE To Do The Heavy Lifting For You : Social Multiplier can invite other people to post to one or more of your boards. When those people post to your board, their own follows often follow YOUR board. When YOU pin to that board, ALL of the followers will see your pins, resulting in more traffic and revenue! It's viral traffic generation at its best.<br></li><li> Your Followers Will SHARE What Social Multiplier Pins = More Traffic! This is no spam tool, that's for sure! Look at all of the interaction our followers have with our pins! Liking and repinning the pins with their own followers -- resulting in even more traffic.<br><br></li></ul><br><img src="http://learnfromjon.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/06/sp.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Social Multiplier 2.1972"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>PinBot 3.0.73 Premium</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1196-pinbot2.html</link>
<description>Name : PinBot 1 + 2 + 3 Version : 1.0.9.11 + 2.0.9.7 + 3.0.73 Premium OS : Windows Type : Pinterest Marketing Bot Price : $179 Homepage : SalePage The secret to marketing on Pinterest is quality and automation. I am basically running multiple accounts on PinBot. The beauty of PinBot is that it automatically keeps my accounts populated with fresh content, it does everything for me, so I can focus on making the money.</description>
<category>Pinterest Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://healzer.com/pinbot/pinbot_files/pb2_1.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2016 22:48:40 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Max. accounts unlimited Updates Repin feature Follow feature Unfollow feature Pin feature Like feature Invite feature Comment feature Proxy support Autopilot First Class support Premium Guides &amp; Tutorials</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/tSKNqg2YqG0?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Max. accounts unlimited<br /></li><li> Updates		<br /></li><li> Repin feature		<br /></li><li> Follow feature		<br /></li><li> Unfollow feature		<br /></li><li> Pin feature		<br /></li><li> Like feature		<br /></li><li> Invite feature		<br /></li><li> Comment feature<br /></li><li> Proxy support		<br /></li><li> Autopilot	<br /></li><li> First Class support		<br /></li><li> <a href="http://healzer.com/category/tutorials/"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Premium Guides & Tutorials</a><br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://healzer.com/pinbot/pinbot_files/pb2_1.png" alt="PinBot 3.0.73 Premium" title="PinBot 3.0.73 Premium"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="PinBot 3.0.73 Premium" title="PinBot 3.0.73 Premium"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>PinZon 1.20</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1709-pinzon.html</link>
<description>Name : PinZon Version : 1.20 OS : Windows Type : Pinterest Marketing Tools, Amazon Marketing Tools Price : $39 Homepage : SalePage Want to combine PINTEREST and AMAZON for quick automated profits? Our POWERFUL Software Automatically Pins Amazon Products To Your Own Pinterest Boards To Drive Viral Traffic To Your Amazon Affiliate Links For Huge Commissions – On Autopilot! Set it up in 3 easy steps, wait for the software to do it’s magic, and watch as your Amazon affiliate commissions skyrocket, without lifting a finger. Introducing PinZon I am not going to sit here and tell you that Pinterest drives more traffic then blah blah blah sites combined… By now you should already know that Pinterest can drive serious traffic! But who has the time to sit and pin images all day long so that you can rake in the cash from that traffic? Well I do not! So I created PinZon. This is my own personal tool that I use to pin Amazon products to Pinterest automatically!</description>
<category>Pinterest Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://i.imgur.com/LcBhDJs.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 22:52:58 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Well it is simple really. 1. You enter a keyword and press “Get Products”. This will return the number of images and descriptions that you specified from Amazon for that keyword. 2. You setup your linking structure. More on this in the next section. This requires just a bit of setup. 3. Enter your Pinterest credentials and click “Refresh Boards”. This will return a list of your available boards to post to. Pick the one you want. Then you need to pick how often you want the program to pin. You can specify a random time between X minutes and X minutes. So for example lets say you pick between 5 minutes and 10 minutes. The program will pin 1 picture on a random time between every 5 and 10 minutes. Once you have that set you press “Start Pinning” and you can minimize the program to the system tray and let it do its thing! I have been pulling down about 125 related products at a time and letting the program post them to a Pinterest board over night. This is so much easier then trying to post products myself!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/Ufmg242mSuA?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><br />Well it is simple really.<br /><br />1. You enter a keyword and press “Get Products”. This will return the number of images and descriptions that you specified from Amazon for that keyword.<br /><br />2. You setup your linking structure. More on this in the next section. This requires just a bit of setup.<br /><br />3. Enter your Pinterest credentials and click “Refresh Boards”. This will return a list of your available boards to post to. Pick the one you want. Then you need to pick how often you want the program to pin. You can specify a random time between X minutes and X minutes. So for example lets say you pick between 5 minutes and 10 minutes. The program will pin 1 picture on a random time between every 5 and 10 minutes. Once you have that set you press “Start Pinning” and you can minimize the program to the system tray and let it do its thing!<br /><br />I have been pulling down about 125 related products at a time and letting the program post them to a Pinterest board over night. This is so much easier then trying to post products myself!<br /><br /><br /><img src="http://i.imgur.com/LcBhDJs.jpg" alt="PinZon 1.20" title="PinZon 1.20"  /><br /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="PinZon 1.20" title="PinZon 1.20"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Repininator 1.35</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1704-repininator.html</link>
<description>Name : Repininator Version : 1.35 OS : Windows Type : Pinterest Marketing Tools Price : $57 Homepage : SalePage Repininator is a very powerful Pinterest tool that can very easily drive thousands of visitors to your blog or website every month. The best part is that is supports multiple Pinterest accounts and proxy support. So don’t limit yourself to one account and one blog. Think on a larger scale and get tens of thousands of visitors to your sites or more! Repininator allows you to search pins by keyword and repin them to your board. It also allows you to change the URL on the pin to any site you want as well as the description on the pin. We also support a spintax format for descriptions. That is all demonstrated in the video below. This initial release of Repininator also supports mass following of users to help build your following. We will be adding many updates to this tool in the weeks and months to come. I feel this tool is one of my most valuable tools to date. The amount of targeted traffic that this tool can drive to your sites can not be ignored!</description>
<category>Pinterest Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://i.imgur.com/lOTnl2c.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 22:52:28 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features It shows boards you can contribute to It shows the owner of the board It shows the followers of the board It shows the number of contributors to the board It allows you to pin one pin to multiple boards on random intervals Support normal or group/contributor boards You can run multiple bulk pins simultaneously Many More...</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/UXY9_e7LpyQ?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> It shows boards you can contribute to<br /></li><li> It shows the owner of the board<br /></li><li> It shows the followers of the board<br /></li><li> It shows the number of contributors to the board<br /></li><li> It allows you to pin one pin to multiple boards on random intervals<br /></li><li> Support normal or group/contributor boards<br /></li><li> You can run multiple bulk pins simultaneously<br /></li><li> Many More...<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://i.imgur.com/lOTnl2c.jpg" alt="Repininator 1.35" title="Repininator 1.35"  /><br /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Repininator 1.35" title="Repininator 1.35"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Pin Demon 1.17</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1187-pindemon.html</link>
<description>Name :Pin Demon – The Ultimate Pinterest Bot Version : 1.17 OS : Windows Type : Pinterest Marketing Bot Price : $299 Homepage : SalePage Using Pin Demon, you will be able to grow your Pinterest audience quickly, easily, and automatically. Pin Demon allows you to mange and set up tasks easily and fast. This is done with just a few clicks. Pinterest bot will help you save time by handling the whole process such as following users, unfollowing users, posting comments, pinning, liking, and adding text. By doing so, you can spread your ads throughout the day and get good exposure on Pinterest. Start to grow your profits without putting much effort with Pin Demon today! All are done automatically and systematically.</description>
<category>Pinterest Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://smmbots.com/screenshots/pin/pin.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://smmbots.com/screenshots/pin/liker.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2016 01:27:07 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Modules Follow/Unfollow Modules Website images uploader Modules Computer images uploader Modules Liker Modules Commenter Modules Re-pinner Modules Mass Promoter Modules Scraper Modules Account Statistic Modules Profile Editor Modules Board Creator Modules Account Creator Modules Captcha Sloving Modules Proxies</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/UksrIbcyMjQ?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Modules Follow/Unfollow<br /></li><li> Modules Website images uploader<br /></li><li> Modules Computer images uploader<br /></li><li> Modules Liker<br /></li><li> Modules Commenter<br /></li><li> Modules Re-pinner<br /></li><li> Modules Mass Promoter<br /></li><li> Modules Scraper<br /></li><li> Modules Account Statistic<br /></li><li> Modules Profile Editor<br /></li><li> Modules Board Creator<br /></li><li> Modules Account Creator<br /></li><li> Modules Captcha Sloving<br /></li><li> Modules Proxies<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://smmbots.com/screenshots/pin/pin.png" alt="Pin Demon 1.17" title="Pin Demon 1.17"  /><br /><img src="http://smmbots.com/screenshots/pin/liker.png" alt="Pin Demon 1.17" title="Pin Demon 1.17"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Pin Demon 1.17" title="Pin Demon 1.17"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Pin Freak 1.0.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1204-pin-freak.html</link>
<description>Name : Pin Freak Version : 1.0.0 OS : Windows/MAC Type : Pinterest Marketing Price : $50 Homepage : SalePage You can now harness the marketing goldmine of Pinterest. This powerful Chrome extension lets you extract popular pins with one click. With this tool, you can easily uncover profitable product ideas and also easily get great content for your facebook page or blog post. The possibilities are endless!</description>
<category>Pinterest Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2015 08:52:49 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Pinterest Research by Like, pin, repin Export Result to TXT List</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/0M3h1aLMEpY?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Pinterest Research by Like, pin, repin<br /></li><li> Export Result to TXT List<br /></li></ul><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Pin Freak 1.0.0" title="Pin Freak 1.0.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>