<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Affiliate plugin - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Affiliate plugin - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>Ultimate Affiliate Pro 3.6</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1790-ultimate-affiliate-pro.html</link>
<description>Name : Ultimate Affiliate Pro WordPress Plugin Version : 3.6 OS : Windows Type : Membership Affiliate Price : $32 Homepage : SalePage Ultimate Affiliate Pro is the newest and most completed Affiliate WordPress Plugin that allow you provide a premium platform for your Affiliates with different rewards and amounts based on Ranks or special Offers. You can turn on your Website into a REAL business and an income machine where you just need to sit down and let the others to work for you! Each Affiliate can creates his own marketing Campagin and brings more Affiliates via the &quot;Multi-Level-Marketing&quot; strategy.</description>
<category>Affiliate plugin</category>
<enclosure url="http://i.imgur.com/QRmjVBC.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 03:07:21 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Ranks with Achievements Classify your affiliates into separate ranks and assign a different commission level. Each Affiliate can be promoted to the next Rank once reached the Achievements Unlimited Affiliates There is no limit for your number of Affiliates that can promote your products and services Custom Amount Set a Percentage or Flat Amount for each Rank, Offer or custom commission, such a MLM rewards Special Offers Affiliates can earn different commissions based on which product/s are purchased. The Offer can be limited by a Date Range. Multi-level Marketing Turn On your Affiliate platform into a MLM system that will boost your own affiliates to recruit new leads. Based on your needs there can be set a UniLevel Plan, Force Matrix or Binary Matrix system. Lifetime Commissions Allow your affiliates to receive a commission on all future purchases by the customer. Now worries anymore about Cookies or different browsers Performance Bonuses Set bonus commissions when one of your Affiliate touch a specific Rank or when he signUp for the first time. Each Rank may have a different Bonus. Banners Management Provides different Banners that will help your Affiliates to promote your products and services on any website with an embedded code. PayPal Payouts Pay your Affiliates their earnings via PayPal directly from Ultimate Affiliate Pro dashboard with just few clicks. Choose to pay specific Referrals or the entire Deposit. Stripe Payouts Pay your US Affiliates their earnings via Stripe directly from Ultimate Affiliate Pro dashboard with just few clicks. Recurring Referrals Award Commissions for recurring subscriptions into Membership systems with a custom amount and a different one from one Rank to another. Allow Own Referrals Allow for your Affiliate to earn commissions from their own referrals Signup Referrals Available for Membership system awarding a flat commission when referred user sign Up Social Share Integrated with Social Share&amp;amp;Locker provides Share button options for your Affiliate to share their Affiliate Links on Social Network. OptIn Integration 9 Email Marketing Platforms integrated where you can store your Affiliates Emails for further Newsletter campaigns. Landing Commission Special module to cover any desired workflow by reward the affiliates based on a Landing Page, such a successful register or complete payment stage. Wallet Affiliates will have the options to spend their Earnings directly into the Website during further purchases based on Generated Coupons with specific flat discount. Affiliate Coupons Correlate an Affiliate with a WooCommerce, Easy Digital Download or Ultimate Membership Pro coupon code to be rewarded when a customer use that Coupon into your systems. Affiliate Custom Slug Provides Personal slugs besides the default username or ID so Affiliates can hide their identity or company name behind a Custom slug. Friendly Affiliate Links Affiliates will be able to use friendly links instead of the default one with a better looking structure when the link is shared and much easier to read Fair Checkout Reward Customers decides who affiliate will be rewarded during the Checkout process. BuddyPress Account Page Integrate the Affiliate Account Page section directly into BudyPress Account page as a regular tab. WooCommerce Account Page Integrate the Affiliate Account Page section directly into WooCommerce Account page as a regular tab. Custom Currency If your Currency is not available into the system, you can add your own currency for further use. Top Affiliates Provides public list with your top affiliates ordered by Earning, Referrals or Visits with 10 predefined templates Custom Fields Form Multiple Custom Fields types that will provide a fully customized Register Form. Account Page Over 15 Menu tab with different options and fully customizable based on 2 predefined Templates and specific sections. Affiliate Info There are many shortcodes that will help you to display for each logged Affiliate personal Info all over the website. Translation Ready Ultimate Affiliate Pro is ready to work into any language being fully translation ready. Reports Detailed Affiliate reports or payments stats for Admin and each Affiliate into Account Page. Notifications Email Notifications for different actions or stages to Affiliates and system Admin</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<p></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/od4VdzcAT9M?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><p></p><br><h3>Features</h3><br><p><br><ul><li> Ranks with Achievements<br></li><li> Classify your affiliates into separate ranks and assign a different commission level. Each Affiliate can be promoted to the next Rank once reached the Achievements<br></li><li> Unlimited Affiliates<br></li><li> There is no limit for your number of Affiliates that can promote your products and services<br></li><li> Custom Amount<br></li><li> Set a Percentage or Flat Amount for each Rank, Offer or custom commission, such a MLM rewards<br></li><li> Special Offers<br></li><li> Affiliates can earn different commissions based on which product/s are purchased. The Offer can be limited by a Date Range.<br></li><li> Multi-level Marketing<br></li><li> Turn On your Affiliate platform into a MLM system that will boost your own affiliates to recruit new leads. Based on your needs there can be set a UniLevel Plan, Force Matrix or Binary Matrix system.<br></li><li> Lifetime Commissions<br></li><li> Allow your affiliates to receive a commission on all future purchases by the customer. Now worries anymore about Cookies or different browsers<br></li><li> Performance Bonuses<br></li><li> Set bonus commissions when one of your Affiliate touch a specific Rank or when he signUp for the first time. Each Rank may have a different Bonus.<br></li><li> Banners Management<br></li><li> Provides different Banners that will help your Affiliates to promote your products and services on any website with an embedded code.<br></li><li> PayPal Payouts<br></li><li> Pay your Affiliates their earnings via PayPal directly from Ultimate Affiliate Pro dashboard with just few clicks. Choose to pay specific Referrals or the entire Deposit.<br></li><li> Stripe Payouts<br></li><li> Pay your US Affiliates their earnings via Stripe directly from Ultimate Affiliate Pro dashboard with just few clicks.<br></li><li> Recurring Referrals<br></li><li> Award Commissions for recurring subscriptions into Membership systems with a custom amount and a different one from one Rank to another.<br></li><li> Allow Own Referrals<br></li><li> Allow for your Affiliate to earn commissions from their own referrals<br></li><li> Signup Referrals<br></li><li> Available for Membership system awarding a flat commission when referred user sign Up<br></li><li> Social Share<br></li><li> Integrated with Social Share&amp;Locker provides Share button options for your Affiliate to share their Affiliate Links on Social Network.<br></li><li> OptIn Integration<br></li><li> 9 Email Marketing Platforms integrated where you can store your Affiliates Emails for further Newsletter campaigns.<br></li><li> Landing Commission<br></li><li> Special module to cover any desired workflow by reward the affiliates based on a Landing Page, such a successful register or complete payment stage.<br></li><li> Wallet<br></li><li> Affiliates will have the options to spend their Earnings directly into the Website during further purchases based on Generated Coupons with specific flat discount.<br></li><li> Affiliate Coupons<br></li><li> Correlate an Affiliate with a WooCommerce, Easy Digital Download or Ultimate Membership Pro coupon code to be rewarded when a customer use that Coupon into your systems.<br></li><li> Affiliate Custom Slug<br></li><li> Provides Personal slugs besides the default username or ID so Affiliates can hide their identity or company name behind a Custom slug.<br></li><li> Friendly Affiliate Links<br></li><li> Affiliates will be able to use friendly links instead of the default one with a better looking structure when the link is shared and much easier to read<br></li><li> Fair Checkout Reward<br></li><li> Customers decides who affiliate will be rewarded during the Checkout process.<br></li><li> BuddyPress Account Page<br></li><li> Integrate the Affiliate Account Page section directly into BudyPress Account page as a regular tab.<br></li><li> WooCommerce Account Page<br></li><li> Integrate the Affiliate Account Page section directly into WooCommerce Account page as a regular tab.<br></li><li> Custom Currency<br></li><li> If your Currency is not available into the system, you can add your own currency for further use.<br></li><li> Top Affiliates<br></li><li> Provides public list with your top affiliates ordered by Earning, Referrals or Visits with 10 predefined templates<br></li><li> Custom Fields Form<br></li><li> Multiple Custom Fields types that will provide a fully customized Register Form.<br></li><li> Account Page<br></li><li> Over 15 Menu tab with different options and fully customizable based on 2 predefined Templates and specific sections.<br></li><li> Affiliate Info<br></li><li> There are many shortcodes that will help you to display for each logged Affiliate personal Info all over the website.<br></li><li> Translation Ready<br></li><li> Ultimate Affiliate Pro is ready to work into any language being fully translation ready.<br></li><li> Reports<br></li><li> Detailed Affiliate reports or payments stats for Admin and each Affiliate into Account Page.<br></li><li> Notifications<br></li><li> Email Notifications for different actions or stages to Affiliates and system Admin<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://i.imgur.com/QRmjVBC.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Ultimate Affiliate Pro 3.6"></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Hijackrr Pro 2.0.3</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3645-hijackrr.html</link>
<description>Name : Hijackrr Pro Version : 2.0.3 Type : Cloak Links Plugins Price : $390 Homepage : SalePage Hijackrr is a brand new state of the art software that allows you to hijack any website in the world and build your own money making machines that convert due to the high level of trust the visitor has for the authority website you initially send them to. Hijackrr combines tricks and tactics that force visitors to interact, opt-in and stay longer on your sites. This enables you to drive visitors to where you want them to be, build emails lists with ease and make commission and sales on auto pilot.</description>
<category>Affiliate plugin</category>
<enclosure url="https://images.clickfunnels.com/7e/b55460291e11e7914703c328778a01/mix2-2.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2017 03:46:56 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Newbie-Friendly plugin is easy to install and use… even with no “tech skills&quot; Hijack the authority of ANY website online in minutes M.comize ANY website you want… Imagine having your affiliate links on sites like Amazon or CNN Get FREE Viral traffic in minutes Boost your sales and get more leads with a few mouse clicks It’s easy-to-customize EVERYTHING inside the plugin for maximum flexibility</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/BEFLJBgOc9E?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><br><ul><li> Newbie-Friendly plugin is easy to install and use… even with no “tech skills"<br></li><li> Hijack the authority of ANY website online in minutes<br></li><li> M.comize ANY website you want… Imagine having your affiliate links on sites like Amazon or CNN<br></li><li> Get FREE Viral traffic in minutes<br></li><li> Boost your sales and get more leads with a few mouse clicks<br></li><li> It’s easy-to-customize EVERYTHING inside the plugin for maximum flexibility<br></li></ul><br><img src="https://images.clickfunnels.com/7e/b55460291e11e7914703c328778a01/mix2-2.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Hijackrr Pro 2.0.3"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>WordPress Affiliate &amp; Referral Plugin 3.1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3538-wordpress-affiliate-amp-referral-plugin-310.html</link>
<description>Name :WordPress Affiliate &amp;amp; Referral Plugin Version : 3.1.0 OS : Linux Type : add-ons Price : 20 Homepage : SalePage WordPress Affiliate &amp;amp; Referral is a very useful plugin that extends your WordPress website with a very effective affiliate / referral system. Starting with v3.0.0 the plugin offers the option to pay affiliates via PayPal Pass Payment system.</description>
<category>Affiliate plugin</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2017 00:22:45 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Easy translations via .po/.mo files Real-time reporting Real-time email notifications for affiliates Option to pay your affiliates with PayPal MassPay (mass payments) Unlimited referrals, unlimited affiliates Statistics (per month, per user) Custom registration URL option (new) Built-in shortcodes Wp.Referral.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Wp.Referral.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Wp.Referral.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Wp.Referral.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Wp.Referral.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<br><b>Features</b><br><ul><li>Easy translations via .po/.mo files<br></li><li>Real-time reporting<br></li><li>Real-time email notifications for affiliates<br></li><li>Option to pay your affiliates with PayPal MassPay (mass payments)<br></li><li>Unlimited referrals, unlimited affiliates<br></li><li>Statistics (per month, per user)<br></li><li>Custom registration URL option (new)<br></li><li>Built-in shortcodes<br></li></ul><br><br> <div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="WordPress Affiliate &amp; Referral Plugin 3.1.0"><br><div class="quote"><br><br><a href="https://clicknupload.link/uiy5v6van8cf"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Wp.Referral.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://dailyuploads.com/m480ebqvepb2"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Wp.Referral.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://uploadocean.com/8j571tphaeyb"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Wp.Referral.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://uplod.ws/clfaz5ztdosm"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Wp.Referral.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://userscloud.com/8gnzyu8ltz89"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Wp.Referral.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br></div><br><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>iTunes Shortcode 1.4.5 - WordPress Plugin</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3537-itunes-shortcode-145-wordpress-plugin.html</link>
<description>Name :iTunes Shortcode - WordPress Plugin Version : 1.4.5 OS : Linux Type : Utilities Price : Homepage : SalePage Free iTunes Shortcode is a WordPress Plugin, which allows you to present always up-to-date information about iTunes Store products (Mac and iOS App Store Apps, iBook Store Ebooks and iTunes Music Store Albums/Songs - more is coming soon) in posts in a simple and elegant way and to earn money in the iTunes Affiliate Program.</description>
<category>Affiliate plugin</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2017 00:22:41 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features three ways of presenting data automatically generate top free/paid/grossing list of iTunes products iTunes Affiliate Program support (PHG) showing information about price reductions QR codes custom CSS responsive ready for translation (.po files) data caching (reducing the number of connections to iTunes lookup) support for soft-launched apps (when they is available only in selected countries) Itunes.Shortcode.Wordpress.Plugin.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Itunes.Shortcode.Wordpress.Plugin.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Itunes.Shortcode.Wordpress.Plugin.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Itunes.Shortcode.Wordpress.Plugin.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Itunes.Shortcode.Wordpress.Plugin.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<br><b>Features</b><br><ul><li>three ways of presenting data<br></li><li>automatically generate top free/paid/grossing list of iTunes products<br></li><li>iTunes Affiliate Program support (PHG)<br></li><li>showing information about price reductions<br></li><li>QR codes<br></li><li>custom CSS<br></li><li>responsive<br></li><li>ready for translation (.po files)<br></li><li>data caching (reducing the number of connections to iTunes lookup)<br></li><li>support for soft-launched apps (when they is available only in selected countries)<br></li></ul><br><br> <div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="iTunes Shortcode 1.4.5 - WordPress Plugin"><br><div class="quote"><br><br><a href="https://clicknupload.link/v5xfzlzdqzdk"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Itunes.Shortcode.Wordpress.Plugin.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://dailyuploads.com/vq6xpt4gwuur"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Itunes.Shortcode.Wordpress.Plugin.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://uploadocean.com/pw1f08hl439w"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Itunes.Shortcode.Wordpress.Plugin.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://uplod.ws/aiev4hntwngw"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Itunes.Shortcode.Wordpress.Plugin.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://userscloud.com/lesnbb8uupig"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Itunes.Shortcode.Wordpress.Plugin.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br></div><br><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>iTunes Content 1.3 - WordPress Plugin</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3536-itunes-content-13-wordpress-plugin.html</link>
<description>Name :iTunes Content - WordPress Plugin Version : 1.3 OS : Linux Type : Utilities Price : 12 Homepage : SalePage Through iTunes, users can purchase and download music, music videos, television shows, audiobooks, podcasts, movies and more. You can now easily add this content to your WordPress website with the Free iTunes Content plugin!</description>
<category>Affiliate plugin</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2017 00:22:37 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Easily add iTunes Content to your WordPress website! Fully Responsive! Support for 120 countries and 27 feed types! Affiliate enabled - earn $$$! Custom widget and [itunes] shortcode included! Custom shortcode generator makes adding iTunes Content even easier! Requests to iTunes are cached to speed up your website! YouTube integration to show videos in a lightbox! Itunes.Content.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Itunes.Content.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Itunes.Content.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Itunes.Content.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Itunes.Content.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<br><b>Features</b><br><ul><li>Easily add iTunes Content to your WordPress website!<br></li><li>Fully Responsive!<br></li><li>Support for 120 countries and 27 feed types!<br></li><li>Affiliate enabled - earn $$$!<br></li><li>Custom widget and [itunes] shortcode included!<br></li><li>Custom shortcode generator makes adding iTunes Content even easier!<br></li><li>Requests to iTunes are cached to speed up your website!<br></li><li>YouTube integration to show videos in a lightbox!<br></li></ul><br><br> <div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="iTunes Content 1.3 - WordPress Plugin"><br><div class="quote"><br><br><a href="https://clicknupload.link/ozkiwd16d6uz"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Itunes.Content.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://dailyuploads.com/yq4vos11j0dq"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Itunes.Content.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://uploadocean.com/7nf2ov58uxcj"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Itunes.Content.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://uplod.ws/oowu725gzgjk"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Itunes.Content.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://userscloud.com/tbcs8fps17e3"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Itunes.Content.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br></div><br><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Envato Affiliate Cash for WordPress 1.0.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3535-envato-affiliate-cash-for-wordpress-100.html</link>
<description>Name :Envato Affiliate Cash for WordPress Version : 1.0.0 OS : Linux Type : Advertising Price : 6 Homepage : SalePage Envato Affiliate Cash for WordPress makes it easy to generate tons of referals to Envato by automagically converting your marketplace links to referral URLs. Do you have a site with a bunch of Envato links already in your posts, comments etc? Are you looking for an easy way to make an affiliate site for Envato? Envato Affiliate Cash is all you need!</description>
<category>Affiliate plugin</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2017 00:22:33 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Installs in seconds, takes even less time to configure! Three different levels of link replacement to choose from - Posts content + post meta, excerpt content and RSS, and even comment content, URLs and comment RSS! Simply select what content to serarch through and the plugin does all the work! Not only adds your own referal code to all links, but Envato Cash will also replace other people&#039;s affiliate links with your own! Inbuilt Cloaking Support! - Easily hide your referal links using the goo.gl service! Includes support for the goo.gl API so you can track your referal links! AJAX admin panel! Includes full documentation and instructions. Envato.Cash.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Envato.Cash.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Envato.Cash.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Envato.Cash.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Envato.Cash.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<br><b>Features</b><br><ul><li>Installs in seconds, takes even less time to configure!<br></li><li>Three different levels of link replacement to choose from - Posts content + post meta, excerpt content and RSS, and even comment content, URLs and comment RSS! Simply select what content to serarch through and the plugin does all the work!<br></li><li>Not only adds your own referal code to all links, but Envato Cash will also replace other people's affiliate links with your own!<br></li><li>Inbuilt Cloaking Support! - Easily hide your referal links using the goo.gl service!<br></li><li>Includes support for the goo.gl API so you can track your referal links!<br></li><li>AJAX admin panel!<br></li><li>Includes full documentation and instructions.<br></li></ul><br><br> <div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Envato Affiliate Cash for WordPress 1.0.0"><br><div class="quote"><br><br><a href="https://clicknupload.link/ff745ip71ph6"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Envato.Cash.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://dailyuploads.com/qaaf0slhjv0m"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Envato.Cash.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://uploadocean.com/t8sl2vpsqil8"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Envato.Cash.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://uplod.ws/9b4tay8bahl7"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Envato.Cash.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://userscloud.com/l60th9586bsb"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Envato.Cash.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><br></div><br><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>CashCow 1.0 - Affiliate Based Money Making System</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3534-cashcow-10-affiliate-based-money-making-system.html</link>
<description>Name :CashCow - Affiliate Based Money Making System Version : 1.0 OS : Linux Type : Miscellaneous Price : 21 Homepage : SalePage CashCow plugin free helps you to collect and show marketplace items&#039; information automatically and immediately on your site. Of course with your referral link. Therefore you don&#039;t need to waste your time for creating posts with new marketplace items. The CashCow wordpress plugin free purpose is to create your site posts easily with the market items, it&#039;s not generating original content for your site. Then you need to make significant content changes or something more on your site content after you run the plugin, such as adding more review message, reproduction of item features that let search engine consider as different contents.</description>
<category>Affiliate plugin</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2017 00:22:29 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Automatic Post Creation Automatic Cron Job with Schedule Unlimited Threats Works on All Envato MarketPlaces Easy to Use Easy to Customize, has Codex Automatic Category Creation Automatic Tags Creation Selection of Specific category Included Free CashCow Theme Affiliate.Based.Money.Making.System.1.0.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Affiliate.Based.Money.Making.System.1.0.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Affiliate.Based.Money.Making.System.1.0.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Affiliate.Based.Money.Making.System.1.0.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Affiliate.Based.Money.Making.System.1.0.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<br><b>Features</b><br><ul><li>Automatic Post Creation<br></li><li>Automatic Cron Job with Schedule<br></li><li>Unlimited Threats<br></li><li>Works on All Envato MarketPlaces<br></li><li>Easy to Use<br></li><li>Easy to Customize, has Codex<br></li><li>Automatic Category Creation<br></li><li>Automatic Tags Creation<br></li><li>Selection of Specific category<br></li><li>Included Free CashCow Theme<br></li></ul><br><br> <div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="CashCow 1.0 - Affiliate Based Money Making System"><br><div class="quote"><br><br><a href="https://clicknupload.link/yhxv27qi1a5s"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Affiliate.Based.Money.Making.System.1.0.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://dailyuploads.com/4dl26u582fdg"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Affiliate.Based.Money.Making.System.1.0.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://uploadocean.com/tv7duvixwo9a"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Affiliate.Based.Money.Making.System.1.0.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://uplod.ws/rqyv0rfwj6ax"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Affiliate.Based.Money.Making.System.1.0.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://userscloud.com/txvgcxhawd98"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Affiliate.Based.Money.Making.System.1.0.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><br></div><br><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>WP-Lister Pro for eBay 2.0.9.14</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1544-wp-lister-pro-for-ebay.html</link>
<description>Name : WP-Lister Pro for eBay Version : 2.0.9.14 Type : Cache plugin Price : $39 Homepage : SalePage WP-Lister connects your WooCommerce site with your eBay Store. You can select multiple products right from your products page, select a profile to apply a set of predefined options and list them all on eBay with just a few clicks. We worked hard to make WP-Lister easy to use but flexible. The workflow of listing items requires not a single click more than necessary. Due to its tight integration in WordPress, you will will feel right at home. Go ahead and download the free version from wordpress.org or buy WP-Lister Pro for eBay right away. Have a look on the feature comparison to see how WP-Lister Pro can save you even more time.</description>
<category>Affiliate plugin</category>
<enclosure url="http://i.imgur.com/tva70E3.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2017 00:38:22 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features manage any number of listing from WP set up a profile once and apply to multiple products verify items and get expected listing fees sync inventory between eBay and WordPress create eBay orders in WooCommerce choose categories from eBay and your eBay Store map your custom categories to eBay categories national and international shipping options supports calculated shipping services best offer options and private listings support for product variations unique feature to split variations into single items create custom listing templates using WordPress post editor built in template editor with HTML / CSS syntax highlighting template engine supports color pickers, custom php code and more download and upload listing templates as zip files</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<br><div style="text-align:center;"><div class="dlevideoplayer" style="width:100%;max-width:425px;"><ul data-theme="default" data-preload="metadata"><li data-title="" data-type="youtube" data-url="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zBQilzwr9UI"></li></ul></div></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> manage any number of listing from WP<br></li><li> set up a profile once and apply to multiple products<br></li><li> verify items and get expected listing fees<br></li><li> sync inventory between eBay and WordPress<br></li><li> create eBay orders in WooCommerce<br></li><li> choose categories from eBay and your eBay Store<br></li><li> map your custom categories to eBay categories<br></li><li> national and international shipping options<br></li><li> supports calculated shipping services<br></li><li> best offer options and private listings<br></li><li> support for product variations<br></li><li> unique feature to split variations into single items<br></li><li> create custom listing templates using WordPress post editor<br></li><li> built in template editor with HTML / CSS syntax highlighting<br></li><li> template engine supports color pickers, custom php code and more<br></li><li> download and upload listing templates as zip files<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://i.imgur.com/tva70E3.png" alt="WP-Lister Pro for eBay 2.0.9.14"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>AffiliateWP 2.0.10.1</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/796-affiliatewp.html</link>
<description>Name : AffiliateWP + Add-ons Version : 2.0.10.1 Type : Affiliate Plugin Price : $449 Homepage : SalePage Free AffiliateWP WordPress Plugin has complete integration with all major WordPress ecommerce and membership plugins. Nulled AffiliateWP WordPress Plugin tracks affiliate referrals reliably, even on servers with aggressive caching. Free AffiliateWP Plugin looks, and feels like it&#039;s part of WordPress. Have an unlimited number of affiliates actively promoting your products and services. Affiliates can easily see how much they have earned, how much is awaiting payment, and even how their referral URLs have done over time.</description>
<category>Affiliate plugin</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2017 01:37:18 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Easy setup Unlimited affiliates Automatic affiliate creation Referral rate types Simple shortcodes Developer-friendly Fully internationalized REST API Customizable emails Easy affiliate registration Manual affiliate approval Unlimited creatives Accurate affiliate tracking Complete integration Affiliate coupon tracking Affiliate Area Affiliate URLs Export data to CSV WP-CLI integration Performance-ready Payout Logs Set cookie expiration Referral link generator Easy affiliate management Real-time reporting Extensive documentation Affiliatewp.2.0.3.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Affiliatewp.2.0.3.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Affiliatewp.2.0.3.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Affiliatewp.2.0.3.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Affiliatewp.2.0.3.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li>Easy setup<br></li><li>Unlimited affiliates<br></li><li>Automatic affiliate creation<br></li><li>Referral rate types<br></li><li>Simple shortcodes<br></li><li>Developer-friendly<br></li><li>Fully internationalized<br></li><li>REST API<br></li><li>Customizable emails<br></li><li>Easy affiliate registration<br></li><li>Manual affiliate approval<br></li><li>Unlimited creatives<br></li><li>Accurate affiliate tracking<br></li><li>Complete integration<br></li><li>Affiliate coupon tracking<br></li><li>Affiliate Area<br></li><li>Affiliate URLs<br></li><li>Export data to CSV<br></li><li>WP-CLI integration<br></li><li>Performance-ready<br></li><li>Payout Logs<br></li><li>Set cookie expiration<br></li><li>Referral link generator<br></li><li>Easy affiliate management<br></li><li>Real-time reporting<br></li><li>Extensive documentation<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="AffiliateWP 2.0.10.1"><br><div class="quote"><br><a href="https://clicknupload.link/codvjpix71sy"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Affiliatewp.2.0.3.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://dailyuploads.com/xgl61wpqeopb"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Affiliatewp.2.0.3.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://uploadocean.com/fdzkqji0tzqu"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Affiliatewp.2.0.3.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://uplod.ws/yxbx9i79iakc"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Affiliatewp.2.0.3.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://userscloud.com/wge0n062o93l"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Affiliatewp.2.0.3.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br></div><br></div><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>AutoZON Builder v1.2</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/800-autozon-builder.html</link>
<description>Name : AutoZON Builder Version : 1.2 Type : Amazon Aff Plugin Price : $18 Homepage : SalePage &quot;Build A Complete Amazon Affiliate Website In Under 60 Seconds With AutoZON Builder...&quot; AutoZON Builder + Azon Plugin Bundle - Build Complete Amazon Affiliate Sites At Lightning Speeds</description>
<category>Affiliate plugin</category>
<enclosure url="http://i.imgur.com/5QX3PWT.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 09:27:10 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<br><div style="text-align:center;"><div class="dlevideoplayer" style="width:100%;max-width:425px;"><ul data-theme="default" data-preload="metadata"><li data-title="" data-type="youtube" data-url="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=shh78GFiiMA"></li></ul></div></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><img src="http://i.imgur.com/5QX3PWT.png" alt="AutoZON Builder v1.2"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>