<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Bulk Mail Sender - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Bulk Mail Sender - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>Black Bulk Mail Elite 1.4.5</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1060-black-bulk-mail.html</link>
<description>Name : Black Bulk Mail Version : Elite 1.4.5 OS : Windows Type : Email Marketing Tools Price : $699 Homepage : SalePage BlackBulkMail - The Smartest Mailer On the Earth! BlackBulkMail can not only uses the biggest email services(hotmail/outlook/live, yahoo, gmail and aol) to send emails, but also it can let you create yourself sending template to send emails using any email account. BlackBulkMail uses webmail (no smtp) to send emails just like you do in your regular browser.</description>
<category>Bulk Mail Sender</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.blackbulkmail.com/css/images/slide-img.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 13:02:05 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Task - Create, Manage and Run Unlimited Task(s) Create and run unlimited task(s) at the same time. Create and run a maximum of 2 task(s) at the same time. Create and run a maximum of 1 task at the same time. Send emails using webmail with no need for smtp. Send unlimited emails using yahoo/outlook/gmail/aol/hotmail accounts super fast. Customize your sending settings using &#039;TO&#039;, &#039;BCC&#039; or &#039;CC&#039; and set the number of recipients per email. Seed email function - add your own email addresses so that you can monitor your inbox success rate. Suppress list - BBM will not send emails to the recipients in this list. (List normally supplied by your CPA company) Loop send option to guarantee that all emails are sent successfully. BBM is 100% set and forget. Realtime sending stats. Account - Perfect Account Management Manage millions of accounts for different task(s). Auto-categorized accounts based on account status (valid, invalid, banned, blocked and locked etc) Remove non functional accounts automatically, so that all tasks will always use working accounts to send emails. Template - Create Amazing Email Template Easily! Add unlimited email templates, so that you can run different campaigns at the same time. Create and send html email templates. Create and send plaint text email templates. Load csv files to create personalised variables in the email template, so that you can send emails such as: &quot;Hi [name],&quot;. Supports the use of tokenized variables or spun text to create unique subjects and messages. Settings - Proxy, Captcha and Spinner Settings Supports unlimited threads for every task to send emails super fast. Supports a maximum of 3 threads for every task to send emails fast. Only supports 1 thread for every task. Auto-captcha solving solution support. Select proxies randomly. Can auto-bind proxy with accounts so that the account logs in with te same IP every time. Helps to prevent account ban. Stats - Full Statistical Functions! Get realtime and full sending stats for every task (Sent, Left, Success Amount, Failed Amount and Speed etc.) Get realtime accounts status stats (valid, invalid, locked, need verify and blocked etc.) Get email open stats. Get update freely.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/9VKDWp58cDk?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Task - Create, Manage and Run Unlimited Task(s)<br></li><li> Create and run unlimited task(s) at the same time. 			<br></li><li> Create and run a maximum of 2 task(s) at the same time. 			<br></li><li> Create and run a maximum of 1 task at the same time. 			<br></li><li> Send emails using webmail with no need for smtp. 			<br></li><li> Send unlimited emails using yahoo/outlook/gmail/aol/hotmail accounts super fast. 			<br></li><li> Customize your sending settings using 'TO', 'BCC' or 'CC' and set the number of recipients per email. 			<br></li><li> Seed email function - add your own email addresses so that you can monitor your inbox success rate. 			<br></li><li> Suppress list - BBM will not send emails to the recipients in this list. (List normally supplied by your CPA company) 			<br></li><li> Loop send option to guarantee that all emails are sent successfully. BBM is 100% set and forget. 			<br></li><li> Realtime sending stats. 			<br></li><li> Account - Perfect Account Management<br></li><li> Manage millions of accounts for different task(s). 			<br></li><li> Auto-categorized accounts based on account status (valid, invalid, banned, blocked and locked etc) 			<br></li><li> Remove non functional accounts automatically, so that all tasks will always use working accounts to send emails. 			<br></li><li> Template - Create Amazing Email Template Easily!<br></li><li> Add unlimited email templates, so that you can run different campaigns at the same time. 			<br></li><li> Create and send html email templates. 			<br></li><li> Create and send plaint text email templates. 			<br></li><li> Load csv files to create personalised variables in the email template, so that you can send emails such as: "Hi [name],". 			<br></li><li> Supports the use of tokenized variables or spun text to create unique subjects and messages. 			<br></li><li> Settings - Proxy, Captcha and Spinner Settings<br></li><li> Supports unlimited threads for every task to send emails super fast. 			<br></li><li> Supports a maximum of 3 threads for every task to send emails fast. 			<br></li><li> Only supports 1 thread for every task. 			<br></li><li> Auto-captcha solving solution support. 			<br></li><li> Select proxies randomly. 			<br></li><li> Can auto-bind proxy with accounts so that the account logs in with te same IP every time. Helps to prevent account ban. 			<br></li><li> Stats - Full Statistical Functions!<br></li><li> Get realtime and full sending stats for every task (Sent, Left, Success Amount, Failed Amount and Speed etc.) 			<br></li><li> Get realtime accounts status stats (valid, invalid, locked, need verify and blocked etc.) 			<br></li><li> Get email open stats. 			<br></li><li> Get update freely.<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://www.blackbulkmail.com/css/images/slide-img.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Black Bulk Mail Elite 1.4.5"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Fast Bulk Mailer Pro 2.3</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1065-fast-bulk-mailer.html</link>
<description>Name : FastBulkMailerPro Version : 2.3 OS : Windows Type : Email sender Price : $347 Homepage : SalePage FastBulkMail is designed for the email marketers who want to send many emails per day, it is a super fast bulk emails sender that can send hundreds of emails per minute. FastBulkMail uses outlook web page inteface to send emails without smtp needed. And the inbox rate is over 90% with right settings.</description>
<category>Bulk Mail Sender</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 04:00:30 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Number of tasks to create and run at the same time : Unlimited The number of threads available per task : Unlimited Sending speed per minute : Over 1000 Emails Send emails using webmail with no need for smtp. Customize your sending settings using &#039;TO&#039;, &#039;BCC&#039; or &#039;CC&#039; and set the number of recipients per email. Seed email function - add your own email addresses so that you can monitor your inbox success rate. Loop send option to guarantee that all emails are sent successfully. BBM is 100% set and forget. Add unlimited email templates, so that you can run different campaigns at the same time. Create and send html email templates. Load csv files to create personalised variables in the email template, so that you can send emails such as: &quot;Hi [name],&quot;. Supports the use of tokenized variables or spun text to create unique subjects and messages. Manage millions of accounts for different task(s). Auto-categorized accounts based on account status (valid, invalid, banned, blocked and locked etc). Remove non functional accounts automatically, so that all tasks will always use working accounts to send emails. Auto-captcha solving solution support. Can auto-bind proxy with accounts so that the account logs in with te same IP every time. Helps to prevent account ban. Get realtime and full sending stats for every task (Sent, Left, Success Amount, Failed Amount and Speed etc.) Get realtime accounts status stats (valid, invalid, locked, need verify and blocked etc.)</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/SfZhp4motKY?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Number of tasks to create and run at the same time : Unlimited<br></li><li> The number of threads available per task : Unlimited<br></li><li> Sending speed per minute : Over 1000 Emails<br></li><li> Send emails using webmail with no need for smtp.<br></li><li> Customize your sending settings using 'TO', 'BCC' or 'CC' and set the number of recipients per email.<br></li><li> Seed email function - add your own email addresses so that you can monitor your inbox success rate.<br></li><li> Loop send option to guarantee that all emails are sent successfully. BBM is 100% set and forget.<br></li><li> Add unlimited email templates, so that you can run different campaigns at the same time.<br></li><li> Create and send html email templates.<br></li><li> Load csv files to create personalised variables in the email template, so that you can send emails such as: "Hi [name],".<br></li><li> Supports the use of tokenized variables or spun text to create unique subjects and messages.<br></li><li> Manage millions of accounts for different task(s).<br></li><li> Auto-categorized accounts based on account status (valid, invalid, banned, blocked and locked etc).<br></li><li> Remove non functional accounts automatically, so that all tasks will always use working accounts to send emails.<br></li><li> Auto-captcha solving solution support.<br></li><li> Can auto-bind proxy with accounts so that the account logs in with te same IP every time. Helps to prevent account ban.<br></li><li> Get realtime and full sending stats for every task (Sent, Left, Success Amount, Failed Amount and Speed etc.)<br></li><li> Get realtime accounts status stats (valid, invalid, locked, need verify and blocked etc.)<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Fast Bulk Mailer Pro 2.3"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Email Jeet 2.5.8.0 Pro</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1292-email-jeet.html</link>
<description>Name : Email Jeet Version : 2.5.8.0 Pro OS : Windows Type : Email Marketing Tools Price : $97 Homepage : SalePage Email Jeet is Desktop Autoresponder app that has all the features u can expect from an autoresponder Email Jeet 2 is the most powerful desktop mail automation tool ever created. There’s nothing close or in comparison anywhere. This is the product that everyone desperately needs. Emailing is something everyone is trying to improve &amp;amp; fix every day. An easy to use interface that a regular computer user can mater in no time at all, with everything available at the user’s fingertips. You can send your emails direct from your computer or a VPS (if you’re a big sender) without bowing to the whims and fancies of autoresponders, and with TOTAL CONTROL over your list and emailing.Included 1.List Management 2.Optin Forms 3.Unsubscribes 4.Mail Sequencing</description>
<category>Bulk Mail Sender</category>
<enclosure url="http://emailjeet.com/Content/emailimg/logo.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://emailjeet.com/Content/emailimg/adds.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 20:30:41 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Plug in any SMTP service Use on your desktop computer. No server or domain name required Create optin forms and get signups List management &amp;amp; and unsubscribe function Mail sequencing and autoresponder functions Desktop Email automation! No need to log in anywhere or remember passwords. Total Freedom! Email Jeet works with any SMTP provider that has a SMTP interface. It can even work with your hosting! Freely import your list! Email Jeet doesn’t need double optin or single optin. If your legitimately acquired list, you can import it right into Email Jeet and mail it instantly. Only you have your list! Never feel insecure about your list. You don’t need to upload it anywhere and worry about who has access to it and what they can use it for. Get Better Delivery! Certain mailing provider getting you bad delivery? No problems! Migrate your list instantly to another SMTP provider and mail out. Keep your delivery rates and open rates high always. Don’t be held at ransom by autoresponder! Autoresponder has all your list and you are their slave because you can’t migrate or import. With Email Jeet you can import your list freely and send it by using any SMTP! No need to pay monthly! Stop paying a hefty monthly fee to manage your lists and send your emails. With Email Jeet you’ll pay only for the mails you send out (To the SMTP provider). Take a break, a vacation, come back and resume without having to pay for the time you were gone. Perfect for Big &amp;amp; Small List Owners! Small list owners, don’t pay a monthly fee. Get Email Jeet one time, and mail forever. Big list owners, get more control over your emailing and access to multiple SMTP providers! No Downtime! Ever experience autoresponder downtime? Won’t happen with Email Jeet as it’s on your PC. Mail anywhere you want, anytime you want. Emailjeet connect to any smtp service including</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ViHfOwlfZYw?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><p></p><br><h3>Features</h3><br><p><br><ul><li> Plug in any SMTP service<br></li><li> Use on your desktop computer. No server or domain name required<br></li><li> Create optin forms and get signups<br></li><li> List management &amp; and unsubscribe function<br></li><li> Mail sequencing and autoresponder functions<br></li><li> Desktop Email automation! No need to log in anywhere or remember passwords.<br></li><li> Total Freedom! Email Jeet works with any SMTP provider that has a SMTP interface. It can even work with your hosting!<br></li><li> Freely import your list! Email Jeet doesn’t need double optin or single optin. If your legitimately acquired list, you can import it right into Email Jeet and mail it instantly.<br></li><li> Only you have your list! Never feel insecure about your list. You don’t need to upload it anywhere and worry about who has access to it and what they can use it for.<br></li><li> Get Better Delivery! Certain mailing provider getting you bad delivery? No problems! Migrate your list instantly to another SMTP provider and mail out. Keep your delivery rates and open rates high always.<br></li><li> Don’t be held at ransom by autoresponder! Autoresponder has all your list and you are their slave because you can’t migrate or import. With Email Jeet you can import your list freely and send it by using any SMTP!<br></li><li> No need to pay monthly! Stop paying a hefty monthly fee to manage your lists and send your emails. With Email Jeet you’ll pay only for the mails you send out (To the SMTP provider). Take a break, a vacation, come back and resume without having to pay for the time you were gone.<br></li><li> Perfect for Big &amp; Small List Owners! Small list owners, don’t pay a monthly fee. Get Email Jeet one time, and mail forever. Big list owners, get more control over your emailing and access to multiple SMTP providers!<br></li><li> No Downtime! Ever experience autoresponder downtime? Won’t happen with Email Jeet as it’s on your PC. Mail anywhere you want, anytime you want.<br></li></ul><br>Emailjeet connect to any smtp service including<br><img src="http://emailjeet.com/Content/emailimg/logo.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Email Jeet 2.5.8.0 Pro"><br><img src="http://emailjeet.com/Content/emailimg/adds.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Email Direct Marketing Chef 2.4.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3881-email-direct-marketing-chef.html</link>
<description>Name : Email Direct Marketing Chef Version : 2.4.0 OS : Windows Type : Bulk Mail Price : $79 Homepage : SalePage Email Direct Marketing Chef (EDM Chef) is a multi-threading application designed to sending bulk emails to an unlimited number of recipients. With this software, you can send unlimited newsletters to your customers. EDM Chef don&#039;t need setting smtp address, it will auto search and download smtp server from inte.com, it will save you lots of time and money.</description>
<category>Bulk Mail Sender</category>
<enclosure url="https://www.email-chef.com/img/edm-chef.gif" type="image/gif" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 21:52:33 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features The main different is EDM Chef don&#039;t need setting sender email address(smtp), it will auto crawl and download new available smtp every time. With this function, you will no longer register or buy bulk sender email address, it&#039;s really save you lots of time and cash. It&#039;s very simple actually. If you are sending newsletters to your customers and you want to be in full control over your data and also you don&#039;t want to pay external services for handling the emails for you then EDM Chef is the right tool that you need. With EDM Chef you just pay the license and use the application on your own hosting server with your own delivery methods, at no additional costs for you!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/NysLNaHayBw?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> The main different is EDM Chef don't need setting sender email address(smtp), it will auto crawl and download new available smtp every time. With this function, you will no longer register or buy bulk sender email address, it's really save you lots of time and cash.<br></li><li> It's very simple actually. If you are sending newsletters to your customers and you want to be in full control over your data and also you don't want to pay external services for handling the emails for you then EDM Chef is the right tool that you need. With EDM Chef you just pay the license and use the application on your own hosting server with your own delivery methods, at no additional costs for you!<br></li></ul><br><br><img src="https://www.email-chef.com/img/edm-chef.gif" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Email Direct Marketing Chef 2.4.0"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>GroupMail 6.00.025</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2105-groupmail.html</link>
<description>Name : GroupMail Version : 6.00.025 OS : Windows Type : Bulk Mailer Price : $349 Homepage : SalePage Our GroupMail Business Edition is the ideal choice for anyone with bigger email marketing campaigns, larger mailing lists, external databases, a need to schedule email campaigns or a desire to integrate with MS Outlook. The GroupMail Business Edition can send campaigns almost 100 times faster than the Personal Edition with 256 simultaneous sending connections.</description>
<category>Bulk Mail Sender</category>
<enclosure url="http://group-mail.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/business.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 12:12:49 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Everything that the Personal Edition has, plus… Send Unique or Personalized Attachments to your contacts Microsoft OneDrive cloud storage integration to store, sync and access your GroupMail data at other locations and on other devices Autoresponder to send welcome emails, automated birthday wishes, reminder notifications and more Display your Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn and Google+ profiles in your email. Place Tweet buttons in your emails to let your readers share your newsletter. Link to databases such as SQL, MySQL, Access, Outlook, Act! Schedule mass email messages to send when you are gone Send email campaigns super fast with 256 delivery connections Bypass external SMTP mail servers with Direct Sending Easy double opt-in email collection and subscription management Automatic unsubscribe, opt-out and bounce processing Import address books and distribution lists from Microsoft Outlook, GroupWise, Lotus Notes, Exchange and PINE Integrate with Microsoft Outlook Toolbar (Outlook 2002 or above) Import Email Lists directly from Microsoft Excel spreadsheets Share email groups with multiple users on a.comwork Over 142 HTML Email Templates to choose from Emails don’t contain Group Mail links Install in English, Spanish, French, German or Polish Additional Add-ons</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/3OLdOKAtRNA?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Everything that the Personal Edition has, plus…<br /></li><li> Send Unique or Personalized Attachments to your contacts<br /></li><li> Microsoft OneDrive cloud storage integration to store, sync and access your GroupMail data at other locations and on other devices<br /></li><li> Autoresponder to send welcome emails, automated birthday wishes, reminder notifications and more<br /></li><li> Display your Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn and Google+ profiles in your email.<br /></li><li> Place Tweet buttons in your emails to let your readers share your newsletter.<br /></li><li> Link to databases such as SQL, MySQL, Access, Outlook, Act!<br /></li><li> Schedule mass email messages to send when you are gone<br /></li><li> Send email campaigns super fast with 256 delivery connections<br /></li><li> Bypass external SMTP mail servers with Direct Sending<br /></li><li> Easy double opt-in email collection and subscription management<br /></li><li> Automatic unsubscribe, opt-out and bounce processing<br /></li><li> Import address books and distribution lists from Microsoft Outlook, GroupWise, Lotus Notes, Exchange and PINE<br /></li><li> Integrate with Microsoft Outlook Toolbar (Outlook 2002 or above)<br /></li><li> Import Email Lists directly from Microsoft Excel spreadsheets<br /></li><li> Share email groups with multiple users on a.comwork<br /></li><li> Over 142 HTML Email Templates to choose from<br /></li><li> Emails don’t contain Group Mail links<br /></li><li> Install in English, Spanish, French, German or Polish<br /></li><li> Additional Add-ons<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://group-mail.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/business.png" alt="GroupMail 6.00.025" title="GroupMail 6.00.025"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="GroupMail 6.00.025" title="GroupMail 6.00.025"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>WIX Sender Email 2016 1.26</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2080-wix-sender-email.html</link>
<description>Name : WIX Sender Email 2016 Version : 1.26 OS : Windows Type : Email Marketing Tools Price : $57 Homepage : SalePage Bulk Sender Email From WIX SMTP Server</description>
<category>Bulk Mail Sender</category>
<enclosure url="http://i.imgur.com/y7OlrQx.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2016 20:08:27 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Web Base App to Send Email From WIX</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/udSsnhsc7Y4?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br />Web Base App to Send Email From WIX<br /><img src="http://i.imgur.com/y7OlrQx.png" alt="WIX Sender Email 2016 1.26" title="WIX Sender Email 2016 1.26"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="WIX Sender Email 2016 1.26" title="WIX Sender Email 2016 1.26"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>TML Outlook 5.5</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2077-tml-outlook.html</link>
<description>Name : TML Outlook Version : 5.5 OS : Windows Type : Bulk Mail Sender Price : $57 Homepage : SalePage Itamar&#039;s testimony about TML MAILING You have problems! Have you ever sent e-mail marketing? We have had low opening rate? Have you had difficulty to put your email address in the recipient&#039;s inbox? Have you noticed that it is expensive and you never know what&#039;s going on in shipments? Have you noticed that most of the inte.com mail servers does not deliver or 0.00005%? Have you noticed that you do not know where was the money spent and have no idea of the operation? We have solutions! The TML Outlook puts 100% of the items in the inbox. In the most difficult accounts like Hotmail emails, Live, Outlook where no program reaches the email marketing TML Outlook enough! These accounts still has his advantage to put the images OPEN (exclusively ours) Speed of sending 50,000 emails per day. Do not use paid server. Do not use paid provider. It is simple to use No longer will pre-configured.</description>
<category>Bulk Mail Sender</category>
<enclosure url="http://i.imgur.com/oWwoNaT.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2016 19:50:35 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Surely you have seen many programs send emails, especially those who speak in Dedicated IP, one of the most sold lies on the Inte.com, Dedicated IP is fixed IP and fixed IP enters blacklist so start sending emails. So why no one warns? Because there is a philosophy to withdraw money from less enlightened in our Brazil that would be a shame, however is the &quot;way&quot; Brazilian ... You do not have to be our customer, most at least have the right to understand how the part of email marketing on the inte.com ... Differences of TML, functions that make efficiency different contents The same happens on the subject, happens in the content, if you start making SPAM and send thousands of emails with the same content, you will easily reach all the trash understand that servers have filters, to test exactly this, and realize that repeated issues or repeated content is spam or chains, and put everything in the garbage, not worth anything the amount of emails you sent. The TML RIP puts a code before and after the subject, however, in the same email background color (white) and changes to every email, so each email is unique, and never gets in the trash. The code can be seen if you completely select the mail, because when selected it takes the white and the rest black. The important thing is that the servers do not understand that is a program that does this, they analyze the content and verify that is different from the previous ones, it makes them put everything in your inbox. HTML, text or scripts If you have a more elaborate announcement, made in HTML, or even videos or scripts, the TML has a specific field for you to put your HTML is simple and sends with speed and efficiency. Use as many images as you want, put videos, mount your HTML simply using a blog or the Front Page a similar program to Word (download FrontPage) Dedicated IP One of the biggest lies of the inte.com is to send thousands of dedicated IP emails. Understand that Dedicated IP has a fixed number, and if you start sending email from an IP fixed number, before reaching 1,000 submissions it will be blacklisted and all your work will be sent to the SPAM box and treated as garbage, you still run the risk that the links that are within your email and your website get blacklisted and no longer appear in search engines like Google or Bing Free e-mails with Outlook TML In TML you put free servers accounts, all with ip random, all approved as ip sending mail servers, and not spam dedicated IPs. Support TML GMail, Yahoo, R7, Bull and others added that from time to time, and you can even insert your server. In TML there are no limits to numbers of servers or accounts, it is totally unlimited, put as many accounts as you like, of the servers you want, outside those in the program, you simply enter your preferences. Daily limit and limit per Hour In TML you limit daily shipments for each registered account, so you do not block their free accounts, created to email with TML, you can also limit shipments per hour, respecting what the servers allow, without trying to force or circumvent accounts created to email marketing Trundle Email The TML has a time limit to change e-mail account when sending it causes you to not exhaust the email at the beginning of sending, TML can send as many emails u want each account, and after finishing it back in early and spends the day always doing this rotation, it exchange account as gives error and you can set the time it is in each account.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/K2y_5Rv4D40?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><br />Surely you have seen many programs send emails, especially those who speak in Dedicated IP, one of the most sold lies on the Inte.com, Dedicated IP is fixed IP and fixed IP enters blacklist so start sending emails. So why no one warns? Because there is a philosophy to withdraw money from less enlightened in our Brazil that would be a shame, however is the "way" Brazilian ... You do not have to be our customer, most at least have the right to understand how the part of email marketing on the inte.com ...<br /> <br />Differences of TML, functions that make efficiency<br />different contents<br />The same happens on the subject, happens in the content, if you start making SPAM and send thousands of emails with the same content, you will easily reach all the trash understand that servers have filters, to test exactly this, and realize that repeated issues or repeated content is spam or chains, and put everything in the garbage, not worth anything the amount of emails you sent. The TML RIP puts a code before and after the subject, however, in the same email background color (white) and changes to every email, so each email is unique, and never gets in the trash. The code can be seen if you completely select the mail, because when selected it takes the white and the rest black. The important thing is that the servers do not understand that is a program that does this, they analyze the content and verify that is different from the previous ones, it makes them put everything in your inbox.<br /> 	 <br />HTML, text or scripts<br />If you have a more elaborate announcement, made in HTML, or even videos or scripts, the TML has a specific field for you to put your HTML is simple and sends with speed and efficiency. Use as many images as you want, put videos, mount your HTML simply using a blog or the Front Page a similar program to Word   (download FrontPage)<br /> 	 <br />Dedicated IP<br />One of the biggest lies of the inte.com is to send thousands of dedicated IP emails. Understand that Dedicated IP has a fixed number, and if you start sending email from an IP fixed number, before reaching 1,000 submissions it will be blacklisted and all your work will be sent to the SPAM box and treated as garbage, you still run the risk that the links that are within your email and your website get blacklisted and no longer appear in search engines like Google or Bing<br /> 	 <br />Free e-mails with Outlook TML<br />In TML you put free servers accounts, all with ip random, all approved as ip sending mail servers, and not spam dedicated IPs. Support TML GMail, Yahoo, R7, Bull and others added that from time to time, and you can even insert your server. In TML there are no limits to numbers of servers or accounts, it is totally unlimited, put as many accounts as you like, of the servers you want, outside those in the program, you simply enter your preferences.<br /> 	 <br />Daily limit and limit per Hour<br />In TML you limit daily shipments for each registered account, so you do not block their free accounts, created to email with TML, you can also limit shipments per hour, respecting what the servers allow, without trying to force or circumvent accounts created to email marketing<br /> <br />Trundle Email<br />The TML has a time limit to change e-mail account when sending it causes you to not exhaust the email at the beginning of sending, TML can send as many emails u want each account, and after finishing it back in early and spends the day always doing this rotation, it exchange account as gives error and you can set the time it is in each account.<br /><img src="http://i.imgur.com/oWwoNaT.png" alt="TML Outlook 5.5" title="TML Outlook 5.5"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="TML Outlook 5.5" title="TML Outlook 5.5"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Email Marketing Studio 2016 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2000-email-marketing-studio.html</link>
<description>Name : Email Marketing Studio Version : 2016 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Email Marketing Tools Price : $47 Homepage : SalePage Email Marketing Studio represents a package of professional software for targeted email marketing campaigns and email lists management. The set includes 3 programs: Bulk Mailer, Email Verifier, and Email Autoresponder. These tools are going to help you with all major tasks in your online business: check your mail lists for validity, send bunches of emails fast and effectively, provide automatic responses when you are out of the office and can’t assist your customers right away.</description>
<category>Bulk Mail Sender</category>
<enclosure url="http://puu.sh/rZwyQ/983db5078d.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2016 23:08:53 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Bulk Mailer is a professional email newsletter software for bulk email campaigns. The tool helps you create successful email marketing campaigns. You can easily manage mailing lists for your subscribers, create personalized messages such as HTML newsletters, e-magazines, account statements, and reports. Email Verifier checks email addresses from Microsoft Outlook Contacts, Windows Address Book, Excel, Text Files and External databases to determine if they are still valid. Email Autoresponder is an easy desktop email marketing software that delivers your auto responders ranging from the simplest &quot;I&#039;m out of office&quot; to personalized HTML messages and newsletters.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/-Go1oHx67_Q?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Bulk Mailer is a professional email newsletter software for bulk email campaigns. The tool helps you create successful email marketing campaigns. You can easily manage mailing lists for your subscribers, create personalized messages such as HTML newsletters, e-magazines, account statements, and reports.<br /></li><li> Email Verifier checks email addresses from Microsoft Outlook Contacts, Windows Address Book, Excel, Text Files and External databases to determine if they are still valid.<br /></li><li> Email Autoresponder is an easy desktop email marketing software that delivers your auto responders ranging from the simplest "I'm out of office" to personalized HTML messages and newsletters.<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://puu.sh/rZwyQ/983db5078d.png" alt="Email Marketing Studio 2016 1.0" title="Email Marketing Studio 2016 1.0"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Email Marketing Studio 2016 1.0" title="Email Marketing Studio 2016 1.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Email Marketing Robot 2.20.1</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1456-email-marketing-robot.html</link>
<description>Name : Email Marketing Robot Version : 2.20.1 Multi- Faster OS : Windows Type : Email Marketing Tools Price : $99 Homepage : SalePage Create, manage and schedule email marketing campaigns using this comprehensive tool with options for sending relevant messages to clients with your company&#039;s details Designed for companies, Email Marketing Robot is a comprehensive software application that gives you the possibility to organize marketing campaigns and send relevant information to your clients via email.</description>
<category>Bulk Mail Sender</category>
<enclosure url="http://i1-win.softpedia-static.com/screenshots/Email-Marketing-Robot_1.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2016 01:34:47 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Pre-loaded with more than 400 business categories : You can use the pre-loaded business types or make your own list of business types you would like to contact. This makes it easy to set up the software so that it can start finding businesses you wish to contact. Complete list of UK towns and US states included : In order to save you time we have included a list of UK towns and US towns and cities to help you get started, or alternatively you can enter postcodes or places. The robot will then find businesses in the local areas that you specify, thereby helping you to focus on businesses in your target area. Scheduler : This feature enables you to leave your computer on, and have the software run on auto pilot during the hours, and days of the week you specify. This helps to ensure that your emails arrive during office hours only, and hence you will receive less call backs out of office hours. The facility exists to pause the software at any time, and resume again at your convenience where the software will start where it left off automatically. Speed Limite : In order to prevent the software sending out too many emails you can limit the email sending to 45 emails per hour, or less. This helps to cope with the flow of incoming enquiries that are generated, and also to stay within your inte.com service provider’s email sending limits by mimicking human behaviour. Anti-Spam System : The software will only email a website once per campaign in order to avoid any accusations of spamming. This helps to comply with your inte.com service provider’s policies, and lessons the risk of alienating your potential clients. Potential customers will not be bombarded with lots of emails, and any email they do receive will be personalised thereby appearing completely genuine. Customisable Templates : Simply edit the supplied specifically designed templates for virtually guaranteed success in your email marketing campaigns. All the templates are written to encourage people to email you back, or pick up the phone and call for more information. This means you don’t need to be a marketing expert to get great results from this software. Spin Code Support : The software supports spin code which allows for randomised emails to be generated. This helps your emails to get through any spam filters, and increases the chances of your emails being read. It further enables you to test different email headlines, and find the ones that people respond to best.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ixTjP6WeLDs?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Pre-loaded with more than 400 business categories : You can use the pre-loaded business types or make your own list of business types you would like to contact. This makes it easy to set up the software so that it can start finding businesses you wish to contact.<br /></li><li> Complete list of UK towns and US states included : In order to save you time we have included a list of UK towns and US towns and cities to help you get started, or alternatively you can enter postcodes or places. The robot will then find businesses in the local areas that you specify, thereby helping you to focus on businesses in your target area.<br /></li><li> Scheduler : This feature enables you to leave your computer on, and have the software run on auto pilot during the hours, and days of the week you specify. This helps to ensure that your emails arrive during office hours only, and hence you will receive less call backs out of office hours. The facility exists to pause the software at any time, and resume again at your convenience where the software will start where it left off automatically.<br /></li><li> Speed Limite : In order to prevent the software sending out too many emails you can limit the email sending to 45 emails per hour, or less. This helps to cope with the flow of incoming enquiries that are generated, and also to stay within your inte.com service provider’s email sending limits by mimicking human behaviour.<br /></li><li> Anti-Spam System : The software will only email a website once per campaign in order to avoid any accusations of spamming. This helps to comply with your inte.com service provider’s policies, and lessons the risk of alienating your potential clients. Potential customers will not be bombarded with lots of emails, and any email they do receive will be personalised thereby appearing completely genuine.<br /></li><li> Customisable Templates : Simply edit the supplied specifically designed templates for virtually guaranteed success in your email marketing campaigns. All the templates are written to encourage people to email you back, or pick up the phone and call for more information. This means you don’t need to be a marketing expert to get great results from this software.<br /></li><li> Spin Code Support : The software supports spin code which allows for randomised emails to be generated. This helps your emails to get through any spam filters, and increases the chances of your emails being read. It further enables you to test different email headlines, and find the ones that people respond to best.<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://i1-win.softpedia-static.com/screenshots/Email-Marketing-Robot_1.png" alt="Email Marketing Robot 2.20.1" title="Email Marketing Robot 2.20.1"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Email Marketing Robot 2.20.1" title="Email Marketing Robot 2.20.1"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Gorilla Email Marketer 2.0.32</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1559-gorilla-email-marketer.html</link>
<description>Name : Gorilla Email Marketer Version : 2.0.32 OS : Windows Type : Email Marketing Tools Price : $97 Homepage : SalePage GorillaContact Desktop Email Marketer - Send Unlimited Emails For Life Time Create, send &amp;amp; track UNLIMITED emails for $97. One time fee. No recurring charges..</description>
<category>Bulk Mail Sender</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.gorillabulkemail.com/images/desktop12.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2016 01:54:00 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Professional Smtp Servers.Professional SMTP Server to use with GorillaContact software available at the rate of $1 per each 10,000 emails send from our partner. Comes with 100% inbox delivery guaranteed 500 free built-in email templates : Create your email newsletter by just changing the text content of over 500 built-in free email templates using the embedded HTML editor or Purchase a tailor made template which is specifically designed to your business with rich graphics, from our professional designers. CRM &amp;amp; Website Forms : Builtin Customer relationship management software. Create customizable forms for your web site. All collected data will be recorded in your lists, and you may start your permission based email marketing with . Download ASP/PHP form scripts - CLICK HERE Built-in email verifier. Check email addresses for validity using the built-in email verifier software. Remove invalid emails from your list, before you send your campaign SMTP &amp;amp; Direct DNS Sending methods : If you don’t have an SMTP server, you can use direct-send method using Built-in SMTP Server. Also useful for Windows Server™ installations. IP/SMTP Rotation : Add multiple IP/SMTP accounts. After each email is send the sending IP/SMTP shifts. This feature is useful to increase the sending limit. For eg: Register 100 gmail email accounts for free and send 100x100=10,000 emails/day at a single click Personalized email for each subscriber : Send personalized messages (“Dear Mr. Johny Harold”, instead of “Dear customer”) Dear [name] -&amp;gt; becomes -&amp;gt; Dear Andrew Each email you send is different using the email merge and email personalization features. Both subject personalization and content personalization are available. Build your permission based list : Create customizable forms for your web site. All collected data will be recorded in your lists, and you may start your permission based email marketing with . Track your email delivery : bulk email software and Google Analytics let you know if, after reading emails, your customers purchase your products, subscribe to your website or meet the goals you set in your Google Analytics account. We also give for free, our email delivery tracking service via www.track-your-email.com WYSIWYG HTML Editor : Message composing is achieved through the powerful visual HTML editor with code access, CHARSET definition and the ability to insert completely customizable field tags Spam score checker : is integrated with built-in score checker tool. Remove spam keywords from your content. It incorporates all the SpamAssassin rules that you need to respect to go straight to your customer’s inbox Scheduled mailing : Schedule your mailing so that it will be automatically sent at a given day and time or every day at a particular time. Subscribe/Unsubscribe by Email or Web Form : Insert an unsubscribe link (opt-out) which is required by the CAN-SPAM Act and software will automatically process the unsubscriptions via email and built-in web based scripts. Subscriptions are also processed automatically via email and web based forms. SET CHARSET : The message CHARSET can be set to send messages with any character system (Hindi, Japanese, Hebrew, Chinese, Arabic). This feature allows you to send your newsletters in different world languages. Advanced Mailing List Management &amp;amp; Filters : comes with powerful mailing list management features like removal of duplicates, filtration of email list based upon the given criteria &amp;amp; export only records that meet specific criteria For eg- export only unsubscribed emails. Bounced Mail Processing : Bounce-backs are automatically recognized, and originating addresses can be either disabled or deleted from the lists Unlimited lists/group with unlimited recipients : can manage multiple distribution lists Black list : Define a lists of email addresses or domains which will be automatically excluded from mailings. for eg - giving domain name yahoo.com in black list will prevent sending emails to all @yahoo.com email ids. Import Contacts from Outlook, gmail, yahoo, msn accounts etc. Imports CSV, TXT, XLS formats, with multiple columns. Import your existing contacts from MS Outllook, Outlook express, Import email ids from your gmail, hotmail, msn, yahoo, aol email accounts. Import existing .htm or .eml files. Complete previous mailings : In case of inte.com connection interruption, crash of the computer or what else write in logs to which emails the message is already sent, so its possible to send the message to those emails that the message has not been sent preventing to duplicate messages. Group multiple servers into one batch : Using the in-built method of smtp server rotation, send packs of emails on separate servers, sequentially, automatically, allowing you to send 10000s of emails on free services. After each email is send, the sender IP will change &amp;amp; rotate. Useful for people sending promotional / marketing emails to any purchased email list. Integrated with Google Analytics : Check your mailing campaigns effectiveness using Google&#039;s powerful tools. Integrated with www.track-your-email.com : We give you a free service to browse data about your mailing opening and click rates, geolocation of recipients and information about each single user&#039;s actions. More advanced settings : Users can now add custom headers, request read receipts, set a high priority for their message, define a customized To: header supporting merge tags, enable or disable automatic filtering out of duplicate addresses when sending out. Advanced data filter : A powerful filter has been added, which lets users select and enable or disable records matching some conditions. Export filtered data to a .csv format. Automatic removal of duplicate records / email ids. Easier backup : Directly accessing database files for backup purposes is now easier, as they are saved inside Documents folder. Social sharing : provides social book marking option, which widens the reach of your emails as your recipients will share your information in social bookmarking sites like Face book, yahoo etc. Thus when you embed your core information in email message using social bookmark option of , Multi-threading &amp;amp; Multiple Connections : Increased Speed with simultaneous multiple connections. Upto 50 Connections can be established at the same time Live chat support (24/5) : For quick answers to your technical and non-technical queries, just click on live chat option in our website. Live chat is available 24 hours a day from monday to friday. 24/7 Email support and 24/5 phone support are also provided. Embedded image support &amp;amp; attachments : Generate newsletters with attachments and embedded images. Each email message can contain file attachments (Zip, Doc, Pdf…). ScreenShot</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/yFDzSXg_Wus?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" gesture="media" allow="encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Professional Smtp Servers.Professional SMTP Server to use with GorillaContact software available at the rate of  per each 10,000 emails send from our partner. Comes with 100% inbox delivery guaranteed<br></li><li> 500 free built-in email templates : Create your email newsletter by just changing the text content of over 500 built-in free email templates using the embedded HTML editor or Purchase a tailor made template which is specifically designed to your business with rich graphics, from our professional designers.<br></li><li> CRM &amp; Website Forms : Builtin Customer relationship management software. Create customizable forms for your web site. All collected data will be recorded in your lists, and you may start your permission based email marketing with . Download ASP/PHP form scripts - CLICK HERE <br></li><li> Built-in email verifier.  Check email addresses for validity using the built-in email verifier software. Remove invalid emails from your list, before you send your campaign <br></li><li> SMTP &amp; Direct DNS Sending methods : If you don’t have an SMTP server, you can use direct-send method using Built-in SMTP Server. Also useful for Windows Server™ installations. <br></li><li> IP/SMTP Rotation : Add multiple IP/SMTP accounts. After each email is send the sending IP/SMTP shifts. This feature is useful to increase the sending limit. For eg: Register 100 gmail email accounts for free and send 100x100=10,000 emails/day at a single click <br></li><li> Personalized email for each subscriber : Send personalized messages (“Dear Mr. Johny Harold”, instead of “Dear customer”) Dear [name] -&gt; becomes -&gt; Dear Andrew Each email you send is different using the email merge and email personalization features. Both subject personalization and content personalization are available. <br></li><li> Build your permission based list : Create customizable forms for your web site. All collected data will be recorded in your lists, and you may start your permission based email marketing with . <br></li><li> Track your email delivery : bulk email software and Google Analytics let you know if, after reading emails, your customers purchase your products, subscribe to your website or meet the goals you set in your Google Analytics account. We also give for free, our email delivery tracking service via www.track-your-email.com <br></li><li> WYSIWYG HTML Editor : Message composing is achieved through the powerful visual HTML editor with code access, CHARSET definition and the ability to insert completely customizable field tags <br></li><li> Spam score checker : is integrated with built-in score checker tool. Remove spam keywords from your content. It incorporates all the SpamAssassin rules that you need to respect to go straight to your customer’s inbox <br></li><li> Scheduled mailing : Schedule your mailing so that it will be automatically sent at a given day and time or every day at a particular time. <br></li><li> Subscribe/Unsubscribe by Email or Web Form : Insert an unsubscribe link (opt-out) which is required by the CAN-SPAM Act and software will automatically process the unsubscriptions via email and built-in web based scripts. Subscriptions are also processed automatically via email and web based forms. <br></li><li> SET CHARSET : The message CHARSET can be set to send messages with any character system (Hindi, Japanese, Hebrew, Chinese, Arabic). This feature allows you to send your newsletters in different world languages. <br></li><li> Advanced Mailing List Management &amp; Filters : comes with powerful mailing list management features like removal of duplicates, filtration of email list based upon the given criteria &amp; export only records that meet specific criteria For eg- export only unsubscribed emails. <br></li><li> Bounced Mail Processing : Bounce-backs are automatically recognized, and originating addresses can be either disabled or deleted from the lists <br></li><li> Unlimited lists/group with unlimited recipients : can manage multiple distribution lists <br></li><li> Black list : Define a lists of email addresses or domains which will be automatically excluded from mailings. for eg - giving domain name yahoo.com in black list will prevent sending emails to all @yahoo.com email ids. <br></li><li> Import Contacts from Outlook, gmail, yahoo, msn accounts etc.  Imports CSV, TXT, XLS formats, with multiple columns. Import your existing contacts from MS Outllook, Outlook express, Import email ids from your gmail, hotmail, msn, yahoo, aol email accounts. Import existing .htm or .eml files. <br></li><li> Complete previous mailings : In case of inte.com connection interruption, crash of the computer or what else write in logs to which emails the message is already sent, so its possible to send the message to those emails that the message has not been sent preventing to duplicate messages. <br></li><li> Group multiple servers into one batch : Using the in-built method of smtp server rotation, send packs of emails on separate servers, sequentially, automatically, allowing you to send 10000s of emails on free services. After each email is send, the sender IP will change &amp; rotate. Useful for people sending promotional / marketing emails to any purchased email list. <br></li><li> Integrated with Google Analytics : Check your mailing campaigns effectiveness using Google's powerful tools. <br></li><li> Integrated with www.track-your-email.com : We give you a free service to browse data about your mailing opening and click rates, geolocation of recipients and information about each single user's actions. <br></li><li> More advanced settings : Users can now add custom headers, request read receipts, set a high priority for their message, define a customized To: header supporting merge tags, enable or disable automatic filtering out of duplicate addresses when sending out. <br></li><li> Advanced data filter : A powerful filter has been added, which lets users select and enable or disable records matching some conditions. Export filtered data to a .csv format. Automatic removal of duplicate records / email ids. <br></li><li> Easier backup : Directly accessing database files for backup purposes is now easier, as they are saved inside Documents folder. <br></li><li> Social sharing : provides social book marking option, which widens the reach of your emails as your recipients will share your information in social bookmarking sites like Face book, yahoo etc. Thus when you embed your core information in email message using social bookmark option of , <br></li><li> Multi-threading &amp; Multiple Connections : Increased Speed with simultaneous multiple connections. Upto 50 Connections can be established at the same time <br></li><li> Live chat support (24/5) : For quick answers to your technical and non-technical queries, just click on live chat option in our website. Live chat is available 24 hours a day from monday to friday. 24/7 Email support and 24/5 phone support are also provided. <br></li><li> Embedded image support &amp; attachments : Generate newsletters with attachments and embedded images. Each email message can contain file attachments (Zip, Doc, Pdf…). <br></li></ul><br><br><h3>ScreenShot</h3><br><img src="http://www.gorillabulkemail.com/images/desktop12.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Gorilla Email Marketer 2.0.32"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>