<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Web Scraper - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Web Scraper - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>Gather Proxy 9.0 Premium</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1355-gather-proxy.html</link>
<description>Name : Gather Proxy Version : 9.0 Premium OS : Windows Type : Proxy Scraper Price : $19 Homepage : SalePage Gather Proxy is a lightweight Windows utility designed to help users gather information about proxy servers and socks. Since this is a portable program, it is important to mention that it doesn’t leave any traces in the Windows Registry. You can copy it on any USB flash drive or other devices, and take it with you whenever you to need to generate proxy and socks lists on the breeze. Although it comes bundled with many useful functions, it boasts a clean and straightforward layout.</description>
<category>Proxies Scraper</category>
<enclosure url="http://i1-win.softpedia-static.com/screenshots/GatherProxy_2.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 17:22:03 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features 1. GatherProxy scrapes thousands of fresh proxies from over 300 daily updated websites. Its include leading sites such as Hidemyass Proxy List. 2. HTTP proxy checker, Socks 4/5 checker, SSL checker, Black List checker, Google Passed proxies checker. 3. Recurring Scaper and Checker. The program repeat gathering and checking proxy. Automatic saving them to your hardware or FTP server. Simple open program and you will get newest proxies and socks 24/7. 4. Url Expression feature, this is allow harvest proxies from Google Search, Forum or any site with smart method. Read more ... 5. It is a portable program, the tool really compact and save memory resource for your PC. WHY SHOULD I USE GATHER PROXY INSTEAD OF COMPETITOR PRODUCTS? 1. Features. GatherProxy giving you some features which are not any program available. (Ex: Url Expression, Scraper proxy from protected source (hidemyass)) 2. Price. For example, the product Forum Proxy Leecher, which ONLY leeches from predefined websites and has no dynamic website discovering ability like GatherProxy, costs $99.95. That also only includes a single year of updates. GatherProxy include updates for lifetime. Another example, Proxy Goblin? $96.00. Also only a leecher and does not include GatherProxy&#039;s unique search ability. Proxy Multiply? Black list check is not available. You can get unsafe proxies. Only scape proxies from unsafe sources. Can not harvest proxies by smart method such as Google Search. 3. Trial. We are offering FREE and PREMIUM version. So you can trial forever on FREE version and upgade to PREMIUM if you like it.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/yQxPhhX_Drc?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> 1. GatherProxy scrapes thousands of fresh proxies from over 300 daily updated websites. Its include leading sites such as Hidemyass Proxy List.<br></li><li> 2. HTTP proxy checker, Socks 4/5 checker, SSL checker, Black List checker, Google Passed proxies checker.<br></li><li> 3. Recurring Scaper and Checker. The program repeat gathering and checking proxy. Automatic saving them to your hardware or FTP server. Simple open program and you will get newest proxies and socks 24/7.<br></li><li> 4. Url Expression feature, this is allow harvest proxies from Google Search, Forum or any site with smart method. Read more ...<br></li><li> 5. It is a portable program, the tool really compact and save memory resource for your PC.<br></li></ul><br>WHY SHOULD I USE GATHER PROXY INSTEAD OF COMPETITOR PRODUCTS?<ul><li> 1. Features. GatherProxy giving you some features which are not any program available. (Ex: Url Expression, Scraper proxy from protected source (hidemyass))<br></li><li> 2. Price. For example, the product Forum Proxy Leecher, which ONLY leeches from predefined websites and has no dynamic website discovering ability like GatherProxy, costs .95. That also only includes a single year of updates. GatherProxy include updates for lifetime. Another example, Proxy Goblin? .00. Also only a leecher and does not include GatherProxy's unique search ability. Proxy Multiply? Black list check is not available. You can get unsafe proxies. Only scape proxies from unsafe sources. Can not harvest proxies by smart method such as Google Search.<br></li><li> 3. Trial. We are offering FREE and PREMIUM version. So you can trial forever on FREE version and upgade to PREMIUM if you like it.<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://i1-win.softpedia-static.com/screenshots/GatherProxy_2.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Gather Proxy 9.0 Premium"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Website Finder 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4215-website-finder.html</link>
<description>Name : Website Finder Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Software Tool for Searching for Websites Price : $59 Homepage : SalePage Website Finder is a software tool for searching for websites by your set criteria. By default the homepage of each website is checked for the criteria but the URL that is returned from Google searches can also be checked.</description>
<category>Url Harvester</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2018 21:54:46 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>[media=https://youtu.be/pZ_IFfKW07Q] Features Website Finder has three methods of finding websites matching your criteria. Crawl a list of websites for matching criteria - If you have a list of websites that you would like to check simply paste them in and Website Finder will check the homepage of each one for your set criteria. Crawl search results by niche related keywords for matching websites/criteria - Enter a list of niche related keywords and Webiste Finder will search Google for all these niche related keywords and check every result (website) for your set criteria. There are two main options with this search, the criteria check can be applied to the result (URL) Google returns or the homepage of the result that is returned. Endless crawl for matching websites - Enter your seed list of websites to start crawling from and Website Finder will check that inital seed website(s) for your criteria but then also crawl a specified amount of URLs on that website (30 by default) extracting all outbound links and then crawling these outbound websites. This process is repeated endlessly. Website Finder will just keep crawling from website to website checking to see if they match your set criteria. Why should I use this tool? List of possible uses are but not limited to... - Find websites with outdated plugins to market to - Find slow websites to sell faster hosting to - Find websites with security issues to offer security patching services to - Find websites to sell themes to, e.g use the Google search option to find all dog related websites running WordPress and sell them dog related WordPress themes</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;">[media=https://youtu.be/pZ_IFfKW07Q]</div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Website Finder has three methods of finding websites matching your criteria.<br></li><li>  Crawl a list of websites for matching criteria<br></li><li>  - If you have a list of websites that you would like to check simply paste them in and Website Finder will check the homepage of each one for your set criteria.<br></li><li>  Crawl search results by niche related keywords for matching websites/criteria<br></li><li>  - Enter a list of niche related keywords and Webiste Finder will search Google for all these niche related keywords and check every result (website) for your set criteria. There are two main options with this search, the criteria check can be applied to the result (URL) Google returns or the homepage of the result that is returned.<br></li><li>  Endless crawl for matching websites<br></li><li>  - Enter your seed list of websites to start crawling from and Website Finder will check that inital seed website(s) for your criteria but then also crawl a specified amount of URLs on that website (30 by default) extracting all outbound links and then crawling these outbound websites. This process is repeated endlessly. Website Finder will just keep crawling from website to website checking to see if they match your set criteria.<br></li><li> Why should I use this tool?<br></li><li>  List of possible uses are but not limited to...<br></li><li>  - Find websites with outdated plugins to market to<br></li><li>  - Find slow websites to sell faster hosting to<br></li><li>  - Find websites with security issues to offer security patching services to<br></li><li>  - Find websites to sell themes to, e.g use the Google search option to find all dog related websites running WordPress and sell them dog related WordPress themes<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Website Finder 1.0 "><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>GSA Proxy Scraper 2.45</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1032-gsa-proxy-scraper.html</link>
<description>Tired of wasting time and money searching for the proxies you need? Or maybe you&#039;re tired of websites spying on you and collecting your data without your consent? Look no further, we have a solution for you GSA Proxy Scraper is a powerful, easy to use, Windows based, proxy scraping software that can harvest and test thousands of proxies quickly and reliably with just a few simple clicks. No more headaches wasting time to find the right proxy GSA Proxy harvester makes harvesting proxies easy. Our powerful proxy harvester has the unique ability to find and harvest proxies from thousands of sources across the web and continues to seek out and find proxies until YOU tell it to stop. If that isn&#039;t enough, GSA Proxy Scraper goes above and beyond by adding in a powerful Port Scanner, which gives GSA Proxy Scraper the power to harvest proxies from places that other competing software on the market can&#039;t touch. Useful features like Smart-Tagging allow you to easily create your own custom proxy tags which automatically filter proxies based on the criteria you set. (E.G. proxy must work with Youtube, Facebook, Etsy, etc.). Easy to use exporting and filtering options will take care of all the organizing, filtering, and exporting without any intervention on your end. Need Google passed proxies sent to one location (E.G. email), but want Ebay passed proxies saved to your local machine? No problem! GSA Proxy Harvester can export proxies to email, FTP upload, local destination, or even web upload. Simply choose the export interval and location to export the proxies, and GSA proxy harvester will handle it all automatically, while you sit back and drink your cup of coffee. After months of research and development, we&#039;re confident that no other software on the market comes close to offering the features that GSA Proxy Harvester comes with right out of the box.</description>
<category>Proxies Scraper</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-05/1431542544_1zf7i83.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-05/1431542806_gsa-ser-extension.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-05/1431542756_gsa-trial-reset.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2018 02:16:00 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>- Powerful Harvester: Built in proxy harvester goes above and beyond the competition by having the unique ability to scrape proxies from almost any site! The proxy harvester is so powerful it can harvest proxies from sources other proxy tools can&#039;t touch - Test Proxies Against: Automatically test newly scraped proxies against websites such as web 2.0&#039;s, social accounts, email providers, search engines and even your own custom URL&#039;s - Smart Tags: Proxy tags allow you to easily tag/group specific types of proxies which can later be used for different tasks - Proxy Types: GSA Proxy Scraper currently has support for Web, Connect, and Socks4/5 proxy types - Port Scanner: Powerful, multi-threaded port scanner allows you to easily scan I.P. and port ranges to discover more proxies - Proxy Filtering: Automatically filter by country, speed, Google passed, anonymity level, dangerous I.P.&#039;s and more - Compatibility: Supports proxy formats from all the most popular SEO tools such as GSA SER, Scrapebox, Gscraper, NohandsSEO, Ultimate Demon and many more - Internal Proxy Server: Internal proxy server allows the software to act as a personal VPN, giving your browser a fresh new I.P. after every refresh. - Export Options: Automatic proxy export to FTP, email, local directory, and web upload (GET, POST) - Lifetime license and updates: Just like other GSA tools, GSA Proxy Scraper is a one-time fee and includes free updates and support for the lifetime of the software. - And much more!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[- Powerful Harvester: Built in proxy harvester goes above and beyond the competition by having the unique ability to scrape proxies from almost any site! The proxy harvester is so powerful it can harvest proxies from sources other proxy tools can't touch<br> - Test Proxies Against: Automatically test newly scraped proxies against websites such as web 2.0's, social accounts, email providers, search engines and even your own custom URL's<br> - Smart Tags: Proxy tags allow you to easily tag/group specific types of proxies which can later be used for different tasks<br> - Proxy Types: GSA Proxy Scraper currently has support for Web, Connect, and Socks4/5 proxy types<br> - Port Scanner: Powerful, multi-threaded port scanner allows you to easily scan I.P. and port ranges to discover more proxies<br> - Proxy Filtering: Automatically filter by country, speed, Google passed, anonymity level, dangerous I.P.'s and more<br> - Compatibility: Supports proxy formats from all the most popular SEO tools such as GSA SER, Scrapebox, Gscraper, NohandsSEO, Ultimate Demon and many more<br> - Internal Proxy Server: Internal proxy server allows the software to act as a personal VPN, giving your browser a fresh new I.P. after every refresh.<br> - Export Options: Automatic proxy export to FTP, email, local directory, and web upload (GET, POST)<br> - Lifetime license and updates: Just like other GSA tools, GSA Proxy Scraper is a one-time fee and includes free updates and support for the lifetime of the software.<br> - And much more!<br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="GSA Proxy Scraper 2.45"></div><br><div class="quote"><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Paigham Bot Proxy Scraper &amp; Checker Pro 1.01</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3946-paigham-bot-proxy-scraper-checker-pro.html</link>
<description>Name : Paigham Bot Proxy Scraper &amp;amp; Checker Pro Version : 1.01 OS : Windows Type : Proxy Service Price : $19.99 Homepage : SalePage Everyone in marketing needs fresh, working proxies! Harvest ten’s of thousands of proxies anytime you need them with Paigham Bot Proxy Scraper &amp;amp; Checker Pro.</description>
<category>Proxies Scraper</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 06:41:03 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Harvest ten’s of thousands of proxies anytime you need them with Paigham Bot Proxy Scraper &amp;amp; Checker Pro. One thing that makes this proxy scraper and checker different than others on the market, is our method for actually testing proxies. We believe our proxy check works better than other software to give you more accurate results with proxies that will last longer than other software using stale proxy sources and inaccurate proxy judges. This software is simple, yet very accurate and efficient. Recent Features added include new checks implemented for testing against Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, Pinterest, Google.com, Google w/ Footprint and also whether or not proxy is showing a captcha and a Port skip/blacklist.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/wfpdlNnfZEo?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Harvest ten’s of thousands of proxies anytime you need them with Paigham Bot Proxy Scraper &amp; Checker Pro.<br></li><li> One thing that makes this proxy scraper and checker different than others on the market, is our method for actually testing proxies. We believe our proxy check works better than other software to give you more accurate results with proxies that will last longer than other software using stale proxy sources and inaccurate proxy judges.<br></li><li> This software is simple, yet very accurate and efficient.<br></li><li> Recent Features added include new checks implemented for testing against Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, Pinterest, Google.com, Google w/ Footprint and also whether or not proxy is showing a captcha and a Port skip/blacklist.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Paigham Bot Proxy Scraper &amp; Checker Pro 1.01"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Wireshark 2.4.6</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3936-wireshark.html</link>
<description>Name : Wireshark Version : 2.4.6 OS : Windows Type : Network Protocol Analyzer Price : $50 Homepage : SalePage Wireshark is the world’s foremost and widely-used.comwork protocol analyzer. It lets you see what’s happening on your.comwork at a microscopic level and is the de facto (and often de jure) standard across many commercial and non-profit enterprises, government agencies, and educational institutions. Wireshark development thrives thanks to the volunteer contributions of.comworking experts around the globe and is the continuation of a project started by Gerald Combs in 1998.</description>
<category>Url Harvester</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 06:40:45 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Wireshark has a rich feature set which includes the following: - Deep inspection of hundreds of protocols, with more being added all the time - Live capture and offline analysis - Standard three-pane packet browser - Multi-platform: Runs on Windows, Linux, macOS, Solaris, FreeBSD, NetBSD, and many others - Captured.comwork data can be browsed via a GUI, or via the TTY-mode TShark utility - The most powerful display filters in the industry - Rich VoIP analysis - Read/write many different capture file formats: tcpdump (libpcap), Pcap NG, Catapult DCT2000, Cisco Secure IDS iplog, Microsoft Network Monitor, Network General Sniffer® (compressed and uncompressed), Sniffer® Pro, and NetXray®, Network Instruments Observer, NetScreen snoop, Novell LANalyzer, RADCOM WAN/LAN Analyzer, Shomiti/Finisar Surveyor, Tektronix K12xx, Visual Networks Visual UpTime, WildPackets EtherPeek/TokenPeek/AiroPeek, and many others - Capture files compressed with gzip can be decompressed on the fly - Live data can be read from Ethe.com, IEEE 802.11, PPP/HDLC, ATM, Bluetooth, USB, Token Ring, Frame Relay, FDDI, and others (depending on your platform) - Decryption support for many protocols, including IPsec, ISAKMP, Kerberos, SNMPv3, SSL/TLS, WEP, and WPA/WPA2 - Coloring rules can be applied to the packet list for quick, intuitive analysis - Output can be exported to XML, PostScript®, CSV, or plain text</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/U0QABcTD-xc?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Wireshark has a rich feature set which includes the following:<br></li><li> - Deep inspection of hundreds of protocols, with more being added all the time<br></li><li> - Live capture and offline analysis<br></li><li> - Standard three-pane packet browser<br></li><li> - Multi-platform: Runs on Windows, Linux, macOS, Solaris, FreeBSD, NetBSD, and many others<br></li><li> - Captured.comwork data can be browsed via a GUI, or via the TTY-mode TShark utility<br></li><li> - The most powerful display filters in the industry<br></li><li> - Rich VoIP analysis<br></li><li> - Read/write many different capture file formats: tcpdump (libpcap), Pcap NG, Catapult DCT2000, Cisco Secure IDS iplog, Microsoft Network Monitor, Network General Sniffer® (compressed and uncompressed), Sniffer® Pro, and NetXray®, Network Instruments Observer, NetScreen snoop, Novell LANalyzer, RADCOM WAN/LAN Analyzer, Shomiti/Finisar Surveyor, Tektronix K12xx, Visual Networks Visual UpTime, WildPackets EtherPeek/TokenPeek/AiroPeek, and many others<br></li><li> - Capture files compressed with gzip can be decompressed on the fly<br></li><li> - Live data can be read from Ethe.com, IEEE 802.11, PPP/HDLC, ATM, Bluetooth, USB, Token Ring, Frame Relay, FDDI, and others (depending on your platform)<br></li><li> - Decryption support for many protocols, including IPsec, ISAKMP, Kerberos, SNMPv3, SSL/TLS, WEP, and WPA/WPA2<br></li><li> - Coloring rules can be applied to the packet list for quick, intuitive analysis<br></li><li> - Output can be exported to XML, PostScript®, CSV, or plain text<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Wireshark 2.4.6"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Free Proxy Finder 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4124-free-proxy-finder.html</link>
<description>Name : Free Proxy Finder Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Proxy Finder Tools Price : $0 Homepage : SalePage Free Proxy Finder is a software tool that allows users to scrape open public proxies off proxy listing websites. It not only does this automatically in the background but it does it at scale, scraping hundreds of websites and then even testing the results for you</description>
<category>Proxies Scraper</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 06:11:37 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features You simply click &quot;find proxies&quot; and the software will fire queries at Google to find websites that have huge lists, once it finds these it will scrape their lists and test each result it finds to make sure its working for you by connecting to test websites. This all happens in the background saving you hours of work. The tool has two main options. Firstly the depth to scrape website results from Google, this can be 10 results per query or it can be up to 100. 100 will be slow but give you more results. 10 will be quicker but give you less results. The second option is the timeout on each proxy test, by default this is 10 seconds so if a successful connection can&#039;t be made to the target website in under 10 seconds it will class that result as failed. This setting can be adjusted to any timeout value you desire.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/huDT_usYOvA?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> You simply click "find proxies" and the software will fire queries at Google to find websites that have huge lists, once it finds these it will scrape their lists and test each result it finds to make sure its working for you by connecting to test websites. This all happens in the background saving you hours of work. The tool has two main options. Firstly the depth to scrape website results from Google, this can be 10 results per query or it can be up to 100. 100 will be slow but give you more results. 10 will be quicker but give you less results. The second option is the timeout on each proxy test, by default this is 10 seconds so if a successful connection can't be made to the target website in under 10 seconds it will class that result as failed. This setting can be adjusted to any timeout value you desire.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Free Proxy Finder 1.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Proxy Checker 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4281-proxy-checker.html</link>
<description>Name : Proxy Checker Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Check Proxy Tools Price : $50 Homepage : SalePage This tool is used for checking if your proxies are functioning as expected. Simply download and enter your proxies then click &quot;Check&quot;. Reliable working proxies are key to successful inte.com marketing. Often you may try and save money by purchasing semi, or even scraping public instead buying dedicated only to find out most of them are not going to work for your project.</description>
<category>Proxies Scraper</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 06:10:24 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features This free tool has three methods of checking if your proxies are working or not. - Basic HTTP - This check takes each proxy and tries to connect to your configured website (example.com by default) if it can successfully connect then it is deemed as working, if it can&#039;t them its deemed to be not working. - HTTP code - This check will allow you to enter your target URL (example.com by default) and the tool will connect through each proxy checking the HTTP response code it receives against the rules you have entered. For example it can fail if a 403 (forbidden) is given by the remote web server, or it can only pass if a 200 (success) is given by the remote web server. - HTML - This check allows you to pass and fail proxies based on what HTML is returned by the remote web server. For example if you think some of your proxies may of been blocked by the web server you can configure this check to fail if the word &quot;blocked&quot; is detected in the HTML returned by the remote web server. Or you can congifure this check to pass if some of the expected HTML is returned in the response from the web server.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/zzlkLpkJ59g?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> This free tool has three methods of checking if your proxies are working or not. <br></li><li> - Basic HTTP - This check takes each proxy and tries to connect to your configured website (example.com by default) if it can successfully connect then it is deemed as working, if it can't them its deemed to be not working.<br></li><li> - HTTP code - This check will allow you to enter your target URL (example.com by default) and the tool will connect through each proxy checking the HTTP response code it receives against the rules you have entered. For example it can fail if a 403 (forbidden) is given by the remote web server, or it can only pass if a 200 (success) is given by the remote web server.<br></li><li> - HTML - This check allows you to pass and fail proxies based on what HTML is returned by the remote web server. For example if you think some of your proxies may of been blocked by the web server you can configure this check to fail if the word "blocked" is detected in the HTML returned by the remote web server. Or you can congifure this check to pass if some of the expected HTML is returned in the response from the web server.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Proxy Checker 1.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Search Engine Scraper 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3731-search-engine-scraper.html</link>
<description>Name : Search Engine Scraper Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Search Engine Scraper Price : $0 Homepage : SalePage Search Engine Scraper is a 100% free and full (no trail etc) desktop application that allows you to scrape results from search engines such as Google and Bing. It will also allow you to check Moz DA and PA for each URL found if you enter a free Moz API key and can search an unlimited amount of keywords. You can also export all URL&#039;s that search engine scraper finds.</description>
<category>Url Harvester</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 05:28:27 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>[media=https://youtu.be/DCUzyxMzOzE] Features Why should I use Search Engine Scraper? Copying URL&#039;s for each keyword&#039;s search results is a massively tedious task, especially if you have hundreds or even thousands of search queries you want to grab the ranking websites for. Then add the time to check Moz stats if needed and this may take weeks. Search Engine Scraper can do this in minutes. How does Search Engine Scraper work? Search Engine Scraper simply sends HTTP requests to Google and Bing just as your browser normally would then automatically parses the response and extracts the URL&#039;s that are returned for your search keyword / query.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;">[media=https://youtu.be/DCUzyxMzOzE]</div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br>Why should I use Search Engine Scraper?<br>Copying URL's for each keyword's search results is a massively tedious task, especially if you have hundreds or even thousands of search queries you want to grab the ranking websites for. Then add the time to check Moz stats if needed and this may take weeks. Search Engine Scraper can do this in minutes.<br><br>How does Search Engine Scraper work?<br>Search Engine Scraper simply sends HTTP requests to Google and Bing just as your browser normally would then automatically parses the response and extracts the URL's that are returned for your search keyword / query.<br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Search Engine Scraper 1.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>DoComment 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3719-docomment.html</link>
<description>Name : DoComment Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Find DoFollow Blog Comments Price : $0 Homepage : SalePage But fear not DoFollow links still exist however now days they are rare and most comments are moderated first. So to successfully use DoFollow blog comments to help rank your website on Google you need to use software to automatically search the inte.com for these websites that have DoFollow blog comment sections then manually leave a comment and link of value that the website owner will approve. DoComment listens to every tweet that is related to your niche then follows any links it finds in those tweets then checks to see if they&#039;re are any DoFollow blog comment links available on that website.</description>
<category>Url Harvester</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 07:11:12 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>[media=https://youtu.be/06e_FYx47ho] Features What are Do Follow Blog Comments? Ok so everyone knows the more websites/links that are pointing to your website, the higher you appear on the Google search results. Yes I know there are other things like link quality and content etc to consider but generally speaking this is true. These links can either be marked with &quot;Do follow&quot; or &quot;No follow&quot; by the website owner when they create the link. If the link is Do Follow generally it will help boost you up the Google search engine results and if its NoFollow it will have little if any effect at all. So obviously you only want DoFollow links. Now a few years ago when you posted a comment on a blog any links you added were all DoFollow so people wrote software to mass automate this leaving annoying spammy comments that caused website owners and CMS creators to make sure most comments were automatically NoFollow. Why should I use DoComment? You should use DoComment because its a great way of finding 100% free niche related spam free safe backlinks to boost your website up the Google search engine results. How does DoComment work? DoComment uses the twitter streaming API to listen to niche realated keywords you set. It then follows the links in these niche related tweets and analyzes the HTML to see if it thinks its found some DoFollow links in the comments section.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;">[media=https://youtu.be/06e_FYx47ho]</div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br>What are Do Follow Blog Comments?<br>Ok so everyone knows the more websites/links that are pointing to your website, the higher you appear on the Google search results. Yes I know there are other things like link quality and content etc to consider but generally speaking this is true. These links can either be marked with "Do follow" or "No follow" by the website owner when they create the link. If the link is Do Follow generally it will help boost you up the Google search engine results and if its NoFollow it will have little if any effect at all. So obviously you only want DoFollow links. Now a few years ago when you posted a comment on a blog any links you added were all DoFollow so people wrote software to mass automate this leaving annoying spammy comments that caused website owners and CMS creators to make sure most comments were automatically NoFollow.<br><br>Why should I use DoComment?<br>You should use DoComment because its a great way of finding 100% free niche related spam free safe backlinks to boost your website up the Google search engine results.<br><br>How does DoComment work?<br>DoComment uses the twitter streaming API to listen to niche realated keywords you set. It then follows the links in these niche related tweets and analyzes the HTML to see if it thinks its found some DoFollow links in the comments section.<br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="DoComment 1.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>WebHarvy 5.2.0.155</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1305-webharvy.html</link>
<description>Name : WebHarvy Version : 5.2.0.155 OS : Windows Type : Web Scraper Tools Price : $499 Homepage : SalePage Intelligent Visual Web Scraper.WebHarvy can automatically scrape data (Text,Image,Email,URL) from web pages and save the scraped content in different formats.</description>
<category>Web Scraper</category>
<enclosure url="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/trx2WRsU8p0/maxresdefault.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 10:00:34 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Visual Point &amp;amp; Click Interface : WebHarvy is a visual web scraper. There is absolutely no need to write any scripts or code to scrape data. You will be using WebHarvy&#039;s in-built browser to navigate web pages. You can select the data to be scraped with mouse clicks. It is that easy ! (Video) Scrape Data Patterns Intelligently Identifies Patterns : WebHarvy automatically identifies patterns of data occurring in web pages. So if you need to scrape a list of items (name, address, email, price etc) from a web page, you need not do any additional configuration. If data repeats, WebHarvy will scrape it automatically. Export scraped data Export Captured Data : You can save the data extracted from web pages in a variety of formats. The current version of WebHarvy Web Scraper allows you to export the scraped data as an XML, CSV, JSON or TSV file. You can also export the scraped data to an SQL database. (Know More) Scrape data from multiple pages Scrape From Multiple Pages : Often web pages display data such as product listings in multiple pages. WebHarvy can automatically crawl and extract data from multiple pages. Just point out the &#039;link to the next page&#039; and WebHarvy Web Scraper will automatically scrape data from all pages. (Know More) Keyword based Scraping Keyword Based Scraping : Keyword based scraping allows you to capture data from search results pages for a list of input keywords. The configuration which you create will be automatically repeated for all given input keywords while mining data. Any number of input keywords can be specified. (Know More) (Video) Scrape via proxy server Scrape via Proxy Servers : To scrape anonymously and to prevent the web scraping software from being blocked by web servers, you have the option to access target websites via proxy servers. Either a single proxy server address or a list of proxy server addresses may be used. (Know More) Category Scraping Scrape Categories : WebHarvy Web Scraper allows you to scrape data from a list of links which leads to similar pages within a website. This allows you to scrape categories or subsections within websites using a single configuration. (Know More) (Video) Scrape with Regular Expressions : WebHarvy allows you to apply Regular Expressions (RegEx) on Text or HTML source of web pages and scrape the matching portion. This powerful technique offers you more flexibility while scraping data.(Know More) (RegEx Tutorial) WebHarvy Support Free Support &amp;amp; Updates : Once you purchase WebHarvy Web Scraper you will receive free updates and free support from us for a period of 1 year from the date of purchase. Bug fixes are free for lifetime. (Support Form) (Contact Us)</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/68369600?app_id=122963" width="425" height="319" frameborder="0" title="WebHarvy Demo" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Visual Point &amp; Click Interface : WebHarvy is a visual web scraper. There is absolutely no need to write any scripts or code to scrape data. You will be using WebHarvy's in-built browser to navigate web pages. You can select the data to be scraped with mouse clicks. It is that easy ! (Video) <br></li><li> Scrape Data Patterns Intelligently Identifies Patterns : WebHarvy automatically identifies patterns of data occurring in web pages. So if you need to scrape a list of items (name, address, email, price etc) from a web page, you need not do any additional configuration. If data repeats, WebHarvy will scrape it automatically. <br></li><li> Export scraped data Export Captured Data : You can save the data extracted from web pages in a variety of formats. The current version of WebHarvy Web Scraper allows you to export the scraped data as an XML, CSV, JSON or TSV file. You can also export the scraped data to an SQL database. (Know More) <br></li><li> Scrape data from multiple pages Scrape From Multiple Pages : Often web pages display data such as product listings in multiple pages. WebHarvy can automatically crawl and extract data from multiple pages. Just point out the 'link to the next page' and WebHarvy Web Scraper will automatically scrape data from all pages. (Know More) <br></li><li> Keyword based Scraping Keyword Based Scraping : Keyword based scraping allows you to capture data from search results pages for a list of input keywords. The configuration which you create will be automatically repeated for all given input keywords while mining data. Any number of input keywords can be specified. (Know More) (Video) <br></li><li> Scrape via proxy server Scrape via Proxy Servers : To scrape anonymously and to prevent the web scraping software from being blocked by web servers, you have the option to access target websites via proxy servers. Either a single proxy server address or a list of proxy server addresses may be used. (Know More) <br></li><li> Category Scraping Scrape Categories : WebHarvy Web Scraper allows you to scrape data from a list of links which leads to similar pages within a website. This allows you to scrape categories or subsections within websites using a single configuration. (Know More) (Video) <br></li><li> Scrape with Regular Expressions : WebHarvy allows you to apply Regular Expressions (RegEx) on Text or HTML source of web pages and scrape the matching portion. This powerful technique offers you more flexibility while scraping data.(Know More) (RegEx Tutorial) <br></li><li> WebHarvy Support Free Support &amp; Updates : Once you purchase WebHarvy Web Scraper you will receive free updates and free support from us for a period of 1 year from the date of purchase. Bug fixes are free for lifetime. (Support Form) (Contact Us)  <br></li></ul><br><img src="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/trx2WRsU8p0/maxresdefault.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt="WebHarvy 5.2.0.155"><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>