<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Market Spy Tools - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Market Spy Tools - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>Ali Inspector 1.41</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1970-ali-inspector.html</link>
<description>Name : Ali Inspector Version : 1.41 OS : Windows Type : AliExpress Spy Tools Price : $50 Homepage : SalePage Powerful 3-in-1 AliExpress Product Research Software that Generates Niche Keywords, Analyzes Bestsellers, and Uncovers Top Performing Dropship Products for Your eCommerce Store in just Minutes!</description>
<category>Market Spy Tools</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.appbreed.com/apps/aliinspector/images/aliinspector-header.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://aliinspector.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/09/ali-inspector-box-combo-2.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 11:42:42 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Keyword Generator Tool : Instantly generate thousands of highly targeted niche keywords in just seconds using the built-in keyword generator tool. Best Sellers Tool : Analyze all the best sellers on AliExpress in any category to instantly uncover the top selling products for your own eCommerce store! Keyword Search Tool : Quickly search AliExpress for any keyword using powerful search options to see the exact top selling products you need for your own eCommerce store!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/182916663?app_id=122963" width="425" height="239" frameborder="0" title="Dave Guindon&#039;s Shopy Spy Bonus - Ali Inspector" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><p><br></p><br><h3>Features</h3><br><p><br><ul><li> Keyword Generator Tool : Instantly generate thousands of highly targeted niche keywords in just seconds using the built-in keyword generator tool.<br></li><li> Best Sellers Tool : Analyze all the best sellers on AliExpress in any category to instantly uncover the top selling products for your own eCommerce store!<br></li><li> Keyword Search Tool : Quickly search AliExpress for any keyword using powerful search options to see the exact top selling products you need for your own eCommerce store!<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://www.appbreed.com/apps/aliinspector/images/aliinspector-header.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Ali Inspector 1.41"><br><img src="http://aliinspector.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/09/ali-inspector-box-combo-2.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>ALI Prospector 1.5</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1882-ali-prospector.html</link>
<description>Name : ALI Prospector Version : 1.5 OS : Windows Type : Alixpress Marketing Tools Price : $17 Homepage : SalePage Don&#039;t Waste Another Minute Researching Items to Sell Online Until You&#039;ve Read This ENTIRE Page! One click software allowing you to discover the hottest, most profitable items at THE SPEED OF LIGHT! I&#039;ve personally used this software to generate HUNDREDS OF THOUSANDS of dollars in sales across my eCommerce Empire. It&#039;s SO POWERFUL and EASY-TO-USE that my business partners literally BEGGED me not to release it publicly. ALI Prospector uses a secret algorithm to search AliExpress.Com (the LARGEST and most POPULAR database of wholesale products) and automatically shows you ONLY the products GUARANTEED to sell on your own websites.</description>
<category>Market Spy Tools</category>
<enclosure url="http://reviewbonuses.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/06/Ali-Prospector-Software-Review.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 09:05:34 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features One click search and amazing fast results! Instant researching software that will shave hours off of your work. Simply choose a category / niche and and receive blazing fast results! Instantly get detailed eCommerce and product intelligence, including the HOTTEST items GUARANTEED to sell! Fast Adobe Air desktop software that runs on Mac or PC without hassle. Easy installation and virtually no learning curve!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/zE-HsY0oW78?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> One click search and amazing fast results! Instant researching software that will shave hours off of your work.<br></li><li> Simply choose a category / niche and and receive blazing fast results!<br></li><li> Instantly get detailed eCommerce and product intelligence, including the HOTTEST items GUARANTEED to sell!<br></li><li> Fast Adobe Air desktop software that runs on Mac or PC without hassle.<br></li><li> Easy installation and virtually no learning curve!<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://reviewbonuses.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/06/Ali-Prospector-Software-Review.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="ALI Prospector 1.5"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Nabster 1.2.7</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1979-nabster.html</link>
<description>Name : Nabster Version : 1.2.7 OS : Windows/MAC Type : Esty/Fab/Wanelo Spy Price : $127 Homepage : SalePage Nabster allows to conduct ecommerce research across several aggregate sites. View products by popularity to shape your campaigns</description>
<category>Market Spy Tools</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 00:15:31 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Nabster allows to conduct ecommerce research across several aggregate sites. View products by popularity, research on AliExpress &amp;amp; save for later to shape your campaigns for the ultimate success. Competitive Research Sites Include: -Fab.com -Society6.com -Wanelo.com</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/tk-udL8MZ90?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br>Nabster allows to conduct ecommerce research across several aggregate sites. View products by popularity, research on AliExpress &amp; save for later to shape your campaigns for the ultimate success.<br>Competitive Research Sites Include:<br>-Fab.com<br>-Society6.com<br>-Wanelo.com<br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Nabster 1.2.7"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Prosperity Power 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/920-prosperity-power.html</link>
<description>Name : Prosperity Power Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Software Download Price : $999 Homepage : SalePage It doesn’t matter if you’re a top dog super affiliate or a newcomer to the game - you’re here to pave the path for future Inte.com marketing super stars to be. You see, earlier this year we saw talent from every corner of the globe...we saw unknowns become household names and shatter all records, and we saw old timers come back to one up them to set even a higher standard... ...From Singapore to the East Coast...guys broke records and showed us not only what’s possible, but also what’s to be expected on a fine launch.</description>
<category>Market Spy Tools</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 00:04:02 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features So, Why Are You Doing This Coordinated Shift? Well...for one... The entire market has limiting or ‘negative’ beliefs about money. Their conscious and subconscious minds are pulling them in two different directions. No wonder their lives are going nowhere with our services and products! Look, we have worked with lots of different people. Many of them became wildly successful as a result of using our systems, tools, and techniques. And we learned something interesting… We can build systems for people. We can give them all the information all the techniques and all the strategies that we have used in our life and in our businesses to make us millions of dollars. But you know what? If you don&#039;t have it ‘right’ between your ears, then NO system will work for them. So, what’s the plan? It’s a grand scheme we call the “Mindset Shift” where we’ll create a massive shift in the minds of the market while shoving our bank accounts full of JVzoo instant paypal payments...all in good fun of course, but...</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/EzpwvRtG54c?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> So, Why Are You Doing This Coordinated Shift?<br></li><li> Well...for one...   <br></li><li> The entire market has limiting or ‘negative’ beliefs about money. Their conscious and subconscious minds are pulling them in two different directions.    <br></li><li> No wonder their lives are going nowhere with our services and products!   <br></li><li> Look, we have worked with lots of different people.  Many of them became wildly successful as a result of using our systems, tools, and techniques.    <br></li><li> And we learned something interesting…   <br></li><li> We can build systems for people.   <br></li><li> We can give them all the information all the techniques and all the strategies that we have used in our life and in our businesses to make us millions of dollars.   <br></li><li> But you know what?   <br></li><li> If you don't have it ‘right’ between your ears, then NO system will work for them.     <br></li><li> So, what’s the plan? <br></li><li> It’s a grand scheme we call the “Mindset Shift” where we’ll create a massive shift in the minds of the market while shoving our bank accounts full of JVzoo instant paypal payments...all in good fun of course, but...  <br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Prosperity Power 1.0 "><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Funnel Spy 2.2.4</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1982-funnel-spy.html</link>
<description>Name : Funnel Spy Version : 2.2.4 OS : Windows Type : Traffic Generate Tools Price : $49 Homepage : SalePage Ethically Spy on Websites by Reverse Engineering the Most Profitable Funnels... with a Single Click! Now you can have X-Ray Vision and Uncover Hidden Pages for any Types of Funnels...</description>
<category>Market Spy Tools</category>
<enclosure url="http://funnelspyapp.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/09/fs-keith-mark-1.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 12:06:34 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Sales Funnels : With one click instantly reveal their complete sales funnel including upsells, downsells and one-time offers. Find out juicy competitor research like product offering, unique selling proposition, price points, design, layout and more! Lead Generation Sequences : Curious where a lead generation page leads to? With one click instantly uncover the thank you page and follow up sequence and m.comization strategy. Webinar Sequences : Expose their complete webinar funnel including any thank you pages, replay pages, encore pages and follow-up sequence. See what type of webinar software they use, watch their webinar presentation and m.comization strategy. Coaching/Consulting Offers : Discover their application process, what type of questions they ask to target the right students, and identify the different types of low, mid and high-end packages they offer for help crafting your own coaching offers Projects : Organize your different searches into projects. This is an easy way to manage your searches by theme, topic, client, etc… Favorites : Easily mark a page or several pages as a “favorite” for quick reference later. Filter Results : Quickly filter the results to find a specific type of page you are looking for. Add Your Own Keywords : Add and save your own keywords and FunnelSpy will add them to the search algorithm.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/rNJYST99Q_w?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Sales Funnels : With one click instantly reveal their complete sales funnel including upsells, downsells and one-time offers. Find out juicy competitor research like product offering, unique selling proposition, price points, design, layout and more!<br></li><li> Lead Generation Sequences : Curious where a lead generation page leads to? With one click instantly uncover the thank you page and follow up sequence and m.comization strategy.<br></li><li> Webinar Sequences : Expose their complete webinar funnel including any thank you pages, replay pages, encore pages and follow-up sequence.  See what type of webinar software they use, watch their webinar presentation and m.comization strategy.<br></li><li> Coaching/Consulting Offers : Discover their application process, what type of questions they ask to target the right students, and identify the different types of low, mid and high-end packages they offer for help crafting your own coaching offers<br></li><li> Projects : Organize your different searches into projects. This is an easy way to manage your searches by theme, topic, client, etc…<br></li><li> Favorites : Easily mark a page or several pages as a “favorite” for quick reference later.<br></li><li> Filter Results : Quickly filter the results to find a specific type of page you are looking for.<br></li><li> Add Your Own Keywords : Add and save your own keywords and FunnelSpy will add them to the search algorithm.<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://funnelspyapp.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/09/fs-keith-mark-1.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Funnel Spy 2.2.4"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>My Ecom Spy 1.0.14</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4067-my-ecom-spy-otos.html</link>
<description>Name : My Ecom Spy Version : 1.0.14 OS : Windows Type : Ecom Spy, Instagram Influence, Easty Spy, FB Research Price : $1320 Homepage : SalePage The Ecom System And Tool That Will Change The Ecom Game Forever! Find The Verified Hottest Products, The Highest Converting Ads, The Top Selling Vendors and The Top Promotions In Seconds!! This Is Our Grand Opening And The Beginning Of A Continual Upgraded Platform. State of the art Ecom research tool. Five tools in one to give you unheard of data for your Ecom business. The tools are unique! The data you receive with all 5 of our tools cannot be found anywhere!</description>
<category>Market Spy Tools</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2018 05:46:26 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FE - My EcomSpy - 1200$/y Finding a hot product is always the biggest hurdle. We are giving you access to thousands of hot selling products with a couple of clicks in real time. The Shopify Research tool will bring back realtime demographics on every aspect of the stores traffic. You will be able to see where they are getting all of their traffic. We have found several huge traffic sources that most Ecom sellers would have no idea where top stores are getting their traffic. Guess what? Many times it is not coming from Facebook and other traditional traffic sources. The Shopify Research tool also brings back the top traffic referral countries for every store. This is a great feature for people outside of the United States. This is an international tool. No other ecom tool brings you this kind of information. Gain access to thousands of promoters who will endorse the products you are selling. Find high converting products and vendors in seconds. The Facebook Research tool will allow you to look at any fanpage and filter by Likes, Views, Shares and Comments so you can find highly converting ads for products that are selling now. The software shows you the top selling vendors for millions of best selling products. This is the only software on the pl.com to offer these 5 unique tools. This gives you an unfair advantage. It is like cheating! Including Shopify, Insta spy tool, Etsy spy tool, Facebook ads spy tool, and the Top Shopify store tool. One stop system. We give you everything you need to succeed. The best selling products in any niche. The best ads to use. The best vendors to use. The best Instagram tool so you can crush it with your promotions. This is a proven system not just some flash in the pan software. We will continue to make updates in the coming days with new options. You will have free access to all new updated versions. Everything that is researched is in real time and sets this tool apart from anything else out there in the market. There is no scraped database. Everything you see is up to date to the second. No API&#039;s accessed! Since everything is in real time you have an infinite amount of products to find and take advantage of. It will never get saturated so take advantage of this opportunity. There is no other software that gives you access to hundreds of thousands of stores and products at your fingertips within seconds. This is not a scraped database like our competitors have that is outdated by months. You can do what would normally take hours for 1 or 2 products into minutes to find a winner and have the entire business laid out in front of you. Then we give you a Instagram tool to market that product to any niche that you would like. Instagram Shout Outs and promotions will give you a huge advantage in 2018 and this software will let you capitalize on this trend. You get access to the only software tool out there that gives you the best selling stores and products on Etsy. This Esty tool can find hot products or top selling vendors to dropship for you in seconds. This system will be constantly updated and all upgrades and updates are free! This is the swiss army knife of Ecom tools. OTO1 - My EcomSpy Gold Training - $47 Exclusive Group And Training For My Ecom Spy Members! OTO1 - My EcomSpy PLatinum Training - $67 Exclusive One On One Training!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/N7pcpU0ldXY?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><a href="https://www.myecomspy.com/sales-page"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer"><b>FE - My EcomSpy - 1200$/y</b></a><br><ul><li> Finding a hot product is always the biggest hurdle. We are giving you access to thousands of hot selling products with a couple of clicks in real time.<br></li><li> The Shopify Research tool will bring back realtime demographics on every aspect of the stores traffic. You will be able to see where they are getting all of their traffic. We have found several huge traffic sources that most Ecom sellers would have no idea where top stores are getting their traffic. Guess what? Many times it is not coming from Facebook and other traditional traffic sources. <br></li><li> The Shopify Research tool also brings back the top traffic referral countries for every store. This is a great feature for people outside of the United States. This is an international tool. No other ecom tool brings you this kind of information. <br></li><li> Gain access to thousands of promoters who will endorse the products you are selling. <br></li><li> Find high converting products and vendors in seconds.<br></li><li> The Facebook Research tool will allow you to look at any fanpage and filter by Likes, Views, Shares and Comments so you can find highly converting ads for products that are selling now. <br></li><li> The software shows you the top selling vendors for millions of best selling products.<br></li><li> This is the only software on the pl.com to offer these 5 unique tools. This gives you an unfair advantage. It is like cheating! Including Shopify, Insta spy tool, Etsy spy tool, Facebook ads spy tool, and the Top Shopify store tool. <br></li><li> One stop system. We give you everything you need to succeed. The best selling products in any niche. The best ads to use. The best vendors to use. The best Instagram tool so you can crush it with your promotions.<br></li><li> This is a proven system not just some flash in the pan software. We will continue to make updates in the coming days with new options. You will have free access to all new updated versions.<br></li><li> Everything that is researched is in real time and sets this tool apart from anything else out there in the market. There is no scraped database. Everything you see is up to date to the second. No API's accessed! <br></li><li> Since everything is in real time you have an infinite amount of products to find and take advantage of. It will never get saturated so take advantage of this opportunity. <br></li><li> There is no other software that gives you access to hundreds of thousands of stores and products at your fingertips within seconds. This is not a scraped database like our competitors have that is outdated by months. <br></li><li> You can do what would normally take hours for 1 or 2 products into minutes to find a winner and have the entire business laid out in front of you. Then we give you a Instagram tool to market that product to any niche that you would like. Instagram Shout Outs and promotions will give you a huge advantage in 2018 and this software will let you capitalize on this trend.<br></li><li> You get access to the only software tool out there that gives you the best selling stores and products on Etsy. This Esty tool can find hot products or top selling vendors to dropship for you in seconds.<br></li><li> This system will be constantly updated and all upgrades and updates are free!<br></li><li> This is the swiss army knife of Ecom tools.<br></li></ul><br><a href="https://www.myecomspy.com/my-ecom-spy-gold-training"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer"><b>OTO1 - My EcomSpy Gold Training - </b></a><br><ul><li> Exclusive Group And Training For My Ecom Spy Members!<br></li></ul><br><a href="https://www.myecomspy.com/my-ecom-spy-platinum-training"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer"><b>OTO1 - My EcomSpy PLatinum Training - </b></a><br><ul><li> Exclusive One On One Training!<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="My Ecom Spy 1.0.14"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Sourcing Samurai 1.5</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1264-sourcing-samurai.html</link>
<description>Name :Sourcing Samurai Version : 1.5 OS : Windows Type : Aliexpress Marketing Price : $57 Homepage : SalePage Sourcing Samurai Software: Apart from being able to uncover hot niches markets that can sell into, one of the hardest things is finding suppliers and manufacturers that can give you the best deals on your inventory. Sourcing Samurai software gives you access to a global.comwork of suppliers. Simply type in the products you want to purchase in bulk or have manufactured and it will let you sort by minimum order volume, pricing, response time from the seller and their current status so you can get the ball moving on your purchase! Finding good, reputable overseas suppliers and manufactures can be an arduous task! Well, that is no longer in issue with this amazing little tool that Sam had created to help him quickly narrow down suppliers.Imagine..within seconds after finding your products you can find your suppliers!</description>
<category>Market Spy Tools</category>
<enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/ecomexposed/sourcing-samurai-screenshot.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2017 07:29:20 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Feature #1: Category Search : Quickly get an idea of what products are hot based on their category. This software is setup with all the main Aliexpress categories so you can rest assured that you are research bases are completely covered! Feature #2: Clear Button : Software includes a “Clear” button so you can start over. Just like the old Nintendo systems with the reset button, you have a chance to reset your search without having to open the software up! Feature #3: Price : Sorting by price enables you to determine what products are selling at different price ranges, so you can better determine what product to sell. Feature #4: Offers : On Aliexpress there can be several different sellers of the exact same product. Sourcing Samurai allows you to see how different businesses are selling the same products, so you can see demand and also view if the product you are looking at would have a lower competition. Feature #5: Reviews : On Aliexpress a product with a high number of reviews is almost all the time a product that is getting a pile of sales. This is one of the favorite parts of this software. You can use the 8 different sorting options for reviews to uncover those hidden gems that you can start to grow your business around. Feature #6: Keyword Research : If you have already settled on your niche market, or just want to sort through products using a certain keyword this software gives you that ability! You can run searches for any type of product and use the results to validate that you are going in the correct direction. With this keyword research option it opens up the capabilities of this software big time!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/t4J8XShRLGA?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div>
<p></p>
<h3>Features</h3>
<p><br><ul><li> Feature #1: Category Search : Quickly get an idea of what products are hot based on their category. This software is setup with all the main Aliexpress categories so you can rest assured that you are research bases are completely covered! <br></li><li> Feature #2: Clear Button : Software includes a “Clear” button so you can start over. Just like the old Nintendo systems with the reset button, you have a chance to reset your search without having to open the software up! <br></li><li> Feature #3: Price : Sorting by price enables you to determine what products are selling at different price ranges, so you can better determine what product to sell. <br></li><li> Feature #4: Offers : On Aliexpress there can be several different sellers of the exact same product. Sourcing Samurai allows you to see how different businesses are selling the same products, so you can see demand and also view if the product you are looking at would have a lower competition. <br></li><li> Feature #5: Reviews : On Aliexpress a product with a high number of reviews is almost all the time a product that is getting a pile of sales. This is one of the favorite parts of this software. You can use the 8 different sorting options for reviews to uncover those hidden gems that you can start to grow your business around. <br></li><li> Feature #6: Keyword Research : If you have already settled on your niche market, or just want to sort through products using a certain keyword this software gives you that ability! You can run searches for any type of product and use the results to validate that you are going in the correct direction. With this keyword research option it opens up the capabilities of this software big time! <br></li></ul><br><img src="https://s3.amazonaws.com/ecomexposed/sourcing-samurai-screenshot.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Sourcing Samurai 1.5"></p>
<div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Handmade Toolbox 2.2</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1669-handmade-toolbox.html</link>
<description>Name : Handmade Toolbox Version : 2.2 OS : Windows Type : Esty Marketing Tools Price : $30 Homepage : SalePage Handmade Toolbox is a fully automated software application for increasing sales on Etsy! Add Followers, Favourites and Message Users! Handmade Toolbox is a low cost solution for marketing your Etsy Store. The application allows you to automatically add/remove followers, add/remove favourites and send messages to users on a large scale! Add, favourite or message other shops buyers! Really increase your sales by targeting specific users who actually make purchases! Stay ahead of your competition by following and messaging other shops buyers. This is a sure way to increase sales and target those users who make purchases of similar products to the ones you sell! Works in any country, worldwide! This application is proven to drive sales by increasing your search ranking. Also, the message template management tool allows you to share promotions, coupon codes and any news with users on Etsy! Once the application is purchased, you will receive Handmade Toolbox and a valid licence key within 24 hours to your payment email address The term &#039;Etsy&#039; is a trademark of Etsy, Inc. This application uses the Etsy API but is not endorsed or certified by Etsy, Inc.&quot;</description>
<category>Market Spy Tools</category>
<enclosure url="http://ginkosolutions.com/handmade-toolbox/img/app/8.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2017 09:19:47 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Add/Remove Etsy Followers... Getting your Etsy Store Noticed! Add/Remove Etsy Favourites... Boosting your Stores Search Ranking Message and Follow your competitions buyers! Mass Message Etsy Users, Followers and Favouriters! Manage Message Templates with an In-built Template Management Tool Manage Multiple Etsy Stores within one Single Application! Supports any Etsy account in any country! Build a Custom Unique Audience by Controlling Which Users to Follow/Favourite and Message Based on Custom Search Criteria Proxy IP Support</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><div class="dlevideoplayer" style="width:100%;max-width:425px;"><ul data-theme="default" data-preload="metadata"><li data-title="" data-type="youtube" data-url="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lH8KI_evF80"></li></ul></div></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Add/Remove Etsy Followers... Getting your Etsy Store Noticed!<br /></li><li> Add/Remove Etsy Favourites... Boosting your Stores Search Ranking<br /></li><li> Message and Follow your competitions buyers!<br /></li><li> Mass Message Etsy Users, Followers and Favouriters!<br /></li><li> Manage Message Templates with an In-built Template Management Tool<br /></li><li> Manage Multiple Etsy Stores within one Single Application!<br /></li><li> Supports any Etsy account in any country!<br /></li><li> Build a Custom Unique Audience by Controlling Which Users to Follow/Favourite and Message Based on Custom Search Criteria<br /></li><li> Proxy IP Support<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://ginkosolutions.com/handmade-toolbox/img/app/8.png" alt="Handmade Toolbox 2.2" title="Handmade Toolbox 2.2"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Handmade Toolbox 2.2" title="Handmade Toolbox 2.2"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Stuff Spy 1.5</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1137-stuff-spy.html</link>
<description>Name : Stuff Spy Version : 1.5 OS : Windows/MAC Type : Ebay/Amazon Research Tool Price : $17 Homepage : SalePage #1 Product Research Software for Affiliate Marketers! Gather Product Data + Insights FAST! Find 1000’s Of Amazon And Ebay Products With The Biggest Commissions! Uncover Products Instantly With The Help Of The World’s Most Comprehensive Ebay/Amazon Research Tool…See It In Action In The Video Below!</description>
<category>Market Spy Tools</category>
<enclosure url="http://stuffspy.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/6.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2016 17:16:52 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Deep Results : Simply enter a keyword or product name and let StuffSpy scour Amazon and Ebay to uncover hundreds or even thousands of products related to your query. Hot/Trending Products : Looking for hot products that are trending now online? StuffSpy keeps an updated record of daily products spiking every day. Product Insights : StuffSpy pulls the most important product data and insights to help you sift through hundreds or thousands of products in seconds. Ratings &amp; Reviews : Each result includes the number of customer reviews and ratings, allowing you to find products that customers LOVE (or hate). Advanced Filters : Looking for a product that meets certain criteria? Use our advanced filters to only display products that meet the criteria you set. Export Options : Export the StuffSpy results so you can conduct further research or send to a client/employee. 5 Reasons Why Inte.com Marketers Are LOVING StuffSpy + Amazon/Ebay Affiliate Programs! Largest Affiliate Programs on the Web : With MILLIONS of products listed on Amazon and Ebay, they are the largest affiliate programs for physical and digital goods on the web. This means there is ENDLESS opportunity Largest Online E-tailers on the Web : Did you realize that Amazon web sales are FIVE times Walmart, Target, and Buy.com web sales combined? Amazon serves 137 million customers a week (that’s a lot of sales…and commissions paid out). It makes sense that affiliates go where people are buying online. Earn Commissions on Total Order, Not Individual Products : It’s very rare that a customer will only by one item on Amazon or Ebay. Think about it, when a customer buys a Blue-Ray player…odds are they will buy a few DVDs with their purchase. With that being said, you will earn commissions on the entire order…not just the item you are promoting. Sift Through Millions of Products, QUICKLY : With millions of products being sold on Amazon and Ebay, that makes it hard for affiliates to manually search and find lucrative products to promote. Which is why StuffSpy is the missing piece of the puzzle. Pick the RIGHT Products to Promote EVERYTIME : Have all of the product research and data you need, at your fingertips, to make an informed decision if you should target a certain product or groups of products.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/1iIZeIy7TqM?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Deep Results : Simply enter a keyword or product name and let StuffSpy scour Amazon and Ebay to uncover hundreds or even thousands of products related to your query.<br /></li><li> Hot/Trending Products : Looking for hot products that are trending now online?  StuffSpy keeps an updated record of daily products spiking every day.  <br /></li><li> Product Insights : StuffSpy pulls the most important product data and insights to help you sift through hundreds or thousands of products in seconds. <br /></li><li> Ratings & Reviews : Each result includes the number of customer reviews and ratings, allowing you to find products that customers LOVE (or hate).  <br /></li><li> Advanced Filters : Looking for a product that meets certain criteria? Use our advanced filters to only display products that meet the criteria you set. <br /></li><li> Export Options : Export the StuffSpy results so you can conduct further research or send to a client/employee.  <br /></li></ul><br />5 Reasons Why Inte.com Marketers Are LOVING StuffSpy + Amazon/Ebay Affiliate Programs!<br /><ul><li> Largest Affiliate Programs on the Web : With MILLIONS of products listed on Amazon and Ebay, they are the largest affiliate programs for physical and digital goods on the web. This means there is ENDLESS opportunity<br /></li><li> Largest Online E-tailers on the Web : Did you realize that Amazon web sales are FIVE times Walmart, Target, and Buy.com web sales combined?  Amazon serves 137 million customers a week (that’s a lot of sales…and commissions paid out).  It makes sense that affiliates go where people are buying online.<br /></li><li> Earn Commissions on Total Order, Not Individual Products : It’s very rare that a customer will only by one item on Amazon or Ebay. Think about it, when a customer buys a Blue-Ray player…odds are they will buy a few DVDs with their purchase.  With that being said, you will earn commissions on the entire order…not just the item you are promoting.<br /></li><li> Sift Through Millions of Products, QUICKLY : With millions of products being sold on Amazon and Ebay, that makes it hard for affiliates to manually search and find lucrative products to promote. Which is why StuffSpy is the missing piece of the puzzle. <br /></li><li> Pick the RIGHT Products to Promote EVERYTIME : Have all of the product research and data you need, at your fingertips, to make an informed decision if you should target a certain product or groups of products. <br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://stuffspy.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/6.png" alt="Stuff Spy 1.5" title="Stuff Spy 1.5"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Stuff Spy 1.5" title="Stuff Spy 1.5"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>eComm Sleuth 1.1</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1695-ecomm-sleuth.html</link>
<description>Name : eComm Sleuth Version : 1.1 OS : Windows Type : Amazon, Etsy, eBay, Shopify, Clickbank Market Spy Tools Price : $47 Homepage : SalePage Tired Of Promoting Look-A-Like Launches And Recycled Ideas? Cutting Edge Technology Spies On Real-Time Traffic To Amazon, Etsy, eBay, Shopify, Clickbank .. Your List Will Love This: SOFTWARE REVEALS TRENDING Viral TeeS, PHYSICAL PRODUCTS .. CPA OFFERS.. Even Google Ads! eComm Sleuth uncovered multiple domains that were promoting the top 3 CLICKBANK products on Facebook. The product above is a Diabetes information product with 1 Million visits per month. I tracked a third of those in eComm Sleuth..</description>
<category>Market Spy Tools</category>
<enclosure url="http://ecommcore.online/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/sleuth-image.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2016 08:34:57 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features trending amazon products : viral traffic &amp; best sellers on amazon trending etsy products : viral and trending products on the craft ecommerce platform trending shopify : viral campaigns and trending products teeshirt trends : teespring, teechip, viralstyle, teefury, redbubble, sunfrog ecomm core: real-time insights</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/BJFRGXlCE04?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> trending amazon products : viral traffic & best sellers on amazon<br /></li><li> trending etsy products : viral and trending products on the craft ecommerce platform<br /></li><li> trending shopify : viral campaigns and trending products<br /></li><li> teeshirt trends : teespring, teechip, viralstyle, teefury, redbubble, sunfrog <br /></li><li> ecomm core: real-time insights<br /><br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://ecommcore.online/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/sleuth-image.png" alt="eComm Sleuth 1.1" title="eComm Sleuth 1.1"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="eComm Sleuth 1.1" title="eComm Sleuth 1.1"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>