<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Wiki Submission - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Wiki Submission - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>Wikipedia Backlink Finder 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4010-wikipedia-backlink-finder.html</link>
<description>Name : Wikipedia Backlink Finder Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Wikipedia Backlinks Tool Price : $200 Homepage : SalePage Wikipedia Backlink Finder is a software tool that allows users to find powerful Wikipedia backlinks to help boost their websites up the Google rankings. Backlinks are still the number one ranking factor in Google&#039;s 200+ ranking factors. Now I know what you are thinking... &quot;but wikipedia links are no follow, only do follow links help boost your rankings!?&quot;. While this may be true in &quot;general&quot;, there appear to be exceptions to this rule. Lets take a look at what google say themselves. Google webmaster guidelines for no follow &quot;In general, we don&#039;t follow them. This means that Google does not transfer PageRank or anchor text across these links.&quot; There you have it. In general they don&#039;t follow them, which means sometimes they do. Which makes sense because if you have one of the worlds most most authoritative websites where 99.9% of its outbound links are no follow some weight should be given to these links either in the form of page rank or general site authority. Many case studies align with this school of thought. Another theory is that Google has evolved past the simple rules of do follow and no follow with machine learning and knows that aged links on wiki pages link to credible high quality websites.Power LSI Finder is a desktop application that allows users to enter their niches keywords and Power LSI Finder will scrape Google in the background finding all the websites (up to 500 deep) that rank for that keyword. Once these websites (Google results) have been scraped it will crawl them all extracting their article content. Once its collected all this information it will aggregate all found LSIs from single 1 word LSIs to long tail 4 word LSIs. It not only does this for the content of all these websites it does it for the headers (h1 through to h6), keywords, title and description also. This is an extremely powerful keyword tool.</description>
<category>Wiki Submission</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2018 09:03:33 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Wikipedia Backlink Finder has two main modes of operation. Find competitors wiki backlinks - Using this mode you can simply enter your competitors keywords and it will scrape domains from google for those keywords or you can enter your competitors domains manually. Once it has your competitors domains it will search wikipedia to find all pages that are linking to your competitors websites. Once you have a list of wiki pages that are linking to your competitors you can edit these pages (see below for tips of this) and add your own websites domain to the wiki page. This mode can also bring back the Moz PA for each page and allow you to preview the link inside of tool and export results. Search for citation requests, known dead links and unknown (not marked as dead yet) dead links - Using this mode you enter your websites keywords and wikipedia pages will be scraped from Google that are related to your keywords or/and (depending on your options select) have dead links. These pages are then analyzed and the dead link target is extracted and displayed in the tool. The tool can also check for unknown dead links. So these are broken links on the wiki pages related to your keyword(s) that haven&#039;t been marked as dead yet. These could be websites where the domain has expired or the article being linked to has simply been moved resulting in a 404 error. This mode can also bring back the Moz PA for each page and allow you to preview the link inside of tool and export results.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/cC85T1Y7T5Y?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Wikipedia Backlink Finder has two main modes of operation.<br></li><li> Find competitors wiki backlinks<br></li><li> - Using this mode you can simply enter your competitors keywords and it will scrape domains from google for those keywords or you can enter your competitors domains manually. Once it has your competitors domains it will search wikipedia to find all pages that are linking to your competitors websites. Once you have a list of wiki pages that are linking to your competitors you can edit these pages (see below for tips of this) and add your own websites domain to the wiki page. This mode can also bring back the Moz PA for each page and allow you to preview the link inside of tool and export results. <br></li><li> Search for citation requests, known dead links and unknown (not marked as dead yet) dead links<br></li><li> - Using this mode you enter your websites keywords and wikipedia pages will be scraped from Google that are related to your keywords or/and (depending on your options select) have dead links. These pages are then analyzed and the dead link target is extracted and displayed in the tool. The tool can also check for unknown dead links. So these are broken links on the wiki pages related to your keyword(s) that haven't been marked as dead yet. These could be websites where the domain has expired or the article being linked to has simply been moved resulting in a 404 error. This mode can also bring back the Moz PA for each page and allow you to preview the link inside of tool and export results.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Wikipedia Backlink Finder 1.0 "><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Wiki Whisperer 2.1</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2053-wiki-whisperer.html</link>
<description>Name : Wiki Whisperer Version : 2.1 Enterprise OS : Windows Type : Wiki Submission Price : $47 Homepage : SalePage Wiki Whisperer is a tool that I classify as an advanced video marketing tool even though it’s simple to run and understand and has nothing directly to do with videos. In short what it does for us is find ultra powerful backlinks Opportunities. Google loves Wikipedia and if you have direct backlinks from Wikipedia and Google automatically trust and treats you as an authority so it’s for true insiders in video marketing. What the software does for us is gives us domains that have direct links from Wikipedia pages where the domain has expired and can be picked up for the cost of a regular domain.</description>
<category>Wiki Submission</category>
<enclosure url="http://locustware.com/get/wikiwhisper/images/u94-4.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2016 17:15:01 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features If you don’t really understand the value of Wikipedia backlinks do a Google search on it. You’ll see that people offer it as a service will charge you from sixty to a hundred dollars per backlink and with the wiki whisper software you’re able to get those backlinks for less than ten dollars plus because you own the domain. You’re able to basically multi-purpose those domain level backlinks on a much larger scale than those services are providing a much higher costs so we’re able to quickly achieve our goals from a video ranking perspective when you’re wanting to rank for a massively hard keyword instead of buying a couple of fiber gigs to get a massive number of garbage backlinks that only helped a little bit spend that ten dollars on a domain and use a single link that provides more power and authority that tens of thousands of those silly little profile backlinks that everyone else is using sort of like having the power of a massive PBN, except at a fraction of the cost and with a lot more instant authority and trust from Google. Video markers need every edge we can get. The software gives us that edge— get the software and join the ranks of elite video marketer around the world. Together will rule the video marketing landscape. All right now— let’s walk through the software together so that you can see and understand the process. Wiki whisper is not only powerful it’s also good fun to play with I constantly find cool little surprises. So, let’s walk through everything and I’ll get you up to speed. Your campaign name is your own personal identifier. It allows you to easily pull up results from previous campaign as all of your campaigns are saved into a folder in your documents directory called wiki whisper. Your settings tab this is where your personal settings are entered. The software will not run until all of the fields in the settings are populated with your personal information: your name, your email your MOZ credentials and your license is all that’s needed. Just click the Save button you have two types of search options keywords and metrics. Most beginning level marketers will stick to the keyword version because the software will find available backlinks there in some way related to your keywords. Just enter your keyword into the keyword section and run it. Using the keyword search will always return fewer results than the metrics searched, I’m using the metrics option will get you a broader level of results. This is something more advanced users are going to be more comfortable with since we know that when it comes to wiki backlink it is truly the page authority of the wiki page that is the true driving force for the results that we’re after. When using the metrics option you do not need to enter any keywords. That option doesn’t use keywords at all. As for your domain and page Authority settings, the higher you set any of these numbers, the lower number of results will be retrieved. It is great if you want to be laser targeted on one specific thing, since it does all of the filtering for you on the fly. The downside of filtering is that you can very easily filter out some amazing finds that you have not even thought of before. Personally, I don’t use the little sliders at all. I don’t drink at all online. I’ll leave them all set to a minimum, so it returns the absolute most results. Which of course means I’m presented with a lot more choices. I can’t tell you how many times, I have run across amazing metric sets that I would have never thought of but were amazingly powerful. One other note— there’s a lot going on behind the scenes in the software and it’s using multi-threading extensively because of the multi threading the activity area just can’t keep up. So it might look like at some points the software stuck, but it isn’t just leave it alone and let it keep running as long as there’s a little blue wave the image that’s going on here the software is doing what it’s supposed to do. So I’ll say this again just to be clear, if you think the software is stuck, it isn’t just leave it alone let it do its thing. Now as far as where it’s saving it I’m going to go ahead and open up one that I’ve done before so as you see the software has given me the domain name it’s given me the stats. It’s given me everything that I need in order to make a decision on whether or not I want to buy that domain and use it as a back link. As far as any other settings that this requires that’s all fully covered in the in the official tutorial that you’ll get after you’ve made your purchase.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/F0NugIrwv6w?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br />If you don’t really understand the value of Wikipedia backlinks do a Google search on it. You’ll see that people offer it as a service will charge you from sixty to a hundred dollars per backlink and with the wiki whisper software you’re able to get those backlinks for less than ten dollars plus because you own the domain. You’re able to basically multi-purpose those domain level backlinks on a much larger scale than those services are providing a much higher costs so we’re able to quickly achieve our goals from a video ranking perspective when you’re wanting to rank for a massively hard keyword instead of buying a couple of fiber gigs to get a massive number of garbage backlinks that only helped a little bit spend that ten dollars on a domain and use a single link that provides more power and authority that tens of thousands of those silly little profile backlinks that everyone else is using sort of like having the power of a massive PBN, except at a fraction of the cost and with a lot more instant authority and trust from Google.<br /><br />Video markers need every edge we can get. The software gives us that edge— get the software and join the ranks of elite video marketer around the world. Together will rule the video marketing landscape. All right now— let’s walk through the software together so that you can see and understand the process. Wiki whisper is not only powerful it’s also good fun to play with I constantly find cool little surprises.<br /><br />So, let’s walk through everything and I’ll get you up to speed. Your campaign name is your own personal identifier. It allows you to easily pull up results from previous campaign as all of your campaigns are saved into a folder in your documents directory called wiki whisper. Your settings tab this is where your personal settings are entered. The software will not run until all of the fields in the settings are populated with your personal information: your name, your email your MOZ credentials and your license is all that’s needed. Just click the Save button you have two types of search options keywords and metrics. Most beginning level marketers will stick to the keyword version because the software will find available backlinks there in some way related to your keywords. Just enter your keyword into the keyword section and run it. Using the keyword search will always return fewer results than the metrics searched, I’m using the metrics option will get you a broader level of results. This is something more advanced users are going to be more comfortable with since we know that when it comes to wiki backlink it is truly the page authority of the wiki page that is the true driving force for the results that we’re after. When using the metrics option you do not need to enter any keywords. That option doesn’t use keywords at all. As for your domain and page Authority settings, the higher you set any of these numbers, the lower number of results will be retrieved. It is great if you want to be laser targeted on one specific thing, since it does all of the filtering for you on the fly. The downside of filtering is that you can very easily filter out some amazing finds that you have not even thought of before. Personally, I don’t use the little sliders at all. I don’t drink at all online. I’ll leave them all set to a minimum, so it returns the absolute most results. Which of course means I’m presented with a lot more choices. I can’t tell you how many times, I have run across amazing metric sets that I would have never thought of but were amazingly powerful. One other note— there’s a lot going on behind the scenes in the software and it’s using multi-threading extensively because of the multi threading the activity area just can’t keep up. So it might look like at some points the software stuck, but it isn’t just leave it alone and let it keep running as long as there’s a little blue wave the image that’s going on here the software is doing what it’s supposed to do. So I’ll say this again just to be clear, if you think the software is stuck, it isn’t just leave it alone let it do its thing. Now as far as where it’s saving it I’m going to go ahead and open up one that I’ve done before so as you see the software has given me the domain name it’s given me the stats. It’s given me everything that I need in order to make a decision on whether or not I want to buy that domain and use it as a back link. As far as any other settings that this requires that’s all fully covered in the in the official tutorial that you’ll get after you’ve made your purchase.<br /><img src="http://locustware.com/get/wikiwhisper/images/u94-4.png" alt="Wiki Whisperer 2.1" title="Wiki Whisperer 2.1"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Wiki Whisperer 2.1" title="Wiki Whisperer 2.1"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>WikiLink Jacker Pro 1.03</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1210-wikilink-jacker.html</link>
<description>Name : WikiLink Jacker Version : Pro 1.03 OS : Windows/MAC Type : Wiki Submission Tools Price : $127 Homepage : SalePage WikiLink Jacker is premium authority backlink building and power content curation software that will grab your subscribers high PR backlinks from one of the hardest sites to get a lasting backlink on. That’s Right, I’m talking about WIKIPEDIA. Plus, build awesome unique content that is even safe to use on your money sites in minutes. When I showed my own subscribers how to do this trick manually, I got MORE excited email replies than on any other technique I’ve ever taught. And the software makes it even easier.</description>
<category>Wiki Submission</category>
<enclosure url="http://s3.amazonaws.com/la.slgraphics/wlj/wlj-03.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="http://s3.amazonaws.com/la.slgraphics/wlj/wlj-01.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 02:06:36 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Build AMAZING Authority Backlinks in Minutes Easily leverage the power of &#039;Expired Content&quot; to create high quality Wikipedia linkable content in minutes Gain trust and niche authority rapidly Easily rank for dozens of long tail terms Use your increased site authority to rank for more competetive keywors</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/hmWkHuqd-0g?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Build AMAZING Authority Backlinks in Minutes<br /></li><li> Easily leverage the power of 'Expired Content" to create high quality Wikipedia linkable content in minutes<br /></li><li> Gain trust and niche authority rapidly<br /></li><li> Easily rank for dozens of long tail terms<br /></li><li> Use your increased site authority to rank for more competetive keywors<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://s3.amazonaws.com/la.slgraphics/wlj/wlj-03.jpg" alt="WikiLink Jacker Pro 1.03" title="WikiLink Jacker Pro 1.03"  /><br /><img src="http://s3.amazonaws.com/la.slgraphics/wlj/wlj-01.jpg" alt="WikiLink Jacker Pro 1.03" title="WikiLink Jacker Pro 1.03"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="WikiLink Jacker Pro 1.03" title="WikiLink Jacker Pro 1.03"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>WikiRobot 1.35 Pro</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/968-wikirobot.html</link>
<description>Name : WikiRobot Professional Version : 1.0.35 OS : Windows Type : Wiki Submission Price : $67 Homepage : SalePage WikiRobot is the best and the most complete wiki solution on the market.It&#039;s a Wiki posting software that will create backlinks to your website in a matter of minutes.</description>
<category>Wiki Submission</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.wikirobot.com/images/screens/proxy.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2016 04:39:33 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Multiple CMS Support : WikiRobot currently supports the following platforms: MediaWiki, DokuWiki, TWiki, WikkaWiki, MacOS Wiki, TikiWiki and MoinMoin. New platforms are being constantly added. Local Database Storage WikiRobot uses local database. That means everything that happens (e.g. when you add sites to a project or create an article) in WikiRobot is stored in the database and stays there until you delete it. [b]Multithreaded : Up to 200 threads can be used for every imaginable action = blazing fast action! For those of you that don&#039;t know what threads are: simply said it&#039;s like having 200 browsers open doing all the work simultaneously in the background. Proxy Support : Anonymous and private HTTP proxies can be used with WikiRobot. It comes with a handy proxy handling interface that includes checking if proxies are alive, measuring response time, etc. When using proxies, they&#039;re always being rotated to prevent unwanted bans. Captcha Support : We have built in captcha solving engine, that will solve the simplest captcha types. DeathByCaptcha, De-Captcher, ImageTyperz, GSA Captcha Breaker and Captcha Sniper are also supported. You can also solve captcha manually by entering text from images or answering questions. Spinning : SpinRewriter, SpinnerChief, WordAI and The Best Spinner are supported in WikiRobot. That means all the content rewriting is like a walk in the park - easy and simple. Nested spinning is also supported. Powerful Scheduler : Jobs, consisting of tasks (Registration, E-mail Confirmation, Posting, Link Verification) are added through a simple wizard. Each task can: run once (date/time specified by user), or repeat: hourly, daily, weekly, monthly. Number of sites can be specified for each task. Tasks can be chained (with delay). WikiBase : WikiBase is a huge database of working and postable wiki sites that is constantly being refreshed and monitored. There are literally thousands of working sites available in WikiBase. Links Indexing : WikiRobot comes with a built in pinger, so your link building efforts won&#039;t go unnoticed. We have also integrated with Indexification, Linklicious and LinkPipeline which will do wonders to your links. Export Links : WikiRobot can export both only posted or also already verified links. It can export them in a simple TXT file or in a much more in-depth Excel format (that includes site&#039;s platform, PR, do-follow status, etc.). Ideal for those that sell wiki services or anyone else that just wants a pretty report. Live Links Checker : Posted articles can easily be checked for link presence. You can also easily export only live links. Logging Facility : Sometimes everything doesn&#039;t go according to the plan. There can be lots of reasons for failure and with WikiRobot you&#039;ll always know what&#039;s wrong. Every action and result can be logged and reviewed at a later time. Sites Filters : You can easily filter individual project and WikiBase sites to target exactly the ones you want. Some of the filters include: Do-Follow filter, PageRank filter, Captcha Filter, Platform Filter, .edu &amp; .gov Filter, etc. Blacklists : We all know that sites in a &quot;bad neighbourhood&quot; can have a negative impact on your rankings. That&#039;s why WikiRobot allows you to add bad sites to a blacklist. This way you can exclude them from your link building. Spyntax support for various fields Custom coded in C# Actions retry/delay Drip feeding Automatic Account Settings Generation Built-in Article Scraper Platform And PR Checker Dead Sites Test / Removal Duplicates Removal Lots Of Customizability And Settings Automatic Updates Beautiful And Intuitive User Interface Detailed User&#039;s Manual And Community Forum Extensive Support</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/dMqx5aPpXo8?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> <b>Multiple CMS Support</b> : WikiRobot currently supports the following platforms: MediaWiki, DokuWiki, TWiki, WikkaWiki, MacOS Wiki, TikiWiki and MoinMoin. New platforms are being constantly added.<br /></li><li> <b>Local Database Storage WikiRobot uses local database. That means everything that happens (e.g. when you add sites to a project or create an article) in WikiRobot is stored in the database and stays there until you delete it. <br /></li><li> [b]Multithreaded</b> : Up to 200 threads can be used for every imaginable action = blazing fast action! For those of you that don't know what threads are: simply said it's like having 200 browsers open doing all the work simultaneously in the background. <br /></li><li> <b>Proxy Support</b> : Anonymous and private HTTP proxies can be used with WikiRobot. It comes with a handy proxy handling interface that includes checking if proxies are alive, measuring response time, etc. When using proxies, they're always being rotated to prevent unwanted bans. <br /></li><li> <b>Captcha Support</b> : We have built in captcha solving engine, that will solve the simplest captcha types. DeathByCaptcha, De-Captcher, ImageTyperz, GSA Captcha Breaker and Captcha Sniper are also supported. You can also solve captcha manually by entering text from images or answering questions. <br /></li><li> <b>Spinning</b> : SpinRewriter, SpinnerChief, WordAI and The Best Spinner are supported in WikiRobot. That means all the content rewriting is like a walk in the park - easy and simple. Nested spinning is also supported. <br /></li><li> <b>Powerful Scheduler</b> : Jobs, consisting of tasks (Registration, E-mail Confirmation, Posting, Link Verification) are added through a simple wizard. Each task can: run once (date/time specified by user), or repeat: hourly, daily, weekly, monthly. Number of sites can be specified for each task. Tasks can be chained (with delay). <br /></li><li> <b>WikiBase</b> : WikiBase is a huge database of working and postable wiki sites that is constantly being refreshed and monitored. There are literally thousands of working sites available in WikiBase. <br /></li><li> <b>Links Indexing</b> : WikiRobot comes with a built in pinger, so your link building efforts won't go unnoticed. We have also integrated with Indexification, Linklicious and LinkPipeline which will do wonders to your links. <br /></li><li> <b>Export Links</b> : WikiRobot can export both only posted or also already verified links. It can export them in a simple TXT file or in a much more in-depth Excel format (that includes site's platform, PR, do-follow status, etc.). Ideal for those that sell wiki services or anyone else that just wants a pretty report. <br /></li><li> <b>Live Links Checker</b> : Posted articles can easily be checked for link presence. You can also easily export only live links. <br /></li><li> <b>Logging Facility</b> : Sometimes everything doesn't go according to the plan. There can be lots of reasons for failure and with WikiRobot you'll always know what's wrong. Every action and result can be logged and reviewed at a later time. <br /></li><li> <b>Sites Filters</b> : You can easily filter individual project and WikiBase sites to target exactly the ones you want. Some of the filters include: Do-Follow filter, PageRank filter, Captcha Filter, Platform Filter, .edu & .gov Filter, etc. <br /></li><li> <b>Blacklists</b> : We all know that sites in a "bad neighbourhood" can have a negative impact on your rankings. That's why WikiRobot allows you to add bad sites to a blacklist. This way you can exclude them from your link building. <br /></li><li> Spyntax support for various fields<br /></li><li> Custom coded in C#<br /></li><li> Actions retry/delay<br /></li><li> Drip feeding<br /></li><li> Automatic Account Settings Generation<br /></li><li> Built-in Article Scraper<br /></li><li> Platform And PR Checker<br /></li><li> Dead Sites Test / Removal<br /></li><li> Duplicates Removal<br /></li><li> Lots Of Customizability And Settings<br /></li><li> Automatic Updates<br /></li><li> Beautiful And Intuitive User Interface<br /></li><li> Detailed User's Manual And Community Forum<br /></li><li> Extensive Support<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://www.wikirobot.com/images/screens/proxy.png" alt="WikiRobot 1.35 Pro" title="WikiRobot 1.35 Pro"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="WikiRobot 1.35 Pro" title="WikiRobot 1.35 Pro"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>LINKFresh 1.01</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1648-linkfresh.html</link>
<description>Name : LINKFresh Version : 1.01 OS : Windows Type : Guest Post Price : $67 Homepage : SalePage 317+ High Quality BacklinksBuilt Automatically... (Watch How LINKFresh can Create Unlimited Backlinks for Your Websites Automatically within Minutes...) Generate Guaranteed Whitehat Backlinks,Page 1 Rankings and dailyFREE Traffic, at the Push of a Button! Your competitors won’t even know what hit them…they’ll just quietly fade away from top results while you dominate the page 1 for even the most competitive keywords.</description>
<category>Wiki Submission</category>
<enclosure url="http://i.imgur.com/W5ldeop.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2016 14:18:02 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Find broken, relevant Wikipedia links in any niche (to get them replaced with yours) Find broken links on high PR sites in any niche (to replace with yours) Deploy a special ‘Delicious Reversal’ method to automatically find influencers &amp; sites who actively link to similar videos &amp; content as yours Find charity sites that allow links for easy high PR, high MOZ authority links Find relevant ‘moved’ sites in your niche that are no longer up (to allow you to contact everyone linking to them to link to yours instead!) Finds easy, relevant places that allow site &amp; link submissions Gives you 100% control over how your links form and look Allows you to organize &amp; store the best linking opportunities to use over &amp; over</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/kzbsMT97miM?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Find broken, relevant Wikipedia links in any niche (to get them replaced with yours)<br /></li><li> Find broken links on high PR sites in any niche (to replace with yours)<br /></li><li> Deploy a special ‘Delicious Reversal’ method to automatically find influencers & sites who actively link to similar videos & content as yours<br /></li><li> Find charity sites that allow links for easy high PR, high MOZ authority links<br /></li><li> Find relevant ‘moved’ sites in your niche that are no longer up (to allow you to contact everyone linking to them to link to yours instead!)<br /></li><li> Finds easy, relevant places that allow site & link submissions<br /></li><li> Gives you 100% control over how your links form and look<br /></li><li> Allows you to organize & store the best linking opportunities to use over & over<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://i.imgur.com/W5ldeop.jpg" alt="LINKFresh 1.01" title="LINKFresh 1.01"  /><br /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="LINKFresh 1.01" title="LINKFresh 1.01"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Wiki Wizard 1.2.3.0 Elite</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1491-wiki-wizard.html</link>
<description>Name : Wiki Wizard Version : 1.2.3.0 Elite OS : Windows Type : Wiki Submission Price : $47 Homepage : SalePage SEO…Backlinks…Software… Buzz Words Warriors Go Crazy For… WikiWizard Has It All..</description>
<category>Wiki Submission</category>
<enclosure url="http://thewikiwizard.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/03/Wiki_WSO31.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="http://thewikiwizard.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/03/Wiki_WSO21.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2016 01:06:52 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Wiki Scraper Wiki Scheduler Wiki Post Drip Feeder</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/CvFes0u917k?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Wiki Scraper<br /></li><li> Wiki Scheduler<br /></li><li> Wiki Post Drip Feeder<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://thewikiwizard.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/03/Wiki_WSO31.jpg" alt="Wiki Wizard 1.2.3.0 Elite" title="Wiki Wizard 1.2.3.0 Elite"  /><br /><img src="http://thewikiwizard.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/03/Wiki_WSO21.jpg" alt="Wiki Wizard 1.2.3.0 Elite" title="Wiki Wizard 1.2.3.0 Elite"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Wiki Wizard 1.2.3.0 Elite" title="Wiki Wizard 1.2.3.0 Elite"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>