<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Article Spinners - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Article Spinners - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>Spun By Google Content Spinner 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4233-spun-by-google-content-spinner.html</link>
<description>Name : Spun By Google Content Spinner Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Article Spinner Price : $0 Homepage : SalePage Spun By Google Article Spinner is an article spinner software tool that uses Google translate to spin your content so you know the result is grammatically correct well formed content in the eyes of Google. This free content spinning tool simply throws your content in and out of Google translate. There are different options for how many times you want it spun and how hard you want it spun. The content it generates is perfect for lower tires in tired link building campaigns and even expired web 2.0s. NOTE: Please do not use spun content on your main/money website it is against Google webmaster terms and can result in your website being deindexed.</description>
<category>Article Spinners</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 06:18:21 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features By throwing your content back and forth through Google translate it changes but is always kept gramatically correct due to Google&#039;s excellent translation service. You can spin the content up to 10 times and spin soft, medium or hard. You can also shuffle the sentances.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Dq1kGb3p7rY?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> By throwing your content back and forth through Google translate it changes but is always kept gramatically correct due to Google's excellent translation service. You can spin the content up to 10 times and spin soft, medium or hard. You can also shuffle the sentances.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Spun By Google Content Spinner 1.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>SpinnerChief 5 Ultimate 9.2.6</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1064-spinnerchief-5.html</link>
<description>Name : SpinnerChief 5 Version : Ultimate Version v9.2.6 OS : Windows Type : Content Marketing Tools Price : $217 Homepage : SalePage The Real Best Article Spinner SpinnerChief III can not only generate hundreds of new articles in minutes for you, but also in one click it can rewrite articles to a very high level of human readability and uniqueness because it uses The Best Natural Language Analysis and Artificial Intelligence techniques to understand your articles in the same way as Google does.</description>
<category>Article Spinners</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 04:39:21 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features All the basic functions of a normal article spinner. Thesaurus is saved locally, so the speed is very fast. Paragraph/Sentence edit mode, you can rewrite paragraphs/sentences easily. Import synonyms from text files - multiple formats supported. Batch-spin articles. Spin large numbers of articles automatically. Export articles with other syntax formats like [|] [/] %% and so on. Favorites function - Add/Manage your favorite synonyms thesaurus based on your own categories and niches. Quick Preview - Easily preview the spun article and quickly locate the position you want to modify. Developer API - Now, programmers can integrate SpinnerChief functions into their own programs. Protect important keywords words in spun articles. Auto-add anchor text links in spun articles. &quot;Uniqueness&quot; percentage indicator. Batch-compare articles similarity function. Super Spin : Rewrite articles to a very high level of human readability and uniqueness using The Best Natural Language Analysis and Artificial Intelligence techniques. Paragraph and setence spin fully automatically. Spin Tree : The spin tree function makes manual paragraph and sentence spinning extremely easy. Cloud Thesaurus : Access over a million synonyms created by real users and use the cloud thesaurus phrase replacement feature to generate human-readable and unique new articles automatically. The number of synonyms in the thesaurus is increasing daily. Click here for more details. Part Of Speech : POS matching identifies the context of words. The POS engine can calculate whether a synonym is a noun, a verb, an adjective etc. SpinnerChief matches the part of speech of a synonym to its original word, so you can achieve grammatically and contextually correct articles! Custom/Cloud Grammar A.I. : This is not a normal grammar checker, it is a revolutionary way to correct your grammar when spinning articles to generate articles that are more readable. You can use your own custom grammar A.I. or use the Cloud A.I. generated by all users. Custom/Cloud Rules : Cloud Rules is supplementary to the POS function. This function can select better synonyms by analysing the related words in the sentence. This will help you to generate more readable articles, the rules are created by users and its effectiveness is increasing daily. Custom/Cloud Negs : Cloud Negs is another revolutionary feature invented by us for removing bad synonyms. The cloud negs database is based on all users&#039; selections and input too. Using this function, the program will use better quality synonyms when spinning your article. Submit article(s) to your blogs and many article directories directly from SpinnerChief (Supports post scheduling). Tips Plugin : You have seen this type of article before - e.g. &quot;10 Tips To Lose Weight&quot; The key factor about this type of article is that each tip (each paragraph) makes sense in its own right - independently of the rest of the article. So if you can get a bunch of these paragraphs together, then you can mix any number of paragraphs in order to make your new article. The SpinnerChief TIPS plugin will do this task effortlessly for you. Check the details by clicking here SK Plugin : It&#039;s a long, long job to research your keywords, keyword phrases, LSi&#039;s etc and then to write content for your chosen search term that has the perfect keywords, and the perfect density of those keywords. This plugin looks at the top 10 Google SERPS for your search term, compares them to each other, and then tells you the keywords that ALL the top 10 pages are using in their content, PLUS the density of those keywords. In less than a minute you will know EXACTLY which keywords and their relevant density to include in your website copy so that it matches Google&#039;s exact keyword expectations. Click here for more details. Miracle Thesaurus : They said it couldn&#039;t be done! Our Miracle Thesaurus CAN auto-spin to a human-readable level! Click here for more details. Video Scraper :This function scrapes videos from Youtube according to your keywords and you can easily insert these videos into your article with one click. Click here for more details. Picture Scraper : This function scrapes pictures from the inte.com according to your keywords and you can easily insert these pictures into your article with one click. Click here for more details. Scraper + Spinner + Submitter All In One Project create/save/load : Save all of the SpinnerChief feature settings as a project - load the project thesaurus automatically. No more having to go through all the settings and set them to your preferences before you start to work - load up your project and you&#039;re away! Article scraper : Choose any one of our carefully selected sources and scrape articles based on your keywords, then import them straight in to SpinnerChief ready to start spinning! Copyscape plugin : Enter your Copyscape ID and api and check any article straight from SpinnerChief. SC duplicate copy checker : Similar function to Copyscape to check if there are duplicate copies of your article published on the inte.com. The good thing is that you don&#039;t need to pay any credits to check your article by using this function - it&#039;s totally free! Content Hurricane plugin : This awesome tool (see contenthurricane.com) is now integrated as a plugin for SpinnerChief! Html Spin : Import full web pages, protect the html code when you spin, easily edit the html code, add and spin images - great for creating simple spun web pages and blog posts. SEO Writing : Keyword Density Count - check the density of your project keywords, and add any more keywords that you want to check. Batch add hyperlink : Highlight a bunch of selected words in your article, and make them all anchortext for any url - great for generating powerful backlinks. Import variables from csv files : in SpinnerChief you can now import sequentially instead of randomly. Swap paragraph : Easily swap paragraphs when you spin to make your articles more unique. Free update : We update our software often and you can always get the newest version by using the auto-update. Much much more are not listed here......</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/OB7DlPrkqiA?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> All the basic functions of a normal article spinner.<br></li><li> Thesaurus is saved locally, so the speed is very fast.<br></li><li> Paragraph/Sentence edit mode, you can rewrite paragraphs/sentences easily.<br></li><li> Import synonyms from text files - multiple formats supported.<br></li><li> Batch-spin articles. Spin large numbers of articles automatically.<br></li><li> Export articles with other syntax formats like [|] [/] %% and so on.<br></li><li> Favorites function - Add/Manage your favorite synonyms thesaurus based on your own categories and niches.<br></li><li> Quick Preview - Easily preview the spun article and quickly locate the position you want to modify.<br></li><li> Developer API - Now, programmers can integrate SpinnerChief functions into their own programs.<br></li><li> Protect important keywords words in spun articles.<br></li><li> Auto-add anchor text links in spun articles.<br></li><li> "Uniqueness" percentage indicator.<br></li><li> Batch-compare articles similarity function.<br></li><li> Super Spin : Rewrite articles to a very high level of human readability  and uniqueness using The Best Natural Language  Analysis and Artificial Intelligence techniques.<br></li><li> Paragraph and setence spin fully automatically.<br></li><li> Spin Tree : The spin tree function makes manual paragraph and sentence spinning extremely easy.<br></li><li> Cloud Thesaurus : Access over a million synonyms created by real users and use the cloud thesaurus phrase replacement feature to generate human-readable and unique new articles automatically. The number of synonyms in the thesaurus is increasing daily. Click here for more details.<br></li><li> Part Of Speech : POS matching identifies the context of words. The POS engine can calculate whether a synonym is a noun, a verb, an adjective etc. SpinnerChief matches the part of speech of a synonym to its original word, so you can achieve grammatically and contextually correct articles!<br></li><li> Custom/Cloud Grammar A.I. : This is not a normal grammar checker, it is a revolutionary way to correct your grammar when spinning articles to generate articles that are more readable. You can use your own custom grammar A.I. or use the Cloud A.I. generated by all users.<br></li><li> Custom/Cloud Rules : Cloud Rules is supplementary to the POS function. This function can select better synonyms by analysing the related words in the sentence. This will help you to generate more readable articles, the rules are created by users and its effectiveness is increasing daily.<br></li><li> Custom/Cloud Negs : Cloud Negs is another revolutionary feature invented by us for removing bad synonyms. The cloud negs database is based on all users' selections and input too. Using this function, the program will use better quality synonyms when spinning your article.<br></li><li> Submit article(s) to your blogs and many article directories directly from SpinnerChief (Supports post scheduling).<br></li><li> Tips Plugin : You have seen this type of article before - e.g. "10 Tips To Lose Weight" The key factor about this type of article is that each tip (each paragraph) makes sense in its own right - independently of the rest of the article. So if you can get a bunch of these paragraphs together, then you can mix any number of paragraphs in order to make your new article. The SpinnerChief TIPS plugin will do this task effortlessly for you. Check the details by clicking here<br></li><li> SK Plugin : It's a long, long job to research your keywords, keyword phrases, LSi's etc and then to write content for your chosen search term that has the perfect keywords, and the perfect density of those keywords. This plugin looks at the top 10 Google SERPS for your search term, compares them to each other, and then tells you the keywords that ALL the top 10 pages are using in their content, PLUS the density of those keywords. In less than a minute you will know EXACTLY which keywords and their relevant density to include in your website copy so that it matches Google's exact keyword expectations. Click here for more details.<br></li><li> Miracle Thesaurus : They said it couldn't be done! Our Miracle Thesaurus CAN auto-spin to a human-readable level! Click here for more details.<br></li><li> Video Scraper :This function scrapes videos from Youtube according to your keywords and you can easily insert these videos into your article with one click. Click here for more details.<br></li><li> Picture Scraper : This function scrapes pictures from the inte.com according to your keywords and you can easily insert these pictures into your article with one click. Click here for more details.<br></li><li> Scraper + Spinner + Submitter All In One<br></li><li> Project create/save/load : Save all of the SpinnerChief feature settings as a project - load the project thesaurus automatically. No more having to go through all the settings and set them to your preferences before you start to work - load up your project and you're away!<br></li><li> Article scraper : Choose any one of our carefully selected sources and scrape articles based on your keywords, then import them straight in to SpinnerChief ready to start spinning!<br></li><li> Copyscape plugin : Enter your Copyscape ID and api and check any article straight from SpinnerChief.<br></li><li> SC duplicate copy checker : Similar function to Copyscape to check if there are duplicate copies of your article published on the inte.com. The good thing is that you don't need to pay any credits to check your article by using this function - it's totally free!<br></li><li> Content Hurricane plugin : This awesome tool (see contenthurricane.com) is now integrated as a plugin for SpinnerChief!<br></li><li> Html Spin : Import full web pages, protect the html code when you spin, easily edit the html code, add and spin images - great for creating simple spun web pages and blog posts.<br></li><li> SEO Writing : Keyword Density Count - check the density of your project keywords, and add any more keywords that you want to check.<br></li><li> Batch add hyperlink : Highlight a bunch of selected words in your article, and make them all anchortext for any url - great for generating powerful backlinks.<br></li><li> Import variables from csv files : in SpinnerChief you can now import sequentially instead of randomly.<br></li><li> Swap paragraph : Easily swap paragraphs when you spin to make your articles more unique.<br></li><li> Free update : We update our software often and you can always get the newest version by using the auto-update.<br></li><li> Much much more are not listed here......<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="SpinnerChief 5 Ultimate 9.2.6"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Spintax Buddy 2.4</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2051-spintax-buddy.html</link>
<description>Name : Spintax Buddy Version : 2.4 OS : Windows Type : Spinner Price : $27 Homepage : SalePage Sooner Or Later All Marketers Use Spintax For most people, using spintax is a major pain in the behind. We use it because it provides a level of flexibility and power unmatched by any other content manipulation model, but that doesn&#039;t mean we have to like it... NEW SOFTWARE SHATTERS THE SPINTAX BARRIER WITH PURE DRIVEN SIMPLICITY</description>
<category>Article Spinners</category>
<enclosure url="http://locustware.com/get/spintax/images/spintax-example.gif" type="image/gif" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2016 17:01:26 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Spintax used to confuse the heck out of me. I understood the concept just fine, but as I built/wrote it, it became more and more confusing to the point that my sentences didn&#039;t end up making since. So I created a new software program that takes all of that hard and confusing stuff and restructures it into a very simple step by step process. Basically, how I do it is one word or phrase at a time So, I create my little word group one word, one line at a time. Then I allow the software to spin it and save that spin file for me. I named mine: me myself and I Then I move on to the next chunk of text I want to spin. Take the same little step, save it with a name that means something to me and so on. I do that with every part - That way I am breaking it all down into very small easy steps. Now, when I get ready to create my full spintax string (phrase/sentence/paragraph) I just click the &amp;quot;Open Spintax&amp;quot; button and one by one select the spintax that I want to paste into whatever project I am working on. I also have the option of creating variants on the fly. In other words, I can select a bunch of the little spintax scripts I created and saved, and the software will properly merge them together and produce however many variations I want in plain text. So, in places that I can&#039;t use spintax, I can still spintax my text and create virtually unlimited unique variations so that I never get hit with any duplicate content nonsense. Having the ability to create great spintax scenarios is what separates hobbyists from professionals. It doesn&#039;t matter if you are spinning complete articles, single paragraphs, or simple sentences, when you use spintax you open a whole new world. I have a friend who is a professional kindle short story writer, and any time he runs into a situation where his sentence or paragraph just doesn&#039;t &amp;quot;feel&amp;quot; right, he opens up SpintaxBuddy and near instantly solves the problem. Here is an example: (created using SpintaxBuddy) I love being able to use SpintaxBuddy to generate unique content on demand! We enjoy having the ability to create unique content using spintax. Here is another example: (created using SpintaxBuddy) When Jacod heard the deep gravely rumble as Thomas yelled Ruuuuun... As Jacob listened to the baritone rumble of Thomas screaming Ruuuuun... Get It? With spintax you can change the game. Always have unique content while saying essentially the same thing. Example Variants Created From Spintax That Took Less Than 2 Minutes To Create Using This Software... I love the software to immediately create articles as needed. I have the knowledge to easily alter posts whenever I want! I have the knowledge to easily alter comments as often as possible. I want the ability to automatically rewrite text on demand. I enjoy the ability to automatically rewrite text on demand. I love the software to immediately create text on demand. I enjoy the ability to automatically rewrite articles as needed. I love the knowledge to easily alter posts whenever I want! I need the software to immediately create articles as needed. I love the software to immediately create articles 45 times per day I need the knowledge to easily alter posts whenever I want! I have the knowledge to automatically rewrite text on demand. I want the software to immediately create articles as needed. I love the software to easily alter posts whenever I want! I enjoy the ability to easily alter posts whenever I want! I love the software to immediately create sentences 45 times per day I love the software to immediately create articles as often as possible. I love the software to immediately create comments as often as possible. I love the ability to automatically rewrite text on demand. I enjoy the ability to automatically alter posts whenever I want! I have the knowledge to easily alter text on demand. I love the software to immediately rewrite text on demand. I enjoy the ability to automatically rewrite text whenever I want! I have the knowledge to easily spin sentences 45 times per day I need the ability to automatically rewrite text on demand.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/UXGJZiXroA0?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><br /><br />Spintax used to confuse the heck out of me. I understood the concept just fine, but as I built/wrote it, it became more and more confusing to the point that my sentences didn't end up making since. <br />So I created a new software program that takes all of that hard and confusing stuff and restructures it into a very simple step by step process.<br /><br />Basically, how I do it is one word or phrase at a time So, I create my little word group one word, one line at a time. Then I allow the software to spin it and save that spin file for me. <br />I named mine: me myself and I Then I move on to the next chunk of text I want to spin. Take the same little step, save it with a name that means something to me and so on. <br />I do that with every part - That way I am breaking it all down into very small easy steps. <br />Now, when I get ready to create my full spintax string (phrase/sentence/paragraph) I just click the &quot;Open Spintax&quot; button and one by one select the spintax that I want to paste into whatever project I am working on. <br />I also have the option of creating variants on the fly. In other words, I can select a bunch of the little spintax scripts I created and saved, and the software will properly merge them together and produce however many variations I want in plain text. So, in places that I can't use spintax, <br />I can still spintax my text and create virtually unlimited unique variations so that I never get hit with any duplicate content nonsense.<br /><br />Having the ability to create great spintax scenarios is what separates hobbyists from professionals. <br />It doesn't matter if you are spinning complete articles, single paragraphs, or simple sentences, when you use spintax you open a whole new world. <br />I have a friend who is a professional kindle short story writer, and any time he runs into a situation where his sentence or paragraph just doesn't &quot;feel&quot; right, he opens up SpintaxBuddy and near instantly solves the problem. Here is an example: (created using SpintaxBuddy) I love being able to use SpintaxBuddy to generate unique content on demand! We enjoy having the ability to create unique content using spintax. Here is another example: (created using SpintaxBuddy) When Jacod heard the deep gravely rumble as Thomas yelled Ruuuuun... As Jacob listened to the baritone rumble of Thomas screaming Ruuuuun... Get It? With spintax you can change the game. Always have unique content while saying essentially the same thing.<br /><br /><br />Example Variants Created From Spintax That Took Less Than 2 Minutes To Create Using This Software... <br />I love the software to immediately create articles as needed. <br />I have the knowledge to easily alter posts whenever I want! <br />I have the knowledge to easily alter comments as often as possible. <br />I want the ability to automatically rewrite text on demand. <br />I enjoy the ability to automatically rewrite text on demand. <br />I love the software to immediately create text on demand. <br />I enjoy the ability to automatically rewrite articles as needed. <br />I love the knowledge to easily alter posts whenever I want! <br />I need the software to immediately create articles as needed. <br />I love the software to immediately create articles 45 times per day <br />I need the knowledge to easily alter posts whenever I want! <br />I have the knowledge to automatically rewrite text on demand. <br />I want the software to immediately create articles as needed.<br />I love the software to easily alter posts whenever I want! <br />I enjoy the ability to easily alter posts whenever I want! <br />I love the software to immediately create sentences 45 times per day <br />I love the software to immediately create articles as often as possible. <br />I love the software to immediately create comments as often as possible. <br />I love the ability to automatically rewrite text on demand. <br />I enjoy the ability to automatically alter posts whenever I want! <br />I have the knowledge to easily alter text on demand. <br />I love the software to immediately rewrite text on demand. <br />I enjoy the ability to automatically rewrite text whenever I want! <br />I have the knowledge to easily spin sentences 45 times per day <br />I need the ability to automatically rewrite text on demand.<br /><br /><img src="http://locustware.com/get/spintax/images/spintax-example.gif" alt="Spintax Buddy 2.4" title="Spintax Buddy 2.4"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Spintax Buddy 2.4" title="Spintax Buddy 2.4"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>SpinnerChief 4 Ultimate 9.2</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1070-spinnerchief-4.html</link>
<description>Name : SpinnerChief 4 Version : Ultimate Version 9.2 OS : Windows Type : Content Marketing Tools Price : $1223 Homepage : SalePage The Real Best Article Spinner SpinnerChief 4 can not only generate hundreds of new articles in minutes for you, but also in one click it can rewrite articles to a very high level of human readability and uniqueness because it uses The Best Natural Language Analysis and Artificial Intelligence techniques to understand your articles in the same way as Google does.</description>
<category>Article Spinners</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.spinnerchief.com/img/home_hero.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2016 22:46:17 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features All the basic functions of a normal article spinner. Thesaurus is saved locally, so the speed is very fast. Paragraph/Sentence edit mode, you can rewrite paragraphs/sentences easily. Import synonyms from text files - multiple formats supported. Batch-spin articles. Spin large numbers of articles automatically. Export articles with other syntax formats like [|] [/] %% and so on. Favorites function - Add/Manage your favorite synonyms thesaurus based on your own categories and niches. Quick Preview - Easily preview the spun article and quickly locate the position you want to modify. Developer API - Now, programmers can integrate SpinnerChief functions into their own programs. Protect important keywords words in spun articles. Auto-add anchor text links in spun articles. &quot;Uniqueness&quot; percentage indicator. Batch-compare articles similarity function. Super Spin : Rewrite articles to a very high level of human readability and uniqueness using The Best Natural Language Analysis and Artificial Intelligence techniques. Paragraph and setence spin fully automatically. Spin Tree : The spin tree function makes manual paragraph and sentence spinning extremely easy. Cloud Thesaurus : Access over a million synonyms created by real users and use the cloud thesaurus phrase replacement feature to generate human-readable and unique new articles automatically. The number of synonyms in the thesaurus is increasing daily. Click here for more details. Part Of Speech : POS matching identifies the context of words. The POS engine can calculate whether a synonym is a noun, a verb, an adjective etc. SpinnerChief matches the part of speech of a synonym to its original word, so you can achieve grammatically and contextually correct articles! Custom/Cloud Grammar A.I. : This is not a normal grammar checker, it is a revolutionary way to correct your grammar when spinning articles to generate articles that are more readable. You can use your own custom grammar A.I. or use the Cloud A.I. generated by all users. Custom/Cloud Rules : Cloud Rules is supplementary to the POS function. This function can select better synonyms by analysing the related words in the sentence. This will help you to generate more readable articles, the rules are created by users and its effectiveness is increasing daily. Custom/Cloud Negs : Cloud Negs is another revolutionary feature invented by us for removing bad synonyms. The cloud negs database is based on all users&#039; selections and input too. Using this function, the program will use better quality synonyms when spinning your article. Submit article(s) to your blogs and many article directories directly from SpinnerChief (Supports post scheduling). Tips Plugin : You have seen this type of article before - e.g. &quot;10 Tips To Lose Weight&quot; The key factor about this type of article is that each tip (each paragraph) makes sense in its own right - independently of the rest of the article. So if you can get a bunch of these paragraphs together, then you can mix any number of paragraphs in order to make your new article. The SpinnerChief TIPS plugin will do this task effortlessly for you. Check the details by clicking here SK Plugin : It&#039;s a long, long job to research your keywords, keyword phrases, LSi&#039;s etc and then to write content for your chosen search term that has the perfect keywords, and the perfect density of those keywords. This plugin looks at the top 10 Google SERPS for your search term, compares them to each other, and then tells you the keywords that ALL the top 10 pages are using in their content, PLUS the density of those keywords. In less than a minute you will know EXACTLY which keywords and their relevant density to include in your website copy so that it matches Google&#039;s exact keyword expectations. Click here for more details. Miracle Thesaurus : They said it couldn&#039;t be done! Our Miracle Thesaurus CAN auto-spin to a human-readable level! Click here for more details. Video Scraper :This function scrapes videos from Youtube according to your keywords and you can easily insert these videos into your article with one click. Click here for more details. Picture Scraper : This function scrapes pictures from the inte.com according to your keywords and you can easily insert these pictures into your article with one click. Click here for more details. Scraper + Spinner + Submitter All In One Project create/save/load : Save all of the SpinnerChief feature settings as a project - load the project thesaurus automatically. No more having to go through all the settings and set them to your preferences before you start to work - load up your project and you&#039;re away! Article scraper : Choose any one of our carefully selected sources and scrape articles based on your keywords, then import them straight in to SpinnerChief ready to start spinning! Copyscape plugin : Enter your Copyscape ID and api and check any article straight from SpinnerChief. SC duplicate copy checker : Similar function to Copyscape to check if there are duplicate copies of your article published on the inte.com. The good thing is that you don&#039;t need to pay any credits to check your article by using this function - it&#039;s totally free! Content Hurricane plugin : This awesome tool (see contenthurricane.com) is now integrated as a plugin for SpinnerChief! Html Spin : Import full web pages, protect the html code when you spin, easily edit the html code, add and spin images - great for creating simple spun web pages and blog posts. SEO Writing : Keyword Density Count - check the density of your project keywords, and add any more keywords that you want to check. Batch add hyperlink : Highlight a bunch of selected words in your article, and make them all anchortext for any url - great for generating powerful backlinks. Import variables from csv files : in SpinnerChief you can now import sequentially instead of randomly. Swap paragraph : Easily swap paragraphs when you spin to make your articles more unique. Free update : We update our software often and you can always get the newest version by using the auto-update. Much much more are not listed here......</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/EVe7YGrSTLU?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> All the basic functions of a normal article spinner.<br></li><li> Thesaurus is saved locally, so the speed is very fast.<br></li><li> Paragraph/Sentence edit mode, you can rewrite paragraphs/sentences easily.<br></li><li> Import synonyms from text files - multiple formats supported.<br></li><li> Batch-spin articles. Spin large numbers of articles automatically.<br></li><li> Export articles with other syntax formats like [|] [/] %% and so on.<br></li><li> Favorites function - Add/Manage your favorite synonyms thesaurus based on your own categories and niches.<br></li><li> Quick Preview - Easily preview the spun article and quickly locate the position you want to modify.<br></li><li> Developer API - Now, programmers can integrate SpinnerChief functions into their own programs.<br></li><li> Protect important keywords words in spun articles.<br></li><li> Auto-add anchor text links in spun articles.<br></li><li> "Uniqueness" percentage indicator.<br></li><li> Batch-compare articles similarity function.<br></li><li> Super Spin : Rewrite articles to a very high level of human readability  and uniqueness using The Best Natural Language  Analysis and Artificial Intelligence techniques.<br></li><li> Paragraph and setence spin fully automatically.<br></li><li> Spin Tree : The spin tree function makes manual paragraph and sentence spinning extremely easy.<br></li><li> Cloud Thesaurus : Access over a million synonyms created by real users and use the cloud thesaurus phrase replacement feature to generate human-readable and unique new articles automatically. The number of synonyms in the thesaurus is increasing daily. Click here for more details.<br></li><li> Part Of Speech : POS matching identifies the context of words. The POS engine can calculate whether a synonym is a noun, a verb, an adjective etc. SpinnerChief matches the part of speech of a synonym to its original word, so you can achieve grammatically and contextually correct articles!<br></li><li> Custom/Cloud Grammar A.I. : This is not a normal grammar checker, it is a revolutionary way to correct your grammar when spinning articles to generate articles that are more readable. You can use your own custom grammar A.I. or use the Cloud A.I. generated by all users.<br></li><li> Custom/Cloud Rules : Cloud Rules is supplementary to the POS function. This function can select better synonyms by analysing the related words in the sentence. This will help you to generate more readable articles, the rules are created by users and its effectiveness is increasing daily.<br></li><li> Custom/Cloud Negs : Cloud Negs is another revolutionary feature invented by us for removing bad synonyms. The cloud negs database is based on all users' selections and input too. Using this function, the program will use better quality synonyms when spinning your article.<br></li><li> Submit article(s) to your blogs and many article directories directly from SpinnerChief (Supports post scheduling).<br></li><li> Tips Plugin : You have seen this type of article before - e.g. "10 Tips To Lose Weight" The key factor about this type of article is that each tip (each paragraph) makes sense in its own right - independently of the rest of the article. So if you can get a bunch of these paragraphs together, then you can mix any number of paragraphs in order to make your new article. The SpinnerChief TIPS plugin will do this task effortlessly for you. Check the details by clicking here<br></li><li> SK Plugin : It's a long, long job to research your keywords, keyword phrases, LSi's etc and then to write content for your chosen search term that has the perfect keywords, and the perfect density of those keywords. This plugin looks at the top 10 Google SERPS for your search term, compares them to each other, and then tells you the keywords that ALL the top 10 pages are using in their content, PLUS the density of those keywords. In less than a minute you will know EXACTLY which keywords and their relevant density to include in your website copy so that it matches Google's exact keyword expectations. Click here for more details.<br></li><li> Miracle Thesaurus : They said it couldn't be done! Our Miracle Thesaurus CAN auto-spin to a human-readable level! Click here for more details.<br></li><li> Video Scraper :This function scrapes videos from Youtube according to your keywords and you can easily insert these videos into your article with one click. Click here for more details.<br></li><li> Picture Scraper : This function scrapes pictures from the inte.com according to your keywords and you can easily insert these pictures into your article with one click. Click here for more details.<br></li><li> Scraper + Spinner + Submitter All In One<br></li><li> Project create/save/load : Save all of the SpinnerChief feature settings as a project - load the project thesaurus automatically. No more having to go through all the settings and set them to your preferences before you start to work - load up your project and you're away!<br></li><li> Article scraper : Choose any one of our carefully selected sources and scrape articles based on your keywords, then import them straight in to SpinnerChief ready to start spinning!<br></li><li> Copyscape plugin : Enter your Copyscape ID and api and check any article straight from SpinnerChief.<br></li><li> SC duplicate copy checker : Similar function to Copyscape to check if there are duplicate copies of your article published on the inte.com. The good thing is that you don't need to pay any credits to check your article by using this function - it's totally free!<br></li><li> Content Hurricane plugin : This awesome tool (see contenthurricane.com) is now integrated as a plugin for SpinnerChief!<br></li><li> Html Spin : Import full web pages, protect the html code when you spin, easily edit the html code, add and spin images - great for creating simple spun web pages and blog posts.<br></li><li> SEO Writing : Keyword Density Count - check the density of your project keywords, and add any more keywords that you want to check.<br></li><li> Batch add hyperlink : Highlight a bunch of selected words in your article, and make them all anchortext for any url - great for generating powerful backlinks.<br></li><li> Import variables from csv files : in SpinnerChief you can now import sequentially instead of randomly.<br></li><li> Swap paragraph : Easily swap paragraphs when you spin to make your articles more unique.<br></li><li> Free update : We update our software often and you can always get the newest version by using the auto-update.<br></li><li> Much much more are not listed here......<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://www.spinnerchief.com/img/home_hero.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt="SpinnerChief 4 Ultimate 9.2"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Instant Article Suite 1.10 Pro</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1150-instant-article-suite.html</link>
<description>Name : Instant Article Suite Version : 1.10 Pro OS : Windows Type : Article Submission, Article Spinner, Article Stuffer Price : $37 Homepage : SalePage Why Pay $100&#039;s For Overhyped Article Rewriting And Spinning Software When You Can Grab Here An...Easy To Use Software That Makes Your Content Achieve 90% Up To 100% Uniqueness For A VERY Low Price! And does the same job as those highly priced spinners. Are you sick and tired of writing articles for your website? Do you want to earn some extra cash blogging or writing for your clients? Thousands of freelancers are doing this using our ‘Tips Approach solution’, and trust us, its so easy that even a child with basic knowledge of English can do it. Introducing Instant Article Suite pro, the ultimate software which is, believe it or not, a three in one solution for all your headaches in creating unique search engine friendly articles. Why pay for your articles when you can get it done for FREE?</description>
<category>Article Spinners</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.instantarticlesuitepro.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/instant-article-suite-pro-logo.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 21:58:12 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Instant Article Shuffler: This is the CORE software that will help you achieve more randomness and uniqueness to your content. Instant Article Spinner: This is a brand new never released spinning software. Instant Article Submitter: This tool helps you to populate YOUR wordpress blogs by mass uploading articles very easily.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><video width="640" height="480" preload="metadata" controls="controls">
				<source src="http://hostideo.com/ias/videos/sales3/IAS%20WSO%203.mp4"></source>
				</video></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Instant Article Shuffler: This is the CORE software that will help you achieve more randomness and uniqueness to your content.<br /></li><li> Instant Article Spinner: This is a brand new never released spinning software.<br /></li><li> Instant Article Submitter: This tool helps you to populate YOUR wordpress blogs by mass uploading articles very easily.<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://www.instantarticlesuitepro.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/instant-article-suite-pro-logo.png" alt="Instant Article Suite 1.10 Pro" title="Instant Article Suite 1.10 Pro"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Instant Article Suite 1.10 Pro" title="Instant Article Suite 1.10 Pro"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Automatic Proofreader 1.0.10</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1446-automatic-proofreader.html</link>
<description>Name : Automatic Proofreader Version : 1.0.10 OS : Windows Type : Content Marketing Tools Price : $67 Homepage : SalePage Automatic Proofreader - grammar checker software. Makes the spun content really readable on Wordpress Spun Content? No problem!... AUTOMATIC PROOFREADER SOFTWARE allows you to find those pesky mistakes and correct them on your WORDPRESS blogs or in the text files on your computer. Finally You Can Fully Equip yourself with this powerful “Must Have” Tools for perfecting All the grammatical errors, spelling mistakes, omissions before your next writing project! AUTOMATIC PROOFREADER SOFTWARE allows you to find those pesky mistakes and correct them on your WORD PRESS blogs or in the text files on your computer.</description>
<category>Article Spinners</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-12/1451229030_12469_automaticproofreader_logo2small.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2015 19:09:40 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Proper check and critical analysis will boost both the writing skills &amp; confidence of the Writer.. Avoiding spelling mistakes, punctuation and common writing errors tends to bring consistency in the use of English language in users&#039; daily writings.. As a blogger that writes engaging articles for your followers, you don’t need to pay for any proofreading services anymore with this tool. Inte.com Marketers cannot do the entire task by themselves, hence the need to outsource a writing and proofreading jobs but with this powerful software, you will save huge money by doing it yourself even better. Anybody can make huge money from this software either directly by setting up PROOFREADING services or indirectly by saving cost of outsourcing. Fully Automated system: software will identify errors, highlighted the errors, give prioritized words suggestions based on writers intention update your blog post without giving you stress. The technology behind AUTOMATIC PROOFREADER SOFTWARE makes us to be aware of mistakes and helps us to detect common possible writing errors before we deliver our writing jobs to client. This technology is a great path to improve on our business communication, particularly when we communicate with our clients and colleagues through e-mails, memos, letters and other business oriented documents.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/vFTrA2pF3JA?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Proper check and critical analysis will boost both the writing skills & confidence of the Writer..<br /></li><li> Avoiding spelling mistakes, punctuation and common writing errors tends to bring consistency in the use of English language in users' daily writings..<br /></li><li> As a blogger that writes engaging articles for your followers, you don’t need to pay for any proofreading services anymore with this tool.<br /></li><li> Inte.com Marketers cannot do the entire task by themselves, hence the need to outsource a writing and proofreading jobs but with this powerful software, you will save huge money by doing it yourself even better.<br /></li><li> Anybody can make huge money from this software either directly by setting up PROOFREADING services or indirectly by saving cost of outsourcing.<br /></li><li> Fully Automated system: software will identify errors, highlighted the errors, give prioritized words suggestions based on writers intention update your blog post without giving you stress.<br /></li><li> The technology behind AUTOMATIC PROOFREADER SOFTWARE makes us to be aware of mistakes and helps us to detect common possible writing errors before we deliver our writing jobs to client. This technology is a great path to improve on our business communication, particularly when we communicate with our clients and colleagues through e-mails, memos, letters and other business oriented documents.<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-12/1451229030_12469_automaticproofreader_logo2small.png" alt="Automatic Proofreader 1.0.10" title="Automatic Proofreader 1.0.10"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Automatic Proofreader 1.0.10" title="Automatic Proofreader 1.0.10"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>X-Spinner Elite Dev 3.5</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1073-x-spinner.html</link>
<description>Name : X-Spinner Version : Elite Dev 3.5 OS : Windows Type : Content Marketing Tools Price : $297 Homepage : SalePage The Best Spinner to Use With Third-Party Software X-Spinner supports all third-party software and allows you to spin unlimited articles with blinding speed, better results and a lower price. And you can even run X-Spinner on a server to provide your own spinning service or integrate it with your software.</description>
<category>Article Spinners</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.x-spinner.com/img/scapi.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2015 07:20:06 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Supports all third-party software. Use our free spin feature to deal with API spinning queries. Use Pro spin&#039;s advanced features (Enable Pos, NLP, AI and grammar checker,etc) to deal with api spinning queries and get better spinning results. Use Elite/Super Spin (Enable Statistical Replacement Technology, Artificial Intelligence and Emulated Natural Language methods) to deal with api spinning queries and get the best spinning results. Deal with one API query very fast. Deal with multi-API queries very fast simultaneously.(This is normally enough for personal use) Import your own thesaurus to work with API queries. Remove original word function. Protect words function. Spin to new article. Spin to {|} format. Html Spin : Spin full web pages, protect the html code when you spin. Super Spin : Rewrite articles to a very high level of human readability and uniqueness using The Best Natural Language Analysis and Artificial Intelligence techniques. Paragraph and setence spin fully automatically. Cloud Thesaurus : Access over a million synonyms created by real users and use the cloud thesaurus phrase replacement feature to generate human-readable and unique new articles automatically. The number of synonyms in the thesaurus is increasing daily. Click here for more details. Part Of Speech : POS matching identifies the context of words. The POS engine can calculate whether a synonym is a noun, a verb, an adjective etc. SpinnerChief matches the part of speech of a synonym to its original word, so you can achieve grammatically and contextually correct articles! Custom/Cloud Grammar A.I. : This is not a normal grammar checker, it is a revolutionary way to correct your grammar when spinning articles to generate articles that are more readable. You can use your own custom grammar A.I. or use the Cloud A.I. generated by all users. Custom/Cloud Rules : Cloud Rules is supplementary to the POS function. This function can select better synonyms by analysing the related words in the sentence. This will help you to generate more readable articles, the rules are created by users and its effectiveness is increasing daily. Custom/Cloud Negs : Cloud Negs is another revolutionary feature invented by us for removing bad synonyms. The cloud negs database is based on all users&#039; selections and input too. Using this function, the program will use better quality synonyms when spinning your article. Free update : We update our software often and you can always get the newest version by using the auto-update. Deal with huge API queries very fast simultaneously. Load all language/thesaurus and spin articles in all languages at the same time. Run X-Spinner on a server to provide spinning service. Auto-Resume from crash. Customize the listen IP address. Cusomize max online amount and max spin object.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/wqW4AtMKKNs?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Supports all third-party software.<br /></li><li> Use our free spin feature to deal with API spinning queries.<br /></li><li> Use Pro spin's advanced features (Enable Pos, NLP, AI and grammar checker,etc) to deal with api spinning queries and get better spinning results.<br /></li><li> Use Elite/Super Spin (Enable Statistical Replacement Technology, Artificial Intelligence and Emulated Natural Language methods) to deal with api spinning queries and get the best spinning results.<br /></li><li> Deal with one API query very fast.<br /></li><li> Deal with multi-API queries very fast simultaneously.(This is normally enough for personal use)<br /></li><li> Import your own thesaurus to work with API queries.<br /></li><li> Remove original word function.<br /></li><li> Protect words function.<br /></li><li> Spin to new article.<br /></li><li> Spin to {|} format.<br /></li><li> Html Spin : Spin full web pages, protect the html code when you spin.<br /></li><li> Super Spin : Rewrite articles to a very high level of human readability  and uniqueness using The Best Natural Language  Analysis and Artificial Intelligence techniques.<br /></li><li> Paragraph and setence spin fully automatically.<br /></li><li> Cloud Thesaurus : Access over a million synonyms created by real users and use the cloud thesaurus phrase replacement feature to generate human-readable and unique new articles automatically. The number of synonyms in the thesaurus is increasing daily. Click here for more details.<br /></li><li> Part Of Speech : POS matching identifies the context of words. The POS engine can calculate whether a synonym is a noun, a verb, an adjective etc. SpinnerChief matches the part of speech of a synonym to its original word, so you can achieve grammatically and contextually correct articles!<br /></li><li> Custom/Cloud Grammar A.I. : This is not a normal grammar checker, it is a revolutionary way to correct your grammar when spinning articles to generate articles that are more readable. You can use your own custom grammar A.I. or use the Cloud A.I. generated by all users.<br /></li><li> Custom/Cloud Rules : Cloud Rules is supplementary to the POS function. This function can select better synonyms by analysing the related words in the sentence. This will help you to generate more readable articles, the rules are created by users and its effectiveness is increasing daily.<br /></li><li> Custom/Cloud Negs : Cloud Negs is another revolutionary feature invented by us for removing bad synonyms. The cloud negs database is based on all users' selections and input too. Using this function, the program will use better quality synonyms when spinning your article.<br /></li><li> Free update : We update our software often and you can always get the newest version by using the auto-update.<br /></li><li> Deal with huge API queries very fast simultaneously.<br /></li><li> Load all language/thesaurus and spin articles in all languages at the same time.<br /></li><li> Run X-Spinner on a server to provide spinning service.<br /></li><li> Auto-Resume from crash.<br /></li><li> Customize the listen IP address.<br /></li><li> Cusomize max online amount and max spin object.<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://www.x-spinner.com/img/scapi.png" alt="X-Spinner Elite Dev 3.5" title="X-Spinner Elite Dev 3.5"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="X-Spinner Elite Dev 3.5" title="X-Spinner Elite Dev 3.5"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>AI Article Rewriter 1.6</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1316-ai-article-rewriter.html</link>
<description>Name : AI Article Rewriter Version : 1.6 OS : Windows Type : Article Rewriter Tools Price : $67 Homepage : SalePage Google loves content and they say &quot;Content Is King&quot;, but good content doesn&#039;t come cheap!! You can easily spend hundreds of dollars getting content written for your blog/site. And, then of course there&#039;s the problem of finding reliable writers who can deliver quality content that passes Copyscape 100%. How about a software that does the research for you and also writes impeccable content at the push of a button? AI Article Rewriter isn&#039;t an average article spinner. It&#039;s going to take premium quality content from the web and turn it 100% Copyscape Proof unique content by spinning Unicodes (language that broiwsers use to read content).The result is 100% unique content to the browsers and search engines without any visible changes to the human eye. The content will read like it&#039;s been hand written by a premium writer!! You can now have hundreds of pages of premium content in a matter of minutes!! Thousands of dollars and dog hours saved!</description>
<category>Article Spinners</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2015 05:41:45 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features HTML encode Copyscape option the spin option post in Wordpress Only on stopwords</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/6z-qBT5Gq5Q?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> HTML encode<br /></li><li> Copyscape option<br /></li><li> the spin option<br /></li><li> post in Wordpress<br /></li><li> Only on stopwords<br /></li></ul><br /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="AI Article Rewriter 1.6" title="AI Article Rewriter 1.6"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Magic Article Rewriter 2.30</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1016-magic-article-rewriter.html</link>
<description>Name : Magic Article Rewriter Version : 2.30 OS : Windows Type : Article Marketing Tools Price : $47 Homepage : SalePage Laugh at Google&#039;s Duplicate Content Ban when you discover.&quot;How to Generate an Avalanche if Hot Prospects and Leads Using the Art and Science of Creating Thousands of Unique Articles in Minutes!.Like Magic!&quot;</description>
<category>Article Spinners</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2015 07:00:17 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Increase web traffic - With article marketing, visitors can constantly come to your website. Achieve massive publicity Build your list of targeted prospects that want to hear from you right now Boost your reputation, credibility, and name recognition Gain link popularity &amp; Improve Search Engine Optimization (SEO) rankings. Create affiliate relationships and JV partnerships with highly influential web publishers.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><video width="640" height="480" preload="metadata" controls="controls">
				<source src="http://www.article-rewriter.info/mar.mp4"></source>
				</video></div><br /><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Increase web traffic - With article marketing, visitors can constantly come to your website.<br /></li><li> Achieve massive publicity<br /></li><li> Build your list of targeted prospects that want to hear from you right now<br /></li><li> Boost your reputation, credibility, and name recognition<br /></li><li> Gain link popularity & Improve Search Engine Optimization (SEO) rankings.<br /></li><li> Create affiliate relationships and JV partnerships with highly influential web publishers.<br /><br /></li></ul><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Magic Article Rewriter 2.30" title="Magic Article Rewriter 2.30"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Article Buddy Pro</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1147-article-buddy.html</link>
<description>Name : Article Buddy Version : Pro OS : Windows/MAC Type : Article Spiner Tools Price : $47 Homepage : SalePage Article Buddy Pro is a software that creates completely unique articles with a click of a button. The articles pass both a Google search test AND Copyscape. It also includes an auto-poster so you can automatically add the content to your WordPress blog.</description>
<category>Article Spinners</category>
<enclosure url="http://article-buddy.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/3.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2015 08:53:09 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/HRakOKlhpZo?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><img src="http://article-buddy.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/3.png" alt="Article Buddy Pro" title="Article Buddy Pro"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Article Buddy Pro" title="Article Buddy Pro"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>