<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>BackUp/Clone Plugins - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>BackUp/Clone Plugins - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>BackupBuddy 8.0.18</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/809-ithemes-backupbuddy.html</link>
<description>Name : BackupBuddy - WordPress Backup Plugin Version : 8.0.18 Type : Backup Plugin Price : $297 Homepage : SalePage The best way to back up (and move) a WordPress site. Site owners and developers love all the options BackupBuddy gives you for safe, offsite storage.</description>
<category>BackUp/Clone Plugins</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 00:57:50 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Database or Full Backups : Run database backups for quick, small, frequent backups or run complete backups to get all your images, themes, plugins and everything else to a safe place. Offsite Storage : Send your backups (individually or on a schedule) to offsite storage destinations like BackupBuddy Stash (our custom backup storage location), Amazon S3, Dropbox, Rackspace Cloud, FTP or email. If your site goes down, you don&#039;t want your backup stored on that same server. Schedule Backups : Schedule backups so you don&#039;t need to remember to make backups every day, week or month. You can also set the schedule to send your backups to any of your offsite storage destinations automatically. BackupBuddy Stash Storage : We built BackupBuddy Stash specifically for storing and managing your BackupBuddy backups so you can manage backups for all of your sites in one central location. BackupBuddy users get 1GB of Stash storage for free! Exclude Files &amp;amp; Tables : Choose which files (or tables) to exclude from your backups. This is helpful if you have a folder with lots of high-res images or videos that you don&#039;t want to back up every time. Backup Profiles : Create custom backup profiles for backups to use their own settings and file exclusions. Email Notifications: Know immediately when BackupBuddy finishes a backup, times out or needs attention. Backup Storage Limits: Limit the number and size of your stored backups. So you don&#039;t fill up your Dropbox account with 34 old backups. Individual File Restore: You don&#039;t have to wipe the whole slate clean to just replace your stylesheet from a a backup you made a few weeks ago. Server Tools: Take a deep look at your server settings and capabilities. Our built-in server tools are super helpful to track down possible hosting problems that could prevent your backups from running. Malware Scan: BackupBuddy does a free malware scan of your site to make sure your site and your online reputation are squeaky clean with all the major blacklist checks. Interactive Site Directory Map: Visualize what takes up the most space on your site. It&#039;s really cool to dig through and view your files this way. Database Mass Text Replacement: Update text throughout your database. Great for updating URLs, strings of text, replacing any mention of your ex&#039;s name, etc. Database Scan &amp;amp; Repair: Automatically scans and repairs common issues with your database. WordPress Cron Manager: View, delete, or manually run WordPress scheduled CRON jobs. Backupbuddy.7301.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Backupbuddy.7301.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Backupbuddy.7301.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Backupbuddy.7301.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Backupbuddy.7301.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/byMWuLXdBvQ?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Database or Full Backups : Run database backups for quick, small, frequent backups or run complete backups to get all your images, themes, plugins and everything else to a safe place. <br></li><li> Offsite Storage : Send your backups (individually or on a schedule) to offsite storage destinations like BackupBuddy Stash (our custom backup storage location), Amazon S3, Dropbox, Rackspace Cloud, FTP or email. If your site goes down, you don't want your backup stored on that same server. <br></li><li> Schedule Backups : Schedule backups so you don't need to remember to make backups every day, week or month. You can also set the schedule to send your backups to any of your offsite storage destinations automatically. <br></li><li> BackupBuddy Stash Storage : We built BackupBuddy Stash specifically for storing and managing your BackupBuddy backups so you can manage backups for all of your sites in one central location. BackupBuddy users get 1GB of Stash storage for free! <br></li><li> Exclude Files &amp; Tables : Choose which files (or tables) to exclude from your backups. This is helpful if you have a folder with lots of high-res images or videos that you don't want to back up every time. <br></li><li> Backup Profiles : Create custom backup profiles for backups to use their own settings and file exclusions.<br></li><li> Email Notifications: Know immediately when BackupBuddy finishes a backup, times out or needs attention.<br></li><li> Backup Storage Limits: Limit the number and size of your stored backups. So you don't fill up your Dropbox account with 34 old backups.<br></li><li> Individual File Restore: You don't have to wipe the whole slate clean to just replace your stylesheet from a a backup you made a few weeks ago.<br></li><li> Server Tools: Take a deep look at your server settings and capabilities. Our built-in server tools are super helpful to track down possible hosting problems that could prevent your backups from running.<br></li><li> Malware Scan: BackupBuddy does a free malware scan of your site to make sure your site and your online reputation are squeaky clean with all the major blacklist checks.<br></li><li> Interactive Site Directory Map: Visualize what takes up the most space on your site. It's really cool to dig through and view your files this way.<br></li><li> Database Mass Text Replacement: Update text throughout your database. Great for updating URLs, strings of text, replacing any mention of your ex's name, etc.<br></li><li> Database Scan &amp; Repair: Automatically scans and repairs common issues with your database.<br></li><li> WordPress Cron Manager: View, delete, or manually run WordPress scheduled CRON jobs.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="BackupBuddy 8.0.18"><br><div class="quote"><br><br><a href="https://clicknupload.link/u4cm0mgyl4bx"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Backupbuddy.7301.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://dailyuploads.com/27klv5obf8m3"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Backupbuddy.7301.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://uploadocean.com/oxaj2n2dx4nw"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Backupbuddy.7301.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://uplod.ws/ebu8ay9dqbn1"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Backupbuddy.7301.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://userscloud.com/npq8a4moc807"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Backupbuddy.7301.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><br></div><br></div><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>UpdraftPlus 2.13.1.21 + Add-ons</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3550-updraftplus-2123222-add-ons.html</link>
<description>Name : UpdraftPlus Premium Developer + All Add-ons Version : 2.13.1.21 Type : Backup Plugin Price : $145 Homepage : Salepage The World&#039;s Most Trusted WordPress Backup Plugin Hacking, server crashes, dodgy updates or simple user error can ruin your WordPress site. That&#039;s why you need UpdraftPlus, the world&#039;s highest-rated and most installed WordPress backup plugin.</description>
<category>BackUp/Clone Plugins</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2017 22:12:00 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features General WordPress Backup - UpdraftPlusHighest-rating backup and restore plugin at wordpress.org (4.9 stars out of 5.0), and ranked in the top 30 (of over 40,000) WordPress plugins for popularity. Designed to run everywhere that WordPress runs Multi-site (i.e. WPMU/WordPress Network) compatible. Proven to backup sites of 100Gb; file size only limited by Web host. Backs up limitless non-WordPress files and external databases. Scheduling Supports both manual and automated (scheduled) backups: every 4, 8, 12 hours; daily, weekly, fortnightly or monthly. Can even be customised to a specific time. Backs up files and databases on separate schedules Reports time of next scheduled backup Routinely prunes the number of old backups kept Automatically backs up when plugins or dashboard themes update and before WordPress core updates run UpdraftVault Storage Central place to store, manage and disconnect backups 1 gigabyte of free storage included, with the option of purchasing more as and when required Remote Storage Options Supports cloud backup to Amazon S3; any region. Can test your Amazon S3 settings and diagnose common problems. Can back up into sub-directories. Supports chunked, resumable uploads (i.e. interrupted jobs can be resumed where they left off). Encryption supported. Supports reduced-redundancy storage (RRS) and Server-Side Encryption (SSE). Supports cloud backup to any Amazon S3 compatible provider, with the same feature set (examples of such providers: Dreamhost Dreamobjects, Cloudian, Connectria, Constant, Eucalyptus, Nifty, Nimbula, Cloudn). Supports cloud backup to Rackspace Cloud Files. Can test you Rackspace Cloud Files settings and diagnose common problems. Supports chunked, resumable uploads (i.e. interrupted jobs can be resumed where they left off). Encryption always used. Supports all Rackspace locations. Support for in-dashboard creation of a unique API user with access only to the backup container. Supports cloud backup to Dropbox. Supports &quot;app folder&quot; backup automatically - i.e. UpdraftPlus only gets to see or touch its own files. Almost zero-setup (you need to know nothing except for your Dropbox username and password). Supports chunked, resumable uploads (i.e. interrupted jobs can be resumed where they left off). Supports cloud backup to Google Drive. Supports chunked, resumable uploads (i.e. interrupted jobs can be resumed where they left off). Full setup guide with screenshots. Supports cloud backup to Microsoft OneDrive (regular/consumer - not OneDrive for Business). Supports chunked, resumable uploads (i.e. interrupted jobs can be resumed where they left off). Full setup guide with screenshots. Supports cloud backup to Google Cloud Storage. Supports chunked, resumable uploads (i.e. interrupted jobs can be resumed where they left off). Full setup guide with screenshots. Supports cloud backup to Microsoft Azure Blob Storage. Supports chunked, resumable uploads (i.e. interrupted jobs can be resumed where they left off). Full setup guide with screenshots. Supports cloud backup to Rackspace Cloud Files. Supports chunked, resumable uploads (i.e. interrupted jobs can be resumed where they left off). Supports cloud backup to OpenStack Swift object storage. Supports chunked, resumable uploads (i.e. interrupted jobs can be resumed where they left off). Supports cloud backup to FTP servers. Supports both normal and TLS-encrypted servers. Supports both implicit and explicit encryption. Supports chunked, resumable uploads (i.e. interrupted jobs can be resumed where they left off). Has test mode to allow easy debugging of login problems. Supports cloud backup to SFTP servers. Supports chunked, resumable uploads (i.e. interrupted jobs can be resumed where they left off). Has test mode to allow easy debugging of login problems. Supports both SFTP and SCP (no chunking support for SCP, but failed uploads will be retried). Supports cloud backup to WebDAV servers, including encrypted servers. Supports chunked, resumable uploads. Supports backup by email. Each dump (e.g. of plugins, or of themes, or of uploads) is emailed separately. Limited only by limits your email provider has on incoming attachments. Supports backup to multiple destinations (e.g. Amazon and Dropbox and FTP) in a single backup. Security Database backups can be encrypted for security Encrypted transport to cloud storage Reporting, Monitoring and Scheduling All backup operations are thoroughly logged. Display status of backups in progress in WordPress admin panel, along with any errors or warnings. Reports when backup completes, including file checksums for verification of backup integrity. &quot;Debug/expert&quot; gives further insight into backup process: option to view a different set of SSL certificates, to turn SSL certificate verification, and to turn off SSL entirely. All log messages can be sent to syslog (Linux/UNIX) / Event Log (Windows). Restoring, Recovering and Migrating Conveniently backs up each WordPress entity (database, plugins, themes, uploaded content and &quot;other&quot; content) in a separate file, all from WordPress control panel. Further files, WordPress core or any arbitrary directory from the server can be backed up via add-on. Databases can be decrypted within WordPress control panel via drag-and-drop. Backups made elsewhere can be imported via drag-and-drop (unlimited size upload) or FTP. Search and replace migrates site database upon import. Restores backed-up entities from console with one-click access. Imports and restores from backups made by other backup plugins: BackupWordPress, BackWPup, WordPress Backup to Dropbox and Simple Backup, and generic SQL (uncompressed, gzip-compressed, or bzip2-compressed) backups. WordPress Network and Multisite Compatible with WordPress Network / Multisite installs. Backup/restore control panel is placed in the.comwork dashboard. Restore individual sites within the.comwork (without having to restore all sites). Import (where possible) single site installs into the.comwork. UpdraftPlus.2.12.32.22.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar UpdraftPlus.2.12.32.22.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar UpdraftPlus.2.12.32.22.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar UpdraftPlus.2.12.32.22.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar UpdraftPlus.2.12.32.22.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<p></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/MZCmAZ8rnMk?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><p><br><b>Features</b><br>General<br><ul><li> WordPress Backup - UpdraftPlusHighest-rating backup and restore plugin at wordpress.org (4.9 stars out of 5.0), and ranked in the top 30 (of over 40,000) WordPress plugins for popularity.<br></li><li> Designed to run everywhere that WordPress runs<br></li><li> Multi-site (i.e. WPMU/WordPress Network) compatible.<br></li><li> Proven to backup sites of 100Gb; file size only limited by Web host.<br></li><li> Backs up limitless non-WordPress files and external databases.<br></li></ul> <br><br>Scheduling<br><ul><li> Supports both manual and automated (scheduled) backups: every 4, 8, 12 hours; daily, weekly, fortnightly or monthly. Can even be customised to a specific time.<br></li><li> Backs up files and databases on separate schedules<br></li><li> Reports time of next scheduled backup<br></li><li> Routinely prunes the number of old backups kept<br></li><li> Automatically backs up when plugins or dashboard themes update and before WordPress core updates run<br></li></ul> <br><br>UpdraftVault Storage<br><ul><li> Central place to store, manage and disconnect backups<br></li><li> 1 gigabyte of free storage included, with the option of purchasing more as and when required<br></li></ul> <br><br>Remote Storage Options<br><ul><li> Supports cloud backup to Amazon S3; any region. Can test your Amazon S3 settings and diagnose common problems. Can back up into sub-directories. Supports chunked, resumable uploads (i.e. interrupted jobs can be resumed where they left off). Encryption supported. Supports reduced-redundancy storage (RRS) and Server-Side Encryption (SSE).<br></li><li> Supports cloud backup to any Amazon S3 compatible provider, with the same feature set (examples of such providers: Dreamhost Dreamobjects, Cloudian, Connectria, Constant, Eucalyptus, Nifty, Nimbula, Cloudn).<br></li><li> Supports cloud backup to Rackspace Cloud Files. Can test you Rackspace Cloud Files settings and diagnose common problems. Supports chunked, resumable uploads (i.e. interrupted jobs can be resumed where they left off). Encryption always used. Supports all Rackspace locations. Support for in-dashboard creation of a unique API user with access only to the backup container.<br></li><li> Supports cloud backup to Dropbox. Supports "app folder" backup automatically - i.e. UpdraftPlus only gets to see or touch its own files. Almost zero-setup (you need to know nothing except for your Dropbox username and password). Supports chunked, resumable uploads (i.e. interrupted jobs can be resumed where they left off).<br></li><li> Supports cloud backup to Google Drive. Supports chunked, resumable uploads (i.e. interrupted jobs can be resumed where they left off). Full setup guide with screenshots.<br></li><li> Supports cloud backup to Microsoft OneDrive (regular/consumer - not OneDrive for Business). Supports chunked, resumable uploads (i.e. interrupted jobs can be resumed where they left off). Full setup guide with screenshots.<br></li><li> Supports cloud backup to Google Cloud Storage. Supports chunked, resumable uploads (i.e. interrupted jobs can be resumed where they left off). Full setup guide with screenshots.<br></li><li> Supports cloud backup to Microsoft Azure Blob Storage. Supports chunked, resumable uploads (i.e. interrupted jobs can be resumed where they left off). Full setup guide with screenshots.<br></li><li> Supports cloud backup to Rackspace Cloud Files. Supports chunked, resumable uploads (i.e. interrupted jobs can be resumed where they left off).<br></li><li> Supports cloud backup to OpenStack Swift object storage. Supports chunked, resumable uploads (i.e. interrupted jobs can be resumed where they left off).<br></li><li> Supports cloud backup to FTP servers. Supports both normal and TLS-encrypted servers. Supports both implicit and explicit encryption. Supports chunked, resumable uploads (i.e. interrupted jobs can be resumed where they left off). Has test mode to allow easy debugging of login problems.<br></li><li> Supports cloud backup to SFTP servers. Supports chunked, resumable uploads (i.e. interrupted jobs can be resumed where they left off). Has test mode to allow easy debugging of login problems. Supports both SFTP and SCP (no chunking support for SCP, but failed uploads will be retried).<br></li><li> Supports cloud backup to WebDAV servers, including encrypted servers. Supports chunked, resumable uploads.<br></li><li> Supports backup by email. Each dump (e.g. of plugins, or of themes, or of uploads) is emailed separately. Limited only by limits your email provider has on incoming attachments.<br></li><li> Supports backup to multiple destinations (e.g. Amazon and Dropbox and FTP) in a single backup.<br></li></ul> <br><br>Security<br><ul><li> Database backups can be encrypted for security<br></li><li> Encrypted transport to cloud storage<br></li></ul> <br><br>Reporting, Monitoring and Scheduling<br><ul><li> All backup operations are thoroughly logged.<br></li><li> Display status of backups in progress in WordPress admin panel, along with any errors or warnings.<br></li><li> Reports when backup completes, including file checksums for verification of backup integrity.<br></li><li> "Debug/expert" gives further insight into backup process: option to view a different set of SSL certificates, to turn SSL certificate verification, and to turn off SSL entirely.<br></li><li> All log messages can be sent to syslog (Linux/UNIX) / Event Log (Windows).<br></li></ul> <br><br>Restoring, Recovering and Migrating<br><ul><li> Conveniently backs up each WordPress entity (database, plugins, themes, uploaded content and "other" content) in a separate file, all from WordPress control panel.<br></li><li> Further files, WordPress core or any arbitrary directory from the server can be backed up via add-on.<br></li><li> Databases can be decrypted within WordPress control panel via drag-and-drop.<br></li><li> Backups made elsewhere can be imported via drag-and-drop (unlimited size upload) or FTP.<br></li><li> Search and replace migrates site database upon import.<br></li><li> Restores backed-up entities from console with one-click access.<br></li><li> Imports and restores from backups made by other backup plugins: BackupWordPress, BackWPup, WordPress Backup to Dropbox and Simple Backup, and generic SQL (uncompressed, gzip-compressed, or bzip2-compressed) backups.<br></li></ul> <br>WordPress Network and Multisite<br><ul><li> Compatible with WordPress Network / Multisite installs.<br></li><li> Backup/restore control panel is placed in the.comwork dashboard.<br></li><li> Restore individual sites within the.comwork (without having to restore all sites).<br></li><li> Import (where possible) single site installs into the.comwork.<br></li></ul> </p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="UpdraftPlus 2.13.1.21 + Add-ons"><br><div class="quote"><br><br><a href="https://clicknupload.link/bow06iom6fh6"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">UpdraftPlus.2.12.32.22.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://dailyuploads.com/q3tvb08iusdk"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">UpdraftPlus.2.12.32.22.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://uploadocean.com/ntqpqyl3r4kp"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">UpdraftPlus.2.12.32.22.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://uplod.ws/964iysp2177u"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">UpdraftPlus.2.12.32.22.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://userscloud.com/1asbf569hr7w"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">UpdraftPlus.2.12.32.22.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br></div></div><br><p></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""> <br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Duplicator Pro 3.3.4 - WordPress Site Migration &amp; BackUp</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3549-duplicator-pro-334-wordpress-site-migration-amp-backup.html</link>
<description>Name : Duplicator Pro - WordPress Site Migration &amp;amp; BackUp Version : 3.3.4 OS : Linux Type : BackUp Price : 49 Homepage : Salepage Create a backup WordPress files and database. Duplicate and move an entire site from one location to another in a few steps. Create a full snapshot of your site at any point in time.</description>
<category>BackUp/Clone Plugins</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2017 00:58:50 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Multisite Support Large Database Support Backup Limits Filter Data Auto Database Creation Easy Plugin Updates Email Notifications Advanced Options 3.3.4 Duplicator.Pro.V3.3.4.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Duplicator.Pro.V3.3.4.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Duplicator.Pro.V3.3.4.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Duplicator.Pro.V3.3.4.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Duplicator.Pro.V3.3.4.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar 3.3.3 Duplicator.Pro.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Duplicator.Pro.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Duplicator.Pro.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Duplicator.Pro.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Duplicator.Pro.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar 3.3.2.1 Duplicator.Pro.3.3.2.1.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Duplicator.Pro.3.3.2.1.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Duplicator.Pro.3.3.2.1.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Duplicator.Pro.3.3.2.1.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Duplicator.Pro.3.3.2.1.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<br><b>Features</b><br><ul><li>Multisite Support<br></li><li>Large Database Support<br></li><li>Backup Limits<br></li><li>Filter Data<br></li><li>Auto Database Creation<br></li><li>Easy Plugin Updates<br></li><li>Email Notifications<br></li><li>Advanced Options<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Duplicator Pro 3.3.4 - WordPress Site Migration &amp; BackUp"><br><div class="quote"><br>3.3.4<br><a href="https://clicknupload.link/1hghdcelmzam"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Duplicator.Pro.V3.3.4.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://dailyuploads.com/scx792fj9pp2"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Duplicator.Pro.V3.3.4.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://uploadocean.com/nfp2d5aqc57s"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Duplicator.Pro.V3.3.4.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://uplod.ws/i2xv7je9i47p"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Duplicator.Pro.V3.3.4.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://userscloud.com/w7i0qmcwd4t9"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Duplicator.Pro.V3.3.4.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><br>3.3.3<br><br><a href="https://clicknupload.link/egohfvqga4cx"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Duplicator.Pro.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://dailyuploads.com/lxyx8bh7bupm"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Duplicator.Pro.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://uploadocean.com/6gamrwnlni9s"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Duplicator.Pro.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://uplod.ws/ibqad2u6ka1l"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Duplicator.Pro.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://userscloud.com/qrti069smsip"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Duplicator.Pro.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br>3.3.2.1<br><a href="https://clicknupload.link/w8ylnki3t7ss"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Duplicator.Pro.3.3.2.1.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://dailyuploads.com/11b29m0japk3"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Duplicator.Pro.3.3.2.1.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://uploadocean.com/8syfxqs3vc19"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Duplicator.Pro.3.3.2.1.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://uplod.ws/5tgqbdln2712"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Duplicator.Pro.3.3.2.1.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://userscloud.com/4th49dcg20pq"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Duplicator.Pro.3.3.2.1.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br></div><br></div><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""> <br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Super Backup &amp; Clone 2.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1952-super-backup-clone.html</link>
<description>Name : Super Backup &amp; Clone - Migrate for WordPress Version : 2.0 OS : Linux Type : Utilities Price : $34 Homepage : SalePage We&#039;re extremely proud to announce that WP SuperBackup allows you to do just that! Working on your site is always a lengthy and cumbersome process, and it would be a pity for all your hard work to go to waste because of a misconfiguration or error that&#039;s perhaps not even your fault! Having a trustworthy backup solution in place can help you prevent that. This is where our plugin comes into play.</description>
<category>BackUp/Clone Plugins</category>
<enclosure url="http://i.imgur.com/M4yGkVf.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2016 11:30:54 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Intuitive Dashboard - Get a quick overview of existing backup instances Cloud Sync - Working with a staging &amp; a production server? We got you covered! WP SuperBackup allows you to easily sync across all files, or just the ones you really need between the servers, in just a few minutes. This all happens automatically based on a schedule you define! Set up &quot;Snapshots&quot; - You can have one, or any number of backup instances Snapshot Logs - Easily track all backup tasks and always know what the current status of your latest backup is Instance Migration - If you&#039;ve stored a backup on your trust hard disk drive, this feature allows you to easily import it and migrate it onto your current WordPress installation! You have full control over what files get migrated, so you can make sure they don&#039;t break the installation, once migration is complete. One Click Restore - Pick any snapshot, click Restore, Done! Cloud Snapshots - If you want to be extra safe, the plugin allows you to upload your backups to the cloud, you know, just in case your server burns altogether! Backup Destinations - WP SuperBackup supports a plethora of cloud services, including but not limited to your own (s)FTP accounts, Google Drive, Dropbox, Amazon, OneDrive, Copy.com, RackSpace etc Easy setup - A quick visit to the &quot;General Settings&quot; tab enables you to set up email notifications, define a quota, the backup directory (on the same server) or simply clean up existing backup files Self-diagnosis - The &quot;System&quot; panel allows you to run a live check on your server settings and immediately flags any potential issues, so that you can address them before you even begin backing up! Great Support - Need help or have a question? Fear not! We&#039;ve built in the documentation so you have it, right there, within the WP SuperBackup dashboard, together with a direct link to contact us via our Support system. MultiSite to MultiSite - The SuperBackup system allows you to run a straight Cloud migration from one MultiSite to another without any worries MultiSite to SingleSite - If you running into a MultiSite Platform, the system will detect that and you have the chance to have a SingleSite Snapshot ready to be Migrated to any regular WP Site or into another SingleSite available on other MultiSite Platform SingleSite to MultiSite - a simple SnapShot from a Standard WP Site can be Migrated into a select SingleSite available on your Multisite Platform. So, you can move all your standalone WP websites to a single WP MultiSite.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<br /><div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/pzxspfYYx_g?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Intuitive Dashboard - Get a quick overview of existing backup instances<br /></li><li> Cloud Sync - Working with a staging & a production server? We got you covered! WP SuperBackup allows you to easily sync across all files, or just the ones you really need between the servers, in just a few minutes. This all happens automatically based on a schedule you define!<br /></li><li> Set up "Snapshots" - You can have one, or any number of backup instances<br /></li><li> Snapshot Logs - Easily track all backup tasks and always know what the current status of your latest backup is<br /></li><li> Instance Migration - If you've stored a backup on your trust hard disk drive, this feature allows you to easily import it and migrate it onto your current WordPress installation! You have full control over what files get migrated, so you can make sure they don't break the installation, once migration is complete.<br /></li><li> One Click Restore - Pick any snapshot, click Restore, Done!<br /></li><li> Cloud Snapshots - If you want to be extra safe, the plugin allows you to upload your backups to the cloud, you know, just in case your server burns altogether!<br /></li><li> Backup Destinations - WP SuperBackup supports a plethora of cloud services, including but not limited to your own (s)FTP accounts, Google Drive, Dropbox, Amazon, OneDrive, Copy.com, RackSpace etc<br /></li><li> Easy setup - A quick visit to the "General Settings" tab enables you to set up email notifications, define a quota, the backup directory (on the same server) or simply clean up existing backup files<br /></li><li> Self-diagnosis - The "System" panel allows you to run a live check on your server settings and immediately flags any potential issues, so that you can address them before you even begin backing up!<br /></li><li> Great Support - Need help or have a question? Fear not! We've built in the documentation so you have it, right there, within the WP SuperBackup dashboard, together with a direct link to contact us via our Support system.<br /></li><li> MultiSite to MultiSite - The SuperBackup system allows you to run a straight Cloud migration from one MultiSite to another without any worries<br /></li><li> MultiSite to SingleSite - If you running into a MultiSite Platform, the system will detect that and you have the chance to have a SingleSite Snapshot ready to be Migrated to any regular WP Site or into another SingleSite available on other MultiSite Platform<br /></li><li> SingleSite to MultiSite - a simple SnapShot from a Standard WP Site can be Migrated into a select SingleSite available on your Multisite Platform. So, you can move all your standalone WP websites to a single WP MultiSite.<br /><br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://i.imgur.com/M4yGkVf.png" alt="Super Backup &amp; Clone 2.0" title="Super Backup &amp; Clone 2.0"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Super Backup &amp; Clone 2.0" title="Super Backup &amp; Clone 2.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>WP BackUp Plus 2.2</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1543-wp-backup-plus.html</link>
<description>Name : WP BackUp Plus 2.2 Version : 2.6.15 Type : Backup plugin, Security Plugins Price : $197 Homepage : SalePage Protect, Clone and Automate Full Site Backup in minutes! The Full Automated Wordpress Backup Plugin that sends your backup to multiple locations that allows you to backup, restore, automate, and clone.</description>
<category>BackUp/Clone Plugins</category>
<enclosure url="http://wpbackupplus.com/images/chart.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2016 11:57:44 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features [list] - Perform Unlimited Wordpress Backups - Clone Any Wordpress Website - Automate with S3,Dropbox,Server - Restore in One Click</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/y6_dFGmDXHw?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div>
<p></p>
<h3>Features</h3>
<p><br>[list]<br>- Perform Unlimited Wordpress Backups<br>- Clone Any Wordpress Website<br>- Automate with S3,Dropbox,Server<br>- Restore in One Click<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://wpbackupplus.com/images/chart.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="WP BackUp Plus 2.2"></p>
<div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>WordPress Backup &amp; Clone Master 2.0.2</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1522-wordpress-backup-clone-master.html</link>
<description>Name : WordPress Backup &amp;amp; Clone Master Version : 2.0.2 OS : Windows Type : Backup Tools Price : $33 Homepage : SalePage WordPress Backup &amp;amp; Clone Master is an all-in-one solution for WordPress backup, restoration, cloning, and migration. The plugin helps you manage the above processes in a secure, easy, and reliable way on a scheduled or on-demand basis.</description>
<category>BackUp/Clone Plugins</category>
<enclosure url="https://0.s3.envato.com/files/133029341/01.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2016 02:04:03 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Create full WordPress backups including database, settings, themes, plugins, and images Download backup to your computer in a ZIP or TAR file Schedule daily / weekly / monthly backups to be updated on your server Store regular backups to remote FTP server Auto upload backups to your Dropbox Auto store backups directly to Google Drive Send regular backups to your email address Restore any backup in one click Clone your whole site to a different domain Create a new database on a remote server directly from the plugin Clone your settings, themes, and plugins to a different WP site Migrate your site to a new host Works on any hosting environment Works with WordPress Network (Multisite) Backup and clone individual subsites in a WordPress Network KEEP YOUR WEBSITE SECURE WITH REGULAR BACKUPS Backup &amp;amp; Clone Master plugin provides secure protection for WordPress sites and their data. You invest a great amount of time into your website, and it is essential to make sure your data is safe. With regular auto backups created, you don&#039;t need to worry about data loss in case of server injections, software upgrades, or site changes. It is also important to have an easy way to restore your backup without advanced knowledge of Cpanel and databases. Backup &amp;amp; Clone Master takes care of the backups, and lets you restore your site in one click, which will definitely bring you peace of mind and added safety. CLONE YOUR WEBSITE EASILY TO A NEW DOMAIN Cloning ability is especially valuable when you are running multiple WordPress sites. It could be a time consuming project to configure WordPress, install and customize theme, install and configure multiple plugins, which is usually the same setup for all of your websites. With the Backup &amp;amp; Clone Master plugin, you can simply copy the settings (including cusomized themes and configured plugins), or the whole site, to a different domain quickly and easily. This feature has great potential for any web master, and is surely to save you tons of time when managing your WordPress sites. MIGRATE YOUR WEBSITE TO A NEW HOST Moving your WordPress site to a new hosting server could be a headache for a non technical person as it involves new database creation, new WordPress installation, data migration, and configuration. With the Backup &amp;amp; Clone Master plugin, this has become a simple task, for which you don&#039;t need any advanced technical knowledge (the plugin will even create a database for you remotely!).</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<br><div style="text-align:center;"><div class="dlevideoplayer" style="width:100%;max-width:425px;"><ul data-theme="default" data-preload="metadata"><li data-title="" data-type="youtube" data-url="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kjJEpSz-Qdw"></li></ul></div></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Create full WordPress backups including database, settings, themes, plugins, and images<br></li><li> Download backup to your computer in a ZIP or TAR file<br></li><li> Schedule daily / weekly / monthly backups to be updated on your server<br></li><li> Store regular backups to remote FTP server<br></li><li> Auto upload backups to your Dropbox<br></li><li> Auto store backups directly to Google Drive<br></li><li> Send regular backups to your email address<br></li><li> Restore any backup in one click<br></li><li> Clone your whole site to a different domain<br></li><li> Create a new database on a remote server directly from the plugin<br></li><li> Clone your settings, themes, and plugins to a different WP site<br></li><li> Migrate your site to a new host<br></li><li> Works on any hosting environment<br></li><li> Works with WordPress Network (Multisite)<br></li><li> Backup and clone individual subsites in a WordPress Network<br></li></ul><br><img src="https://0.s3.envato.com/files/133029341/01.png" alt="WordPress Backup &amp; Clone Master 2.0.2"><br>KEEP YOUR WEBSITE SECURE WITH REGULAR BACKUPS<br><br>Backup &amp; Clone Master plugin provides secure protection for WordPress sites and their data. You invest a great amount of time into your website, and it is essential to make sure your data is safe. With regular auto backups created, you don't need to worry about data loss in case of server injections, software upgrades, or site changes.<br><br>It is also important to have an easy way to restore your backup without advanced knowledge of Cpanel and databases. Backup &amp; Clone Master takes care of the backups, and lets you restore your site in one click, which will definitely bring you peace of mind and added safety.<br><br>CLONE YOUR WEBSITE EASILY TO A NEW DOMAIN<br><br>Cloning ability is especially valuable when you are running multiple WordPress sites. It could be a time consuming project to configure WordPress, install and customize theme, install and configure multiple plugins, which is usually the same setup for all of your websites.<br><br>With the Backup &amp; Clone Master plugin, you can simply copy the settings (including cusomized themes and configured plugins), or the whole site, to a different domain quickly and easily. This feature has great potential for any web master, and is surely to save you tons of time when managing your WordPress sites.<br><br>MIGRATE YOUR WEBSITE TO A NEW HOST<br><br>Moving your WordPress site to a new hosting server could be a headache for a non technical person as it involves new database creation, new WordPress installation, data migration, and configuration.<br><br>With the Backup &amp; Clone Master plugin, this has become a simple task, for which you don't need any advanced technical knowledge (the plugin will even create a database for you remotely!).<br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>