<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Grammar Checker - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Grammar Checker - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>Grammarly 8.639.494 Premium</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1512-grammarly.html</link>
<description>Name : Grammarly Version : 8.639.494 Premium OS : Windows Type : Content Marketing Tools,Plagiarism Checker Tools,Proofreader Tools Price : $139.95 /year Homepage : SalePage Better Writing Made EasyGrammarly makes you a better writer by finding and correcting up to 10 times more mistakes than your word processor. Best Plagiarism Checker &amp; Proofreader Grammarly is an automated proofreader and plagiarism checker.It corrects up to 10 times as many mistakes as other word processors. Grammarly’s online proofreader automatically detects grammar, spelling, punctuation, word choice and style mistakes in your writing. Grammarly makes you a better writer by finding and correcting up to 10&amp;#215; more mistakes than your word processor.</description>
<category>Grammar Checker</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2016-02/1454496873_2016-02-03_17-52-19.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2016 14:54:26 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Eliminate : ErrorsInstantly fix over 250 types of errors, most of which Microsoft Word® can’t find. Enhance : Clarity and MeaningFind the perfect word every time with context-optimized synonym suggestions. Become a Better : WriterLearn about your mistakes so that you can avoid them next time. Write Anywhere : Whether you’re writing emails, essays, or social media posts, Grammarly has your back. Grammarly Check : Eliminates most writing mistakes Grammarly corrects over 250 types of grammatical mistakes, while also catching contextual spelling errors and poor vocabulary usage. Grammar Check Anywhere : Works wherever you write online Grammarly helps you write mistake-free on Gmail, Facebook, Twitter, Tumblr, LinkedIn, and nearly anywhere else you write on the web. Grammar Check Linguists : Built by the world’s leading linguists Grammarly’s powerful grammar checking algorithms are developed by the world’s leading authorities on linguistic technology. 250 points of grammar:Grammarly scans your text for proper use of more than 250 advanced grammar rules, spanning everything from subject-verb agreement to article use to modifier placement. Contextual spelling checker:Correctly spelled words used in the wrong context mean embarrassing mistakes for you. Grammarly spots erroneous use of lose/loose, affect/effect, lie/lay, there/their/they’re, and many other commonly confused words. Vocabulary enhancement: Words can make an impact, or they can fall flat. Enhance your sentences with Grammarly’s context-optimized word choice suggestions to instantly improve the readability of your document. Proof Screen</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/s8RRsWCvsYk?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Eliminate : ErrorsInstantly fix over 250 types of errors, most of which Microsoft Word® can’t find.<br /></li><li> Enhance : Clarity and MeaningFind the perfect word every time with context-optimized synonym suggestions.<br /></li><li> Become a Better : WriterLearn about your mistakes so that you can avoid them next time.<br /></li><li> Write Anywhere : Whether you’re writing emails, essays, or social media posts, Grammarly has your back.<br /></li><li> Grammarly Check : Eliminates most writing mistakes Grammarly corrects over 250 types of grammatical mistakes, while also catching contextual spelling errors and poor vocabulary usage.<br /></li><li> Grammar Check Anywhere : Works wherever you write online Grammarly helps you write mistake-free on Gmail, Facebook, Twitter, Tumblr, LinkedIn, and nearly anywhere else you write on the web.<br /></li><li> Grammar Check Linguists : Built by the world’s leading linguists Grammarly’s powerful grammar checking algorithms are developed by the world’s leading authorities on linguistic technology.    <br /></li><li> 250 points of grammar:Grammarly scans your text for proper use of more than 250 advanced grammar rules, spanning everything from subject-verb agreement to article use to modifier placement.<br /></li><li> Contextual spelling checker:Correctly spelled words used in the wrong context mean embarrassing mistakes for you. Grammarly spots erroneous use of lose/loose, affect/effect, lie/lay, there/their/they’re, and many other commonly confused words.<br /></li><li> Vocabulary enhancement: Words can make an impact, or they can fall flat. Enhance your sentences with Grammarly’s context-optimized word choice suggestions to instantly improve the readability of your document.<br /></li></ul><br /><h3>Proof Screen</h3><br /><img src="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2016-02/1454496873_2016-02-03_17-52-19.jpg" alt="Grammarly 8.639.494 Premium" title="Grammarly 8.639.494 Premium"  /><br /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Grammarly 8.639.494 Premium" title="Grammarly 8.639.494 Premium"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Sales Copy Cloner 2.0.3</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1452-sales-copy-cloner.html</link>
<description>Name : Sales Copy Cloner Version : 2.0.3 OS : Windows Type : Content Marketing Tools Price : $67 Homepage : SalePage SALES PAGE SPINNER</description>
<category>Grammar Checker</category>
<enclosure url="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/-0JSf3Ki42U/hqdefault.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2015 19:29:39 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features search articles by keywords Advance search spin sales page Advance HTML editor</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/-0JSf3Ki42U?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> search articles by keywords<br /></li><li> Advance search<br /></li><li> spin sales page<br /></li><li> Advance HTML editor<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/-0JSf3Ki42U/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Sales Copy Cloner 2.0.3" title="Sales Copy Cloner 2.0.3"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Sales Copy Cloner 2.0.3" title="Sales Copy Cloner 2.0.3"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>