<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Social Bookmark - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Social Bookmark - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>Social Synd Alpha 1.3.10</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/923-social-synd-alpha.html</link>
<description>Name : Social Synd Alpha Version : 1.3.10 OS : Windows Type : IFTT Tools Price : $19.90 Homepage : SalePage &quot;Easy Drag &amp;amp; Drop Wizard Technology To Create Your Own IFTTT Tiered Linking Sequences, Interlinking Rings &amp;amp; Syndicate Your Content on 100% Autopilot!..&quot; With Revolutionary New Software That Unleashes The Power Of IFTTT For SEO &amp;amp; Social Traffic Like Never Before!</description>
<category>Social Bookmark</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 00:17:33 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features - One Click Account Creation The account creator will automate the creation of IFTTT accounts and many of the sites within the IFTTT platform that we can work with and attach these to IFTTT without ever leaving the software - High Success Rate We have implemented features to improve success rate of account creation with the integration of captcha solving services and our own email servers for fast email creation and verification. - Pre Made Sequences WE realize that not everyone wants to create their own advanced syndication sequences, do have included 6 pre made syndication strategies which you can create for your own IFTTT accounts with one click. - Super Fast Speed With one click you can bulk create IFTTT accounts &amp;amp; profiles. After you have designed your sequences you can create them in the tool with one click again without logging into IFTTT - Profile &amp;amp; Bio Info Auto Filled Profile and Bio info automated for you with author avatars and you can add links within the profile too using short urls. Short urls created are done with 301 redirects using our traffic redirect tool so that you can change the destination URL anytime you choose. - On Site Optimization Some sites like blogger for example can have sidebars we can use to add hyperlinks to other accounts with each profile which creates additional interlinking. This is an optional choice along with random templates being selected automatically for you. - YouTube, Facebook &amp;amp; Daily Motion Video Posting We have added the basc version of the Video Synd Alpha poster for easy uploading to YouTube, Facebook &amp;amp; Daily Motion which can be used as triggers for your syndication sequences additional tiered linking. - Social Traffic Strategies Social Synd Alpha can also be used for social traffic strategies for branded accounts. It can replicate what tools like onlywire can do on autopilot with just a few clicks and take advantage of high traffic social platforms like Facebook, Twitter and Instagram.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/gOPACUIiak4?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br> - One Click Account Creation<br>The account creator will automate the creation of IFTTT accounts and many of the sites within the IFTTT platform that we can work with and attach these to IFTTT without ever leaving the software<br> - High Success Rate<br>We have implemented features to improve success rate of account creation with the integration of captcha solving services and our own email servers for fast email creation and verification.<br> - Pre Made Sequences<br>WE realize that not everyone wants to create their own advanced syndication sequences, do have included 6 pre made syndication strategies which you can create for your own IFTTT accounts with one click.<br> - Super Fast Speed<br>With one click you can bulk create IFTTT accounts &amp; profiles. After you have designed your sequences you can create them in the tool with one click again without logging into IFTTT<br> - Profile &amp; Bio Info Auto Filled<br>Profile and Bio info automated for you with author avatars and you can add links within the profile too using short urls. Short urls created are done with 301 redirects using our traffic redirect tool so that you can change the destination URL anytime you choose.<br> - On Site Optimization<br>Some sites like blogger for example can have sidebars we can use to add hyperlinks to other accounts with each profile which creates additional interlinking. This is an optional choice along with random templates being selected automatically for you.<br> - YouTube, Facebook &amp; Daily Motion Video Posting<br>We have added the basc version of the Video Synd Alpha poster for easy uploading to YouTube, Facebook &amp; Daily Motion which can be used as triggers for your syndication sequences additional tiered linking.<br> - Social Traffic Strategies<br>Social Synd Alpha can also be used for social traffic strategies for branded accounts. It can replicate what tools like onlywire can do on autopilot with just a few clicks and take advantage of high traffic social platforms like Facebook, Twitter and Instagram.<br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Social Synd Alpha 1.3.10"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>SocialRobot 1.1.9 Pro</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/926-socialrobot.html</link>
<description>Name : SocialRobot Professional Version : 1.1.9 OS : Windows Type : Social Submission, Social Bookmarking Tools Price : $67 Homepage : SalePage SocialRobot is the best and the most feature rich social bookmarking solution on the market</description>
<category>Social Bookmark</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.social-robot.com/images/screens/socialbase.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2016 04:43:04 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features One-Click Posting : Once your project is configured all you need to do is click the &quot;One-Click Posting&quot; button and the whole process from social bookmarking account creation, email verification, posting and link verification will happen automatically. Pure magic! Multiple CMS Support : SocialRobot currently supports the following platforms: Pligg, PHPDug, Scuttle and ScuttlePlus. New platforms are being constantly added. Automatic Updates : Software updates are pushed out frequently. Bugs are fixed fast. Customer&#039;s ideas and requests are heard and often integrated. But most importantly - the update happens automatically on SocialRobot startup. Local Database Storage : SocialRobot uses local database. That means everything that happens (e.g. when you add sites to a project or create an article) in SocialRobot is stored in the database and stays there until you delete it. Multithreaded : Up to 200 threads can be used for every imaginable action = blazing fast action! For those of you that don&#039;t know what threads are: simply said it&#039;s like having 200 browsers open doing all the work simultaneously in the background. Proxy Support : Anonymous and private HTTP proxies can be used with SocialRobot. It comes with a handy proxy handling interface that includes checking if proxies are alive, measuring response time, etc. When using proxies, they&#039;re always being rotated to prevent unwanted bans. Captcha Support : We have built in captcha solving engine, that will solve the simplest captcha types. DeathByCaptcha, De-Captcher, ImageTyperz, GSA Captcha Breaker and Captcha Sniper are also supported. You can also solve captcha manually by entering text from images or answering questions. Spinning : SpinRewriter, SpinnerChief, WordAI and The Best Spinner are supported in SocialRobot. That means all the content rewriting is like a walk in the park - easy and simple. Nested spinning is also supported. Powerful Scheduler : Jobs, consisting of tasks (Registration, E-mail Confirmation, Posting, Link Verification) are added through a simple wizard. Each task can: run once (date/time specified by user), or repeat: hourly, daily, weekly, monthly. Number of sites can be specified for each task. Tasks can be chained (with delay). SocialBase : SocialBase is a huge database of working social bookmarking sites that is constantly being refreshed and monitored. There are literally hundreds of working sites available in SocialBase. Links Indexing : SocialRobot comes with a built in pinger, so your link building efforts won&#039;t go unnoticed. We have also integrated with Indexification, Linklicious and LinkPipeline which will do wonders to your links. Export Links : SocialRobot can export both only posted or also already verified links. It can export them in a simple TXT file or in a much more in-depth Excel format (that includes site&#039;s platform, PR, do-follow status, etc.). Ideal for those that provide social bookmarking services or anyone else that just wants a pretty report. Live Links Checker : Posted articles can easily be checked for link presence. You can also easily export only live links. Logging Facility : Sometimes everything doesn&#039;t go according to the plan. There can be lots of reasons for failure and with SocialRobot you&#039;ll always know what&#039;s wrong. Every action and result can be logged and reviewed at a later time. Sites Filters : You can easily filter individual project and SocialBase sites to target exactly the ones you want. Some of the filters include: Do-Follow filter, PageRank filter, Captcha Filter, Platform Filter, .edu &amp; .gov Filter, etc. Blacklists : We all know that sites in a &quot;bad neighbourhood&quot; can have a negative impact on your rankings. That&#039;s why SocialRobot allows you to add bad sites to a blacklist. This way you can exclude them from your link building. Spyntax support for various fields Custom coded in C# Actions retry/delay Drip feeding Automatic Account Settings Generation Built-in Article Scraper Platform And PR Checker Dead Sites Test / Removal Duplicates Removal Lots Of Customizability And Settings Automatic AOL Email Account Creation Beautiful And Intuitive User Interface Detailed User&#039;s Manual And Community Forum Extensive Support :::Free Members ::: Download Now Password : www.tgmember.com :::ViP Only:::</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/-IcnSdOgJbA?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> <b>One-Click Posting</b> : Once your project is configured all you need to do is click the "One-Click Posting" button and the whole process from social bookmarking account creation, email verification, posting and link verification will happen automatically. Pure magic! <br /></li><li> <b>Multiple CMS Support</b> : SocialRobot currently supports the following platforms: Pligg, PHPDug, Scuttle and ScuttlePlus. New platforms are being constantly added.<br /></li><li> <b>Automatic Updates</b> : Software updates are pushed out frequently. Bugs are fixed fast. Customer's ideas and requests are heard and often integrated. But most importantly - the update happens automatically on SocialRobot startup. <br /></li><li> <b>Local Database Storage</b> : SocialRobot uses local database. That means everything that happens (e.g. when you add sites to a project or create an article) in SocialRobot is stored in the database and stays there until you delete it. <br /></li><li> <b>Multithreaded</b> : Up to 200 threads can be used for every imaginable action = blazing fast action! For those of you that don't know what threads are: simply said it's like having 200 browsers open doing all the work simultaneously in the background.  <br /></li><li> <b>Proxy Support</b> : Anonymous and private HTTP proxies can be used with SocialRobot. It comes with a handy proxy handling interface that includes checking if proxies are alive, measuring response time, etc. When using proxies, they're always being rotated to prevent unwanted bans.  <br /></li><li> <b>Captcha Support</b> : We have built in captcha solving engine, that will solve the simplest captcha types. DeathByCaptcha, De-Captcher, ImageTyperz, GSA Captcha Breaker and Captcha Sniper are also supported. You can also solve captcha manually by entering text from images or answering questions. <br /></li><li> <b>Spinning</b> : SpinRewriter, SpinnerChief, WordAI and The Best Spinner are supported in SocialRobot. That means all the content rewriting is like a walk in the park - easy and simple. Nested spinning is also supported. <br /></li><li> <b>Powerful Scheduler</b> : Jobs, consisting of tasks (Registration, E-mail Confirmation, Posting, Link Verification) are added through a simple wizard. Each task can: run once (date/time specified by user), or repeat: hourly, daily, weekly, monthly. Number of sites can be specified for each task. Tasks can be chained (with delay).  <br /></li><li> <b>SocialBase</b> : SocialBase is a huge database of working social bookmarking sites that is constantly being refreshed and monitored. There are literally hundreds of working sites available in SocialBase.  <br /></li><li> <b>Links Indexing</b> : SocialRobot comes with a built in pinger, so your link building efforts won't go unnoticed. We have also integrated with Indexification, Linklicious and LinkPipeline which will do wonders to your links. <br /></li><li> <b>Export Links</b> : SocialRobot can export both only posted or also already verified links. It can export them in a simple TXT file or in a much more in-depth Excel format (that includes site's platform, PR, do-follow status, etc.). Ideal for those that provide social bookmarking services or anyone else that just wants a pretty report. <br /></li><li> <b>Live Links Checker</b> : Posted articles can easily be checked for link presence. You can also easily export only live links. <br /></li><li> <b>Logging Facility</b> : Sometimes everything doesn't go according to the plan. There can be lots of reasons for failure and with SocialRobot you'll always know what's wrong. Every action and result can be logged and reviewed at a later time.<br /></li><li> <b>Sites Filters</b> : You can easily filter individual project and SocialBase sites to target exactly the ones you want. Some of the filters include: Do-Follow filter, PageRank filter, Captcha Filter, Platform Filter, .edu & .gov Filter, etc.<br /></li><li> <b>Blacklists</b> : We all know that sites in a "bad neighbourhood" can have a negative impact on your rankings. That's why SocialRobot allows you to add bad sites to a blacklist. This way you can exclude them from your link building. <br /></li><li> Spyntax support for various fields<br /></li><li> Custom coded in C#<br /></li><li> Actions retry/delay<br /></li><li> Drip feeding<br /></li><li> Automatic Account Settings Generation<br /></li><li> Built-in Article Scraper<br /></li><li> Platform And PR Checker<br /></li><li> Dead Sites Test / Removal<br /></li><li> Duplicates Removal<br /></li><li> Lots Of Customizability And Settings<br /></li><li> Automatic AOL Email Account Creation<br /></li><li> Beautiful And Intuitive User Interface<br /></li><li> Detailed User's Manual And Community Forum<br /></li><li> Extensive Support<br /><br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://www.social-robot.com/images/screens/socialbase.png" alt="SocialRobot 1.1.9 Pro" title="SocialRobot 1.1.9 Pro"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><span style="font-size:12pt;"><b><span style="color:#006600">:::Free Members  :::</span></b></span><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" alt="SocialRobot 1.1.9 Pro" title="SocialRobot 1.1.9 Pro"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><a href="http://www.tgmember.com/engine/go.php?url=aHR0cDovL3VzZXJzZmlsZXMuY29tLzZtdndmNGFibzAyNg%3D%3D"  target="_blank">Download Now</a><br />Password : www.tgmember.com<br /></div><br /></div><br /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><span style="font-size:12pt;"><b><span style="color:#FF0000">:::ViP Only:::</span></b></span><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="SocialRobot 1.1.9 Pro" title="SocialRobot 1.1.9 Pro"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Bookmark Alpha 1.8</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1344-bookmark-alpha.html</link>
<description>Name : Bookmark Alpha Version : 1.8 OS : Windows Type : Social Bookmarking software, Social Bookmark Submision Price : $127 Homepage : SalePage New Automated Social Bookmarking Software Drives Page One Traffic At The Click Of A Button!... Warning!...Best Suited For Lazy Video Marketers Who Want Fast Traffic &amp;amp; Rankings! Bookmark Alpha, my latest automated Social Bookmarking Software is ready to be released in a few days and its looking really good! Bookmark Alpha is our second &quot;Alpha&quot; software tool following on from Video Synd Alpha, and as the name suggests its an automated social bookmarking tool and is way beyond our Social Bookmark Commando tool (which is still being supported and updated and still on sale). A Lot of the tool will look familiar to Video synd alpha users as we kept features such as the Long Tail Synd Alpha tool, captcha, proxy and spinner settings and a few more. VSA users will find this tool very intuitive as they will be familar with the various settings.</description>
<category>Social Bookmark</category>
<enclosure url="http://cdn.commandoseoltd.comdna-cdn.com/wp-content/uploads/Main-Bookmark-Alpha-Dashboard.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 05:10:49 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features The Most Powerful, Easy To Use, Social Bookmarking Tool Around! Drives Fast Rankings &amp;amp; Traffic, Built Especially For Video Marketers But Will Work For Ranking Websites Too! Built In Unique, Proprietory SEO Strategies Made Push Buttton Simple! Intelligent Tiered Linking : Automation &amp;amp; Tiered Linking is the least we should expect from SEO software tools these days. We have taken this to a whole new level by adding proven, effective, intelligent tiered linking that does not exist anywhere else Intelligent SEO Strategies : We have built in simple &amp;amp; advanced SEO strategies and made them push button simple. These are unique, proprietory strategies that just plain work, and won&#039;t be found on any other bookmarking tool. Intelligent Site Management : Bookmark Alpha works with multiple platforms, with unlimited sites and unlimited accounts from those sites. Used with our built in strategies this is extreme power, especially for video marketers! Works With Multiple Platforms To Give You Options Of 1000&#039;s More Sites! Add Your Own Sites! Built in multi platform site scraper with &quot;bad neighbourhood&quot; filterering! Bulk 301 Url Shortner To Make Your Links Look Natural! Lazy Backlinks IFTTT Strategy To Backlink Your Money Url Even More &amp;amp; Hands Free! *NEW Easy Project Management Our Own Built In Email Servers Proprietory Long Tail Synd Tool Built In Proprietory Push Button SEO Strategies That Work! Automated, Multi Threaded, 1 Click Bulk Account Creation &amp;amp; Posting Auto Indexing &amp;amp; Pinging! Live Links Checker! Easy Re-use of Your Accounts On Multiple Campaigns! Easy Import &amp;amp; Export Of Your Profiles &amp;amp; Accounts Advanced Site Management Set &amp;amp; Forget Auto Scheduling with Drip Feed Works With Popular 3rd party Indexers, Spinners, Captcha Solvers &amp;amp; Proxies Multi Task With Different Tools Make Unique Tiitles &amp;amp; Descriptions Easily Designed With Video Marketers in Mind, But With Built In SEO Strategies For Websites too! :::ViP Only:::</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/x-pqSC5r5Xs?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div>
<p></p>
<h3>Features</h3>
<p><br><ul><li> The Most Powerful, Easy To Use, Social Bookmarking Tool Around!<br></li><li> Drives Fast Rankings &amp; Traffic, Built Especially For Video Marketers But Will Work For Ranking Websites Too!<br></li><li> Built In Unique, Proprietory SEO Strategies Made Push Buttton Simple!<br></li><li> Intelligent Tiered Linking : Automation &amp; Tiered Linking is the least we should expect from SEO software tools these days. We have taken this to a whole new level by adding proven, effective, intelligent tiered linking that does not exist anywhere else<br></li><li> Intelligent SEO Strategies : We have built in simple &amp; advanced SEO strategies and made them push button simple. These are unique, proprietory strategies that just plain work, and won't be found on any other bookmarking tool.<br></li><li> Intelligent Site Management : Bookmark Alpha works with multiple platforms, with unlimited sites and unlimited accounts from those sites. Used with our built in strategies this is extreme power, especially for video marketers!<br></li><li> Works With Multiple Platforms To Give You Options Of 1000's More Sites!<br></li><li> Add Your Own Sites!<br></li><li> Built in multi platform site scraper with "bad neighbourhood" filterering!<br></li><li> Bulk 301 Url Shortner To Make Your Links Look Natural!<br></li><li> Lazy Backlinks IFTTT Strategy To Backlink Your Money Url Even More &amp; Hands Free! *NEW<br></li><li> Easy Project Management<br></li><li> Our Own Built In Email Servers <br></li><li> Proprietory Long Tail Synd Tool <br></li><li> Built In Proprietory Push Button SEO Strategies That Work!<br></li><li> Automated, Multi Threaded, 1 Click Bulk Account Creation &amp; Posting<br></li><li> Auto Indexing &amp; Pinging!<br></li><li> Live Links Checker!<br></li><li> Easy Re-use of Your Accounts On Multiple Campaigns!<br></li><li> Easy Import &amp; Export Of Your Profiles &amp; Accounts<br></li><li> Advanced Site Management<br></li><li> Set &amp; Forget Auto Scheduling with Drip Feed<br></li><li> Works With Popular 3rd party Indexers, Spinners, Captcha Solvers &amp; Proxies<br></li><li> Multi Task With Different Tools<br></li><li> Make Unique Tiitles &amp; Descriptions Easily<br></li><li> Designed With Video Marketers in Mind, But With Built In SEO Strategies For Websites too!<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://cdn.commandoseoltd.comdna-cdn.com/wp-content/uploads/Main-Bookmark-Alpha-Dashboard.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Bookmark Alpha 1.8"><br><br></p>
<div style="text-align:center;"><br><span style="font-size:12pt;"><b><span style="color:#ff0000;">:::ViP Only:::</span></b></span><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Social Rank Jet Suite Pro 1.0.10</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1242-social-rank-jet-suite.html</link>
<description>Name : Social Rank Jet Suite Version : Pro 1.0.10 OS : Windows Type : Social Sumissions Tools Price : $9 Homepage : [leech=#]SalePage[/leech] Social Rank Jet Suite is a kind of huge social backlinking tool which creates contextual social.comwork backlinks from popular social.comworking platform with high PR and high authority sites. In this new era of Google algorithm, one of the Google 7 critical ranking signals are Social Proof, and this latest software was specially designed to increase the Social Proof of our website. With one click, we can get hundreds of social backlinks automatically that will help to rank our sites on Google, Yahoo and Bing in a short period of time. Social Rank Jet Suite is the easiest way to Rank Any Website and Video In Any Niche Fast. and Get Hundreds of Quality Backlinks Fully Automated Traffic On Demand.</description>
<category>Social Bookmark</category>
<enclosure url="http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-Y8P0wsjHswI/UQFK_6511WI/AAAAAAAAAJk/MOh-n-xOx_k/s1600/Social%20Rank%20Jet%20Suite.gif" type="image/gif" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2015 21:01:41 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Automate Backlinking creation from hundreds of high authority social.comworking sites. Fully Automate registration and article submission process. Automatically create email accounts on the social.comwork for you. Automaticaly solve captchas through de captcher and death by captcha. Suport Private and password protected proxies Fully support multiple level(nested) spin syntax for a much better article uniqueness. Win Socket Based Submission for a very fast submission speed. and the just when you thought it couldn’t do any more social Rank Jet Will Then. Convert your backlink to RSS FeddsandThen Submit it Automatically to RSS Directories. And Much Much More.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/_xx2DHdftZI?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Automate Backlinking creation from hundreds of high authority social.comworking sites.<br /></li><li> Fully Automate registration and article submission process.<br /></li><li> Automatically create email accounts on the social.comwork for you.<br /></li><li> Automaticaly solve captchas through de captcher and death by captcha.<br /></li><li> Suport Private and password protected proxies<br /></li><li> Fully support multiple level(nested) spin syntax for a much better article uniqueness.<br /></li><li> Win Socket Based Submission for a very fast submission speed.<br /></li><li> and the just when you thought it couldn’t do any more social Rank Jet Will Then.<br /></li><li> Convert your backlink to RSS FeddsandThen Submit it Automatically to RSS Directories.<br /></li><li> And Much Much More.<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-Y8P0wsjHswI/UQFK_6511WI/AAAAAAAAAJk/MOh-n-xOx_k/s1600/Social%20Rank%20Jet%20Suite.gif" alt="Social Rank Jet Suite Pro 1.0.10" title="Social Rank Jet Suite Pro 1.0.10"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Social Rank Jet Suite Pro 1.0.10" title="Social Rank Jet Suite Pro 1.0.10"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Social Hub Submitter 1.0.0.36</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1241-social-hub-submitter.html</link>
<description>Name : Social Hub Submitter Version : 1.0.0.36 OS : Windows Type : Social Submission Tools Price : $17 Homepage : SalePage Social Hub Submitter - Brand New Software Automates Social Media Submissions, Featuring state of the art Project management Controls. Allowing a &quot;Set it and Forget it&quot; process unlike anything you&#039;ve seen before...</description>
<category>Social Bookmark</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.socialhubsubmitter.com/group1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="http://www.socialhubsubmitter.com/pingf.comwork.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2015 20:59:51 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Posts to multiple Hellotxt, Ping.fm, Posterous, Seesmic, Dlvr, Hootsuite and Scoopit accounts (Pingfm and Hellotxt Obsolete services) Works with spinned syntax Works with bit.ly url shortner for tracking and important perm 301 redirect The best spinner integrated- requires account (optional) Group management system Project content management system User controlled delay Control number of posts Multi-threaded Advanced free and private proxy control Works with Rss Feeds, combine and merge entries with or without Articles Runs whilst minimized and on system start-up Making it truly Set and forget Randomize posting to mix up projects and post with or without links Built in Logic posts to accounts based on time stamp, ensuring posts are spread between connections</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/6H1qKm3qt7g?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Posts to multiple Hellotxt, Ping.fm, Posterous, Seesmic, Dlvr, Hootsuite and Scoopit accounts (Pingfm and Hellotxt Obsolete services)<br /></li><li> Works with spinned syntax<br /></li><li> Works with bit.ly url shortner for tracking and important perm 301 redirect<br /></li><li> The best spinner integrated- requires account (optional)<br /></li><li> Group management system<br /></li><li> Project content management system<br /></li><li> User controlled delay<br /></li><li> Control number of posts<br /></li><li> Multi-threaded<br /></li><li> Advanced free and private proxy control<br /></li><li> Works with Rss Feeds, combine and merge entries with or without Articles<br /></li><li> Runs whilst minimized and on system start-up Making it truly Set and forget<br /></li><li> Randomize posting to mix up projects and post with or without links<br /></li><li> Built in Logic posts to accounts based on time stamp, ensuring posts are spread between connections<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://www.socialhubsubmitter.com/group1.jpg" alt="Social Hub Submitter 1.0.0.36" title="Social Hub Submitter 1.0.0.36"  /><br /><img src="http://www.socialhubsubmitter.com/pingf.comwork.jpg" alt="Social Hub Submitter 1.0.0.36" title="Social Hub Submitter 1.0.0.36"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Social Hub Submitter 1.0.0.36" title="Social Hub Submitter 1.0.0.36"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Social Backlink Empire Suite Pro 1.0.20</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1240-social-backlink-empire-suite.html</link>
<description>Name : Social Backlink Empire Suite Version : Pro 1.0.20 OS : Windows Type : Social Sumissions Tools Price : $9 Homepage : SalePage Social Backlink Empire Suite is a powerful social backlinking software and the main points are: Will help to rank sites on Google, Yahoo and Bing in a short period of time (2 weeks or less). Will help to increase the sites authority in google eyes by building backlinks from high authority social sites. Increased social presence that will also help to increase the overall site’s traffic. The backlinks that is being created by this software is a powerful contextual web 2.0 backlinks from popular social.comworking platform (BuddyPress). A lot of these are from high PR sites. This software can be used to rank anything, eg: you can use this to rank videos for offliners as well and sell them the rankings…and show the client that they have people looking for their business everyday and if they show up with video they can have more exposure which in the end will give them more branding and more clients.</description>
<category>Social Bookmark</category>
<enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/rodrigowerner/sbesuite/FE/1.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/rodrigowerner/sbesuite/FE/3.1.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2015 20:58:28 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/rjw3Kg6bt68?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><img src="https://s3.amazonaws.com/rodrigowerner/sbesuite/FE/1.png" alt="Social Backlink Empire Suite Pro 1.0.20" title="Social Backlink Empire Suite Pro 1.0.20"  /><br /><img src="https://s3.amazonaws.com/rodrigowerner/sbesuite/FE/3.1.png" alt="Social Backlink Empire Suite Pro 1.0.20" title="Social Backlink Empire Suite Pro 1.0.20"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Social Backlink Empire Suite Pro 1.0.20" title="Social Backlink Empire Suite Pro 1.0.20"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>