<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Email Scraper &amp; Extractor - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Email Scraper &amp; Extractor - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>Adam Auto Mailer 2018 6.10</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1921-adam-auto-mailer.html</link>
<description>Name : Adam Auto Mailer 2018 Version : titleman OS : Windows Type : Email Scraper Price : $47 Homepage : SalePage Extract REAL TARGETED EMAILS From ANY WEBSITE, ANY FACEBOOK GROUPS, ANY FACEBOOK ACCOUNTS How AdamAutoMailer Can Help You to Obtain REAL Emails From ANY WEBSITE AdamAutoMailer is a Must Have tool For Any Professional Marketer to Extract REAL Email Addresses from Any Website ! Fast and Accurate. From FACEBOOK, It retrives all valid email addresses by Subjects, Keywords, Interests. From FACEBOOK GROUPS, It extracts all valid email addresses in all groups you join in or Any Public Groups. From FACEBOOK ACCOUNTS, It Extracts all Valid Email Addresses Of your Friends in Your Facebook Account, Or Friends Of Your Friends On Facebook =&amp;gt; Most Powerful Feature From GOOGLE, It retrives all valid email addresses on any Website by Keywords. It automatically removes duplicates, and intelligently takes off false email addresses.</description>
<category>Email Scraper &amp; Extractor</category>
<enclosure url="http://adamtranonline.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/04/Feedbacks10.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 05:00:25 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Email Addresses of all Merchant , Businessmen, Entrepreneur on Linkedin.com! WOW =&amp;gt; A big chance to promote lots of LOANs CPA Offers From Maxbounty or Peerfly ,.... =&amp;gt; MONEY Email Addresses of many membes on WarriorForum.com! WOW =&amp;gt; A great opportunity to promote Making Money Online Products from Jvzoo, WarriorPlus, ClickBank,...as affiliate marketer=&amp;gt; MONEY Again ! Email Addresses of people Who are Interested in Losing Weight, Keeping Fit,... =&amp;gt; Promote Health , Keeping Fit,... Products =&amp;gt; MONEY Again Again! Email Addresses of all the members who are Vendors, affiliate Marketers in a group =&amp;gt; Even you can sell Database for them =&amp;gt; MONEY Again Again Again! Email Addresses in all targeted Facebook Groups =&amp;gt; Import To Facebook Custom Audience =&amp;gt; Sell Anything You Want</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/JY2C0fDtYQ8?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><p><br></p><br><h3>Features</h3><br><p><br><ul><li> Email Addresses of all Merchant , Businessmen, Entrepreneur on Linkedin.com! WOW =&gt; A big chance to promote lots of LOANs CPA Offers From Maxbounty or Peerfly ,.... =&gt; MONEY <br></li><li> Email Addresses of many membes on WarriorForum.com! WOW =&gt; A great opportunity to promote Making Money Online Products from Jvzoo, WarriorPlus, ClickBank,...as affiliate marketer=&gt; MONEY Again ! <br></li><li> Email Addresses of people Who are Interested in Losing Weight, Keeping Fit,... =&gt; Promote Health , Keeping Fit,... Products =&gt; MONEY Again Again! <br></li><li> Email Addresses of all the members who are Vendors, affiliate Marketers in a group =&gt; Even you can sell Database for them =&gt; MONEY Again Again Again! <br></li><li> Email Addresses in all targeted Facebook Groups =&gt; Import To Facebook Custom Audience =&gt; Sell Anything You Want<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://adamtranonline.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/04/Feedbacks10.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Adam Auto Mailer 2018 6.10"><br><br><br></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Email Scraper 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3723-email-scraper.html</link>
<description>Name : Email Scraper Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Email Scraper Price : $0 Homepage : SalePage Email scraper can gather thousands of emails from websites by domain or keyword without the need for proxies. Spamming emails is so 2001! Use these huge email lists to create cheap Facebook ads. Many marketing platforms allow you to load in email lists. Email scraper allows you to crawl niche realted websites it generates through Bing based on your search terms for email addresses. It allows you to generate massive email lists without the need for proxies. How you use these email lists is up to you. However as it is illegal to email scraped/harvested emails under the CAN-SPAM act I would strongly enourage you to use these lists for targetting users on adverising platforms such as Facebook who allow you to load in an email list and target users based on their email address.</description>
<category>Email Scraper &amp; Extractor</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 14:00:42 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>[media=https://youtu.be/k0XYij4hCs4] Features How Email Scraper works If you own a body building forum and you want to find the email addresses of other people who might be interested in body building you would simply enter something like &quot;body building forum&quot; into the Email Scraper it will then serch the Bing search engine for websites related to &quot;body building forum&quot;. Once it has a list of these websites it will crawl each page on each of these websites for any email addresses it can find. Why should I use Email Scraper? Email Scraper allows you to build huge email lists without the need for proxies like a lot of other email scraping software. You can then target people by email address on advertising platforms that you may not typically reach if they haven&#039;t shown an interest in that niche while using that platform/social.comwork.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;">[media=https://youtu.be/k0XYij4hCs4]</div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br>How Email Scraper works<br>If you own a body building forum and you want to find the email addresses of other people who might be interested in body building you would simply enter something like "body building forum" into the Email Scraper it will then serch the Bing search engine for websites related to "body building forum". Once it has a list of these websites it will crawl each page on each of these websites for any email addresses it can find.<br><br>Why should I use Email Scraper?<br>Email Scraper allows you to build huge email lists without the need for proxies like a lot of other email scraping software. You can then target people by email address on advertising platforms that you may not typically reach if they haven't shown an interest in that niche while using that platform/social.comwork.<br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Email Scraper 1.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Detect-Email 2018 1.7</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1929-detect-email.html</link>
<description>Name : Detect-Email 2018 Version : 1.7 OS : Windows Type : Lead Extract Tools Price : $127 Homepage : SalePage The Detect-Email search thousands of emails from the Web. This software help you to gain new customers ! Also Support italian and French</description>
<category>Email Scraper &amp; Extractor</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.detect-email.com/images/contact_express_emailing.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2018 10:48:54 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Find targeted emails easily ! Detect-Email is a powerful email search engine. Choose your key words and the software can do a research with your requirements: it will find thousands of emails. Detect-Email also offers completed emailing tool for successful e-marketing campaign with yours Emails lists. Emailing campaigns will become easy ! You can choose your email lists with Detect-Email or find other ones. email marketing software. Compose your message (advertising, newsletter, communication...) and send it with Detect-Email: it takes just three clicks ! Add &quot;links followed&quot; in your email to analyze the impact of your communication. Measure the power of your campaigns : Who opened your email ? At what moment ? Get the statistics emails openings on your sites ! Managing unsubscriptions (black lists) is automatic. Your recipients may delete your emailing lists with a single click. Extract emails on directories or on your computer Browse the inte.com and automatically capture emails with the option &quot;Clic &amp;amp; Go&quot;. Detect-Email also allows capturing emails from your own file (hard drives, Excel, CSV or other software).</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Sbpq-zVIiOo?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Find targeted emails easily !   Detect-Email is a powerful email search engine.  Choose your key words and the software can do a research with  your requirements: it will find thousands of emails.  Detect-Email also offers completed emailing tool for successful  e-marketing campaign with yours Emails lists. <br></li><li> Emailing campaigns will become easy ! You can choose your email lists with Detect-Email or find other ones.  email marketing software. Compose your message (advertising,  newsletter, communication...) and send it with Detect-Email: it  takes just three clicks ! Add "links followed" in your email to  analyze the impact of your communication. <br></li><li> Measure the power of your campaigns : Who opened your email ? At what moment ? Get the statistics emails  openings on your sites ! Managing unsubscriptions (black lists) is  automatic. Your recipients may delete your emailing lists with a  single click. <br></li><li> Extract emails on directories or on your computer   Browse the inte.com and automatically capture emails with the  option "Clic &amp; Go". Detect-Email also allows capturing emails  from your own file (hard drives, Excel, CSV or other software). <br></li></ul><br><img src="http://www.detect-email.com/images/contact_express_emailing.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Detect-Email 2018 1.7"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Mega Mailing 2018 1.7</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1930-mega-mailing.html</link>
<description>Name : Mega Mailing 2018 (Brazil Only) Version : 1.7 Premium OS : Windows Type : Lead Extractor Price : $727 Homepage : SalePage No1 Brazil Lead Software Capture new customers from keywords Find suppliers of any field of activity Search positioning in the web of its competitors capture entire lists of mailing, professional and personal contacts Review posts where appears your company or name on the Inte.com megamailing is a capture software updated emails and phone numbers. megamailing capture entire lists of updated e-mail, landline numbers, cell phone numbers, mailing companies, mailing lists of people, many mailing list, geolocated data (state, zip code, city), url directly inte.com sites.</description>
<category>Email Scraper &amp; Extractor</category>
<enclosure url="https://megamailing.com.br/wp-content/uploads/2016/08/logo-megamailing-png.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2018 10:48:24 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Emails companies Emails from people customer emails corporate email Government e-mails Numbers of landlines Mobile phone numbers Data companies and people Addresses of companies and people (state, city, zip code) Visit the sites identified by the program Conduct targeted searches (research companies, people) Perform research on geographic filters (by city or national) Create custom databases Perform your own research using keywords Capture the archived e-mails on your computer Capture thousands of emails in navigation mode on the Inte.com Save your searches in Excel, .txt, .csv Saves your searches on your computer and / or USB stick Analyze the results of research with various reading filter Export your searches for emails Perform their research without relying on others All captured data is updated online Create and send your marketing emails (required SMTP)</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Sbpq-zVIiOo?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Emails companies<br></li><li> Emails from people<br></li><li> customer emails<br></li><li> corporate email<br></li><li> Government e-mails<br></li><li> Numbers of landlines<br></li><li> Mobile phone numbers<br></li><li> Data companies and people<br></li><li> Addresses of companies and people  (state, city, zip code)<br></li><li> Visit the sites identified by the program<br></li><li> Conduct targeted searches  (research companies, people)<br></li><li> Perform research on geographic filters  (by city or national)<br></li><li> Create custom databases<br></li><li> Perform your own research using keywords<br></li><li> Capture the archived e-mails on your computer<br></li><li> Capture thousands of emails in navigation mode on the Inte.com<br></li><li> Save your searches in Excel, .txt, .csv<br></li><li> Saves your searches on your computer and / or USB stick<br></li><li> Analyze the results of research with various reading filter<br></li><li> Export your searches for emails<br></li><li> Perform their research without relying on others<br></li><li> All captured data is updated online<br></li><li> Create and send your marketing emails (required SMTP)<br></li></ul><br><img src="https://megamailing.com.br/wp-content/uploads/2016/08/logo-megamailing-png.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Mega Mailing 2018 1.7"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Contact Express 2018 1.7</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1681-contact-express.html</link>
<description>Name : Contact Express (Fr Only) Version : 2018 1.7 OS : Windows Type : Email Scraper by Local Price : $159 Homepage : SalePage Collect thousands of emails with Contact Express! Contact Express can collect on the Inte.com targeted hundreds of emails according to your criteria and your core target! If you are looking for new clients, new business contacts or if you want to market your product, contact the Express software will make your incredible service Contact-Express is not only a high-speed mails cleaner, it&#039;s also a professional tool for creating e-mailing with professional formatting, embedded images and attachments.</description>
<category>Email Scraper &amp; Extractor</category>
<enclosure url="http://i.imgur.com/M51Dhqf.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2018 10:30:16 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Contact Express is a vacuum dE mail software: it can capture emails on the Inte.com and create an emailing to the email lists of captured. The software is for all those looking for a vacuum cleaner emails to research emails on the web, Contact-Express allows customers to generate files for commercial prospecting or getting email lists to find new prospects and new customers. Search email list : Besides email lists that you can retrieve with Contact Express, emailing software that will allow you capture targeted emails and show you how to make effective emailing. This email search software on the Inte.com is a great way to build up email files to increase your company&#039;s sales force. E-Mailing targeted : The vacuum cleaner Emails Contact Express offers powerful tools to make your emailing. Use the capture of targeted emails to increase the relevance of your search for emails and optimize the power of research new customers and prospects. Prospecting and Marketing : Make your campaigns E-mailing with the new features of the search engine email contact Express: tracking links for the analysis of your campaigns and churn links to manage your email mailing lists. Prospecting Techniques : With its new engine targeted emails research, Contact-Express offers your company new suction methods of emails and email list extraction. The software offers eg geographic filtering options.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/RLgozcBkk0o?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Contact Express is a vacuum dE mail software: it can capture emails on the Inte.com and create an emailing to the email lists of captured. The software is for all those looking for a vacuum cleaner emails to research emails on the web, Contact-Express allows customers to generate files for commercial prospecting or getting email lists to find new prospects and new customers.<br></li><li> Search email list : Besides email lists that you can retrieve with Contact Express, emailing software that will allow you capture targeted emails and show you how to make effective emailing. This email search software on the Inte.com is a great way to build up email files to increase your company's sales force.<br></li><li> E-Mailing targeted : The vacuum cleaner Emails Contact Express offers powerful tools to make your emailing. Use the capture of targeted emails to increase the relevance of your search for emails and optimize the power of research new customers and prospects.<br></li><li> Prospecting and Marketing : Make your campaigns E-mailing with the new features of the search engine email contact Express: tracking links for the analysis of your campaigns and churn links to manage your email mailing lists.<br></li><li> Prospecting Techniques : With its new engine targeted emails research, Contact-Express offers your company new suction methods of emails and email list extraction. The software offers eg geographic filtering options.<br><br></li></ul><br><img src="http://i.imgur.com/M51Dhqf.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Contact Express 2018 1.7"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Power Leads Pro X 3.3.1.199</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1932-power-leads-pro-x.html</link>
<description>Name : Power Leads Pro X Version : 3.3.1.199 Enterprise Edition OS : Windows Type : Email Marketing Tool Price : $997 Homepage : SalePage Advanced Lead Generation Software Increases Your Sales, Production &amp;amp; CRM...Guaranteed! Power Leads Pro Users Celebrating</description>
<category>Email Scraper &amp; Extractor</category>
<enclosure url="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/tdj7eBgh4vo/maxresdefault.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2018 11:26:28 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Power Leads Pro X Core Support Google Maps Support Bing Maps Support Yelp Support Yellow Pages Support Yellow Book Support Yahoo Local Support Twillio Support LinkedIn Support Super Pages Business Support Manta Support Super Extractor Support Skype Support Merchant Circle Support Google Search Engine Support Yahoo Search Engine Support Bing Search Engine Support Craigslist Support Backpage Support Gumtree Support Ebay Classifieds Support Kijiji Support Facebook Support Google Adwords Support Super Pages People</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/uj9eiI2vj1M?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><p><br></p><br><h3>Features</h3><br><p><br><ul><li> Power Leads Pro X Core <br></li><li> Support Google Maps <br></li><li> Support Bing Maps <br></li><li> Support Yelp <br></li><li> Support Yellow Pages <br></li><li> Support Yellow Book <br></li><li> Support Yahoo Local <br></li><li> Support Twillio <br></li><li> Support LinkedIn <br></li><li> Support Super Pages Business <br></li><li> Support Manta <br></li><li> Support Super Extractor <br></li><li> Support Skype <br></li><li> Support Merchant Circle <br></li><li> Support Google Search Engine <br></li><li> Support Yahoo Search Engine <br></li><li> Support Bing Search Engine <br></li><li> Support Craigslist <br></li><li> Support Backpage <br></li><li> Support Gumtree <br></li><li> Support Ebay Classifieds <br></li><li> Support Kijiji <br></li><li> Support Facebook <br></li><li> Support Google Adwords <br></li><li> Support Super Pages People<br></li></ul><br><img src="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/tdj7eBgh4vo/maxresdefault.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Power Leads Pro X 3.3.1.199"><br><br></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Email Extractor Pro 6.0.3</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1467-email-extractor.html</link>
<description>Name : Email Extractor Pro Version : 6.0.3 OS : Windows Type : Email Marketing Tools Price : $44.95 Homepage : SalePage Email Extractor is free all-in-one email spider software. It is a lightweight and powerful utility designed to extract email addresses from various sources: local files, websites, search engines, etc. It is a great tool for creating your customer contact list using your mailbox data. Email Extractor is a great helper in conducting email marketing campaigns. Every email campaign requires large lists of email addresses. It’s almost impossible to extract the email addresses manually. Email Extractor is a perfect tool for building your customers’ email lists using the files from your mailbox. You can download free email extractor trial and test if it works for you. Email extractor is the fastest email harvester on the Web. Unlike other email harvesters, Email Extractor possesses all essential features of extraction software: it’s extremely fast, easy in usage, and feature-rich.</description>
<category>Email Scraper &amp; Extractor</category>
<enclosure url="http://emailextractorpro.com/images/screenshots/email-extractor-whois.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 04:13:49 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features It is developed to collect e-mail addresses and user names from various sources: Search Engines: Google, Yahoo, MSN, etc. Website: scan all pages of the specified website Url List: scan list of specified web pages Email Accounts: scan email accounts Computer: any local file, folder, drive or CD-/ DVD-Rom Website Owners Info: extract domain owner&#039;s data MS Outlook Express Network Netscape Messenger, Eudora</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><object type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="425" height="264" data="http://emailextractorpro.com/video/extractor-whois_skin.swf"><param name="movie" value="http://emailextractorpro.com/video/extractor-whois_skin.swf"><param name="wmode" value="transparent" /><param name="play" value="true"><param name="loop" value="true"><param name="quality" value="high"><param name="allowScriptAccess" value="never"><param name="allowNetworking" value="internal"><embed allowscriptaccess="never" allo.comworking="internal" src="http://emailextractorpro.com/video/extractor-whois_skin.swf" width="425" height="264" play="true" loop="true" quality="high" wmode="transparent"></embed></object></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><br>It is developed to collect e-mail addresses and user names from various sources:<br><ul><li> Search Engines: Google, Yahoo, MSN, etc.<br></li><li> Website: scan all pages of  the specified website<br></li><li> Url List: scan list of specified web pages<br></li><li> Email Accounts: scan email accounts<br></li><li> Computer: any local file, folder, drive or CD-/ DVD-Rom<br></li><li> Website Owners Info: extract domain owner's data<br></li><li> MS Outlook Express<br></li><li> Network<br></li><li> Netscape Messenger, Eudora<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://emailextractorpro.com/images/screenshots/email-extractor-whois.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Email Extractor Pro 6.0.3"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Email Extractor 14</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3890-email-extractor-14.html</link>
<description>Name : Email Extractor 14 Version : 1.4 OS : Windows Type : Email Extractor Price : $169 Homepage : SalePage Email Extractor 14 is an award-winning software for extracting thousands of email addresses within seconds using one of the following extraction methods. Email Extractor 1.4 is a spider program that crawls the web to harvest addresses based on criteria outlined by the user. For instance, if the user is running an e-mail marketing campaign aimed at birdwatchers, the user can easily search for addresses likely to belong to individuals who share that interest. You can also use EE 14 to extract emails by domain name or from local files in your computer.</description>
<category>Email Scraper &amp; Extractor</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 21:45:07 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Extract emails from the search engines, using keywords. Extract emails from local files in your computer. Extract emails from a website/domain e.g twitter,facebook.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/bXPTDKkQcR4?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Extract emails from the search engines, using keywords.<br></li><li> Extract emails from local files in your computer.<br></li><li> Extract emails from a website/domain e.g twitter,facebook.<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Email Extractor 14"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Email Extractor 4.7</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3757-email-extractor.html</link>
<description>Name : Email Extractor 4.7 Version : 1.0.27 OS : Windows/MAC Type : Email Extractor Price : $9 Homepage : SalePage Powerful Extension To Extract E-Mail ID&#039;s Automatically From Web Pages. NEW FEATURES: AutoVisit websites and AutoSave Email IDs. Find email addresses in seconds. Email Extractor is a powerful email extraction extension for Chrome. Extension automatically fetches valid email IDs from the web page, you can copy paste particular email ids you need or export all of them to a text or CSV file.</description>
<category>Email Scraper &amp; Extractor</category>
<enclosure url="http://i.imgur.com/Tde3oEv.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2017 20:00:43 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features AutoVisit: build a queue of URL that you want to visit automatically Automation: discover all email ID&#039;s ending with a specific domain name Extract Email Address from Web Pages Automatically Auto-save all Email Address in the cloud while you browse any website (cloud storage starting at $9.99/month) share your Premium subscription with your colleagues Download stored Email IDs Extracts Emails on Ajax Pages as well, for example Google Search Extracts Cloaked Emails Filters for Duplicate Email ID, so you get only Unique ones Local Storage Export Option to export list of your extracted emails to a text file Offline Support (Added as of v1.6 Beta) Needs permission Extract Emails from Local HTML Documents Extract Emails from Text Files Fast, Light(Only 51KB) removes duplicate email addresses</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/M-Gd8Yhg3y0?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> AutoVisit: build a queue of URL that you want to visit automatically<br></li><li> Automation: discover all email ID's ending with a specific domain name<br></li><li> Extract Email Address from Web Pages Automatically<br></li><li> Auto-save all Email Address in the cloud while you browse any website (cloud storage starting at .99/month)<br></li><li> share your Premium subscription with your colleagues<br></li><li> Download stored Email IDs<br></li><li> Extracts Emails on Ajax Pages as well, for example Google Search<br></li><li> Extracts Cloaked Emails<br></li><li> Filters for Duplicate Email ID, so you get only Unique ones<br></li><li> Local Storage<br></li><li> Export Option to export list of your extracted emails to a text file<br></li><li> Offline Support (Added as of v1.6 Beta) Needs permission<br></li><li> Extract Emails from Local HTML Documents<br></li><li> Extract Emails from Text Files<br></li><li> Fast, Light(Only 51KB)<br></li><li> removes duplicate email addresses<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://i.imgur.com/Tde3oEv.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Email Extractor 4.7"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Email and Phone Extractor Files 5.2.6.32</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1978-email-and-phone-extractor-files.html</link>
<description>Name : Email and Phone Extractor Files Version : 5.2.6.32 OS : Windows Type : Email Extractor, Phone Extractor Price : $69 Homepage : SalePage Email and Phone Extractor Files is a tool to extract email ids and Phone numbers, mobile numbers from files such as DOC, DOCX, DOT, XLS, XLSX, PDF, TXT, RTF, PPT, PPTX, XML, HTML, ASP, PHP &amp; all other files. It extracts Email Addresses and phone number as well as Mobile &amp; Fax numbers from multiple files, those you just need to define the search criteria &amp; automatically remove duplicate entries. It has the feature of Filter out the Email Addresses and phone numbers and gets the desired results. Main Advantage is you can get Mobile as well Email id’s from a single software from all sorts of files. With the help of this feature the users are able to get only those Email Addresses and Mobile number which are relevant to the search criteria and required by the users. It is fastest software tool for extracting Email Addresses and phone numbers from all supported files simultaneously. This tool is single tool to extract Email id’s and Phone as well mobile numbers from all sorts of files on your PC. It also supports filter the extracted phone numbers and email addresses through which you can remove all the unwanted entries from the list. The software is widely used by the business organizations for carrying out marketing. It processes multiple files and folders to extract the phone, Mobile &amp; Fax numbers and email addresses in a very short time. This software tool is very efficient and super fast in extracting phone numbers and email addresses in just minutes.</description>
<category>Email Scraper &amp; Extractor</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.technocomsolutions.com/images/email-phone-extractor-files/img5.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 00:27:30 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Extracts email addresses and phone numbers from MS word Files (DOC, DOCX, DOT, DOTM, DOCM, DOTX, RTF, WPS, TXT). It works will Version of MS Word, Excel, Powerpoint, Text files &amp; RTF files like MS Office 2003, 2007, 2010, 2012, 2016 etc This tool extracts email addresses and phone numbers from PDF files and does not require Adobe Acrobat or extra tools. It extracts email addresses and phone numbers from Power Point Files (PPT, PPTX, POT, POTM, PPTM, POTX, PPSM, PPSX, PPS, PPAM, PPA). Software extracts email addresses and phone numbers from MS- Excel files (XLS, XLSX, XLSM, XLTX, XLT, XLA) Email and Phone Extractor Files is the Best tool for Online Marketing. It can extract email addresses and phone numbers from multiple files in one click. Extracts email addresses and phone numbers from all the folders and sub folders. Email and Phone Extractor Files is very fast and efficient tool to extract email addresses and phone numbers from various files in matter of minutes. It can save extracted email addresses and phone numbers in Excel CSV and TXT formats which can be opened in various Databases and Excel. Email and Phone Extractor Files is great Email and number Extracting tool and is cheapest &amp; best software available on the inte.com.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Extracts email addresses and phone numbers from MS word Files (DOC, DOCX, DOT, DOTM, DOCM, DOTX, RTF, WPS, TXT).<br /></li><li> It works will Version of MS Word, Excel, Powerpoint, Text files & RTF files like MS Office 2003, 2007, 2010, 2012, 2016 etc<br /></li><li> This tool extracts email addresses and phone numbers from PDF files and does not require Adobe Acrobat or extra tools.<br /></li><li> It extracts email addresses and phone numbers from Power Point Files (PPT, PPTX, POT, POTM, PPTM, POTX, PPSM, PPSX, PPS, PPAM, PPA).<br /></li><li> Software extracts email addresses and phone numbers from MS- Excel files (XLS, XLSX, XLSM, XLTX, XLT, XLA)<br /></li><li> Email and Phone Extractor Files is the Best tool for Online Marketing.<br /></li><li> It can extract email addresses and phone numbers from multiple files in one click.<br /></li><li> Extracts email addresses and phone numbers from all the folders and sub folders.<br /></li><li> Email and Phone Extractor Files is very fast and efficient tool to extract email addresses and phone numbers from various files in matter of minutes.<br /></li><li> It can save extracted email addresses and phone numbers in Excel CSV and TXT formats which can be opened in various Databases and Excel.<br /></li><li> Email and Phone Extractor Files is great Email and number Extracting tool and is cheapest & best software available on the inte.com.<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://www.technocomsolutions.com/images/email-phone-extractor-files/img5.png" alt="Email and Phone Extractor Files 5.2.6.32 " title="Email and Phone Extractor Files 5.2.6.32 "  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Email and Phone Extractor Files 5.2.6.32 " title="Email and Phone Extractor Files 5.2.6.32 "  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>