<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Sound Marketing - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Sound Marketing - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>Soundcloud Manager 3.422</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/930-soundcloud-manager.html</link>
<description>Name : Soundcloud Manager by RootJazz Version : 3.422 OS : Windows Type : Social Marketing, SoundCloud Marketing Price : $97 Homepage : SalePage SoundcloudManager makes it easy to get your music heard above the rest. From track sharing, to initialising interactions with other users, to finding users interested in your music styles. SoundcloudManager gets you REAL followers, REAL likes, REAL comments, REAL plays and REAL reposts</description>
<category>Sound Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 12:56:40 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Increase Soundcloud plays Increase Soundcloud downloads Follow users Multi account follow Bulk create accounts Search and favourite tracks Search and repost tracks (Unique) Bulk Create playlists (Unique) Mass increase track favourites Mass increase track comments Mass increase user followings Mass increase Track Reposts (Unique) Share tracks to users and groups Comment on tracks</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/yfeGtyPpEiE?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><br><ul><li> Increase Soundcloud plays<br></li><li> Increase Soundcloud downloads<br></li><li> Follow users<br></li><li> Multi account follow<br></li><li> Bulk create accounts<br></li><li> Search and favourite tracks<br></li><li> Search and repost tracks (Unique)<br></li><li> Bulk Create playlists (Unique)<br></li><li> Mass increase track favourites<br></li><li> Mass increase track comments<br></li><li> Mass increase user followings<br></li><li> Mass increase Track Reposts (Unique)<br></li><li> Share tracks to users and groups<br></li><li> Comment on tracks<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Soundcloud Manager 3.422"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Adobe Audition CC 2018 v11.1.1.3</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4489-adobe-audition.html</link>
<description>Name : Adobe Audition CC 2018 Version : v11.1.1.3 OS : Windows Type : Sound Creator Price : $120 Homepage : SalePage Audition CC is a comprehensive toolset that includes multitrack, waveform, and spectral display for creating, mixing, editing, and restoring audio content. This powerful audio workstation is designed to accelerate video production workflows and audio finishing — and deliver a polished mix with pristine sound</description>
<category>Sound Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 12 May 2018 05:46:43 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features What is Audition CC? Meet the industry’s best audio cleanup, restoration, and precision editing tool for video, podcasting, and sound effect design. Record, edit, and integrate music clips. This step-by-step tutorial guides you through the robust audio toolkit that is Adobe Audition, including its seamless workflow with Adobe Premiere Pro CC. Add oomph to your audio. Use the Essential Sound panel to achieve professional-quality audio — even if you’re not a professional.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/_0OZPx4FyD4?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> What is Audition CC?<br></li><li> Meet the industry’s best audio cleanup, restoration, and precision editing tool for video, podcasting, and sound effect design. <br></li><li> Record, edit, and integrate music clips. <br></li><li> This step-by-step tutorial guides you through the robust audio toolkit that is Adobe Audition, including its seamless workflow with Adobe Premiere Pro CC.<br></li><li> Add oomph to your audio.<br></li><li> Use the Essential Sound panel to achieve professional-quality audio — even if you’re not a professional.<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Adobe Audition CC 2018 v11.1.1.3"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Cockos REAPER 5.78</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4058-cockos-reaper.html</link>
<description>Name : Cockos REAPER Version : 5.78 OS : Windows Type : Digital Audio Production Application for Windows and OS Price : $19.99 Homepage : SalePage REAPER is a complete digital audio production application for Windows and OS X, offering a full multitrack audio and MIDI recording, editing, processing, mixing and mastering toolset. REAPER supports a vast range of hardware, digital formats and plugins, and can be comprehensively extended, scripted and modified.</description>
<category>Sound Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 06:41:03 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Efficient, fast to load, and tightly coded. Can be installed and run from a portable or.comwork drive. Powerful audio and MIDI routing with multichannel support throughout. 64-bit internal audio processing. Import, record to, and render to many media formats, at almost any bit depth and sample rate. Thorough MIDI hardware and software support. Support for thousands of third-party plug-in effects and virtual instruments, including VST, VST3, AU, DX, and JS. Hundreds of studio-quality effects for processing audio and MIDI, and built-in tools for creating new effects. Automation, modulation, grouping, VCA, surround, macros, OSC, scripting, control surfaces, custom skins and layouts. A whole lot more.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Efficient, fast to load, and tightly coded. Can be installed and run from a portable or.comwork drive.<br></li><li> Powerful audio and MIDI routing with multichannel support throughout.<br></li><li> 64-bit internal audio processing. Import, record to, and render to many media formats, at almost any bit depth and sample rate.<br></li><li> Thorough MIDI hardware and software support.<br></li><li> Support for thousands of third-party plug-in effects and virtual instruments, including VST, VST3, AU, DX, and JS.<br></li><li> Hundreds of studio-quality effects for processing audio and MIDI, and built-in tools for creating new effects.<br></li><li> Automation, modulation, grouping, VCA, surround, macros, OSC, scripting, control surfaces, custom skins and layouts.<br></li><li> A whole lot more.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Cockos REAPER 5.78"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Acoustica Premium 7.0.56</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3934-acoustica-premium.html</link>
<description>Name : Acoustica Premium Version : 7.0.56 OS : Windows Type : State-of-the-art Audio Resolutions Price : $200 Homepage : SalePage Re-implemented from scratch for the highest quality demands and cross-platform support, Acoustica 7 is now the perfect tool for editing, mastering and restoration work on both Mac and PC (32 and 64 bit). The brand new user interface comes with a modern dark theme and appears crystal sharp on retina style displays. Acoustica 7 is available in a Premium Edition and a feature limited Standard Edition.</description>
<category>Sound Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 06:40:45 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Acoustica offers support for state-of-the-art audio resolutions up to 32 bit and sampling rates up to 384 kHz, ensuring that all of your work comes across at the highest quality. Acoustica Premium Edition even supports multichannel audio recording and editing such as 5.1 and 7.1 surround sound. The new spectral editing mode in Acoustica Premium Edition 7 allows precise restoration work since processing can be limited to isolated regions in time and frequency. Selection tools such as brush, freehand or magic wand are available. The retouch tool removes noise based on a freely selectable reference from the surrounding audio. High quality processing tools ranging from a new suite of dynamic processing tools to EQ and effects like reverb and chorus are integrated along with sample rate conversion, time stretching and pitch shifting. You can create chains of audio processors and apply or store them for later use. A powerful batch processor is included and VST, VST3 and AU (Mac only) plug-ins are supported. Integrated audio restoration tools help you get the most out of recordings impaired by background noise, clicks, crackle, clipping or missing high frequency content. The Premium Edition contains the same set of professional tools as our Restoration Suite. Mix audio from different tracks in real-time, insert audio effects or create cross-fades easily in multitrack sessions. You can loop or time stretch clips directly from the multitrack timeline and automate volume, pan and send levels. Analysis tools such as spectrum, spectrogram and wavelet analysis are available. Real-time analyzers visualize your audio output (EBU R-128 loudness, level, spectral and phase correlation).</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Ymub9-YF2kw?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Acoustica offers support for state-of-the-art audio resolutions up to 32 bit and sampling rates up to 384 kHz, ensuring that all of your work comes across at the highest quality. Acoustica Premium Edition even supports multichannel audio recording and editing such as 5.1 and 7.1 surround sound.<br></li><li> The new spectral editing mode in Acoustica Premium Edition 7 allows precise restoration work since processing can be limited to isolated regions in time and frequency. Selection tools such as brush, freehand or magic wand are available. The retouch tool removes noise based on a freely selectable reference from the surrounding audio.<br></li><li> High quality processing tools ranging from a new suite of dynamic processing tools to EQ and effects like reverb and chorus are integrated along with sample rate conversion, time stretching and pitch shifting. You can create chains of audio processors and apply or store them for later use. A powerful batch processor is included and VST, VST3 and AU (Mac only) plug-ins are supported.<br></li><li> Integrated audio restoration tools help you get the most out of recordings impaired by background noise, clicks, crackle, clipping or missing high frequency content. The Premium Edition contains the same set of professional tools as our Restoration Suite.<br></li><li> Mix audio from different tracks in real-time, insert audio effects or create cross-fades easily in multitrack sessions. You can loop or time stretch clips directly from the multitrack timeline and automate volume, pan and send levels.<br></li><li> Analysis tools such as spectrum, spectrogram and wavelet analysis are available. Real-time analyzers visualize your audio output (EBU R-128 loudness, level, spectral and phase correlation).<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Acoustica Premium 7.0.56 "><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>SoundCloud Automator 3.0.3.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/929-soundcloud-automator.html</link>
<description>Name : SoundCloud Automator Version : 3.0.3.0 OS : Windows Type : Social Marketing, SoundCloud Marketing Price : $77 SoundCloudAutomator is the industry&#039;s most advanced Soundcloud bot to systematically grow your Soundcloud audience. Works by automating the tasks you normally do on Soundcloud: following users, unfollowing users, commenting, messaging users, playing tracks and other features that will greatly enhance your exposure on Soundcloud. SoundCloudAutomator allows you to follow and unfollow users automatically which leads to many people following you back and you retaining followers interested in your music. This is a great way to get organic followers and to gain quick exposure. Don&#039;t worry about following users you&#039;ve already followed, SoundCloudAutomator remembers what you&#039;ve done and avoids duplicating. With the built-in proxy scraper you don&#039;t have to worry about buying proxies again, SoundCloudAutomator downloads fresh proxies for you which you can use to increase your play/download count. Increasing plays gets you higher in the Soundcloud search results and therefore gives rise to more additional plays and more exposure! Mass message/comment - you can message your followers and comment your tracks. Our mass message tool supports spinning functionality so no two messages will be exactly the same! SoundCloudAutomator remembers users already messaged and does not send duplicate messages. Share/Unshare tracks to group enables you to automatically share your tracks with any groups you have joined. You can share to 75 groups with a paid Soundcloud account.</description>
<category>Sound Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://xorbots.com/images/soundcloudautomator.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2017 21:31:52 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Free lifetime automatic update One time purchase, no monthly fees Easy to use layout 24/ customer support Instant download Video tutorials Enhanced winsock technology Multi-Threading that further speeds up Multiple account support Proxy support with built-in downloader CAPTCHA support Delay functionality User-Agent changer Mass follow/unfollow tool Track plays increaser Track downloads increaser Mass message tool with spinning capability Mass track commenter with spinning capability Mass share/unshare tracks to groups Internal database of already followed/messaged users Account checker Account statistics User scraper from search, followers, following and group members Track scraper from search, user tracks, group contributions Group scraper from search results Mass follower from group members, user followers or provided list Mass unfollower tool with option to keep those following back Mass track liker Mass track unliker Mass track reposter/unreposter Soundcloud track uploader Group joiner Mass group poster MAC OS X 10.5 or later support Mass message sender :::Free Members ::: Download Now Password : www.tgmember.com :::ViP Only:::</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/HMRpf6zs_xg?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" gesture="media" allow="encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Free lifetime automatic update<br></li><li> One time purchase, no monthly fees<br></li><li> Easy to use layout<br></li><li> 24/ customer support<br></li><li> Instant download<br></li><li> Video tutorials<br></li><li> Enhanced winsock technology<br></li><li> Multi-Threading that further speeds up<br></li><li> Multiple account support<br></li><li> Proxy support with built-in downloader<br></li><li> CAPTCHA support<br></li><li> Delay functionality<br></li><li> User-Agent changer<br></li><li> Mass follow/unfollow tool<br></li><li> Track plays increaser<br></li><li> Track downloads increaser<br></li><li> Mass message tool with spinning capability<br></li><li> Mass track commenter with spinning capability<br></li><li> Mass share/unshare tracks to groups<br></li><li> Internal database of already followed/messaged users<br></li><li> Account checker<br></li><li> Account statistics<br></li><li> User scraper from search, followers, following and group members<br></li><li> Track scraper from search, user tracks, group contributions<br></li><li> Group scraper from search results<br></li><li> Mass follower from group members, user followers or provided list<br></li><li> Mass unfollower tool with option to keep those following back<br></li><li> Mass track liker<br></li><li> Mass track unliker<br></li><li> Mass track reposter/unreposter<br></li><li> Soundcloud track uploader<br></li><li> Group joiner<br></li><li> Mass group poster<br></li><li> MAC OS X 10.5 or later support<br></li><li> Mass message sender<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://xorbots.com/images/soundcloudautomator.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="SoundCloud Automator 3.0.3.0"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><span style="font-size:12pt;"><b><span style="color:#006600">:::Free Members  :::</span></b></span><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><a href="http://31.220.48.156/engine/go.php?url=aHR0cDovL3VzZXJzZmlsZXMuY29tL2V5dnU5cXh4ZzU1OA%3D%3D"  target="_blank">Download Now</a><br>Password : www.tgmember.com<br></div><br></div><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><span style="font-size:12pt;"><b><span style="color:#FF0000">:::ViP Only:::</span></b></span><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Reverbnation Bot 1.406</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/919-reverbnation-bot.html</link>
<description>Name : Reverbnation Bot by RootJazz Version : 1.406 OS : Windows Type : Reverbnation Marketing Tools, Sound Marketing Tools Price : $97 Homepage : SalePage The Ultimate Reverbnation Automation Bot , increase plays, video plays, widget views, chart positions, likes, favourites, comments and more Reverbnation is one of the original music based social.comworks. Reverbnation charts are a respected metric in the music industry. Rank well in these charts and your music must be a high quality. Chart positions are based on many metrics, but one of the most valued is tracks listened to by other Reverbnation users. Create an army of Reverbnation accounts then pass these through the proxies the Reverbnation Bot from Rootjazz can scrape in order to storm up the charts. Engage new fans, find new users, encourage users / fans / artists to check our your music via tried and tested techniques. Search and follow users (a % will check out your tracks and follow you back), search and Like tracks ( a % will check your tracks out and interact with your account), search and comment for direct interaction with other users.</description>
<category>Sound Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2017 19:05:31 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Increase Track Plays Increase Widget Views Increase Video plays Increase Page Views Search and Become Fan with welcome message Mass Fan Search and follow Automatic Liking Search and Like Ask Questions Search and Comment Mass Comments Mass Follows Mass Likes / Mass Favourites Account creation and automatic email verification Manage an unlimited amount of accounts Account Verification Account management and updating Scrape content lists of users tracks Scrape profile details of users Scrape email details of artists from a list Fully socket implemented. No webbrowser / WYSIWYG bot here. This is a lean, mean fighting machine Increase your chart rankings by manipulating your plays / likes / comments Proxy scraper Proxy verification Auto content spinning control Full Spintax support Control all aspects of the application via Settings Schedule all actions for Drip Feeding potential. Time delay between actions for increased realism Repeat all actions for continual chart ranking Frequent updates Good quality support via multiple systems Full Captcha API support All processes are stored so can be restarted in case of power failure Detailed logs of all processes Import/Export features for profiles, proxies. It is your data to take and do what you want with Redo / retry / pause / cancel any action</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/CzSyvMV6PnM?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><p></p><br><h3>Features</h3><br><p><br><ul><li> Increase Track Plays<br></li><li> Increase Widget Views<br></li><li> Increase Video plays<br></li><li> Increase Page Views<br></li><li> Search and Become Fan with welcome message<br></li><li> Mass Fan<br></li><li> Search and follow<br></li><li> Automatic Liking<br></li><li> Search and Like<br></li><li> Ask Questions<br></li><li> Search and Comment<br></li><li> Mass Comments<br></li><li> Mass Follows<br></li><li> Mass Likes / Mass Favourites<br></li><li> Account creation and automatic email verification<br></li><li> Manage an unlimited amount of accounts<br></li><li> Account Verification<br></li><li> Account management and updating<br></li><li> Scrape content lists of users tracks<br></li><li> Scrape profile details of users<br></li><li> Scrape email details of artists from a list<br></li><li> Fully socket implemented. No webbrowser / WYSIWYG bot here. This is a lean, mean fighting machine<br></li><li> Increase your chart rankings by manipulating your plays / likes / comments<br></li><li> Proxy scraper<br></li><li> Proxy verification<br></li><li> Auto content spinning control<br></li><li> Full Spintax support<br></li><li> Control all aspects of the application via Settings<br></li><li> Schedule all actions for Drip Feeding potential.<br></li><li> Time delay between actions for increased realism<br></li><li> Repeat all actions for continual chart ranking<br></li><li> Frequent updates<br></li><li> Good quality support via multiple systems<br></li><li> Full Captcha API support<br></li><li> All processes are stored so can be restarted in case of power failure<br></li><li> Detailed logs of all processes<br></li><li> Import/Export features for profiles, proxies. It is your data to take and do what you want with<br></li><li> Redo / retry / pause / cancel any action<br><br></li></ul></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Reverbnation Bot 1.406"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Cakewalk SONAR Platinum 23.8.0.30 Rebuild 2</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2127-cakewalk-sonar.html</link>
<description>Name : Cakewalk SONAR Platinum + Plugins + Content Version : 23.8.0.30 Rebuild 2 OS : Windows Type : Music Creator Price : $499 Homepage : SalePage SONAR: Craft your masterpiece Fueled by over 25 years in the relentless pursuit of innovation, SONAR is re-inventing the modern recording studio. The most complete music production package The creative experience only SONAR offers: advanced technology, effortless workflow, and an interface that amplifies inspiration.</description>
<category>Sound Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://static.cakewalk.com/cakewalk/products/sonar-2016/overview/03_Instruments/SONAR-Instruments-Drums.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 16:35:41 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features SONGWRITING FEATURES Get Started Quickly : Track templates, screensets, matrix view, step sequencers, and more let you focus on music as soon as SONAR boots Compose!Score your music with SONAR’s integrated staff view - ideal for songwriters and composers New Piano Roll View : SONAR’s new, improved, and powerful PRV streamlines creating and editing MIDI sequences We bring the band : No band? No problem. Count on SONAR to fill out your tracks with an impressive suite of virtual instruments Social media sharing : Use SoundCloud integration to share your music on Facebook, Twitter, and other social media sites Sing your instrument parts : Hum, whistle or sing into SONAR - then use Melodyne&#039;s audio-to-MIDI function to convert your melodies into instrument parts GUITAR FEATURES Overloud TH2 Amps : Plug in to exclusive virtual rigs - and take your guitar anywhere, from sparkly clean to high-gain madness Strum Acoustic Session : Accompany yourself as SONAR triggers realistically strummed acoustic guitar parts Blue Tubes Valve Driver : Add character, warmth, and serious mojo with vintage tube amp saturation effects Comp the perfect solo : SONAR re-invents comping with the fastest, most efficient way to transform multiple performances into a perfect composite track Chord Chart &amp;amp; Tab : Notate, compose, or print music with standard notation staff view and guitar tab - perfect for guitar students and teachers YouTube Export : Export your songs and performances directly from SONAR to today’s #1 music delivery medium VOCAL FEATURES VocalSync : Quickly align and tighten multiple vocal takes - whether doubled vocals, background vocals, or ADR for film Melodyne Essential : The world&#039;s leading pitch correction software integrates seamlessly with SONAR, thanks to ARA protocol support Take Lanes &amp;amp; Comping : SONAR re-invents comping with the fastest, most efficient way to transform multiple performances into a perfect composite track REmatrix Solo : Convolution technology flatters your vocals with lush, super-realistic Hall, Room, Plate, and other reverb effects PC76 U-Type Compressor : Experience lightning-fast vocal dynamics control with this accurate model of iconic FET-based compression VX-64 Vocal Strip : Polish vocals with one-stop dynamics, de-essing, EQ, doubling, saturation, and frequency-selective delay DRUM FEATURES Addictive Drums 2 : The world&#039;s finest drum kits, percussion instruments, and patterns (included in Professional/Platinum versions) Session Drummer 3 : This drummer shows up on time, never misses a beat, and brings high quality kits from Roland, Steven Slate, and more Step Sequencer : From hip-hop to hardcore, make body-shaking beats in minutes - with options for deep editing and “humanization” PX-64 Percussion Strip : One-stop drum processing with EQ, dynamics, transient shaping, saturation, and delay PC4K Bus Compressor : &quot;Glue&quot; your kit’s audio tracks together with this meticulously modeled classic bus compressor TS-64 Transient Shaper : Go beyond conventional dynamics for larger-than-life sounds - from cracking snares to ultra-powerful kicks MIXING FEATURES Skylight Interface : Combining beauty, brains, and efficiency, this award-winning interface makes serious recording fun again Mix Recall : Never second-guess a mix again: switch among multiple saved mixes for easy, one-click comparisons ProChannel : Experience that big analog sound - and even create your own mixer architecture - with customizable channel strips 64-bit Mix engine : Record your performances with utmost precision using SONAR&#039;s brilliant 64-bit audio engine. Expandable Sends &amp;amp; FX : See the big picture, and add as many sends or FX as your screen resolution can handle Direct Stream Digital (DSD) : SONAR now supports DSD, a high definition 1-bit audio format commonly used to archive masters in high resolution PRODUCING FEATURES Dynamic Control Bar : From compact laptop to multiple monitors, SONAR’s revamped Control Bar gives instant access to your go-to functions New Pattern Tool : Save time and speed workflow by “painting” MIDI loops and patterns across the PRV and Track View AudioSnap : Revamped with new a look and algorithm, AudioSnap performs timing and tempo tweaking in style Tone2 Bifilter2 : This sound designer’s dream offers a mind-boggling 47 unique filter types and 8 different distortion models Matrix View : Remix on the fly, try different arrangements, and even capture everything in track view - never lose your inspirations Step Sequencer : From hip-hop to hardcore, make body-shaking beats in minutes - with options for deep editing and “humanization”</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/0DGlHM8TT7s?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br>SONGWRITING FEATURES<br><ul><li> Get Started Quickly : Track templates, screensets, matrix view, step sequencers, and more let you focus on music as soon as SONAR boots<br></li><li> Compose!Score your music with SONAR’s integrated staff view - ideal for songwriters and composers<br></li><li> New Piano Roll View : SONAR’s new, improved, and powerful PRV streamlines creating and editing MIDI sequences<br></li><li> We bring the band : No band? No problem. Count on SONAR to fill out your tracks with an impressive suite of virtual instruments<br></li><li> Social media sharing : Use SoundCloud integration to share your music on Facebook, Twitter, and other social media sites<br></li><li> Sing your instrument parts : Hum, whistle or sing into SONAR - then use Melodyne's audio-to-MIDI function to convert your melodies into instrument parts<br></li></ul><br><br>GUITAR FEATURES<br><ul><li> Overloud TH2 Amps : Plug in to exclusive virtual rigs - and take your guitar anywhere, from sparkly clean to high-gain madness<br></li><li> Strum Acoustic Session : Accompany yourself as SONAR triggers realistically strummed acoustic guitar parts<br></li><li> Blue Tubes Valve Driver : Add character, warmth, and serious mojo with vintage tube amp saturation effects<br></li><li> Comp the perfect solo : SONAR re-invents comping with the fastest, most efficient way to transform multiple performances into a perfect composite track<br></li><li> Chord Chart &amp; Tab : Notate, compose, or print music with standard notation staff view and guitar tab - perfect for guitar students and teachers<br></li><li> YouTube Export : Export your songs and performances directly from SONAR to today’s #1 music delivery medium<br></li></ul><br><br>VOCAL FEATURES<br><ul><li> VocalSync : Quickly align and tighten multiple vocal takes - whether doubled vocals, background vocals, or ADR for film<br></li><li> Melodyne Essential : The world's leading pitch correction software integrates seamlessly with SONAR, thanks to ARA protocol support<br></li><li> Take Lanes &amp; Comping : SONAR re-invents comping with the fastest, most efficient way to transform multiple performances into a perfect composite track<br></li><li> REmatrix Solo : Convolution technology flatters your vocals with lush, super-realistic Hall, Room, Plate, and other reverb effects<br></li><li> PC76 U-Type Compressor : Experience lightning-fast vocal dynamics control with this accurate model of iconic FET-based compression<br></li><li> VX-64 Vocal Strip : Polish vocals with one-stop dynamics, de-essing, EQ, doubling, saturation, and frequency-selective delay<br></li></ul><br><br>DRUM FEATURES<br><ul><li> Addictive Drums 2 : The world's finest drum kits, percussion instruments, and patterns (included in Professional/Platinum versions)<br></li><li> Session Drummer 3 : This drummer shows up on time, never misses a beat, and brings high quality kits from Roland, Steven Slate, and more<br></li><li> Step Sequencer : From hip-hop to hardcore, make body-shaking beats in minutes - with options for deep editing and “humanization”<br></li><li> PX-64 Percussion Strip : One-stop drum processing with EQ, dynamics, transient shaping, saturation, and delay<br></li><li> PC4K Bus Compressor : "Glue" your kit’s audio tracks together with this meticulously modeled classic bus compressor<br></li><li> TS-64 Transient Shaper : Go beyond conventional dynamics for larger-than-life sounds - from cracking snares to ultra-powerful kicks<br></li></ul><br><br>MIXING FEATURES<br><ul><li> Skylight Interface : Combining beauty, brains, and efficiency, this award-winning interface makes serious recording fun again<br></li><li> Mix Recall : Never second-guess a mix again: switch among multiple saved mixes for easy, one-click comparisons<br></li><li> ProChannel : Experience that big analog sound - and even create your own mixer architecture - with customizable channel strips<br></li><li> 64-bit Mix engine : Record your performances with utmost precision using SONAR's brilliant 64-bit audio engine.<br></li><li> Expandable Sends &amp; FX : See the big picture, and add as many sends or FX as your screen resolution can handle<br></li><li> Direct Stream Digital (DSD) : SONAR now supports DSD, a high definition 1-bit audio format commonly used to archive masters in high resolution<br></li></ul><br><br>PRODUCING FEATURES<br><ul><li> Dynamic Control Bar :  From compact laptop to multiple monitors, SONAR’s revamped Control Bar gives instant access to your go-to functions<br></li><li> New Pattern Tool :  Save time and speed workflow by “painting” MIDI loops and patterns across the PRV and Track View<br></li><li> AudioSnap : Revamped with new a look and algorithm, AudioSnap performs timing and tempo tweaking in style<br></li><li> Tone2 Bifilter2 : This sound designer’s dream offers a mind-boggling 47 unique filter types and 8 different distortion models<br></li><li> Matrix View : Remix on the fly, try different arrangements, and even capture everything in track view - never lose your inspirations<br></li><li> Step Sequencer : From hip-hop to hardcore, make body-shaking beats in minutes - with options for deep editing and “humanization”<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://static.cakewalk.com/cakewalk/products/sonar-2016/overview/03_Instruments/SONAR-Instruments-Drums.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Cakewalk SONAR Platinum 23.8.0.30 Rebuild 2"><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>MAGIX Music Maker Premium 24.1.5.119</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2119-magix-music-maker-2017-premium.html</link>
<description>Name : MAGIX Music Maker 2017 Premium + Full VITA Instruments Collection+ Live Version : 24.1.5.119 OS : Windows Type : Music Creator Price : $129 Homepage : SalePage Music Maker Premium is a unique virtual studio with more than 8,000 included sounds, intuitive drag &amp;amp; drop controls, countless instruments and professional functions for mixing &amp;amp; mastering.</description>
<category>Sound Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.magix.com/fileadmin/user_upload/Produkte/Musik/Music_Maker_2017/Classic/KA2/grafik-982-gui-123-music-maker-2017-update-int.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 21:55:43 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features All features, instruments and sounds in Music Maker and Music Maker Live More than 8,000 Sounds &amp;amp; Loops 12 Soundpools for popular music genres like Dubstep, Trap and many more Exclusive premium instruments: Cinematic Soundscapes, Choir Church Organ MIDI Editor with piano roll Mastering Suite with Auto Mastering Unlimited number of tracks</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/QfeWoNrSTZ8?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> All features, instruments and sounds in Music Maker and Music Maker Live <br></li><li> More than 8,000 Sounds &amp; Loops <br></li><li> 12 Soundpools for popular music genres like Dubstep, Trap and many more <br></li><li> Exclusive premium instruments: Cinematic Soundscapes, Choir Church Organ <br></li><li> MIDI Editor with piano roll <br></li><li> Mastering Suite with Auto Mastering <br></li><li> Unlimited number of tracks<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://www.magix.com/fileadmin/user_upload/Produkte/Musik/Music_Maker_2017/Classic/KA2/grafik-982-gui-123-music-maker-2017-update-int.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt="MAGIX Music Maker Premium 24.1.5.119"><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>MAGIX Audio &amp; Music Lab 2017 Premium 22.1.0.38</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2130-magix-audio-music-lab-premium.html</link>
<description>Name : MAGIX Audio &amp; Music Lab 2017 Premium Version : 22.1.0.38 OS : Windows Type : Music Creator Price : $99 Homepage : SalePage PROFESSIONAL SOUND FOR MUSIC &amp; VIDEO. Discover professional audio editing for all your music and video projects. Edit, optimize and play recordings in top quality with Audio &amp; Music Lab Premium.</description>
<category>Sound Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.magix.com/fileadmin/user_upload/Produkte/Musik/Audio_Cleaning_Lab_2017/Audio_Music_Lab_2017_Premium/Detail/grafik-ts-455-schneller-fokussiert-spur-int.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 16:36:44 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Record in studio quality at up to 96 kHz/24-bit 6,000 current Inte.com radio stations Remove noise with 1-click solutions More than 360 presets for sound optimization Optimize video sound Audio &amp; video converter for all standard formats Tools for visual sound analysis Burn projects to CD &amp; DVD</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><div class="dlevideoplayer" style="width:100%;max-width:425px;"><ul data-theme="default" data-preload="metadata"><li data-title="" data-type="youtube" data-url="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=b6T9jRylDKo"></li></ul></div></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Record in studio quality at up to 96 kHz/24-bit <br /></li><li> 6,000 current Inte.com radio stations <br /></li><li> Remove noise with 1-click solutions <br /></li><li> More than 360 presets for sound optimization <br /></li><li> Optimize video sound Audio & video converter for all standard formats <br /></li><li> Tools for visual sound analysis <br /></li><li> Burn projects to CD & DVD<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://www.magix.com/fileadmin/user_upload/Produkte/Musik/Audio_Cleaning_Lab_2017/Audio_Music_Lab_2017_Premium/Detail/grafik-ts-455-schneller-fokussiert-spur-int.jpg" alt="MAGIX Audio &amp; Music Lab 2017 Premium 22.1.0.38" title="MAGIX Audio &amp; Music Lab 2017 Premium 22.1.0.38"  /><br /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="MAGIX Audio &amp; Music Lab 2017 Premium 22.1.0.38" title="MAGIX Audio &amp; Music Lab 2017 Premium 22.1.0.38"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>MixcloudFunked 1.403</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/906-mixcloudfunked.html</link>
<description>Name : MixcloudFunked by RootJazz Version : 1.403 , September 05,2016 OS : Windows Type : Social Marketing, Mixcloud Marketing Price : $67 Homepage : SalePage The Ultimate Mixcloud Automation bot, increase plays, follow, like, comment, account creation...</description>
<category>Sound Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2016 02:02:36 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Automatic Following Automatic Liking Automatic Track Commenting Automatic Profile Commenting Account creation Mixcloud Profile details / Email scraper Mixcloud List Scraper Manage an unlimited amount of accounts. Account Verification Fully socket implemented. No webbrowser / WYSIWYG bot here. MixcloudFunked is a lean, mean fighting machine Proxy scraper Proxy verification Full Spintax support Schedule all actions for Drip Feeding potential. Get your tracks trending by utilizing our MASS features, Mass Like, Mass Profile Comments, Mass Track Comments Mass Follow. Use your accounts to create a social signalling web of likes / comments / follows. Time delay between actions to appear realistic Repeat all actions for constant promotions hands free! Frequent updates Good quality support via multiple systems Full Captcha API support All processes are stored so can be restarted in case of power failure Detailed logs of all processes Import / Export features for profiles, proxies. It is your data to take and do what you want with Redo / retry / pause / cancel any action</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/dizle6zi_D8?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Automatic Following<br /></li><li> Automatic Liking<br /></li><li> Automatic Track Commenting<br /></li><li> Automatic Profile Commenting<br /></li><li> Account creation<br /></li><li> Mixcloud Profile details / Email scraper<br /></li><li> Mixcloud List Scraper<br /></li><li> Manage an unlimited amount of accounts.<br /></li><li> Account Verification<br /></li><li> Fully socket implemented. No webbrowser / WYSIWYG bot here. MixcloudFunked is a lean, mean fighting machine<br /></li><li> Proxy scraper<br /></li><li> Proxy verification<br /></li><li> Full Spintax support<br /></li><li> Schedule all actions for Drip Feeding potential.<br /></li><li> Get your tracks trending by utilizing our MASS features, Mass Like, Mass Profile Comments, Mass Track Comments Mass Follow. Use your accounts to create a social signalling web of likes / comments / follows.<br /></li><li> Time delay between actions to appear realistic<br /></li><li> Repeat all actions for constant promotions hands free!<br /></li><li> Frequent updates<br /></li><li> Good quality support via multiple systems<br /></li><li> Full Captcha API support<br /></li><li> All processes are stored so can be restarted in case of power failure<br /></li><li> Detailed logs of all processes<br /></li><li> Import / Export features for profiles, proxies. It is your data to take and do what you want with<br /></li><li> Redo / retry / pause / cancel any action<br /><br /></li></ul><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="MixcloudFunked 1.403" title="MixcloudFunked 1.403"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>