<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Plagiarism Checker - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Plagiarism Checker - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>SEO Plagiarism Checker 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4236-seo-plagiarism-checker.html</link>
<description>Name : SEO Plagiarism Checker Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : SEO Tools Price : $50 Homepage : SalePage SEO Plagiarism Checker is a desktop tool that will crawl your website checking every page&#039;s content to see if that content is elsewhere on the inte.com.</description>
<category>Plagiarism Checker</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 06:18:51 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features If another website is stealing your websites content then this is one of the fastest ways you can be notified of it. There are several reasons plagiarism can damage your website... - SEO damage - Although Google has repeatedly said there is no &quot;Duplicate content penalty&quot;, it has said it will filter out duplicate content. Imagine how frustrating it would be if you spent weeks working on an article only to publish it and have someone else copy it, then request Google to index it on their website through Google webmaster tools before the Google bot found the article on your website. Your brand new amazing article may be filtered out of Google&#039;s search results. - Brand damage - If someone copies your content then claims it&#039;s theirs this can greatly damage your brand. How do you prove you wrote it if they copy it straight away before Google indexes it? - Free backlinks - If someone has quoted/cited your content this can often be a great opportunity to get a backlink by reaching out to them and asking them to link to your in return for allowing them to use your content.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ho7L18g2Pno?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> If another website is stealing your websites content then this is one of the fastest ways you can be notified of it. There are several reasons plagiarism can damage your website...<br></li><li> - SEO damage - Although Google has repeatedly said there is no "Duplicate content penalty", it has said it will filter out duplicate content. Imagine how frustrating it would be if you spent weeks working on an article only to publish it and have someone else copy it, then request Google to index it on their website through Google webmaster tools before the Google bot found the article on your website. Your brand new amazing article may be filtered out of Google's search results.<br></li><li> - Brand damage - If someone copies your content then claims it's theirs this can greatly damage your brand. How do you prove you wrote it if they copy it straight away before Google indexes it?<br></li><li> - Free backlinks - If someone has quoted/cited your content this can often be a great opportunity to get a backlink by reaching out to them and asking them to link to your in return for allowing them to use your content.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="SEO Plagiarism Checker 1.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Plagiarism Detector Pro 1.92</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4386-plagiarism-detector-pro.html</link>
<description>Name : Plagiarism Detector Pro Version : 1.0.92 OS : Windows Type : Software to Detect Plagiarism Price : $0 Homepage : SalePage Plagiarism Detector - is a Software to detect Plagiarism in online and offline documents: - Plagiarism Detector - is a Plagiarism Detection Software to check for Plagiarism in text documents. It is a fast and reliable Plagiarism Checker! - - Plagiarism Detector is a Microsoft Windows 10 (XP,Vista,7,8 etc.) desktop application to check sets of documents against the major search engines databases trying to locate the possible sources and define the exact amount of shared information. - - Plagiarism Detector&#039;s main task is the automated detection of digital plagiarism (that is unauthorized copy-paste of textual material) that originated from the world wide web. It was designed to use the biggest digital publicly open database in the world - that of the search engines. - - Plagiarism Detector has lots of features (see next page) that cover all possible situations when it comes to text comparison and search! - - Plagiarism Detector has won multiple Plagiarism Detection competitions in multiple countries. It has been recognized as one of the best available solutions for Plagiarism Detection and Prevention! - - Plagiarism Detector was built with KISS principle: structural complexity with functional simplicity!</description>
<category>Plagiarism Checker</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 08:11:33 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Plagiarism Detector honors your privacy: 1. Checked Documents do not leave your computer! 2. Reports are strictly private! 3. Checked Documents are not stored in any database! Plagiarism Detector works efficiently: 4. Works fast - less than 2 minutes per average document! 5. Your documents are checked immediately - no waiting in queue! 6. Checks are done against more than 7 billion on-line sources! Plagiarism Detector integrates easily with Microsoft products: 7. Microsoft WordPowerPoint &#039;single click&#039; plagiarism check. 8. Microsoft Word Integration. 9. Microsoft PowerPoint Integration. Plagiarism Detector has cool reporting capabilities: 10. State-of-art Advanced Report Viewer. 11. Extended Source Tracing Mechanism. 12. On-the-Fly Original to Source comparison with dynamic statistics. Plagiarism Detector supports multiple document formats: 11. *.pdf, *.doc, *.docx, *.html, *.txt, *.rtf, *.odt. 12. Microsoft Word versions from 2000 to 2017 (*.docx). 13. Microsoft PowerPoint versions from 2000 to 2017 (*.pptx). 14. Native PDF support - no 3rd party software required. 15. Multiple text extraction engines available to ensure correctness. 16. Automatic encoding detection. 17. Multiple encoding support for plain text documents. Plagiarism Detector has advanced functions: 18. 97% Effectiveness - No False Positives. 19. Automatic Reference Detection and processing. 20. Multiple documents processing. 21. Quotes detection algorithms. 22. PDF reports online converter. 23. Online Report Sharing. 24. Robust functions to run plagiarism checks easy and effective!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Plagiarism Detector honors your privacy:<br></li><li> 1. Checked Documents do not leave your computer!<br></li><li> 2. Reports are strictly private!<br></li><li> 3. Checked Documents are not stored in any database!<br></li><li> Plagiarism Detector works efficiently:<br></li><li> 4. Works fast - less than 2 minutes per average document!<br></li><li> 5. Your documents are checked immediately - no waiting in queue!<br></li><li> 6. Checks are done against more than 7 billion on-line sources!<br></li><li> Plagiarism Detector integrates easily with Microsoft products:<br></li><li> 7. Microsoft WordPowerPoint 'single click' plagiarism check.<br></li><li> 8. Microsoft Word Integration.<br></li><li> 9. Microsoft PowerPoint Integration.<br></li><li> Plagiarism Detector has cool reporting capabilities:<br></li><li> 10. State-of-art Advanced Report Viewer.<br></li><li> 11. Extended Source Tracing Mechanism.<br></li><li> 12. On-the-Fly Original to Source comparison with dynamic statistics.<br></li><li> Plagiarism Detector supports multiple document formats:<br></li><li> 11. *.pdf, *.doc, *.docx, *.html, *.txt, *.rtf, *.odt.<br></li><li> 12. Microsoft Word versions from 2000 to 2017 (*.docx).<br></li><li> 13. Microsoft PowerPoint versions from 2000 to 2017 (*.pptx).<br></li><li> 14. Native PDF support - no 3rd party software required.<br></li><li> 15. Multiple text extraction engines available to ensure correctness.<br></li><li> 16. Automatic encoding detection.<br></li><li> 17. Multiple encoding support for plain text documents. Plagiarism Detector has advanced functions:<br></li><li> 18. 97% Effectiveness - No False Positives.<br></li><li> 19. Automatic Reference Detection and processing.<br></li><li> 20. Multiple documents processing.<br></li><li> 21. Quotes detection algorithms.<br></li><li> 22. PDF reports online converter.<br></li><li> 23. Online Report Sharing.<br></li><li> 24. Robust functions to run plagiarism checks easy and effective!<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Plagiarism Detector Pro 1.92"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Plagiarism Checker X 2018 v6.0.6</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/913-plagiarism-checker-x.html</link>
<description>Name : Plagiarism Checker X Version : 2018 v6.0.6 OS : Windows Type : Keyword Reseach,Keyword Analyzer, SEO Competition Analysis Price : $50 Homepage : SalePage #1 Plagiarism Checker Plagiarism Checker X helps you detect plagiarism in your research papers, blogs, assignments, and websites. With higher speed and accuracy, you can easily check your document&#039;s authenticity in just a few seconds.</description>
<category>Plagiarism Checker</category>
<enclosure url="http://screenshots.en.sftcdn.com/en/scrn/3335000/3335528/543b7874baaadscr_1412966469-700x494.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 04:21:42 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Enhanced Compatibility : Plagiarism Checker X is designed to examine most popular file formats, including doc, docx, rtf, PDF, and plain text, and it is compatible with Windows 8, 7, Vista, and XP. Available in 7 Languages : No more language barriers for international users: Plagiarism Checker X is now available in English, Spanish, French, German, Italian, Dutch, and Portuguese. Used in 60+ Countries : People from more than 60 countries are enjoying the benefits of Plagiarism Checker X. Our clients are located in USA, UK, Canada, Indonesia, Germany, India, Malaysia and in many other countries. Online Plagiarism Detection : Plagiarism Checker X helps students, teachers, and professional researchers by checking plagiarism in their documents, quickly and accurately. Side By Side Comparison : You can compare two documents side by side to check for similarities. This feature highlights both original and alternate content wherever it finds duplicate. Bulk Search : Teachers have to check multiple assignments, a time-consuming and cumbersome task. With our Bulk Search feature, you can scan an entire batch of assignments in just one click. Blog/Webpage Checking : Web-content writers, bloggers, and publishers can use Plagiarism Checker X to analyze the quality of their online content in order to avoid the penalties by the search engines. Keyword Analyzer : If you are an SEO expert, you know the importance of keywords. Using this tool, you can now extract the keywords along with their occurrence and density ratio. Comprehensive Reports : Detailed and comprehensive HTML reporting is a hallmark of Plagiarism Checker X software. The reports are color-highlighted, indicating the level of plagiarism. Used by Leading Institutes : We value our customer experiences. The speed, accuracy, and easy user interface has made customers satisfied and loyal.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li>Enhanced Compatibility : Plagiarism Checker X is designed to examine most popular file formats, including doc, docx, rtf, PDF, and plain text, and it is compatible with Windows 8, 7, Vista, and XP.<br></li><li>Available in 7 Languages : No more language barriers for international users: Plagiarism Checker X is now available in English, Spanish, French, German, Italian, Dutch, and Portuguese.<br></li><li>Used in 60+ Countries : People from more than 60 countries are enjoying the benefits of Plagiarism Checker X. Our clients are located in USA, UK, Canada, Indonesia, Germany, India, Malaysia and in many other countries.<br></li><li>Online Plagiarism Detection :  Plagiarism Checker X helps students, teachers, and professional researchers by checking plagiarism in their documents, quickly and accurately.<br></li><li>Side By Side Comparison : You can compare two documents side by side to check for similarities. This feature highlights both original and alternate content wherever it finds duplicate.<br></li><li>Bulk Search : Teachers have to check multiple assignments, a time-consuming and cumbersome task. With our Bulk Search feature, you can scan an entire batch of assignments in just one click.<br></li><li>Blog/Webpage Checking : Web-content writers, bloggers, and publishers can use Plagiarism Checker X to analyze the quality of their online content in order to avoid the penalties by the search engines.<br></li><li>Keyword Analyzer : If you are an SEO expert, you know the importance of keywords. Using this tool, you can now extract the keywords along with their occurrence and density ratio.<br></li><li>Comprehensive Reports : Detailed and comprehensive HTML reporting is a hallmark of Plagiarism Checker X software. The reports are color-highlighted, indicating the level of plagiarism.<br></li><li>Used by Leading Institutes : We value our customer experiences. The speed, accuracy, and easy user interface has made customers satisfied and loyal.<br><br></li></ul><br><img src="http://screenshots.en.sftcdn.com/en/scrn/3335000/3335528/543b7874baaadscr_1412966469-700x494.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Plagiarism Checker X 2018 v6.0.6"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>AntiPlagiarism 4.52</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1922-antiplagiarism.html</link>
<description>Name : AntiPlagiarism.COM Version : 4.52 OS : Windows Type : Plagiarism Checker Tools Price : $20 Homepage : SalePage AntiPlagiarism.COM is the program for automated detection of digital plagiarism that originated from the world wide web. It&#039;s designed to use the biggest open database in the world - that of the search engines. Checked documents do not leave you computer. The application uses Google, Bing and other search engines.</description>
<category>Plagiarism Checker</category>
<enclosure url="http://antiplagiarism.com/images/screenshots/en/scr_text_editor2.JPG" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2017 00:20:52 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Determines the percentage of the uniqueness of the text. Shows non-unique phrases by marking it with different colours. Batch check. WebSite check. Advanced preferences. Multiple formats support: doc, docx, pdf, odt, html, txt, rtf. Predefined set of check preferences (Default, Express, Deep). Simple interface. Proxy lists support.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/7NpzYz41RPs?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Determines the percentage of the uniqueness of the text.<br></li><li> Shows non-unique phrases by marking it with different colours.<br></li><li> Batch check.<br></li><li> WebSite check.<br></li><li> Advanced preferences.<br></li><li> Multiple formats support: doc, docx, pdf, odt, html, txt, rtf.<br></li><li> Predefined set of check preferences (Default, Express, Deep).<br></li><li> Simple interface.<br></li><li> Proxy lists support.<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://antiplagiarism.com/images/screenshots/en/scr_text_editor2.JPG" style="max-width:100%;" alt="AntiPlagiarism 4.52"><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>NBridge Plagiarism Finder 4.00.05.915 Pro</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1959-nbridge-plagiarism-finder.html</link>
<description>Name : NBridge Plagiarism Finder Version : 4.00.05.915 Pro OS : Windows Type : Plagiarism Checker Price : $80 Homepage : SalePage NBridge Plagiarism Finder — Deep Anti-Copying Checker at Budget Prices Welcome to one of the best plagiarism checker tools online — NBridge Plagiarism Finder. Plagiarism Finder by NBridge offers quick detection of previously published exerts in texts. With the help of this application students can check their work before submission to ensure it will pass plagiarism checkers, and teachers&#039; job of finding copies becomes simpler. Cross-referencing allows lecturers to notice similar passages in assignments of a particular class or group. Being able to instantly identify unoriginal paragraphs is also a great assistance for researchers, journalists, and blog writers. Unintentional plagiarism may not be forgiven, and properly investigating a chosen topic is the responsibility of the writer. For publishers, running a swift check of submitted stories for plagiarism is a compulsory requirement to have a piece of mind. Copyright violation may become an expensive oversight. If you are seeking a cheap plagiarism checker, Nbridge Plagiarism Finder combines affordability with deep text analysis. It checks through more search engines and databases (including Google Books and Google Scholar), while being substantially more affordable than its analogues. Constant updates and cross-checking against its own unique database increase its ability to find duplicate content.</description>
<category>Plagiarism Checker</category>
<enclosure url="http://nbridge.com/images/plagiarism_finder_main_1.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2016 22:09:28 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Unlimited checks Detailed reports that can be saved Free lifetime technical support PDF and Webpage Scan Keywords counter Check multiple files at once Compare documents between themselves *Professional version is aimed to educational institutes, schools, colleges, universities, allowing users to compare several documents at the same time. It&#039;s a powerful plagiarism checker that offers deep investigation by small segments, cross referencing, and permits loading several files in a queue in bulk.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/QqtKTP1NDqM?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Unlimited checks<br /></li><li> Detailed reports that can be saved<br /></li><li> Free lifetime technical support<br /></li><li> PDF and Webpage Scan<br /></li><li> Keywords counter<br /></li><li> Check multiple files at once<br /></li><li> Compare documents between themselves<br /></li></ul><br />*Professional version is aimed to educational institutes, schools, colleges, universities, allowing users to compare several documents at the same time. It's a powerful plagiarism checker that offers deep investigation by small segments, cross referencing, and permits loading several files in a queue in bulk.<br /><br /><img src="http://nbridge.com/images/plagiarism_finder_main_1.png" alt="NBridge Plagiarism Finder 4.00.05.915 Pro" title="NBridge Plagiarism Finder 4.00.05.915 Pro"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="NBridge Plagiarism Finder 4.00.05.915 Pro" title="NBridge Plagiarism Finder 4.00.05.915 Pro"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Duplicate Sniper Pro 2.0.3</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1057-duplicate-sniper.html</link>
<description>Name : Duplicate Sniper Version : Pro 2.0.3 OS : Windows Type : Content Marketing Tools, Plagiarism Checker Tools Price : $47 Homepage : SalePage Make sure you have no duplicate content on your site. No-one wants duplicate content on their site, Google hates it! DuplicateSniper tells you if the content is safe or duplicate for publishing to your site, or it will check to see if someone is stealing your site content. You just need paste your content or input your url into the software, then click one button.</description>
<category>Plagiarism Checker</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2015 03:10:44 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Basic Search : Search the inte.com quickly to find the duplicate content, the result is normally about 90% correct. Deep Check : The program will make a deeper check than the normal duplicate content basic search and find 100% of the duplicate content or sites, and then show them to you. Check Url : You can just input your site url and the program will check to see if there is duplicate content or any website on the inte.com with content similar to the site you input. Bulk Check : Check your files to find which ones have duplicate content, and then you can select to delete duplicate files in your folder. Use Google to check Use Yahoo to check</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/OB7DlPrkqiA?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Basic Search : Search the inte.com quickly to find the duplicate content, the result is normally about 90% correct.<br /></li><li> Deep Check : The program will make a deeper check than the normal duplicate content basic search and find 100% of the duplicate content or sites, and then show them to you.<br /></li><li> Check Url : You can just input your site url and the program will check to see if there is duplicate content or any website on the inte.com with content similar to the site you input.<br /></li><li> Bulk Check : Check your files to find which ones have duplicate content, and then you can select to delete duplicate files in your folder. <br /></li><li> Use Google to check 	<br /></li><li> Use Yahoo to check<br /></li></ul><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Duplicate Sniper Pro 2.0.3" title="Duplicate Sniper Pro 2.0.3"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>