<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Misc - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Misc - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>Excel PowerUps Premium Suite 1.12.3</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4054-excel-powerups-premium-suite.html</link>
<description>Name : Excel PowerUps Premium Suite Version : 1.12.3 OS : Windows Type : Excel Power Up Price : $999 Homepage : SalePage Excel PowerUps has thousands of users worldwide. And why not? Extend the life of legacy versions of Excel you’ve already invested in without sacrificing the advancements of the new functions in the newest version of Excel. Get new groups of functions opening new capability doors for your worksheets.</description>
<category>Misc</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 06:41:03 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features The Text Analysis functions enable you to more easily work with text values to analyze, evaluate, search with regular expressions, and evaluate sentiment to help you quickly analyze and process large volumes of text or verbatim responses. The Randomizer functions give you new randomizing functions for random text, random name generation, random selections from lists or regions, and random outcomes based on likelihood. The Excel PowerUps Premium Suite includes more functions to identify the current user, handle many types of unit conversions, and more. Cool tools such as the Fuzzy Find and Replace tool make this a super useful add-in. The Field Validator functions are used to verify your data conforms to formatting standards for phone numbers, addresses, credit card numbers, email addresses, etc. Now you can more easily detect bad data or bogus entries from forms or other sources. The Web Assistant functions extend Excel to be &quot;web aware&quot;. Now you can work with online web services, work with XML using XPath, and even verify URLs and filepaths are valid. Create new dynamic worksheets from services and create new live reports. The Excel PowerUp functions add the new functions only available in Excel 2013 to your copy of Excel 2010, 2007, or 2003. Share more files across Excel 2013, 2010, 2007 and 2003 that use the newest functions.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> The Text Analysis functions enable you to more easily work with text values to analyze, evaluate, search with regular expressions, and evaluate sentiment to help you quickly analyze and process large volumes of text or verbatim responses.<br></li><li> The Randomizer functions give you new randomizing functions for random text, random name generation, random selections from lists or regions, and random outcomes based on likelihood.<br></li><li> The Excel PowerUps Premium Suite includes more functions to identify the current user, handle many types of unit conversions, and more. Cool tools such as the Fuzzy Find and Replace tool make this a super useful add-in.<br></li><li> The Field Validator functions are used to verify your data conforms to formatting standards for phone numbers, addresses, credit card numbers, email addresses, etc. Now you can more easily detect bad data or bogus entries from forms or other sources.<br></li><li> The Web Assistant functions extend Excel to be "web aware". Now you can work with online web services, work with XML using XPath, and even verify URLs and filepaths are valid. Create new dynamic worksheets from services and create new live reports.<br></li><li> The Excel PowerUp functions add the new functions only available in Excel 2013 to your copy of Excel 2010, 2007, or 2003. Share more files across Excel 2013, 2010, 2007 and 2003 that use the newest functions.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Excel PowerUps Premium Suite 1.12.3"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Visual Studio 2017 v15.6.5</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4256-visual-studio.html</link>
<description>Name : Visual Studio 2017 Version : 15.6.5 OS : Windows Type : App Development Price : $1000 Homepage : SalePage Unparalleled productivity for all developments, applications and platforms</description>
<category>Misc</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 06:41:03 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Quickly generate smarter applications New features, such as live architectural validation, help drive development operations (DevOps) earlier in the development process. And improvements to popular features such as code navigation, IntelliSense, refactoring, and code fixes save you time and effort, regardless of language or platform. . Detect and fix bugs sooner The entire debugging and testing experience has been enhanced to help you detect and resolve problems as early as possible. Features such as Live Unit Testing, exception helper programs, and click-through execution tighten your DevOps loop by reducing the chance of regression and immediately exposing the root cause of new bugs. Integrate with the cloud Built-in tools enable full integration with all your .COM and .COM Core applications, Azure applications, Azure Functions, Docker and Windows containers, and more. The experience is so well integrated that you&#039;ll feel like working inside an Azure data center. Collaborate effectively Manage your hosted team projects directly from any vendor, including Visual Studio Team Services, Team Foundation Server or GitHub. Or use the new Open Any Folder feature to immediately open and edit virtually any code file without associated formal project or solution. Provide quality mobile apps With advanced debug and profiling tools, as well as Xamarin&#039;s unit test generation capabilities, you can create, connect, and tune mobile apps for Android, iOS, and Windows faster and easier than ever before. You can also choose to develop mobile applications with Apache Cordova or generate cross-platform C ++ libraries. Raise the level of your language Visual Studio continues to invest in support for the latest programming language features. Whether with C #, Visual Basic, C ++, TypeScript, F #, or even third-party languages such as jаvascript and Python, you get first-class functionality support throughout the development experience. Develop your ideal IDE A brand new workload-based installer optimizes your installation to ensure you have everything you need and nothing to worry about. Optimized for performance Visual Studio includes a lot of performance improvements for the basic features you use every day. You&#039;ll also experience a significantly faster boot time, lower memory footprint, and a higher degree of responsiveness throughout the development cycle. Provide software faster With Visual Studio Team Services and Team Foundation Server, you can easily deliver software for any targeted platform. Extend DevOps processes to SQL Server using Redgate Data Tools and securely automate database deployments from Visual Studio. Xamarin Test Recorder and Xamarin Test Cloud allow you to test thousands of physical devices directly from the IDE. Stay one step ahead Take advantage of complementary access to training provided by leading partners, including Pluralsight and Opsgility, for professional and corporate clients. You will also have access to software licenses from selected partners, such as Parallels and SyncFusion</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Quickly generate smarter applications<br></li><li> New features, such as live architectural validation, help drive development operations (DevOps) earlier in the development process. And improvements to popular features such as code navigation, IntelliSense, refactoring, and code fixes save you time and effort, regardless of language or platform. .<br></li><li> Detect and fix bugs sooner<br></li><li> The entire debugging and testing experience has been enhanced to help you detect and resolve problems as early as possible. Features such as Live Unit Testing, exception helper programs, and click-through execution tighten your DevOps loop by reducing the chance of regression and immediately exposing the root cause of new bugs.<br></li><li> Integrate with the cloud<br></li><li> Built-in tools enable full integration with all your .COM and .COM Core applications, Azure applications, Azure Functions, Docker and Windows containers, and more. The experience is so well integrated that you'll feel like working inside an Azure data center.<br></li><li> Collaborate effectively<br></li><li> Manage your hosted team projects directly from any vendor, including Visual Studio Team Services, Team Foundation Server or GitHub. Or use the new Open Any Folder feature to immediately open and edit virtually any code file without associated formal project or solution.<br></li><li> Provide quality mobile apps<br></li><li> With advanced debug and profiling tools, as well as Xamarin's unit test generation capabilities, you can create, connect, and tune mobile apps for Android, iOS, and Windows faster and easier than ever before. You can also choose to develop mobile applications with Apache Cordova or generate cross-platform C ++ libraries.<br></li><li> Raise the level of your language<br></li><li> Visual Studio continues to invest in support for the latest programming language features. Whether with C #, Visual Basic, C ++, TypeScript, F #, or even third-party languages such as jаvascript and Python, you get first-class functionality support throughout the development experience.<br></li><li> Develop your ideal IDE<br></li><li> A brand new workload-based installer optimizes your installation to ensure you have everything you need and nothing to worry about.<br></li><li> Optimized for performance<br></li><li> Visual Studio includes a lot of performance improvements for the basic features you use every day. You'll also experience a significantly faster boot time, lower memory footprint, and a higher degree of responsiveness throughout the development cycle.<br></li><li> Provide software faster<br></li><li> With Visual Studio Team Services and Team Foundation Server, you can easily deliver software for any targeted platform. Extend DevOps processes to SQL Server using Redgate Data Tools and securely automate database deployments from Visual Studio. Xamarin Test Recorder and Xamarin Test Cloud allow you to test thousands of physical devices directly from the IDE.<br></li><li> Stay one step ahead<br></li><li> Take advantage of complementary access to training provided by leading partners, including Pluralsight and Opsgility, for professional and corporate clients. You will also have access to software licenses from selected partners, such as Parallels and SyncFusion<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Visual Studio 2017 v15.6.5"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>JetBrains PhpStorm 2018.1.2</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3940-jetbrains-phpstorm.html</link>
<description>Name : JetBrains PhpStorm Version : 2018.1.2 OS : Windows/MAC Type : PHP IDE Tool Price : $500 Homepage : SalePage Lightning-smart PHP IDE PhpStorm deeply understands your code.</description>
<category>Misc</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 06:40:45 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Hundreds of inspections take care of verifying your code as you type, analyzing the whole project. PHPDoc support, code (re)arranger and formatter, quick-fixes, and other features help you write neat code that’s easy to maintain. Be the master of your codebase thanks to efficient, lightning-fast navigation features. The IDE understands where you want to go and gets you there instantly. Refactor your code reliably with safe Rename, Move, Delete, Extract Method, Inline Variable, Push members Up / Pull members Down, Change Signature, and many other refactorings. Language-specific refactorings help you perform project-wide changes in a matter of a few clicks, and can be safely undone.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/U0QABcTD-xc?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Hundreds of inspections take care of verifying your code as you type, analyzing the whole project. PHPDoc support, code (re)arranger and formatter, quick-fixes, and other features help you write neat code that’s easy to maintain.<br></li><li> Be the master of your codebase thanks to efficient, lightning-fast navigation features. The IDE understands where you want to go and gets you there instantly.<br></li><li> Refactor your code reliably with safe Rename, Move, Delete, Extract Method, Inline Variable, Push members Up / Pull members Down, Change Signature, and many other refactorings. Language-specific refactorings help you perform project-wide changes in a matter of a few clicks, and can be safely undone.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="JetBrains PhpStorm 2018.1.2"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Coolutils Total Excel Converter 5.1.0.172</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4368-coolutils-total-excel-converter.html</link>
<description>Name : Coolutils Total Excel Converter Version : 5.1.0.172 OS : Windows Type : Excel Converter Software Price : $59 Homepage : SalePage Total Excel Converter is the perfect choice to convert any type of table. Supported input formats include Excel and Excel 2007, XLSM, XLT, XLTM as well as OpenOffice formats ODS, XML, SQL, WK2, WKS, WAB, DBF, TEX, and DIF. The list of target formats is even more extensive: convert your tabled files into DOC, DOCX, PDF, HTML, Access, TXT, ODT, ODS, XML, SQL, CSV, Lotus, DBF, TEX, DIFF, SYLK, and LaTeX. Imagine how much time you&#039;ll save with this amazing conversion tool. Instead of spending hours trying to gather various converters for each file type, download the one tool that can handle them all!</description>
<category>Misc</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 08:31:06 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Total Excel Converter strictly preserves document layout; you&#039;ll get an exact copy of the source file but in a new format. In addition, we&#039;ve included a number of handy options: - With Total Excel Converter, you can convert each sheet into a new file. - When you convert Excel to PDF you can set user permissions. This will protect your PDF files from being modified or copied. - Total Excel Converter can easily convert OpenOffice ODS files to Microsoft XLS documents; making it so that spread sheets produced by different programs are compatible with your viewer. More unique options.. Whether you&#039;re an beginner or advanced user, our transparent interface provides the perfect blend of usability and functionality. Full command line support is also available. Here is a server version without any GUI or interrupting messages. Experience the time-saving benefits of the Total Excel Converter by downloading our one month trial version today for free!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/f28r4xBJnqU?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Total Excel Converter strictly preserves document layout; you'll get an exact copy of the source file but in a new format. In addition, we've included a number of handy options:<br></li><li> - With Total Excel Converter, you can convert each sheet into a new file.<br></li><li> - When you convert Excel to PDF you can set user permissions. This will protect your PDF files from being modified or copied.<br></li><li> - Total Excel Converter can easily convert OpenOffice ODS files to Microsoft XLS documents; making it so that spread sheets produced by different programs are compatible with your viewer. More unique options..<br></li><li> Whether you're an beginner or advanced user, our transparent interface provides the perfect blend of usability and functionality. Full command line support is also available. Here is a server version without any GUI or interrupting messages. Experience the time-saving benefits of the Total Excel Converter by downloading our one month trial version today for free!<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Coolutils Total Excel Converter 5.1.0.172 "><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Kutools for Excel 17.00</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4367-kutools-for-excel.html</link>
<description>Name : Kutools for Excel Version : 17.00 OS : Windows Type : Tools For Microsoft Excel Price : $59 Homepage : SalePage Kutools - Combines More Than 200 Advanced Functions And Tools For Microsoft Excel</description>
<category>Misc</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 08:29:49 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features If you are tired of merging worksheets one by one, or frustrated by all kinds of complicated tasks in Excel, Kutools for Excel is the handy tool for you to simplify complicated tasks into a few clicks. It enhances and adds more than 200 advanced functions for you to easily cope with various kinds of tasks in Excel. For example, you can combine sheets quickly, merge cells without losing data, paste to only visible cells, count cells by color, batch operations with one click in Excel and so on. Kutools for Excel is undoubtedly an incredible handy add-in which will save your time and effort.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> If you are tired of merging worksheets one by one, or frustrated by all kinds of complicated tasks in Excel, Kutools for Excel is the handy tool for you to simplify complicated tasks into a few clicks. It enhances and adds more than 200 advanced functions for you to easily cope with various kinds of tasks in Excel. For example, you can combine sheets quickly, merge cells without losing data, paste to only visible cells, count cells by color, batch operations with one click in Excel and so on. Kutools for Excel is undoubtedly an incredible handy add-in which will save your time and effort.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Kutools for Excel 17.00"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>ToolbarTerminator 2018 v5.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4103-toolbarterminator-2018.html</link>
<description>Name : ToolbarTerminator 2018 Version : v5.0 OS : Windows Type : Eliminates Toolbars Tool Price : $19.90 Homepage : SalePage Removes annoying toolbars and other hidden crap software from your web browser – even those that are hard to find for experts. Toolbars that have been detected are shown in a neat dashboard and may be removed with just 1 simple click.</description>
<category>Misc</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 00:18:14 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features - Removes annoying Toolbars from your web browser ToolbarTerminator has been developed by a team of experts with one goal: To fight back toolbars and to throw them out of your system. - Yes: It supports your Browser All of the most used web browsers in the market are supported by ToolbarTerminator. ToolbarTerminator scans your system and shows you all browsers in an overview. - Startup-Scan for your Windows PC ToolbarTerminator scans your PC for toolbars on each Windows start and shows you all of them in a neat dashboard allowing you to remove them easily. It perfectly protects your system against unwanted toolbars. - Free „ToolbarDefinition“-Updates Abelssoft helps you to find them by keeping ToolbarTerminator up-to-date with its new “ToolbarDefinition” updates. This service is free of charge for you!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br> - Removes annoying Toolbars from your web browser<br>ToolbarTerminator has been developed by a team of experts with one goal: To fight back toolbars and to throw them out of your system.<br><br> - Yes: It supports your Browser<br>All of the most used web browsers in the market are supported by ToolbarTerminator. ToolbarTerminator scans your system and shows you all browsers in an overview.<br><br> - Startup-Scan for your Windows PC<br>ToolbarTerminator scans your PC for toolbars on each Windows start and shows you all of them in a neat dashboard allowing you to remove them easily. It perfectly protects your system against unwanted toolbars.<br><br> - Free „ToolbarDefinition“-Updates<br>Abelssoft helps you to find them by keeping ToolbarTerminator up-to-date with its new “ToolbarDefinition” updates. This service is free of charge for you!<br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="ToolbarTerminator 2018 v5.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Heated Sneaks All in One 8.6.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3889-heated-sneaks-all-in-one.html</link>
<description>Name : Heated Sneaks All in One Version : 8.6.0 OS : Windows/MAC/Linux Type : Shoes Marketing Price : $125 Homepage : SalePage The premiere Heated Sneaks App option. All In One by Heated Sneaks - All HS Apps for one price. The best program on the market. Secure all limited releases online for retail on various websites online! The absolute best program support Heated Sneaks offers with the absolute highest success rate on the market. Supports hundreds of sites. This is the absolute best program on the market to secure Yeezys, NMDs, Jordans, Supreme, BAPE, Palace, Boost and more!</description>
<category>Misc</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 21:13:45 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Auto Add to Cart (ATC) (Instant &amp;amp; Repeated) - All Sites Auto Checkout (Select Sites) Backdoor Carting (Select Sites)? Simultaneous Task Running - Run all sites at same time. Unlimited Accounts (All Sites) Site Monitoring (All Sites) Implemented Captcha Solver (manual) Restock Monitoring (Select Sites) Proxy Support Server Support Keyword Finder (Select Sites) Start Timer (Supreme Only) Multi-Item Mode (All Sites) Undetectable Link Monitoring (Nike Only) Next-Best Size (Nike Only) MORE!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/lDPixXGsJmI?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Auto Add to Cart (ATC) (Instant &amp; Repeated) - All Sites<br></li><li> Auto Checkout (Select Sites)<br></li><li> Backdoor Carting (Select Sites)?<br></li><li> Simultaneous Task Running - Run all sites at same time.<br></li><li> Unlimited Accounts (All Sites)<br></li><li> Site Monitoring (All Sites)<br></li><li> Implemented Captcha Solver (manual)<br></li><li> Restock Monitoring (Select Sites)<br></li><li> Proxy Support<br></li><li> Server Support<br></li><li> Keyword Finder (Select Sites)<br></li><li> Start Timer (Supreme Only)<br></li><li> Multi-Item Mode (All Sites)<br></li><li> Undetectable<br></li><li> Link Monitoring (Nike Only)<br></li><li> Next-Best Size (Nike Only)<br></li><li> MORE!<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Heated Sneaks All in One 8.6.0"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Microsoft Office 2016 Professional Plus</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3503-microsoft-office.html</link>
<description>Name : Microsoft Office 2016 Professional Plus + Visio Pro + Project Pro / Standard Version : 16.0.4678.1000 OS : Windows Type : Office Price : $399 Homepage : SalePage Office Professional 2016 helps you create, present, communicate, and publish professional-looking documents with time-saving features, a new modern look, and built-in collaboration tools. Save your work in the cloud on OneDrive and access it from anywhere.</description>
<category>Misc</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2017 10:00:35 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Word 2016, Excel 2016, PowerPoint 2016, OneNote 2016, Outlook 2016, Publisher 2016, and Access 2016. Capture your ideas however you work best, using keyboard, pen, or touchscreen. Be a power Office user—the easy way. Type what you want help with in the new Tell Me box on the ribbon and it will tell you how to do it. New themes let you choose the Office experience that’s right for you. Dark and Dark Gray themes provide high contrast that’s easier on the eyes, and the Colorful theme gives you a modern look that’s consistent across your devices. Enhance your reading experience with Insights, powered by Bing, which shows you relevant information from the web when you’re reading an Office file. Let one of the templates from the Start screen do most of the setup and design, so you can focus on your ideas and data Keep track of comments in Word documents and mark them as done with the new reply button. Pull content from PDFs straight into Word. Open PDFs and edit paragraphs, lists, and tables just as you do in familiar Word documents. Save time formatting information in Excel so you can draw insights from your data faster. New tools recognize your pattern and auto-complete data. New modern charts and graphs in Excel give you more ways to explore and tell compelling stories with your business data. Excel recommends charts best suited for your data, and gives you a preview how your data will look. In Excel, you can now create basic forecasts on your data series with one click to visualize future trends. Share your PowerPoint presentation over the web by sending a link to it or using the free Office Presentation Service to deliver it, so your audience can join you from anywhere. Embed Excel spreadsheets, diagrams, audio clips, videos, and almost any other kind of file in your OneNote notebooks. Your notes are saved, searchable, and synced to OneNote apps on your other devices, so you can use or share them from anywhere. Respond faster with inline replies—replies positioned right within the body of the original message—in Outlook. Just type your response in the Reading Pane. Save time with the online photo printing options in Publisher. List and summarize data from a related table or query fast in Access. Simply click an item to open a detailed view of that item. Best for home businesses and very small businesses</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/RIdJ0ib1lSw?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Word 2016, Excel 2016, PowerPoint 2016, OneNote 2016, Outlook 2016, Publisher 2016, and Access 2016.<br></li><li> Capture your ideas however you work best, using keyboard, pen, or touchscreen.<br></li><li> Be a power Office user—the easy way. Type what you want help with in the new Tell Me box on the ribbon and it will tell you how to do it.<br></li><li> New themes let you choose the Office experience that’s right for you. Dark and Dark Gray themes provide high contrast that’s easier on the eyes, and the Colorful theme gives you a modern look that’s consistent across your devices.<br></li><li> Enhance your reading experience with Insights, powered by Bing, which shows you relevant information from the web when you’re reading an Office file.<br></li><li> Let one of the templates from the Start screen do most of the setup and design, so you can focus on your ideas and data<br></li><li> Keep track of comments in Word documents and mark them as done with the new reply button.<br></li><li> Pull content from PDFs straight into Word. Open PDFs and edit paragraphs, lists, and tables just as you do in familiar Word documents.<br></li><li> Save time formatting information in Excel so you can draw insights from your data faster. New tools recognize your pattern and auto-complete data.<br></li><li> New modern charts and graphs in Excel give you more ways to explore and tell compelling stories with your business data. Excel recommends charts best suited for your data, and gives you a preview how your data will look.<br></li><li> In Excel, you can now create basic forecasts on your data series with one click to visualize future trends.<br></li><li> Share your PowerPoint presentation over the web by sending a link to it or using the free Office Presentation Service to deliver it, so your audience can join you from anywhere.<br></li><li> Embed Excel spreadsheets, diagrams, audio clips, videos, and almost any other kind of file in your OneNote notebooks. Your notes are saved, searchable, and synced to OneNote apps on your other devices, so you can use or share them from anywhere.<br></li><li> Respond faster with inline replies—replies positioned right within the body of the original message—in Outlook. Just type your response in the Reading Pane.<br></li><li> Save time with the online photo printing options in Publisher.<br></li><li> List and summarize data from a related table or query fast in Access. Simply click an item to open a detailed view of that item.<br></li><li> Best for home businesses and very small businesses<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Microsoft Office 2016 Professional Plus"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>QuarkXPress 2017 13.0.2</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2129-quarkxpress.html</link>
<description>Name : QuarkXPress 2017 Version : 13.0.2 OS : Windows Type : PDF Creator Price : $67 Homepage : SalePage Building on the foundation of performance and reliability delivered by its predecessor, QuarkXPress 2016 is the must-have upgrade for every QuarkXPress user. From the simplicity of the new colour picker tool to the innovation of exporting HTML5 Publications, QuarkXPress 2016 takes design and productivity to the next level. QuarkXPress 2016 is sold as a perpetual license with 60-days of free support, free dual activation, cross platform licenses (Mac and PC) and ongoing access to free updates.</description>
<category>Misc</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.quark.com/images/native-objects.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 16:36:22 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>[media=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=] Features Paste InDesign Objects as Native QuarkXPress Objects Paste Excel Charts as Native QuarkXPress Objects Paste Illustrator Objects as Native QuarkXPress Objects Convert Print Layout as HTML5 Publication Create and Export HTML5 Publications Colour Picker (Eye Dropper Tool) Multi-Colour Blends New User Interface for QuarkXPress on Windows Dynamic Guides Now Also for Textbox Columns Support for OpenType Stylistic Sets Find/Change Non-breaking Characters Fit Textbox to Text Touchpad Support for Pinch and Zoom (Mac only) Option to Make Measurement Palette 50% Larger Option to Line Wrap Content Variables</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;">[media=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=]</div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Paste InDesign Objects as Native QuarkXPress Objects<br></li><li> Paste Excel Charts as Native QuarkXPress Objects<br></li><li> Paste Illustrator Objects as Native QuarkXPress Objects<br></li><li> Convert Print Layout as HTML5 Publication<br></li><li> Create and Export HTML5 Publications<br></li><li> Colour Picker (Eye Dropper Tool)<br></li><li> Multi-Colour Blends<br></li><li> New User Interface for QuarkXPress on Windows<br></li><li> Dynamic Guides Now Also for Textbox Columns<br></li><li> Support for OpenType Stylistic Sets<br></li><li> Find/Change Non-breaking Characters<br></li><li> Fit Textbox to Text<br></li><li> Touchpad Support for Pinch and Zoom (Mac only)<br></li><li> Option to Make Measurement Palette 50% Larger<br></li><li> Option to Line Wrap Content Variables<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://www.quark.com/images/native-objects.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="QuarkXPress 2017 13.0.2"><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Serif PagePlus X9 19.0.2.22</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2126-serif-pageplus.html</link>
<description>Name : Serif PagePlus X9 Version : 19.0.2.22 OS : Windows Type : PDF Creator Price : $20 Homepage : SalePage PagePlus X9 - Simple document design Our number one desktop publisher, just got better! Create your best ever documents, PDFs and promotional materials using the incredible new features and improvements in PagePlus X9! See what’s new in our famous desktop publisher. With all these new features, plus over 80 improvements to enjoy; PagePlus X9 is our easiest, fastest and most efficient page designer to date! Create your best ever documents with our famous desktop publisher that over 95% of customers would recommend.</description>
<category>Misc</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.serif.com/_media/img/pageplus/x9/new-features/total-control--desk.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 16:35:14 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Enhanced PDF Export : PagePlus X9 supports the latest PDF/X-4 and PDF/X-5 standards so you can preserve transparency to enable faster output, smaller files and higher quality print output. PDF Overprint : Avoid printing mistakes using new PDF overprint settings that allow you to output objects on top of one another, without cutting each other out, making the PDF more editable by other designers and professional printers. PDF Pass Through : Placing PDF files such as adverts into your documents is now more accurate than ever before with the new PDF Pass Through mode. EPS Export : You can now export as EPS, with control over colour space and transparency, output text as curves, and also embed fonts. Placeable DPP files : Place DrawPlus X8 files as images into your PagePlus documents, and even convert them to objects to further modify the design. WebP Support : Google’s new WebP files are now supported, ideal for when you need a smaller, more compressed file for sharing electronically on the web or via email. Customisable QR codes : Create your own QR codes from scratch, and add them into any document so readers can enjoy more interactivity such as getting directions to an event, opening contact us forms, viewing links to your website, and so much more. Improved language support : Enjoy greater language accuracy and flexibility with support for Hunspell spelling and hyphenation dictionaries, which cover a wide range of languages. Text, to tables : Creating tables from a mountain of unformatted information can be time consuming, especially when importing data from different sources such as Word documents or emails. Now PagePlus can create a formatted table from text in a frame, which is perfect when collaborating with others to gather information from event schedules or business statistics to combine into one document without manually inputting data. Save the date : The Calendar Event Manager has been completely redesigned, giving you the easiest, most customisable, and compatible PagePlus calendar tool to date. Choose from a wide range of built-in annual holidays and events to add to your calendar, and also import calendars from popular calendar file types such as iCal, .ics, .ifb, iCalendar and many more. There are even more fully customisable templates to choose from too, so you can add your own photos, change font styles, colours and size to create a unique, personalised calendar in minutes. Make your words, go further : PagePlus is the perfect tool for creating long, text-rich documents. Auto-frame lets you experience a seamless workflow by automatically creating a new page as you type, and also saving time when copying and pasting long documents from Microsoft Word or other sources. Documents look cleaner and more stylish than ever before with paragraph spacing options, more attractive typography using automatic letter spacing and the ability to apply formatting to text objects with the new Text Format Painter.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/6VBwxLD1l28?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Enhanced PDF Export : PagePlus X9 supports the latest PDF/X-4 and PDF/X-5 standards so you can preserve transparency to enable faster output, smaller files and higher quality print output.<br></li><li> PDF Overprint : Avoid printing mistakes using new PDF overprint settings that allow you to output objects on top of one another, without cutting each other out, making the PDF more editable by other designers and professional printers.<br></li><li> PDF Pass Through : Placing PDF files such as adverts into your documents is now more accurate than ever before with the new PDF Pass Through mode.<br></li><li> EPS Export : You can now export as EPS, with control over colour space and transparency, output text as curves, and also embed fonts.<br></li><li> Placeable DPP files : Place DrawPlus X8 files as images into your PagePlus documents, and even convert them to objects to further modify the design.<br></li><li> WebP Support : Google’s new WebP files are now supported, ideal for when you need a smaller, more compressed file for sharing electronically on the web or via email.<br></li><li> Customisable QR codes : Create your own QR codes from scratch, and add them into any document so readers can enjoy more interactivity such as getting directions to an event, opening contact us forms, viewing links to your website, and so much more.<br></li><li> Improved language support : Enjoy greater language accuracy and flexibility with support for Hunspell spelling and hyphenation dictionaries, which cover a wide range of languages.<br></li><li> Text, to tables : Creating tables from a mountain of unformatted information can be time consuming, especially when importing data from different sources such as Word documents or emails. Now PagePlus can create a formatted table from text in a frame, which is perfect when collaborating with others to gather information from event schedules or business statistics to combine into one document without manually inputting data.<br></li><li> Save the date : The Calendar Event Manager has been completely redesigned, giving you the easiest, most customisable, and compatible PagePlus calendar tool to date. Choose from a wide range of built-in annual holidays and events to add to your calendar, and also import calendars from popular calendar file types such as iCal, .ics, .ifb, iCalendar and many more. There are even more fully customisable templates to choose from too, so you can add your own photos, change font styles, colours and size to create a unique, personalised calendar in minutes.<br></li><li> Make your words, go further : PagePlus is the perfect tool for creating long, text-rich documents. Auto-frame lets you experience a seamless workflow by automatically creating a new page as you type, and also saving time when copying and pasting long documents from Microsoft Word or other sources. Documents look cleaner and more stylish than ever before with paragraph spacing options, more attractive typography using automatic letter spacing and the ability to apply formatting to text objects with the new Text Format Painter.<br><br></li></ul><br><img src="http://www.serif.com/_media/img/pageplus/x9/new-features/total-control--desk.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Serif PagePlus X9 19.0.2.22 "><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>