<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Page Builder Plugins - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Page Builder Plugins - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>WPBakery Page Builder for WordPress 5.4.5</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/832-visual-composer.html</link>
<description>Name : WPBakery Page Builder for WordPress (formerly Visual Composer) Version : 5.4.5 Type : Landing Page Price : $33 Homepage : SalePage WordPress Page Builder Plugin with Frontend and Backend Editor Free Visual Composer is a drag and drop frontend and backend page builder that will save you tons of time working on your website content. Take full control of your WordPress website, and build any layout you can imagine - no programming knowledge required! Not only that, but with our frontend and backend editor you can now choose whether you want to work on backend or move your page building process to frontend and instantly see any changes you make. Nulled Visual Composer is the #1 Best Selling drag and drop frontend and backend page builder plugin, already powering 1,000,000+ websites. Join now, and create beautiful WordPress websites in no time at all, with minimum effort, and - of course - no coding and [shortcodes].</description>
<category>Page Builder Plugins</category>
<enclosure url="http://wpbakery.com/_tf_files/vc_5/9_options.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://wpbakery.com/_tf_files/vc_5/elements.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2017 19:06:07 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>[media=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gpOyscHUM80] Features Intuitive Drag and Drop Interface Easily Extendable Frontend Editor Backend Editor Object Oriented Code Multilingual Ready Template System Responsive Design User Role Manager Custom Post Types Support Lifetime Update - Free of Charge Professional Dedicated Support Design Options Shortcode Mapper Multi-language Support SEO Friendly Woo Commerce Support Advanced Grid Builder Full Width and Height Rows Parallax Background for Rows Image Filters Video Background Element Presets Column Height, Gaps and Position Advanced Custom Fields Support Icon Sets and Social Icons Hide Content</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;">[media=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gpOyscHUM80]</div><br><b>Features</b><br><ul><li>Intuitive Drag and Drop Interface<br></li><li>Easily Extendable<br></li><li>Frontend Editor<br></li><li>Backend Editor<br></li><li>Object Oriented Code<br></li><li>Multilingual Ready<br></li><li>Template System<br></li><li>Responsive Design<br></li><li>User Role Manager<br></li><li>Custom Post Types Support<br></li><li>Lifetime Update - Free of Charge<br></li><li>Professional Dedicated Support<br></li><li>Design Options<br></li><li>Shortcode Mapper<br></li><li>Multi-language Support<br></li><li>SEO Friendly<br></li><li>Woo Commerce Support<br></li><li>Advanced Grid Builder<br></li><li>Full Width and Height Rows<br></li><li>Parallax Background for Rows<br></li><li>Image Filters<br></li><li>Video Background<br></li><li>Element Presets<br></li><li>Column Height, Gaps and Position<br></li><li>Advanced Custom Fields Support<br></li><li>Icon Sets and Social Icons<br></li><li>Hide Content<br></li></ul><br><br><img src="http://wpbakery.com/_tf_files/vc_5/9_options.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="WPBakery Page Builder for WordPress 5.4.5"><br><img src="http://wpbakery.com/_tf_files/vc_5/elements.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>WP Profit Builder 2.3.8</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/844-wp-profit-builder.html</link>
<description>Name : WP Profit Builder (plugins + template + themes 3.6) Version : 2.3.8 Type : Page BUilder Price : $147 Homepage : SalePage Click, Drag, PROFIT... It&#039;s That Simple! The Easiest Way to Create High-Converting Lead Pages, Sales Pages, Member Portals and Marketing Pages Like the PROs... The ULTIMATE Marketing Page Creation System is Finally Here...</description>
<category>Page Builder Plugins</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 16:22:21 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Over 60+ Pre-Designed Lead, Sales and Marketing Layouts in Our HUGE Library... Easy-to-Use Drag and Drop Marketing Page Builder Works with ANY WordPress Site... Be a Marketing Master in Minutes with ZERO Coding or Design Skills... Just Click and GO! If You Can DREAM it, You Can BUILD it. Transform ANY Site into a Profit Powerhouse</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/cISHPZlSj1A?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" gesture="media" allow="encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Over 60+ Pre-Designed Lead, Sales and Marketing Layouts in Our HUGE Library...<br></li><li> Easy-to-Use Drag and Drop Marketing Page Builder Works with ANY WordPress Site...<br></li><li> Be a Marketing Master in Minutes with ZERO Coding or Design Skills... Just Click and GO!<br></li><li> If You Can DREAM it, You Can BUILD it. Transform ANY Site into a Profit Powerhouse<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="WP Profit Builder 2.3.8"><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Visual Composer Extensions All in One 3.4.9.3</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2090-visual-composer-extensions-all-in-one.html</link>
<description>Name : Visual Composer Extensions All in One Version : 3.4.9.3 Type : Page Builder Price : $33 Homepage : SalePage Visual Composer is very smart to save your time and bandwidth it includes j&amp;#1072;vascript files only if they are used on the page, no extra traffic and faster loading. This item put all exist Visual Composer add-ons (57 elements), and will add more add-ons for free in the future update. All the add-ons are in a simple design and extend Visual Composer with more function. This bundle works fine with VC that installed as plugin or in a theme.</description>
<category>Page Builder Plugins</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 00:38:36 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Visual Composer Extensions All in One Features Font Awesome Animation App Mockup Gallery DA (Direction-Aware) Gallery Scrolling Notification Masonry Gallery Testimonial Carousel Stack Gallery Figure Navigation To Do List or Price Table Medium Gallery Product Cover Gallery Image with Arrow CSS3 Accordion Tabs Zoom or Magnify (image) Carousel &amp;amp; Gallery Metro Carousel and Tile Fullscreen Intro Separator with Text or Icon Thumbnail with Caption Page Transition Draggable Timeline Parallax Cube Box Before &amp;amp; After Gradient Box Flip Box Image Hotspot with Tooltip iHover Expand Grid</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<b>Visual Composer Extensions All in One Features</b><br><ul><li>Font Awesome Animation<br></li><li>App Mockup Gallery<br></li><li>DA (Direction-Aware) Gallery<br></li><li>Scrolling Notification<br></li><li>Masonry Gallery<br></li><li>Testimonial Carousel<br></li><li>Stack Gallery<br></li><li>Figure Navigation<br></li><li>To Do List or Price Table<br></li><li>Medium Gallery<br></li><li>Product Cover Gallery<br></li><li>Image with Arrow<br></li><li>CSS3 Accordion<br></li><li>Tabs<br></li><li>Zoom or Magnify (image)<br></li><li>Carousel &amp; Gallery<br></li><li>Metro Carousel and Tile<br></li><li>Fullscreen Intro<br></li><li>Separator with Text or Icon<br></li><li>Thumbnail with Caption<br></li><li>Page Transition<br></li><li>Draggable Timeline<br></li><li>Parallax<br></li><li>Cube Box<br></li><li>Before &amp; After<br></li><li>Gradient Box<br></li><li>Flip Box<br></li><li>Image Hotspot with Tooltip<br></li><li>iHover<br></li><li>Expand Grid<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Visual Composer Extensions All in One 3.4.9.3"><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>WP Quiz Pro 1.0.3</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2111-wp-quiz-pro.html</link>
<description>Name : WP Quiz Pro Version : 1.0.3 Type : Quiz plugin Price : $29 Homepage : SalePage WP Quiz Pro is the number one WordPress plugin for building powerful and beautiful quizzes. This can increase engagement for any website or blog by keeping your users glued to the page. Use quizzes to go viral and destroy your bounce rate! Thanks to WP Quiz Pro, it couldn’t be easier!</description>
<category>Page Builder Plugins</category>
<enclosure url="https://cdn.mythemeshop.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/07/WP-Quiz-Pro-Text.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2017 13:27:15 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Add New Quizzes Trivia Quiz Type Personality Quiz Type Swiper Quiz Type Flip Card Quiz Type Facebook Quiz Add Questions Add Results Different Quiz Possibilities Facebook Quiz Personality Quiz Single Page Personality Quiz Multipage Personality Quiz with Subscription Box Personality Quiz FB Share to see Results Trivia Quiz Single Page Trivia Quiz Multipage Trivia Quiz with Subscription Box Trivia Quiz FB Share to see Results Trivia Quiz with Timer Flip Card Quiz Type Swiper Quiz Single Quiz Styling Change Question Color Choose from 2 Unique Skins Change Question Font Change Question Background Color Single Quiz Settings Randomize Questions Randomized Answers Restart Questions Enable Plugin Mention Show Embed Code Toggle Show or Hide Share Buttons Enable Countdown Timer Enable Auto Scroll to Next Question Show Correct/Incorrect Answers After Quiz Force Action to See Results Show or Hide Ads from Quiz General Plugin Settings Integrate Google Analytics Use MailChimp or GetResponse to Gather Email IDs Enable Randomize Questions for All Quizzes Randomized Answers for All Quizzes Enable Restart Questions for All Quizzes Promote the Plugin Across All Quizzes Option to Use MyThemeShop User ID for Earning Commissions Show Embed Code Toggle Hide or Show Share Buttons Across the Board Enable or Disable OpenGraph Enter Facebook ID Show or Hide Ads on All Quizzes Show Ads after every Nth question Repeat Ads Enable Option Countdown Timer Auto Scroll Option Force Action Before Results</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/YEhCGFT2Cr8?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br>Add New Quizzes<br><ul><li> Trivia Quiz Type<br></li><li> Personality Quiz Type<br></li><li> Swiper Quiz Type<br></li><li> Flip Card Quiz Type<br></li><li> Facebook Quiz<br></li><li> Add Questions<br></li><li> Add Results<br></li></ul><br>Different Quiz Possibilities<br><ul><li> Facebook Quiz<br></li><li> Personality Quiz Single Page<br></li><li> Personality Quiz Multipage<br></li><li> Personality Quiz with Subscription Box<br></li><li> Personality Quiz FB Share to see Results<br></li><li> Trivia Quiz Single Page<br></li><li> Trivia Quiz Multipage<br></li><li> Trivia Quiz with Subscription Box<br></li><li> Trivia Quiz FB Share to see Results<br></li><li> Trivia Quiz with Timer<br></li><li> Flip Card Quiz Type<br></li><li> Swiper Quiz<br></li></ul><br>Single Quiz Styling<br><ul><li> Change Question Color<br></li><li> Choose from 2 Unique Skins<br></li><li> Change Question Font<br></li><li> Change Question Background Color<br></li></ul><br>Single Quiz Settings<br><ul><li> Randomize Questions<br></li><li> Randomized Answers<br></li><li> Restart Questions<br></li><li> Enable Plugin Mention<br></li><li> Show Embed Code Toggle<br></li><li> Show or Hide Share Buttons<br></li><li> Enable Countdown Timer<br></li><li> Enable Auto Scroll to Next Question<br></li><li> Show Correct/Incorrect Answers After Quiz<br></li><li> Force Action to See Results<br></li><li> Show or Hide Ads from Quiz<br></li></ul><br>General Plugin Settings<br><ul><li> Integrate Google Analytics<br></li><li> Use MailChimp or GetResponse to Gather Email IDs<br></li><li> Enable Randomize Questions for All Quizzes<br></li><li> Randomized Answers for All Quizzes<br></li><li> Enable Restart Questions for All Quizzes<br></li><li> Promote the Plugin Across All Quizzes<br></li><li> Option to Use MyThemeShop User ID for Earning Commissions<br></li><li> Show Embed Code Toggle<br></li><li> Hide or Show Share Buttons Across the Board<br></li><li> Enable or Disable OpenGraph<br></li><li> Enter Facebook ID<br></li><li> Show or Hide Ads on All Quizzes<br></li><li> Show Ads after every Nth question<br></li><li> Repeat Ads Enable Option<br></li><li> Countdown Timer<br></li><li> Auto Scroll Option<br></li><li> Force Action Before Results<br></li></ul><br><img src="https://cdn.mythemeshop.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/07/WP-Quiz-Pro-Text.jpg" alt="WP Quiz Pro 1.0.3"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt=""> <br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Yellow Pencil 5.5.5</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2093-yellow-pencil.html</link>
<description>Name : Yellow Pencil : Visual CSS Style Editor Version : 5.5.5 Type : Page Builder Price : $25 Homepage : SalePage Free Yellow Pencil Plugin is advanced visual CSS style editor wordpress plugin that you can customize your website in real-time with a few clicks. Yellow Pencil wordpress plugin works with any theme and plugin. Its will Keep your site design in your control with 100% front-end Style Editor. Yellow Pencil nulled plugin created for beginners and advanced users.</description>
<category>Page Builder Plugins</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 13:28:27 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Yellow Pencil WordPress Plugin Features 600+ Font family 300+ Background patterns 3 Color palette Hover and focus selectors Animation Generator Visual Resizer 50+ Animations Code Editor Undo and redo feature Clean CSS Output Color Picker Feature Parallax background CSS Manager Custom Selector CSS3 Filter Effects 50+ CSS properties Drag &amp; Drop feature Working With All Plugin And Themes Customize any page. Support Responsive Ruler Shortcuts Well Documentation A must have plugin</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<br /><b>Yellow Pencil WordPress Plugin Features</b><br /><ul><li>600+ Font family<br /></li><li>300+ Background patterns<br /></li><li>3 Color palette<br /></li><li>Hover and focus selectors<br /></li><li>Animation Generator<br /></li><li>Visual Resizer<br /></li><li>50+ Animations<br /></li><li>Code Editor<br /></li><li>Undo and redo feature<br /></li><li>Clean CSS Output<br /></li><li>Color Picker Feature<br /></li><li>Parallax background<br /></li><li>CSS Manager<br /></li><li>Custom Selector<br /></li><li>CSS3 Filter Effects<br /></li><li>50+ CSS properties<br /></li><li>Drag & Drop feature<br /></li><li>Working With All Plugin And Themes<br /></li><li>Customize any page.<br /></li><li>Support Responsive<br /></li><li>Ruler<br /></li><li>Shortcuts<br /></li><li>Well Documentation<br /></li><li>A must have plugin<br /></li></ul><br /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Yellow Pencil 5.5.5" title="Yellow Pencil 5.5.5"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Ultimate Addons for Visual Composer 3.16.7</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1951-ultimate-addons-for-visual-composer.html</link>
<description>Name : Ultimate Addons for Visual Composer Version : 3.16.7 OS : Linux Type : Page Builder Price : $18 Homepage : SalePage This plugin adds several premium elements in your Visual Composer on top of the built-in ones given by WPBakery. Every single element in the package is crafted with utmost attention to details and a simple objective to provide you an ultimate experience. We&#039;ve put a lot of time and care to ensure that all the elements are flexible so that they will open limitless possibilities for you, while maintaining simplicity at the core.</description>
<category>Page Builder Plugins</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2016 11:25:21 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Addon Elements - Icons - You can use this element to integrate a simple icon (font &amp; image, both kinds) in your page and use it as you want. Or you can utilize Visual Composer grids and display a list of logos of your clients, partners, sponsors, etc. Info Box - Perhaps, the most popular trend right now, Info Boxes truly make your website stand out helping you highlight the important things you have on offer. Info List - Traditional HTML lists are boring, aren&#039;t they? This elements simply re-imagines the lists. You may take an opportunity and utilize it&#039;s cool design to show some process or simply highlight your most popular / related products, services &amp; features. Flip Box - This element combines the power of &quot;Info Box&quot; &amp; &quot;Call to Action&quot; block altogether. On the front, it would look like a normal Info Box but as visitor hovers on the block, it flips with a cool CSS3 effect and shows a Call to Action section, provoking him to take a call. Counter - Want to show your milestones, achievements and any other numeric statistics with animated numbers? This element will help! Interactive Banner - Many times, image banners come in handy as they are very convenient and obvious way to deliver your message precisely. This element will display those image blocks in a nicer &amp; interactive way. Modal Popup Box - This is one of the very useful element that can go on any website. Create modal popup boxes and embed anything you wish inside the popup box through easy WYSIWYG editor. Timeline - Display a timeline in a Facebook style or simply showcase your features, process or highlights little creatively. We have taken special efforts with custom j&amp;#097;vascript &amp; CSS codes to make it as perfect as possible. Extended Google Maps - Visual Composer comes with Google Maps element by default. But our Extended Googles Maps element uses latest APIs and allows you to do more with it. Upload marker images, write custom HTML in map info box and control everything that goes with map. Row Backgrounds - Creative backgrounds do truly set the tone for your website. So we offer you easy tools that will help you utilize them quickly. Features - Fixed Image Background - Keeps the image fixed at it&#039;s position while the other content moves on scroll. Vertical &amp; Horizontal Parallax - The background moves at different speed &amp; direction from your content on scroll. Hover Parallax - The background moves creatively with cursor movement. Video Background - - Plays a video in the background. Supports hosted as well as YouTube videos. Multilayer Hover Parallax - - Design a real 3D parallax. Go ahead - impress your users ;) While we believe the above six elements will benefit your site immediately, these are not really all! We&#039;re already working on few more elements that we look forward including in this plugin as we complete them. We want to make this plugin as an &quot;ultimate&quot; source for you to get most of the essential Visual Composer addon elements in one package. The long wait has finally come to an end.Introducing, WordPress Icon Fonts Manager! This project was originally started with a slightly different objective of developing a functionality that will help people use the Icon Fonts in their WordPress site easily. But then, we realized - providing just the Icon Fonts functionality wasn&#039;t enough to make it go. There was a need to make Icon Fonts even more intuitive for normal WordPress users and that&#039;s when we decided to develop several Visual Composer element that will make usage of Icon Fonts even easier. So - &quot;Ultimate Visual Composer Addons&quot; is technically an extension of two things; firstly of our Icon Font Manager and secondly, the obvious one - Visual Composer :-) Features of the Icon Fonts Manager - Customize Your Own Icon Fonts - We understand you don&#039;t use all those hundreds of prebuilt unnecessary icons that come with any of those popular libraries like Font Awesome, Entypo, etc; but you care more about only the few ones that relate to your business more. That&#039;s why, we&#039;ve made our Icon Fonts Manager very compatible with the famous IcoMoon&#039;s APIs where you can create your own customize font by shortlisting your favorite icons from the choice of 2500+ icons! If those 2500+ icons still fall short, IcoMoon will still cover you with their amazing feature that helps you convert your SVG designs in the Icon Fonts. Real Time Icon Search - Okay, many of us would like big numbers &amp; more choices of icons, wouldn&#039;t we? Though this choice is really very fancy, it certainly comes with a pain as we can&#039;t easily find the icon that we are looking for when we need it. And that&#039;s why we have integrated a real time search feature which can help you sort through all the Icon Fonts you have in your library very smartly. More features on the way! As said earlier - Icon Fonts Manager is our individual, long term project; and we look forward adding more features in it with time such as integration with WordPress&#039;s Menu, TinyMCE editor, etc. When these features will be developed - they will be provided in this plugin as well.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<br /><div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Pjz2CdmS_VQ?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br />Addon Elements -<br /><br />Icons - You can use this element to integrate a simple icon (font & image, both kinds) in your page and use it as you want. Or you can utilize Visual Composer grids and display a list of logos of your clients, partners, sponsors, etc.<br /><br />Info Box - Perhaps, the most popular trend right now, Info Boxes truly make your website stand out helping you highlight the important things you have on offer.<br /><br />Info List - Traditional HTML lists are boring, aren't they? This elements simply re-imagines the lists. You may take an opportunity and utilize it's cool design to show some process or simply highlight your most popular / related products, services & features.<br /><br />Flip Box - This element combines the power of "Info Box" & "Call to Action" block altogether. On the front, it would look like a normal Info Box but as visitor hovers on the block, it flips with a cool CSS3 effect and shows a Call to Action section, provoking him to take a call.<br /><br />Counter - Want to show your milestones, achievements and any other numeric statistics with animated numbers? This element will help!<br /><br />Interactive Banner - Many times, image banners come in handy as they are very convenient and obvious way to deliver your message precisely. This element will display those image blocks in a nicer & interactive way.<br /><br />Modal Popup Box - This is one of the very useful element that can go on any website. Create modal popup boxes and embed anything you wish inside the popup box through easy WYSIWYG editor.<br /><br />Timeline - Display a timeline in a Facebook style or simply showcase your features, process or highlights little creatively. We have taken special efforts with custom j&#097;vascript & CSS codes to make it as perfect as possible.<br /><br />Extended Google Maps - Visual Composer comes with Google Maps element by default. But our Extended Googles Maps element uses latest APIs and allows you to do more with it. Upload marker images, write custom HTML in map info box and control everything that goes with map.<br />Row Backgrounds -<br /><br />Creative backgrounds do truly set the tone for your website. So we offer you easy tools that will help you utilize them quickly.<br /><br />Features -<br /><br />Fixed Image Background<br />- Keeps the image fixed at it's position while the other content moves on scroll.<br /><br />Vertical & Horizontal Parallax<br />- The background moves at different speed & direction from your content on scroll.<br /><br />Hover Parallax<br />- The background moves creatively with cursor movement.<br /><br />Video Background -<br />- Plays a video in the background. Supports hosted as well as YouTube videos.<br /><br />Multilayer Hover Parallax -<br />- Design a real 3D parallax. Go ahead - impress your users ;)<br /><br /><br />While we believe the above six elements will benefit your site immediately, these are not really all!<br />We're already working on few more elements that we look forward including in this plugin as we complete them. We want to make this plugin as an "ultimate" source for you to get most of the essential Visual Composer addon elements in one package.<br />The long wait has finally come to an end.Introducing, WordPress Icon Fonts Manager!<br /><br />This project was originally started with a slightly different objective of developing a functionality that will help people use the Icon Fonts in their WordPress site easily. But then, we realized - providing just the Icon Fonts functionality wasn't enough to make it go. There was a need to make Icon Fonts even more intuitive for normal WordPress users and that's when we decided to develop several Visual Composer element that will make usage of Icon Fonts even easier. So - "Ultimate Visual Composer Addons" is technically an extension of two things; firstly of our Icon Font Manager and secondly, the obvious one - Visual Composer :-)<br />Features of the Icon Fonts Manager -<br />Customize Your Own Icon Fonts - We understand you don't use all those hundreds of prebuilt unnecessary icons that come with any of those popular libraries like Font Awesome, Entypo, etc; but you care more about only the few ones that relate to your business more.<br /><br />That's why, we've made our Icon Fonts Manager very compatible with the famous IcoMoon's APIs where you can create your own customize font by shortlisting your favorite icons from the choice of 2500+ icons! If those 2500+ icons still fall short, IcoMoon will still cover you with their amazing feature that helps you convert your SVG designs in the Icon Fonts.<br /><br />Real Time Icon Search - Okay, many of us would like big numbers & more choices of icons, wouldn't we? Though this choice is really very fancy, it certainly comes with a pain as we can't easily find the icon that we are looking for when we need it. And that's why we have integrated a real time search feature which can help you sort through all the Icon Fonts you have in your library very smartly.<br /><br />More features on the way! As said earlier - Icon Fonts Manager is our individual, long term project; and we look forward adding more features in it with time such as integration with WordPress's Menu, TinyMCE editor, etc. When these features will be developed - they will be provided in this plugin as well.<br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Ultimate Addons for Visual Composer 3.16.7" title="Ultimate Addons for Visual Composer 3.16.7"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>OptimizePress 2.5.7</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1950-optimizepress.html</link>
<description>Name : OptimizePress + OptimizeMember Version : 2.5.7 OS : Linux Type : Page Builder Price : $297 Homepage : SalePage Marketing Site Creation, Made Easy... OptimizePress is the new way to create high converting landing pages, sales pages and membership portals</description>
<category>Page Builder Plugins</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2016 11:20:28 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Landing Pages : Create high converting landing pages Sales &amp;amp; Marketing Pages : Create full scale marketing sites and sales pages Free Training &amp;amp; Course Pages : Deliver free training or courses with progress bars Webinar Registration Page : Create high impact webinar registration pages Secure Membership Portals : Protect your content in secure membership portals Product Launch Funnels : Use our unique LaunchSuite to create product launch funnels Authority Blogs : Grow your audience with our premium blogging system Mobile Ready Versions of All Pages : All your pages will be mobile responsive automatically</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ert4yXCcm_k?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Landing Pages : Create high converting landing pages<br></li><li> Sales &amp; Marketing Pages : Create full scale marketing sites and sales pages<br></li><li> Free Training &amp; Course Pages : Deliver free training or courses with progress bars<br></li><li> Webinar Registration Page : Create high impact webinar registration pages<br></li><li> Secure Membership Portals : Protect your content in secure membership portals<br></li><li> Product Launch Funnels : Use our unique LaunchSuite to create product launch funnels<br></li><li> Authority Blogs : Grow your audience with our premium blogging system<br></li><li> Mobile Ready Versions of All Pages : All your pages will be mobile responsive automatically<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="OptimizePress 2.5.7"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>OriginBuilder 1.0.2 Pro</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1833-originbuilder.html</link>
<description>Name : OriginBuilder Version : 1.0 Premium OS : Windows Type : Create Landing Pages Price : $97 Homepage : SalePage This is The Only Builder in Our Space Right Now that Will Allow You to Create NON-IM Style Landing Pages Needed for Your Real Businesses and It Works on Any Theme With No Design Skills Required! Build Gorgeous, Industry-Standard Pages and Professional Landing Pages with Our New Drag n&#039; Drop Live Page Builder for Any Niche on the Fly. The World&#039;s True Drag n&#039; Drop Page Composer with Seamless Instant Actions Technology That Will Allow You to Build Innovative, Beautiful and Super-Intelligent Websites/Landing Pages in Minutes without Designing or Coding Anything Yourself.</description>
<category>Page Builder Plugins</category>
<enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/originbuilder/animations/BE.gif" type="image/gif" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2016 03:48:33 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Here&#039;s What You Can Create with Origin Builder Right Now A beautiful blog post Lead capture page Personal/Company Portfolio Countdown/launch pages Amazon product review Video sales page Photography/video blog Membership sites Download page Presell for physical products Authority Sites in Any Niche Sweepstakes/offer pages Niche affiliate site CPA landing page Bridge page for your Ads Robust eCommerce store Company website Thank you &amp;amp; shipping pages</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Mb7ZxiCXjSE?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br>Here's What You Can Create with Origin Builder Right Now<br><ul><li> A beautiful blog post<br></li><li> Lead capture page<br></li><li> Personal/Company Portfolio<br></li><li> Countdown/launch pages<br></li><li> Amazon product review<br></li><li> Video sales page<br></li><li> Photography/video blog<br></li><li> Membership sites<br></li><li> Download page<br></li><li> Presell for physical products<br></li><li> Authority Sites in Any Niche<br></li><li> Sweepstakes/offer pages<br></li><li> Niche affiliate site<br></li><li> CPA landing page<br></li><li> Bridge page for your Ads<br></li><li> Robust eCommerce store<br></li><li> Company website<br></li><li> Thank you &amp; shipping pages<br></li></ul><br><img src="https://s3.amazonaws.com/originbuilder/animations/BE.gif" alt="OriginBuilder 1.0.2 Pro"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Insta Builder 2.1.6</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/808-insta-builder.html</link>
<description>Name : Insta Builder Version : 2.1.6 (Fixed) Type : Landing Page Price : $149 Homepage : SalePage Easy-To-Use Drag and Drop Software Creates All Your Landing Pages In Mere Minutes... Without Expensive Fees! &amp;#65279;And Unlike Our Competition You Have Full Control Over Your Sales Funnel.</description>
<category>Page Builder Plugins</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2016 22:08:14 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features It&#039;s As Sexy As It Is Effective. So Easy It Feels Like Playing A Video Game. (Easy To Use - Drag and Drop Visual Editor) Sales Funnel Design For The Golden Age Of Mobile (100% Responsive) More Templates Than The &quot;Other Guys.&quot; Better Looking Too. You Get To Control Every Word You Get To Make It Just How You Want It. (Custom Elements) Mix And Match Makes Designing Even EASIER (Combo Elements) Marketing Technology So Powerful It&#039;s Becoming Infamous It&#039;s Where Future Technology Meets Modern Day Marketing Research (3-Step Opt-in Technology) You Can Collect Even More Leads By Simply Asking Questions Lock Your Content. Get More Leads (Welcome Gate) Make Your Pretty Pictures Even Prettier (Built-in Image Editor) Graphics Packs Ready To Go (Built-in Marketing Graphics) Numbers. Numbers. Numbers It&#039;s The Holy Grail Of Inte.com Marketing Packaged With The Greatest Page Builder On The Pl.com (Split Testing) Control Visitor Movements And Get More Leads (Exit Traffic Redirection) You Can Make &#039;Em Wait For It. And Increase Conversions By Doing So One-Click Scarcity Building. The Easiest Way To Increase Sales Our Count-Down Timer Is Just Better (Count-Down Timer) Get More Shares With A Better Social Sharing System (Social Sharing) We&#039;ve Got Notification Bars Can Your Other Landing Page Tools Create Animations? I Didn&#039;t Think So (Animation/ Dynamic Elements) InstaBuilder Pages Can Be Awesome WITHOUT Wordpress Too (Publish to HTML) Facebook Publishing Made Easy You Can Design And Save Your Own Template. (Save Template) Powerful SEO Built Right In It&#039;s One Of The Most Versatile Autoresponder Integrations On the Market Today (Easy Autoresponder Integration) It Integrates With The World&#039;s Leading Webinar Provider Creating and Editing Pages Just Became Easier and Faster Landing Page Organization Like You&#039;ve Never Seen Before (Grouping) Make Your Pages &quot;Legit&quot; With Auto-Generated Legal Pages (Disclaimer, Privacy Policy, TOS Page Generator) Create Your Own Designs And Export Them To Your Clients&#039; Sites</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<br /><div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/x8AFG2RMsEI?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> It's As Sexy As It Is Effective. <br /></li><li> So Easy It Feels Like Playing A Video Game. (Easy To Use - Drag and Drop Visual Editor)<br /></li><li> Sales Funnel Design For The Golden Age Of Mobile (100% Responsive)<br /></li><li> More Templates Than The "Other Guys." Better Looking Too. <br /></li><li> You Get To Control Every Word <br /></li><li> You Get To Make It Just How You Want It. (Custom Elements)<br /></li><li> Mix And Match Makes Designing Even EASIER (Combo Elements)<br /></li><li> Marketing Technology So Powerful It's Becoming Infamous<br /></li><li> It's Where Future Technology Meets Modern Day Marketing Research (3-Step Opt-in Technology)<br /></li><li> You Can Collect Even More Leads By Simply Asking Questions <br /></li><li> Lock Your Content. Get More Leads (Welcome Gate)<br /></li><li> Make Your Pretty Pictures Even Prettier (Built-in Image Editor)<br /></li><li> Graphics Packs Ready To Go (Built-in Marketing Graphics)<br /></li><li> Numbers. Numbers. Numbers<br /></li><li> It's The Holy Grail Of Inte.com Marketing Packaged With The Greatest Page Builder On The Pl.com (Split Testing)<br /></li><li> Control Visitor Movements And Get More Leads (Exit Traffic Redirection)<br /></li><li>  You Can Make 'Em Wait For It. And Increase Conversions By Doing So <br /></li><li> One-Click Scarcity Building. The Easiest Way To Increase Sales <br /></li><li> Our Count-Down Timer Is Just Better (Count-Down Timer)<br /></li><li> Get More Shares With A Better Social Sharing System (Social Sharing)<br /></li><li> We've Got Notification Bars <br /></li><li> Can Your Other Landing Page Tools Create Animations? I Didn't Think So (Animation/ Dynamic Elements)<br /></li><li> InstaBuilder Pages Can Be Awesome WITHOUT Wordpress Too (Publish to HTML)<br /></li><li> Facebook Publishing Made Easy <br /></li><li> You Can Design And Save Your Own Template. (Save Template)<br /></li><li> Powerful SEO Built Right In <br /></li><li> It's One Of The Most Versatile Autoresponder Integrations On the Market Today (Easy Autoresponder Integration)<br /></li><li> It Integrates With The World's Leading Webinar Provider<br /></li><li> Creating and Editing Pages Just Became Easier and Faster <br /></li><li> Landing Page Organization Like You've Never Seen Before (Grouping)<br /></li><li> Make Your Pages "Legit" With Auto-Generated Legal Pages (Disclaimer, Privacy Policy, TOS Page Generator)<br /></li><li> Create Your Own Designs And Export Them To Your Clients' Sites <br /></li></ul><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Insta Builder 2.1.6" title="Insta Builder 2.1.6"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Profit Canvas Pro 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1425-profit-canvas-pro.html</link>
<description>Name : Profit Canvas Version : Pro 1.0 OS : Linux Type : Page Builder Plugin Price : $497 Homepage : SalePage A $50,000.00+ SOFTWARE SUITE You may have seen tiny pieces of software like this selling for $1,000+ WITH monthly fees... So this deal will shock you!</description>
<category>Page Builder Plugins</category>
<enclosure url="http://profitcanvas.com/images2/pcipad.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2015 20:38:57 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FIRST... THE WORLD&#039;S BEST PAGE BUILDER SOFTWARE SECOND... CASH COW VIDEO SOFTWARE: THIRD... LIVE WEBINAR PRESENTATION SOFTWARE: FORTH...PLACE A GORGEOUS &quot;POP UP&quot; OVER ANY WEBSITE YOU WANT A drag-and-drop page builder that allows you to create squeeze pages, video landing pages with calls-to-action inside the video, webinar pages, salesletters, and CPA landing pages. Over 75 ready made templates Many ready-made templates that look great. You can use a visual editor to modify them and use them in your own marketing. You can create a page online and then link directly to it, without downloading or uploading anything. You can also download the page, and upload it to your own site if you want. Publish to Facebook</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<br /><div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/opZB1AqsRmg?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> FIRST... THE WORLD'S BEST PAGE BUILDER SOFTWARE<br /></li><li> SECOND... CASH COW VIDEO SOFTWARE:<br /></li><li> THIRD... LIVE WEBINAR PRESENTATION SOFTWARE:<br /></li><li> FORTH...PLACE A GORGEOUS "POP UP" OVER ANY WEBSITE YOU WANT<br /></li><li> A drag-and-drop page builder that allows you to create squeeze pages, video landing pages with calls-to-action inside the video, webinar pages, salesletters, and CPA landing pages.<br /></li><li> Over 75 ready made templates<br /></li><li> Many ready-made templates that look great. You can use a visual editor to modify them and use them in your own marketing.<br /></li><li> You can create a page online and then link directly to it, without downloading or uploading anything.<br /></li><li> You can also download the page, and upload it to your own site if you want.<br /></li><li> Publish to Facebook<br /><br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://profitcanvas.com/images2/pcipad.png" alt="Profit Canvas Pro 1.0" title="Profit Canvas Pro 1.0"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Profit Canvas Pro 1.0" title="Profit Canvas Pro 1.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>