<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>LinkedIN Marketing - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>LinkedIN Marketing - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>LinkedDominator 3.5.0.18</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/896-linkeddominator.html</link>
<description>Name :LinkedDominator Version : 3.5.0.18 OS : Windows Type : Linkedin Marketing Price : $1499 Homepage : SalePage With a growing base of more than 300 million users, LinkedIn has become more than just a digital resume database. LinkedIn is considered the world&#039;s largest audience of influential, affluent professionals at one place. An estimated 50% of LinkedIn users are the final decision makers for their companies. Marketing on LinkedIn definitely needs your full consideration if you want your business to succeed and grow. LinkedIn provides numerous social media advertising solutions to increase brand awareness and lead generation. You can reach the most influential and educated audience with your well-managed LinkedIn marketing strategies. But are you happy with how you are using LinkedIn? If you are going to get the most from LinkedIn you will need to do more than just list yourself. Here&#039;s where LinkedDominator comes to your rescue!!!</description>
<category>LinkedIN Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 06:06:39 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Linkedin Search : If you want to search people or company information by their name then you can use this feature to have the details of their profiles. Compose Message : Send direct messages to all your first connections in no time. Linkedin Scrapper : Scrap the data you need for your robust social media marketing initiatives and campaigns. Add Connection : Add connection easily through email or just key words. Msg Group Member : Instantly message many group members outside your.comwork . Create Group : Create groups and send invites to join the group in jiffy. Join Friends Group : Join your friend&#039;s all/specific groups you want Join Search Group : Find groups for a particular niche and join them right there Group Status Update : Post updates to your required groups easily. :::Free Members ::: Download Now Password : www.tgmember.com :::ViP Only:::</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ckh7Qpl1s2Y?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Linkedin Search : If you want to search people or company information by their name then you can use this feature to have the details of their profiles.<br></li><li> Compose Message : Send direct messages to all your first connections in no time.<br></li><li> Linkedin Scrapper : Scrap the data you need for your robust social media marketing initiatives and campaigns.<br></li><li> Add Connection : Add connection easily through email or just key words.<br></li><li> Msg Group Member : Instantly message many group members outside your.comwork .<br></li><li> Create Group : Create groups and send invites to join the group in jiffy.<br></li><li> Join Friends Group : Join your friend's all/specific groups you want<br></li><li> Join Search Group : Find groups for a particular niche and join them right there<br></li><li> Group Status Update : Post updates to your required groups easily.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><span style="font-size:12pt;"><b><span style="color:#006600">:::Free Members :::</span></b></span><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="LinkedDominator 3.5.0.18"><br><div class="quote"><br><a href="http://31.220.48.156/engine/go.php?url=aHR0cDovL3VzZXJzZmlsZXMuY29tL242OXcyMzR6Mmx4eg%3D%3D"  target="_blank">Download Now</a><br>Password : www.tgmember.com<br></div><br></div><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><span style="font-size:12pt;"><b><span style="color:#FF0000">:::ViP Only:::</span></b></span><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Linkedomata 2.0.2.104</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1383-linkedomata.html</link>
<description>Name : Linkedomata Version : 2.0.2.104 OS : Windows Type : linkedin Marketing Tools Price : $157 Homepage : SalePage Linkedomata helps you to overcome the In-mail limitation by allowing you to automate linkedin process of sending a message along with a connection request. The linkedin message can be personalized in-depth by including the first name , company , location , job title of connection to whom you are sending message.</description>
<category>LinkedIN Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 04:12:10 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Manage multiple LinkedIn accounts Automate Add New Connection to 2nd , 3rd degree connections Advance search incorporated with filters. Create and Import Multiple Searches directly into Linkedomata. Automatically fill Search parameters in Linkedin from LinkedOMata. Automate sending Messages to 1st degree connections. Get Top Level Connection Details of your Network Connections.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/dQO-BzXD4vQ?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Manage multiple LinkedIn accounts<br></li><li> Automate Add New Connection to 2nd , 3rd degree connections<br></li><li> Advance search incorporated with filters.<br></li><li> Create and Import Multiple Searches directly into Linkedomata.<br></li><li> Automatically fill Search parameters in Linkedin from LinkedOMata.<br></li><li> Automate sending Messages to 1st degree connections.<br></li><li> Get Top Level Connection Details of your Network Connections.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Linkedomata 2.0.2.104"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Hot Prospector 3.9.26</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1218-hot-prospector.html</link>
<description>Name : Hot Prospector - Hot Lead Finder Version : 3.9.26 OS : Windows/MAC Type : Lead Marketing Tools, Gplus Lead Marketing Tools, Linkedin Lead Marketing Tools Price : $2997 Homepage : SalePage Attention Local Marketing Consultants: Get a 10 Marketing Tools for the price of ONE! You Must Have this Tool in Your Arsenal for your Offline Marketing Business. Start Turning Your Leads Into Customers!</description>
<category>LinkedIN Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2017 22:11:13 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Inbound call tracking – Track your results on multiple campaigns with ease. Set up unlimited inbound numbers to monitor all of your advertising efforts. Google PPC, Facebook, Craigslist, Yahoo, Bing…you name it, you can track it! Customize Phone System – Drag and drop your way to your very own Virtual Phone System or PBX with all the bells and whistles. Call menus, call transfer, personal greetings and much more! Inbound Marketing Campaigns – Create custom call groups and transfer calls simultaneously to your sales teams, support agents or even use it to distribute leads to multiple clients at the same time. Appointment Manager and Online Scheduler (With Google Calendar Sync) – Create and share UNLIMITED calendars, with custom forms! Use our widget on your website to allow your customers to view your availability and schedule and book an appointments in real time. Integrate the calendar into our power dialer and allow agents to book appointments for you or clients with one click! Elite Mass Email System – Create, schedule and send thousands of text or html based emails with ease from multiple SMTP accounts. Perfect for bypassing SMTP send limits from hosting providers and blasting out your message to that masses. SMS Marketing System – Build unlimited text message marketing campaigns and send unlimited text messages for either you or on behalf of your clients. Texts pricing starts at just 1cpm in USA and Canada. Phone numbers available in over 40 countries and can send messages to most countries and phone carriers. Blazing Fast Voice Broadcast System – Powerful system allows you to send out thousands of voice calls with an option to press any digit on their phone and be connected live. Calls pricing start out at just 2cpm in USA and Canada. Phone numbers available to purchase from over 40 countries and can call over 208 countries worldwide! Unlimited Outbound Power Dial Campaigns – More than just phone dialer, this powerful dialing software eliminates tedious hand dialing and increases productivity by more than triple! It’s simple, just “hit start” and our system will go to work and start making your calls. Fully Expandable – Add your team now, or later. We’ve got you covered and will grow with you. Single user for a small office or 100 users in a large call center, no matter the size of your business, Hot Prospector is your perfect choice solution. Low Rates – Calling rates start at just 2cpm in the USA and Canada. Available in most countries too, purchase phone numbers from over 40 countries and call to over 208 countries worldwide! Contact Control Panel – Instantly get to know your prospect with Google Maps, Local Weather Reports, Website Grade Reports, and previous notes at your fingertips. Progressive Dialing – Click start and sit back. All calls are made for you. No answer, no problem. Hot Prospector will skip to the next lead automatically. Voice Mail Forwarding – No need to stop and fumble for answering machines or voicemails. Create unlimited voicemail templates to send them instantly while you move to the next lead. Appointment Setter Calendar Integration – Book appointments and automatically add them to you or your customer’s calendar with just a click. Assisted Voice Broadcasts – Allow your agents to ask permission and play an automated message to live callers (with an option to be transferred) so you can get more qualified leads and guarantee your message is delivered consistently every call. “One click “call back scheduler – Create and send customized email and text message reminders to you and your customer and ensure you’ll never miss another opportunity to close a sale again. Triggered Email and SMS templates – Save time and increase productivity by creating and sending template emails, custom email proposals or text messages that are trigged by a call status and sent to your prospect instantly. Custom Call Status – Manage leads and calls better by assigning default or customize call statuses as you dial. Now you can effectively track the number of voicemails left or even monitor the number of answering machines, no answers, bad numbers you or your agent are getting every day. Live Agent monitoring – Listen to calls or barge and talk on your agent calls for very effective coaching, training, quality assurance or provide assistance closing a deal. Outbound and Inbound Call Recording – Record all or none of your calls, it’s your choice. Perfect for identifying opportunities missed, improving scripts or objection handling. Full Agent Reporting – Track your agent’s daily, weekly and monthly performance with talk time reporting, number of calls made, call status tracking and more.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/GudOEBJ16pY?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Inbound call tracking – Track your results on multiple campaigns with ease. Set up unlimited inbound numbers to monitor all of your advertising efforts. Google PPC, Facebook, Craigslist, Yahoo, Bing…you name it, you can track it!<br></li><li> Customize Phone System – Drag and drop your way to your very own Virtual Phone System or PBX with all the bells and whistles. Call menus, call transfer, personal greetings and much more!<br></li><li> Inbound Marketing Campaigns – Create custom call groups and transfer calls simultaneously to your sales teams, support agents or even use it to distribute leads to multiple clients at the same time.<br></li><li> Appointment Manager and Online Scheduler (With Google Calendar Sync) – Create and share UNLIMITED calendars, with custom forms!  Use our widget on your website to allow your customers to view your availability and schedule and book an appointments in real time. Integrate the calendar into our power dialer and allow agents to book appointments for you or clients with one click!<br></li><li> Elite Mass Email System – Create, schedule and send thousands of text or html based emails with ease from multiple SMTP accounts. Perfect for bypassing SMTP send limits from hosting providers and blasting out your message to that masses.<br></li><li> SMS Marketing System – Build unlimited text message marketing campaigns and send unlimited text messages for either you or on behalf of your clients. Texts pricing starts at just 1cpm in USA and Canada. Phone numbers available in over 40 countries and can send messages to most countries and phone carriers.<br></li><li> Blazing Fast Voice Broadcast System – Powerful system allows you to send out thousands of voice calls with an option to press any digit on their phone and be connected live. Calls pricing start out at just 2cpm in USA and Canada. Phone numbers available to purchase from over 40 countries and can call over 208 countries worldwide!<br></li><li> Unlimited Outbound Power Dial Campaigns – More than just phone dialer, this powerful dialing software eliminates tedious hand dialing and increases productivity by more than triple! It’s simple, just “hit start” and our system will go to work and start making your calls.<br></li><li> Fully Expandable – Add your team now, or later. We’ve got you covered and will grow with you. Single user for a small office or 100 users in a large call center, no matter the size of your business, Hot Prospector is your perfect choice solution.<br></li><li> Low Rates – Calling rates start at just 2cpm in the USA and Canada. Available in most countries too, purchase phone numbers from over 40 countries and call to over 208 countries worldwide!<br></li><li> Contact Control Panel – Instantly get to know your prospect with Google Maps, Local Weather Reports, Website Grade Reports, and previous notes at your fingertips.<br></li><li> Progressive Dialing – Click start and sit back. All calls are made for you. No answer, no problem. Hot Prospector will skip to the next lead automatically.<br></li><li> Voice Mail Forwarding – No need to stop and fumble for answering machines or voicemails. Create unlimited voicemail templates to send them instantly while you move to the next lead.<br></li><li> Appointment Setter Calendar Integration – Book appointments and automatically add them to you or your customer’s calendar with just a click.<br></li><li> Assisted Voice Broadcasts – Allow your agents to ask permission and play an automated message to live callers (with an option to be transferred) so you can get more qualified leads and guarantee your message is delivered consistently every call.<br></li><li>  “One click “call back scheduler – Create and send customized email and text message reminders  to you and your customer and ensure you’ll never miss another opportunity to close a sale again.<br></li><li> Triggered Email and SMS templates – Save time and increase productivity by creating and sending template emails, custom email proposals or text messages that are trigged by a call status and sent to your prospect instantly.<br></li><li> Custom Call Status – Manage leads and calls better by assigning default or customize call statuses as you dial. Now you can effectively track the number of voicemails left or even monitor the number of answering machines, no answers, bad numbers you or your agent are getting every day.<br></li><li> Live Agent monitoring – Listen to calls or barge and talk on your agent calls for very effective coaching, training, quality assurance or provide assistance closing a deal.<br></li><li> Outbound and Inbound Call Recording – Record all or none of your calls, it’s your choice. Perfect for identifying opportunities missed, improving scripts or objection handling.<br></li><li> Full Agent Reporting – Track your agent’s daily, weekly and monthly performance with talk time reporting, number of calls made, call status tracking and more.<br><br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Hot Prospector 3.9.26"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Social Lead Machine 2.0.2</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2063-social-lead-machine.html</link>
<description>Name : Social Lead Machine Version : 2.0.2 OS : Windows Type : Linkedin Marketing Tools Price : $45/M Homepage : SalePage Easily increase views to your LinkedIn profile and turn cold leads into warm prospects. Gain more visits to your LinkedIn profile, build your social media.comworks, monitor your prospects&#039; activities and find quality leads with this Chrome extension.</description>
<category>LinkedIN Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2016 10:03:22 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Social Lead Machine will help you: meet your monthly revenue goals land new contracts, sign more deals consistently generate traffic, referrals and sales for your business</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/mrz3EU7HBwk?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><p><br></p><br><h3>Features</h3><br><p><br>Social Lead Machine will help you:<br><br><ul><li> meet your monthly revenue goals<br></li><li> land new contracts, sign more deals<br></li><li> consistently generate traffic, referrals and sales for your business<br></li></ul></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Social Lead Machine 2.0.2"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Linkedin Marketing 2016 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2015-linkedin-marketing.html</link>
<description>Name : Linkedin Marketing Version : 2016 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Linkedin Marketing Tools Price : $50 Linkedin Marketing will have you automate add connect, message..and more</description>
<category>LinkedIN Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://i.imgur.com/fbtEV6i.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2016 03:05:17 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features - Auto Add Connection - Message to People</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br />- Auto Add Connection<br />- Message to People<br /><br /><img src="http://i.imgur.com/fbtEV6i.png" alt="Linkedin Marketing 2016 1.0" title="Linkedin Marketing 2016 1.0"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Linkedin Marketing 2016 1.0" title="Linkedin Marketing 2016 1.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>LinkedIn Missing Data Extractor 3.1.5</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1838-linkedin-missing-data-extractor.html</link>
<description>Name : LinkedIn Missing Data Extractor Version : 3.1.5 OS : Windows Type : Linkedin Marketing Tools Price : $50 Homepage : SalePage LinkedIn Missing Data Extractor extracts LinkedIn profiles&#039; missing contact information like email address, phone number, messenger IDs. It takes LinkedIn profiles list as an input to extract email, phone, messenger Ids from search engines, websites list. LinkedIn Missing Data Extractor is the supporting software to LinkedIn Lead Extractor, LinkedIn Sales Navigator Extractor, LinkedIn Recruiter Extractor, LinkedIn Company Extractor software. It takes LinkedIn profiles (exported by LinkedIn Extractor software) as an input and extracts missing information like email address, phone number, skype ids, icq ids from search engines, websites list. You can export searched information in .XLSX, .CSV file (Opens in EXCEL), TAB delimited .TXT file. It has easy-to-use, straightforward and user friendly user interface.</description>
<category>LinkedIN Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.ahmadsoftware.com/upload/LinkedIn-missing-data-extractor.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2016 05:54:59 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Email Extractor : &quot;LinkedIn Missing Data Extractor&quot; searches for email addresses by using its multithreading power to run the process quickly. Phone Extractor : Search phone numbers on specified sites, or search by keyword, selecting suitable sites in search engines. Instant Contact Extractor : The software is capable of finding not only email addresses and phone numbers, but also Messenger IDs such as Skype, ICQ, AIM, MSN. Save Bandwidth and Time : To save bandwidth and precious time it has an option &quot;Don&#039;t allow recrawling of already crawled pages in new searches&quot;. Auto-save and Recovery : Sometimes computer/software shuts-down unexpectedly; don&#039;t worry you can recover your search results just by one click. Inte.com Failure Detector : &quot;LinkedIn Missing Data Extractor&quot; automatically pauses/resumes on inte.com failure during processing. Unicode Support : &quot;LinkedIn Missing Data Extractor&quot; support unicode contacts. You can also save fetched contacts in unicode format. Customizeable Crawler : User can customize the crawler behaviour according to his needs. Proxy Support : In case if any site or search engine block the IP, you can add proxy-settings. Big Search Engine List : &quot;LinkedIn Missing Data Extractor&quot; support more than 66 search engines. You can search according to your country. Export : You can export in .xlsx files, .CSV files (Opens in EXCEL), TAB delimited (.txt files) format opens in NOTEPAD. It is best tool for businesses to get necessary business contact information from sources ranging from business directories to search engines. Used primarily by marketing consultants for businesses quickly looking to find leads for their companies. This piece of software has a multi-threading system, in which the contact information is being searched can be found at an exhilarated speed, without compromising computer performance.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/n7nGi4QqM9k?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Email Extractor : "LinkedIn Missing Data Extractor" searches for email addresses by using its multithreading power to run the process quickly.<br /></li><li> Phone Extractor : Search phone numbers on specified sites, or search by keyword, selecting suitable sites in search engines.<br /></li><li> Instant Contact Extractor : The software is capable of finding not only email addresses and phone numbers, but also Messenger IDs such as Skype, ICQ, AIM, MSN.<br /></li><li> Save Bandwidth and Time : To save bandwidth and precious time it has an option "Don't allow recrawling of already crawled pages in new searches".<br /></li><li> Auto-save and Recovery : Sometimes computer/software shuts-down unexpectedly; don't worry you can recover your search results just by one click.<br /></li><li> Inte.com Failure Detector : "LinkedIn Missing Data Extractor" automatically pauses/resumes on inte.com failure during processing.<br /></li><li> Unicode Support : "LinkedIn Missing Data Extractor" support unicode contacts. You can also save fetched contacts in unicode format.<br /></li><li> Customizeable Crawler : User can customize the crawler behaviour according to his needs.<br /></li><li> Proxy Support : In case if any site or search engine block the IP, you can add proxy-settings.<br /></li><li> Big Search Engine List : "LinkedIn Missing Data Extractor" support more than 66 search engines. You can search according to your country.<br /></li><li> Export : You can export in .xlsx files, .CSV files (Opens in EXCEL), TAB delimited (.txt files) format opens in NOTEPAD.<br /></li><li> It is best tool for businesses to get necessary business contact information from sources ranging from business directories to search engines. Used primarily by marketing consultants for businesses quickly looking to find leads for their companies.<br /></li><li> This piece of software has a multi-threading system, in which the contact information is being searched can be found at an exhilarated speed, without compromising computer performance. <br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://www.ahmadsoftware.com/upload/LinkedIn-missing-data-extractor.png" alt="LinkedIn Missing Data Extractor 3.1.5" title="LinkedIn Missing Data Extractor 3.1.5"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="LinkedIn Missing Data Extractor 3.1.5" title="LinkedIn Missing Data Extractor 3.1.5"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Linkedin Lead Extractor 3.0.8.1</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1374-linkedin-lead-extractor.html</link>
<description>Name : Linkedin Lead Extractor Version : 3.0.8.1 OS : Windows Type : Linkedin Marketing Tools Price : $70 Homepage : SalePage LinkedIn Lead Extractor extracts data from Linkedin. This tool can captures contact information such as name, email, business name, address, phone number, websites, country, profile link and other important information from LinkedIn. Tired of Copying Linkedin Leads Into Excel Spreadsheets? If yes &quot;Linkedin Lead Extractor&quot; is the right choice saving your valuable time and money. Linkedin is the best source of contact information of professionals worldwide with 120 million users and extensive targeting capabilities to allure advertisers. You can approach Physicians to freshly baked food providers listed on Linkedin in through our Linkedin in Lead Extractor. If your product is particularly useful for community e.g selling surgical apparatus to hospitals you can get contact information of the Administrators rightly divided up by category on Linkedin in. Simple searches in your field will reveal thousands of experts, service providers and potential clients. Linkedin in Lead Extractor will help you to extract that data within minutes. Linkedin Lead Extractor is a desktop application which allows you to extract endless number of data from Linkedin at an exceptionally fast rate. It automatically extracts Business Name, Email, Phone Address, Yahoo messenger id, Skype Id, Google Talk ID, etc. You can export your data in .xlsx, .csv,(opens in excel) .txt files.</description>
<category>LinkedIN Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://ahmadsoftware.com/upload/LinkedIn-Lead-Extractor.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2016 05:54:47 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Extract Leads : Linkedin Lead Extractor can extract your targeted customer&#039;s Linkedin contact information and complete profile. Keyword based searching : Lead Extractor searches your targeted customers based on your search keywords. Advance Search : Using LinkedIn Advanced search feature, search for people by keywords, industry, location, company, experience level, and more. Unicode Support : Linkedin Lead Extractor support Unicode character-set. You can save fetched search results in Unicode format. Inte.com Failure Detector : Linkedin Lead Extractor automatically pauses/resumes on inte.com failure during processing. Contacts Filtering : You can also apply filters to get your targeted contact list. Export Data : Software provides options to save e-mail addresses in EXCEL format, .CSV files (Opens in EXCEL), TAB delimited (.txt files) format. Why Use LinkedIn Lead Extractor? LinkedIn has been creating buzz in social media circles for many years now, however many businesses are yet to fully capitalize on this remarkable tool for their online marketing and promotional needs. LinkedIn Lead Extractor is the best tool to get contact information from LinkedIn according to your business needs. Something about what is LinkedIn? This might appear a rather simplistic question; however it&#039;s important to understand that LinkedIn is not merely a social.comwork aimed for business users. Rather, it should be viewed as an online.comwork of influential people all over the world. For most individuals, gaining contact with the most powerful people in business is one of their biggest challenges. Getting round conventional &#039;real-life&#039; obstacles, LinkedIn essentially brings business people together in a new and unique way. If utilised properly, this tool can even allow the humble office junior to engage in discussion and build connections with company CEOs. Find Business Partners, Clients and Service Providers Whatever your business objectives, LinkedIn will help you to build a.comwork of useful contacts. Simple searches in your field will reveal thousands of experts, service providers and potential clients. If you do not personally know an individual, you may request to be introduced through a mutual contact or can send an introductory email. Recruitment If your business is recruiting, LinkedIn can provide easy access to potential candidates. There are both paid options and those involving no financial outlay. Businesses can search for candidates that fit their required level of expertise and approach them directly, provided they are at least &#039;2nd degree&#039; contacts. In order to search further afield, a monthly subsciption is needed. However, even the basic or &#039;business&#039; package allows users to contact any individual with a LinkedIn profile.Whatever your recruitment objectives, LinkedIn is the ideal.comworking site to find the connections you need to grow your business and here is LinkedIn Lead extractor to help you.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/6qJqBbWXDEA?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Extract Leads : Linkedin Lead Extractor can extract your targeted customer's Linkedin contact information and complete profile.<br /></li><li> Keyword based searching : Lead Extractor searches your targeted customers based on your search keywords.<br /></li><li> Advance Search : Using LinkedIn Advanced search feature, search for people by keywords, industry, location, company, experience level, and more.<br /></li><li> Unicode Support : Linkedin Lead Extractor support Unicode character-set. You can save fetched search results in Unicode format.<br /></li><li> Inte.com Failure Detector : Linkedin Lead Extractor automatically pauses/resumes on inte.com failure during processing.<br /></li><li> Contacts Filtering : You can also apply filters to get your targeted contact list.<br /></li><li> Export Data : Software provides options to save e-mail addresses in EXCEL format, .CSV files (Opens in EXCEL), TAB delimited (.txt files) format.<br /><br /></li></ul><br /><b>Why Use LinkedIn Lead Extractor?</b><br />LinkedIn has been creating buzz in social media circles for many years now, however many businesses are yet to fully capitalize on this remarkable tool for their online marketing and promotional needs. LinkedIn Lead Extractor is the best tool to get contact information from LinkedIn according to your business needs.<br /><br /><b>Something about what is LinkedIn?</b><br />This might appear a rather simplistic question; however it's important to understand that LinkedIn is not merely a social.comwork aimed for business users. Rather, it should be viewed as an online.comwork of influential people all over the world. For most individuals, gaining contact with the most powerful people in business is one of their biggest challenges. Getting round conventional 'real-life' obstacles, LinkedIn essentially brings business people together in a new and unique way. If utilised properly, this tool can even allow the humble office junior to engage in discussion and build connections with company CEOs.<br /><br /><b>Find Business Partners, Clients and Service Providers</b><br />Whatever your business objectives, LinkedIn will help you to build a.comwork of useful contacts. Simple searches in your field will reveal thousands of experts, service providers and potential clients. If you do not personally know an individual, you may request to be introduced through a mutual contact or can send an introductory email.<br /><br /><b>Recruitment</b><br />If your business is recruiting, LinkedIn can provide easy access to potential candidates. There are both paid options and those involving no financial outlay. Businesses can search for candidates that fit their required level of expertise and approach them directly, provided they are at least '2nd degree' contacts. In order to search further afield, a monthly subsciption is needed. However, even the basic or 'business' package allows users to contact any individual with a LinkedIn profile.Whatever your recruitment objectives, LinkedIn is the ideal.comworking site to find the connections you need to grow your business and here is LinkedIn Lead extractor to help you. <br /><br /><img src="http://ahmadsoftware.com/upload/LinkedIn-Lead-Extractor.png" alt="Linkedin Lead Extractor 3.0.8.1" title="Linkedin Lead Extractor 3.0.8.1"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Linkedin Lead Extractor 3.0.8.1" title="Linkedin Lead Extractor 3.0.8.1"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>LinkedIn Company Extractor 3.0.6.1</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1624-linkedin-company-extractor.html</link>
<description>Name : LinkedIn Company Extractor Version : 3.0.6.1 OS : Windows Type : LinkedIn Marketing Tools Price : $60 Homepage : SalePage LinkedIn Company Extractor extracts companies profiles data on LinkedIn. It automatically extracts companies information like LinkedIn profile link, Business Name, Company Size, Followers, Website, Year founded, Industry, company type, Specialties, Address, postcode, and Country name etc. You can export your data in .xlsx, .csv,(opens in excel) .txt files LinkedIn Company Extractor is a desktop application which allows you to extract endless number of companies&#039; data from LinkedIn at an exceptionally fast rate. It automatically extracts LinkedIn profile link, Business Name, Company Size, Followers, Website, Year founded, Industry, company type, Specialties, Address, postcode, and Country name etc. You can export your data in .xlsx, .csv,(opens in excel) .txt files.</description>
<category>LinkedIN Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://ahmadsoftware.com/upload/LinkedInCompanyExtractor.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2016 05:54:37 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Extract Leads : LinkedIn Company Extractor can extract your targeted companies&#039; information from Linkedin. Keyword based searching : Lead Extractor searches your targeted companies based on your search keywords. Advance Search : Using LinkedIn Advanced search feature, search for companies by keywords, industry, location, company, and more. Auto-save and Recovery : Sometimes computer/software shut-downs unexpectedly; don&#039;t worry you can recover your search results just by one click. Save Viewed Profiles History : LinkedIn Company Extractor has the ability to save the history of viewed and saved companies so that already saved companies profiles should not view again. Delay Option : Option to set delay between requests to simulate as is human being is surfing in a browser. Unicode Support : LinkedIn Company Extractor support Unicode character-set. You can save fetched search results in Unicode format. Inte.com Failure Detector : LinkedIn Company Extractor automatically pauses/resumes on inte.com failure during processing. Contacts Filtering : You can also apply filters to get your targeted contact list. Export Data : Software provides options to save e-mail addresses in EXCEL format, .CSV files (Opens in EXCEL), TAB delimited (.txt files) format. LinkedIn has some commercial use limitations on search: Basic Account: 100 profiles daily. LinkedIn Premium Account: Free: 100 profiles daily. Business Plus: 500 profiles daily. Executive: 700 profiles daily. Pro: 1,000 profiles daily. For reading commercial use limitations on LinkedIn click More LinkedIn also blocks user accounts/IP address if too many requests are fired within a certain time limit. For example 150 - 200 requests in 2 - 3 minutes. User can see Email address, Phone, Website, Address of the connections only if LinkedIn member has made it publicaly available. The product may not work properly or show error if there is any change in linkedin.com structure.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/6qJqBbWXDEA?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Extract Leads : LinkedIn Company Extractor can extract your targeted companies' information from Linkedin.<br /></li><li> Keyword based searching : Lead Extractor searches your targeted companies based on your search keywords.<br /></li><li> Advance Search : Using LinkedIn Advanced search feature, search for companies by keywords, industry, location, company, and more.<br /></li><li> Auto-save and Recovery : Sometimes computer/software shut-downs unexpectedly; don't worry you can recover your search results just by one click.<br /></li><li> Save Viewed Profiles History : LinkedIn Company Extractor has the ability to save the history of viewed and saved companies so that already saved companies profiles should not view again.<br /></li><li> Delay Option : Option to set delay between requests to simulate as is human being is surfing in a browser.<br /></li><li> Unicode Support : LinkedIn Company Extractor support Unicode character-set. You can save fetched search results in Unicode format.<br /></li><li> Inte.com Failure Detector : LinkedIn Company Extractor automatically pauses/resumes on inte.com failure during processing.<br /></li><li> Contacts Filtering : You can also apply filters to get your targeted contact list.<br /></li><li> Export Data : Software provides options to save e-mail addresses in EXCEL format, .CSV files (Opens in EXCEL), TAB delimited (.txt files) format.<br /></li></ul><br /><b>LinkedIn has some commercial use limitations on search:<br /></b><ul><li> Basic Account: 100 profiles daily.<br /></li><li> LinkedIn Premium Account:<br /></li><li> Free: 100 profiles daily.<br /></li><li> Business Plus: 500 profiles daily.<br /></li><li> Executive: 700 profiles daily.<br /></li><li> Pro: 1,000 profiles daily.<br /></li><li> For reading commercial use limitations on LinkedIn click More<br /></li><li> LinkedIn also blocks user accounts/IP address if too many requests are fired within a certain time limit. For example 150 - 200 requests in 2 - 3 minutes. User can see Email address, Phone, Website, Address of the connections only if LinkedIn member has made it publicaly available.<br /></li><li> The product may not work properly or show error if there is any change in linkedin.com structure.<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://ahmadsoftware.com/upload/LinkedInCompanyExtractor.png" alt="LinkedIn Company Extractor 3.0.6.1" title="LinkedIn Company Extractor 3.0.6.1"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="LinkedIn Company Extractor 3.0.6.1" title="LinkedIn Company Extractor 3.0.6.1"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>LinkedIn Sale Navigator Extractor 3.1.8.1</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1626-linkedin-sale-navigator-extractor.html</link>
<description>Name : LinkedIn Sale Navigator Extractor Version : 3.1.8.1 OS : Windows Type : Linkedin Marketing Tools Price : $70 Homepage : SalePage LinkedIn Sale Navigator Extractor extracts data from LinkedIn and Sales Navigator. This tool can captures contact information such as first name, last name, email, phone number, twitter, messenger id, job title, company, website, skills, industry, country, profile link from LinkedIn and Sale Navigator.</description>
<category>LinkedIN Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://ahmadsoftware.com/upload/linkedInLeadExtractorPlus.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2016 05:54:16 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Extract Leads : LinkedIn Sales Navigator Extractor can extract your targeted customer&#039;s Linkedin contact information and complete profile. Sales Navigator Support : It can extract your targeted customer&#039;s data from sales navigator. Keyword based searching : Lead Extractor searches your targeted customers based on your search keywords. Advance Search : Using LinkedIn Advanced search feature, search for people by keywords, industry, location, company, experience level, and more. Auto-save and Recovery : Sometimes computer/software shut-downs unexpectedly; don&#039;t worry you can recover your search results just by one click. Save Viewed Profiles History : LinkedIn Sales Navigator Extractor has the ability to save the history of viewed and saved profiles so that already saved profile should not view again. Delay Option : Option to set delay between requests to simulate as is human being is surfing in a browser. Unicode Support : LinkedIn Sales Navigator Extractor support Unicode character-set. You can save fetched search results in Unicode format. Inte.com Failure Detector : LinkedIn Sales Navigator Extractor automatically pauses/resumes on inte.com failure during processing. Contacts Filtering : You can also apply filters to get your targeted contact list. Export Data : Software provides options to save e-mail addresses in EXCEL format, .CSV files (Opens in EXCEL), TAB delimited (.txt files) format.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/6qJqBbWXDEA?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Extract Leads : LinkedIn Sales Navigator Extractor can extract your targeted customer's Linkedin contact information and complete profile.<br /></li><li> Sales Navigator Support : It can extract your targeted customer's data from sales navigator.<br /></li><li> Keyword based searching : Lead Extractor searches your targeted customers based on your search keywords.<br /></li><li> Advance Search : Using LinkedIn Advanced search feature, search for people by keywords, industry, location, company, experience level, and more.<br /></li><li> Auto-save and Recovery : Sometimes computer/software shut-downs unexpectedly; don't worry you can recover your search results just by one click.<br /></li><li> Save Viewed Profiles History : LinkedIn Sales Navigator Extractor has the ability to save the history of viewed and saved profiles so that already saved profile should not view again.<br /></li><li> Delay Option : Option to set delay between requests to simulate as is human being is surfing in a browser.<br /></li><li> Unicode Support : LinkedIn Sales Navigator Extractor support Unicode character-set. You can save fetched search results in Unicode format.<br /></li><li> Inte.com Failure Detector : LinkedIn Sales Navigator Extractor automatically pauses/resumes on inte.com failure during processing.<br /></li><li> Contacts Filtering : You can also apply filters to get your targeted contact list.<br /></li><li> Export Data : Software provides options to save e-mail addresses in EXCEL format, .CSV files (Opens in EXCEL), TAB delimited (.txt files) format.<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://ahmadsoftware.com/upload/linkedInLeadExtractorPlus.png" alt="LinkedIn Sale Navigator Extractor 3.1.8.1" title="LinkedIn Sale Navigator Extractor 3.1.8.1"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="LinkedIn Sale Navigator Extractor 3.1.8.1" title="LinkedIn Sale Navigator Extractor 3.1.8.1"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Linkedin Recruiter Extractor 3.1.8.1</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1625-linkedin-recruiter-extractor.html</link>
<description>Name : Linkedin Recruiter Extractor Version : 3.1.8.1 OS : Windows Type : Linkedin Marketing Tools Price : $100 Homepage : SalePage LinkedIn Recruiter Extractor extracts data from LinkedIn and LinkedIn Recruiter profiles. This tool can captures contact information such as first name, last name, email, phone number, twitter, messenger id, job title, company, website, skills, industry, country, profile link.</description>
<category>LinkedIN Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://ahmadsoftware.com/upload/LinkedIn-Lead-Extractor.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2016 05:54:05 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Extract Leads : LinkedIn Recruiter Extractor can extract your targeted customer&#039;s LinkedIn contact information and complete profile. Recruiter Account Support : It can extract your targeted customer&#039;s data from LinkedIn as well as LinkedIn Recruiter. Keyword based searching : Recruiter Extractor searches your targeted customers based on your search keywords. Advance Search : Using LinkedIn Advanced search feature, search for people by keywords, industry, location, company, experience level, and more. Auto-save and Recovery : Sometimes computer/software shut-downs unexpectedly; don&#039;t worry you can recover your search results just by one click. Save Viewed Profiles History : LinkedIn Recruiter Extractor has the ability to save the history of viewed and saved profiles so that already saved profile should not view again. Delay Option : Options to set fixed or random delay between requests to simulate as is human being is surfing in a browser. Unicode Support : LinkedIn Recruiter Extractor support Unicode character-set. You can save fetched search results in Unicode format. Inte.com Failure Detector : LinkedIn Recruiter Extractor automatically pauses/resumes on inte.com failure during processing. Contacts Filtering : You can also apply filters to get your targeted contact list. Export Data : Software provides options to save e-mail addresses in EXCEL format, .CSV files (Opens in EXCEL), TAB delimited (.txt files) format.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/6qJqBbWXDEA?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Extract Leads : LinkedIn Recruiter Extractor can extract your targeted customer's LinkedIn contact information and complete profile.<br /></li><li> Recruiter Account Support : It can extract your targeted customer's data from LinkedIn as well as LinkedIn Recruiter.<br /></li><li> Keyword based searching : Recruiter Extractor searches your targeted customers based on your search keywords.<br /></li><li> Advance Search : Using LinkedIn Advanced search feature, search for people by keywords, industry, location, company, experience level, and more.<br /></li><li> Auto-save and Recovery : Sometimes computer/software shut-downs unexpectedly; don't worry you can recover your search results just by one click.<br /></li><li> Save Viewed Profiles History : LinkedIn Recruiter Extractor has the ability to save the history of viewed and saved profiles so that already saved profile should not view again.<br /></li><li> Delay Option : Options to set fixed or random delay between requests to simulate as is human being is surfing in a browser.<br /></li><li> Unicode Support : LinkedIn Recruiter Extractor support Unicode character-set. You can save fetched search results in Unicode format.<br /></li><li> Inte.com Failure Detector : LinkedIn Recruiter Extractor automatically pauses/resumes on inte.com failure during processing.<br /></li><li> Contacts Filtering : You can also apply filters to get your targeted contact list.<br /></li><li> Export Data : Software provides options to save e-mail addresses in EXCEL format, .CSV files (Opens in EXCEL), TAB delimited (.txt files) format.<br /></li></ul><br /><br /><img src="http://ahmadsoftware.com/upload/LinkedIn-Lead-Extractor.png" alt="Linkedin Recruiter Extractor 3.1.8.1" title="Linkedin Recruiter Extractor 3.1.8.1"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Linkedin Recruiter Extractor 3.1.8.1" title="Linkedin Recruiter Extractor 3.1.8.1"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>