<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Apps Builder - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Apps Builder - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>Website 2 APK Builder 3.1 Pro Plus</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1783-website-2-apk-builder.html</link>
<description>Name : Website 2 APK Builder Version : 3.1 Pro Plus OS : Windows Type : APK Builder Price : $25 Homepage : SalePage WEBSITE 2 APK BUILDER Transform your site to an Android App. Convert your HTML, CSS, JS or Web URL to an Android App. Website 2 APK Builder is very easy to use, just make step by step customizations to your app, build while you finish it.</description>
<category>Apps Builder</category>
<enclosure url="http://html2apk.praveshagrawal.com/images/services/video.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2017 23:35:22 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features BOXED &amp;amp; WIDE LAYOUTS : We have prepared the best internal layout for app, so that your web content looks pretty well. ABOUT DIALOG: We have included about dialog in app, where you can set up your branding. M.COMIZE YOUR APPS: M.comize your apps with AdMob and start earning right now. HTML5 VIDEO SUPPORT: It supports HTML videos for online as well as offline apps. ENDLESS POSSIBILITIES: Complete control on each &amp;amp; every element that provides endless customization. SET CUSTOM ERROR PAGES: You can put custom error pages in your app to warn user if there is no.comwork available.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/8VCeSy1_bns?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" gesture="media" allow="encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> BOXED &amp; WIDE LAYOUTS : We have prepared the best internal layout for app, so that your web content looks pretty well.<br></li><li> ABOUT DIALOG: We have included about dialog in app, where you can set up your branding.<br></li><li> M.COMIZE YOUR APPS: M.comize your apps with AdMob and start earning right now.<br></li><li> HTML5 VIDEO SUPPORT: It supports HTML videos for online as well as offline apps.<br></li><li> ENDLESS POSSIBILITIES: Complete control on each &amp; every element that provides endless customization.<br></li><li> SET CUSTOM ERROR PAGES: You can put custom error pages in your app to warn user if there is no.comwork available.<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://html2apk.praveshagrawal.com/images/services/video.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Website 2 APK Builder 3.1 Pro Plus"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>App Builder 2018.17</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1826-app-builder.html</link>
<description>Name : App Builder Version : 2018.17 OS : Windows Type : Apk Builder Tools Price : $97 Homepage : SalePage App Builder is the first and unique visual development environment that allow you to create, with or without programming knowledge, HTML5 apps, WebApps, Progressive WebApps, WebExtensions and Hybrid apps for mobile and the desktop. App Builder is a complete development environment. Itself can create HTML5 apps, WebApps, Progressive WebApps and WebExtensions applications ready to run on desktop browsers and mobiles. Along with Apache Cordova ™ we also can build applications for platforms like as Android ™.</description>
<category>Apps Builder</category>
<enclosure url="https://www.davidesperalta.com/Humm/Sites/Main/Views/Images/AppBuilder/Capture01.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 02:09:21 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Visual designer: App Builder has a visual editor for quick and fast application development. Visual actions: You do not need jаvascript knowledge to create applications with App Builder. Integrated debugger: Also save time with the integrated debugger, fast and easy to use. WebExtensions! Deploy also your applications as WebExtensions for the modern browsers. Apache Cordova.You can also build your apps to be deployed in Windows 10, Android, iOS and others! App Builder CLI:App Builder include a command line compiler in addition with the visual environment. In this way we can compile our applications from the command line, simply and fast. And many more...</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/7Xg8-ZsV2Ws?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" gesture="media" allow="encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Visual designer: App Builder has a visual editor for quick and fast application development.<br></li><li> Visual actions: You do not need jаvascript knowledge to create applications with App Builder.<br></li><li> Integrated debugger: Also save time with the integrated debugger, fast and easy to use.<br></li><li> WebExtensions! Deploy also your applications as WebExtensions for the modern browsers.<br></li><li> Apache Cordova.You can also build your apps to be deployed in Windows 10, Android, iOS and others!<br></li><li> App Builder CLI:App Builder include a command line compiler in addition with the visual environment. In this way we can compile our applications from the command line, simply and fast.<br></li><li> And many more...<br></li></ul><br><img src="https://www.davidesperalta.com/Humm/Sites/Main/Views/Images/AppBuilder/Capture01.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="App Builder 2018.17"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>RPG Maker MV 1.33</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2022-rpg-maker-mv.html</link>
<description>Name : RPG Maker MV Version : 1.33 OS : Windows Type : Mobile Game Creator Price : $79 Homepage : SalePage RPGMAKER was born to fulfill the desire of creating an original RPG without programming knowledge. Four years have passed since the release of the previous RPGMAKER, VX Ace. The landscape of gaming, especially for RPGs, has changed greatly. So did the needs of our users. With the latest installment, RPGMAKER MV allows the dreams of many of its fans to come true! RPGMAKER can now create RPGs for MacOSX, Android and iPhone!</description>
<category>Apps Builder</category>
<enclosure url="http://rsload.com/images5/RPGMakerMV.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2016 04:11:31 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features SAMPLE DATA INCLUDED RPG Maker MV Feature Map, effect and more, including rich sample data To help everyone create a game easily, we included some sample datas that you can easily use! We have over 100 Sample Maps, Character Generator Parts and more! RTP is now integrated in the engine to save the users trouble. j&amp;#097;vascript TO CREATE COMPLEX GAMES RPG Maker MV uses the well known j&amp;#097;vascript, in combination with HTML5 export. By mastering j&amp;#097;vascript, you will be able to change the game to your liking, from Battles to Menu UIs. This feature is oriented to experienced developers. You now have the ability to control all parts of the game. No more hidden classes! RPG Maker MV Feature j&amp;#097;vascript scripting MULTIPLATFORM DISTRIBUTION &amp; MAC SUPPORT RPG Maker MV Feature Multiplatform Distribution And Mac Support You can now create your own RPG Maker games on Macintosh. It will be released at the same time as the Windows version. RPG Maker MV users will be able to build games for the following platforms: Windows/EXE MacOSX/APP Android/APK iOS/IPA HTML 5 for Web Browsers MOUSE &amp; TOUCH INPUT SUPPORT Tired of doing all actions via the keyboard? You can now play your RPG with your finger on touch devices, and mouse on computers. RPG Maker MV Feature Mouse And Touch Input Support LARGE DATABASE RPG Maker MV Feature Large Database Support for twice as many items as VX Ace for a grand total of 2,000! BATTLE SYSTEM MODES With a tick of a checkbox, you can switch from the classic Front View Battle to Side View. RPG Maker MV Battle System Modes 01 RPG Maker MV Battle System Modes 02 THREE MAP LAYERS RPG Maker MV Feature Three Map Layers RPG Maker MV has an automated upper layer to make it easy to create and edit elaborate maps! HIGHER SCREEN RESOLUTION The previous RPG Maker&#039;s screen resolution was 544x416 pixels. RPG Maker MV&#039;s screen resolution is now 816x624 pixels. The size of all graphical assets (including animations) are now 1.5 times the previous versions of RPG Maker. For example, characters used to be 32x32, and now they are 48x48. RPG Maker MV Feature Higher Screen Resolution INTRODUCING PLUGIN MANAGER RPG Maker MV Feature Plugin Manager By adding js files in the project&#039;s plugin folder, you will be able to select the plugin in the Plugin Manager. You can see script details, script parameters and the ability to set it ON and OFF. Using Plugin Manager will be much easier to use than the old format. Allowing minimal user interference to prevent errors and easily order the scripts than the previous makers. EVENT SEARCHER One of the missed functions from RPG Maker 2003, The Event Search function is back! The bigger your game gets, the more Variables, Switches and Events you&#039;ll use. It quickly becomes harder to manage and find specific parameters. Using the Event Search tool will allow you to save time and quickly see all instances of a particular variable or switch!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/AdLt8ZcyCqA?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br />SAMPLE DATA INCLUDED<br /><br />RPG Maker MV Feature Map, effect and more, including rich sample data<br />To help everyone create a game easily, we included some sample datas that you can easily use! We have over 100 Sample Maps, Character Generator Parts and more! RTP is now integrated in the engine to save the users trouble.<br /><br />j&#097;vascript TO CREATE COMPLEX GAMES<br /><br />RPG Maker MV uses the well known j&#097;vascript, in combination with HTML5 export. By mastering j&#097;vascript, you will be able to change the game to your liking, from Battles to Menu UIs. This feature is oriented to experienced developers. You now have the ability to control all parts of the game. No more hidden classes!<br /><br />RPG Maker MV Feature j&#097;vascript scripting<br />MULTIPLATFORM DISTRIBUTION & MAC SUPPORT<br /><br />RPG Maker MV Feature Multiplatform Distribution And Mac Support<br />You can now create your own RPG Maker games on Macintosh. It will be released at the same time as the Windows version. RPG Maker MV users will be able to build games for the following platforms:<br /><br />Windows/EXE<br />MacOSX/APP<br />Android/APK<br />iOS/IPA<br />HTML 5 for Web Browsers<br />MOUSE & TOUCH INPUT SUPPORT<br /><br />Tired of doing all actions via the keyboard? You can now play your RPG with your finger on touch devices, and mouse on computers.<br /><br />RPG Maker MV Feature Mouse And Touch Input Support<br />LARGE DATABASE<br /><br />RPG Maker MV Feature Large Database<br />Support for twice as many items as VX Ace for a grand total of 2,000!<br /><br />BATTLE SYSTEM MODES<br /><br />With a tick of a checkbox, you can switch from the classic Front View Battle to Side View.<br /><br />RPG Maker MV Battle System Modes 01 RPG Maker MV Battle System Modes 02<br />THREE MAP LAYERS<br /><br />RPG Maker MV Feature Three Map Layers<br />RPG Maker MV has an automated upper layer to make it easy to create and edit elaborate maps!<br /><br />HIGHER SCREEN RESOLUTION<br /><br />The previous RPG Maker's screen resolution was 544x416 pixels. RPG Maker MV's screen resolution is now 816x624 pixels. The size of all graphical assets (including animations) are now 1.5 times the previous versions of RPG Maker. For example, characters used to be 32x32, and now they are 48x48.<br /><br />RPG Maker MV Feature Higher Screen Resolution<br />INTRODUCING PLUGIN MANAGER<br /><br />RPG Maker MV Feature Plugin Manager<br />By adding js files in the project's plugin folder, you will be able to select the plugin in the Plugin Manager. You can see script details, script parameters and the ability to set it ON and OFF. Using Plugin Manager will be much easier to use than the old format. Allowing minimal user interference to prevent errors and easily order the scripts than the previous makers.<br /><br />EVENT SEARCHER<br /><br />One of the missed functions from RPG Maker 2003, The Event Search function is back! The bigger your game gets, the more Variables, Switches and Events you'll use. It quickly becomes harder to manage and find specific parameters. Using the Event Search tool will allow you to save time and quickly see all instances of a particular variable or switch!<br /><br /><img src="http://rsload.com/images5/RPGMakerMV.jpg" alt="RPG Maker MV 1.33" title="RPG Maker MV 1.33"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="RPG Maker MV 1.33" title="RPG Maker MV 1.33"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>GameMaker Studio Master Collection 2.1.4.285</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2021-gamemaker-studio.html</link>
<description>Name : GameMaker Studio Master Collection Version : 2.1.4.285 OS : Windows Type : Mobile Game Creator Price : $399 Homepage : SalePage GameMaker Studio 2 is the latest and greatest incarnation of GameMaker! It has everything you need to take your idea from a concept to a finished game. With no barriers to entry and powerful functionality, GameMaker Studio 2 is the ultimate 2D development environment!</description>
<category>Apps Builder</category>
<enclosure url="http://my.smithmicro.com/images/photos/moho12-non-sale_1200x500px.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2016 04:03:42 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features ROOM EDITOR : Rooms in GameMaker are where everything happens in your game. With Layers, Inheritance, Tile Brushes, and more, GameMaker&#039;s Room Editor is better than ever. IMAGE EDITOR : Completely reworked and packed full of features our new Image Editor gives you the tools you need to create the assets you want for your games. TILESETS : Our new and powerful Tile Editor gives you a simple way to add a lot of content to your levels swiftly and efficiently. DRAG AND DROP : With more actions and the ability to see the code behind the DnD, we have made learning how to make a game easier than ever.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/GVb5py7QL3Q?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> ROOM EDITOR : Rooms in GameMaker are where everything happens in your game. With Layers, Inheritance, Tile Brushes, and more, GameMaker's Room Editor is better than ever.<br></li><li> IMAGE EDITOR : Completely reworked and packed full of features our new Image Editor gives you the tools you need to create the assets you want for your games.<br></li><li> TILESETS : Our new and powerful Tile Editor gives you a simple way to add a lot of content to your levels swiftly and efficiently.<br></li><li> DRAG AND DROP : With more actions and the ability to see the code behind the DnD, we have made learning how to make a game easier than ever.<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://my.smithmicro.com/images/photos/moho12-non-sale_1200x500px.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="GameMaker Studio Master Collection 2.1.4.285"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Buildbox 2.3.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1771-buildbox.html</link>
<description>Name : Buildbox Version : 2.3.0 OS : Windows Type : APK Builder Price : $997 Homepage : SalePage Buildbox is the easiest drag and drop game maker software.Make your own games without coding and export them to iPhone, iPad, Android, Mac, PC and ...</description>
<category>Apps Builder</category>
<enclosure url="https://i.imgur.com/7lhmBaT.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 21:17:23 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features True Drag and Drop Creation : With Buildbox, creating games does not require any programming or scripting skills. Simply import images, assign them properties and move them around your game scene. Use one of our many presets to get started and preview your game in real time. Unlimited Gameplay Possibillities : With Buildbox 2.0, the possibilities are endless. You can now create nearly any 2D game imaginable with the help of our gameplay settings, character settings, logic pieces and new component control. Chart Topping Games Made Here : Since it’s release, Buildbox has made more Apple Features and Top 100 hits than any other drag and drop game builder</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ua1O_Q0Tikg?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> True Drag and Drop Creation : With Buildbox, creating games does not require any programming or scripting skills.  Simply import images, assign them properties and move them around your game scene.  Use one of our many presets to get started and preview your game in real time.<br></li><li> Unlimited Gameplay Possibillities : With Buildbox 2.0, the possibilities are endless.  You can now create nearly any 2D game imaginable with the help of our gameplay settings, character settings, logic pieces and new component control.<br></li><li> Chart Topping Games Made Here : Since it’s release, Buildbox has made more Apple Features and Top 100 hits than any other drag and drop game builder<br></li></ul><br><img src="https://i.imgur.com/7lhmBaT.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Buildbox 2.3.0"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Xojo 2016 r3</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1848-xojo-2016.html</link>
<description>Name : Xojo 2016 Version : r3 OS : Windows Type : Mobile App Creator Price : $699 Homepage : SalePage Create powerful, native apps for desktop, web, iOS &amp; Raspberry Pi™ Fast development. Easy deployment. Create native cross-platform desktop, web, mobile &amp; Raspberry Pi apps</description>
<category>Apps Builder</category>
<enclosure url="https://app-universe.com/site/assets/files/1201/8d93q-top.736x0.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2016 20:44:35 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Create Anything With built-in support for graphics, database servers, inte.com protocols and more, you can build just about anything you can imagine with Xojo. Using Xojo, you can make commercial software products, utilities to help make your life easier, or even learn to program. In fact, Xojo itself is a Xojo app! Build Apps 10x Faster You can use one set of source code to support multiple platforms and there are over 40 user interface controls built in, allowing your app to look and behave how you’d want it to on any platform. On the web you can use one powerful language to create your web app instead of HTML, CSS, PHP, j&amp;#097;vascript, or AJAX, saving you tons of development time! Modern Development Xojo is a modern, object-oriented language. It supports inheritance, interfaces, polymorphism and is strongly-typed as well. There are thousands of differences in OS API calls and Xojo abstracts you from these details, dramatically reducing development time and allowing you to focus on what makes your application unique. Native, Cross-Platform Xojo apps don’t have an interpreter or virtual machine – they’re compiled to machine code for fast execution and the protection of your intellectual property. Xojo uses native controls so your app looks and feels right on each platform. Development is cross-platform as well. Create your project on your favorite OS and then build it for any platform Xojo supports. LightSpeed LightSpeed is a robust, fully integrated Point-of-Sale and retail management suite. Shine Shine is a photo editing suite for enhancing photos with hyper-realistic effects. Movie Draft SE Movie Draft is a tool for writing screenplays from concept, outline and finished draft.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/C0opJdHiVOc?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><b>Create Anything</b><br />With built-in support for graphics, database servers, inte.com protocols and more, you can build just about anything you can imagine with Xojo. Using Xojo, you can make commercial software products, utilities to help make your life easier, or even learn to program. In fact, Xojo itself is a Xojo app!<br /><br />Build Apps 10x Faster<br />You can use one set of source code to support multiple platforms and there are over 40 user interface controls built in, allowing your app to look and behave how you’d want it to on any platform. On the web you can use one powerful language to create your web app instead of HTML, CSS, PHP, j&#097;vascript, or AJAX, saving you tons of development time!<br /><b><br />Modern Development</b><br />Xojo is a modern, object-oriented language. It supports inheritance, interfaces, polymorphism and is strongly-typed as well. There are thousands of differences in OS API calls and Xojo abstracts you from these details, dramatically reducing development time and allowing you to focus on what makes your application unique.<br /><br /><b>Native, Cross-Platform</b><br />Xojo apps don’t have an interpreter or virtual machine – they’re compiled to machine code for fast execution and the protection of your intellectual property. Xojo uses native controls so your app looks and feels right on each platform. Development is cross-platform as well. Create your project on your favorite OS and then build it for any platform Xojo supports.<br /><b><br />LightSpeed</b><br />LightSpeed is a robust, fully integrated Point-of-Sale and retail management suite.<br /><br /><b>Shine</b><br />Shine is a photo editing suite for enhancing photos with hyper-realistic effects.<br /><br /><b>Movie Draft SE</b><br />Movie Draft is a tool for writing screenplays from concept, outline and finished draft.<br /><img src="https://app-universe.com/site/assets/files/1201/8d93q-top.736x0.png" alt="Xojo 2016 r3" title="Xojo 2016 r3"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Xojo 2016 r3" title="Xojo 2016 r3"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Unity 3D Professional 2018.1</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1844-unity-3d.html</link>
<description>Name : Unity 3D Professional Version : 2018.1 OS : Windows x64 Type : Game Developer For Mobile Price : $125 Homepage : SalePage Create games, connect with your audience, and achieve success You can create any 2D or 3D game with Unity. You can make it with ease, you can make it highly-optimized and beautiful, and you can deploy it with a click to more platforms than you have fingers and toes. What’s more, you can use Unity’s integrated services to speed up your development process, optimize your game, connect with an audience, and achieve success. Renowned throughout the industry as the multiplatform game engine, Unity allows you to target more devices more easily. With Unity, you get one-click deployment to the full range of mobile, VR, desktop, Web, Console and TV platforms.</description>
<category>Apps Builder</category>
<enclosure url="http://rsload.com/images3/Unity.3D.Pro.4.1.2f1.crack-matro3.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2016 20:38:10 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Fully Integrated Editor The Unity game engine is happily married to the Unity development environment. This tight integration allows the Editor to do everything a published game can do. The simple, visual, and intuitive nature of the Editor makes building games fun again. Graphical Fidelity Unity has a highly optimized graphics pipeline for both DirectX and OpenGL. Animated meshes, particle systems, advanced lighting and shadows, all will run blazing fast. Unity&#039;s Asset Pipeline is Unmatched. All major tools and file formats are supported, any art application can be used with Unity. One-Click Deployment Unity supports a wide range of publishing platforms, all available at the push of a single button. Shaders Unity&#039;s shader system combines ease of use, flexibility and performance. All the built-in shaders integrate perfectly with any type of light, with cookies or without. If that&#039;s not enough you can write your own shaders in Unity&#039;s powerful ShaderLab language with Cg and GLSL. Terrains Vast, densely foliaged landscapes that work smooth on low-end hardware. All that and they take up almost no disk space. Networking Take your single-player game and easily bring it online. Add some online high scores and chat. Create real-time.comworked multiplayer functionality. Unity supports all.comworking needs out of the box with little learning and even less effort. Advanced Physics Give your GameObjects life with the built-in Ageia PhysX Physics Engine. It&#039;s the world&#039;s most advanced physics engine and is used in games like Unreal Tournament 2007 and Ghost Recon 3. Audio and Video Mix realtime 3D graphics with streamed audio and video. Best Of All Worlds Unity supports three scripting languages: jаvascript, C#, and a dialect of Python called Boo. All three are equally fast and interoperate. All three can use the underlying .COM libraries which support databases, regular expressions, XML, file access and.comworking. Unity Asset Server The essence of game development is multi-disciplinary collaboration. The Unity Asset Server is an add-on product which adds version control to Unity. Shadow and Light Unity&#039;s provides a highly optimized lighting system with realtime shadows and baked lightmaps. Use shadow and light to great effect, without worrying about the gritty technical details. Thorough Learning Materials There is a wealth of support and knowledge to soak up. From User Guides to Scripting References to PDF Tutorials, it&#039;s easy to have all your questions answered. Not enough for you? Highly-active forums, IRC, and an open community wiki will get you the answers you need, every time.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<p><br></p><div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/nVF8HrO9hm4?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><b>Fully Integrated Editor</b><br><br>The Unity game engine is happily married to the Unity development environment. This tight integration allows the Editor to do everything a published game can do. The simple, visual, and intuitive nature of the Editor makes building games fun again.<br><b>Graphical Fidelity</b><br><br>Unity has a highly optimized graphics pipeline for both DirectX and OpenGL. Animated meshes, particle systems, advanced lighting and shadows, all will run blazing fast.<br><b>Unity's Asset Pipeline is Unmatched.</b><br><br>All major tools and file formats are supported, any art application can be used with Unity.<br><b>One-Click Deployment</b><br><br>Unity supports a wide range of publishing platforms, all available at the push of a single button.<br><b>Shaders</b><br><br>Unity's shader system combines ease of use, flexibility and performance. All the built-in shaders integrate perfectly with any type of light, with cookies or without. If that's not enough you can write your own shaders in Unity's powerful ShaderLab language with Cg and GLSL.<br><b>Terrains</b><br><br>Vast, densely foliaged landscapes that work smooth on low-end hardware. All that and they take up almost no disk space.<br><b>Networking</b><br><br>Take your single-player game and easily bring it online. Add some online high scores and chat. Create real-time.comworked multiplayer functionality. Unity supports all.comworking needs out of the box with little learning and even less effort.<br><b>Advanced Physics</b><br><br>Give your GameObjects life with the built-in Ageia PhysX Physics Engine. It's the world's most advanced physics engine and is used in games like Unreal Tournament 2007 and Ghost Recon 3.<br><b>Audio and Video</b><br><br>Mix realtime 3D graphics with streamed audio and video.<br><b>Best Of All Worlds</b><br><br>Unity supports three scripting languages: jаvascript, C#, and a dialect of Python called Boo. All three are equally fast and interoperate. All three can use the underlying .COM libraries which support databases, regular expressions, XML, file access and.comworking.<br><b>Unity Asset Server</b><br><br>The essence of game development is multi-disciplinary collaboration. The Unity Asset Server is an add-on product which adds version control to Unity.<br><b>Shadow and Light</b><br><br>Unity's provides a highly optimized lighting system with realtime shadows and baked lightmaps. Use shadow and light to great effect, without worrying about the gritty technical details.<br><b>Thorough Learning Materials</b><br><br>There is a wealth of support and knowledge to soak up. From User Guides to Scripting References to PDF Tutorials, it's easy to have all your questions answered. Not enough for you? Highly-active forums, IRC, and an open community wiki will get you the answers you need, every time.<br><img src="http://rsload.com/images3/Unity.3D.Pro.4.1.2f1.crack-matro3.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Unity 3D Professional 2018.1"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>MOBILedit! 9.2.0.22984 Forensic Express</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1799-mobiledit.html</link>
<description>Name : MOBILedit! Forensic Express Version : 9.2.0.22984 Enterprise OS : Windows Type : Mobile Manage Tools, Phone Copied Tools, Phone Report Tools Price : $499 Homepage : SalePage Universal PC suite for ultimate management of your phone content A modular program which allows users to control their mobile phone from the PC via Bluetooth, infrared or cable. MOBILedit Forensic is a digital forensics product by Compelson Labs that searches, examines and report on data from GSM/CDMA/PCS cell phone devices. The professional phone management tool for enterprises, organizations, cellular retail stores, service centers and mobile operators. It includes all features including Phone Copier plus Wipe function</description>
<category>Apps Builder</category>
<enclosure url="https://a248.e.akamai.com/f/248/5462/2d/images.element5.com/pimages/P300004360/THUMB/300004360.JPG" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2016 23:11:49 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Full phone status information Picture of your phone Name of the phone - manufacturer and model Signal strength, battery status Current.comwork operator, connection type, hardware and software revision IMEI SIM card information Remaining storage space Phone&#039;s display resolution Phone&#039;s platform/OS Complete Phonebook management Robust editor of structured contacts, such as fax, more phones, email, addresses... Contact photo support Printing of whole phonebook is the best backup, especially for travelers Full-text search across all contacts and messages Comfortable internationalization - automatically adds prefix of selected country - great feature for travelers Swap the first name for the last name with one click Drag &amp;amp; drop contacts between MOBILedit! and other programs like Word, Excel, etc. Import and export of contacts into various formats more... Easy connection via cable, Bluetooth, Wi-Fi or IrDA Wizard helps you to connect your phone explaining all the needed steps Guides you through the step-by-step actions, making it easy even for a beginner Installs all necessary drivers for your phone Recognizes running applications that may block the phone communication channel Having trouble connecting the phone to a PC? Use our mobile application to establish a connection over a Wi-Fi more... Inte.com Storage New way of copying phones to the inte.com cloud Access your backup from anywhere Use our mobile app to upload/download and migrate your contacts and messages using our Inte.com Storage Transfer your contacts wirelessly and import them to MOBILedit more... Create a backup Never lose your data Store your backup either locally on a PC or in inte.com storage You can restore your backup later to other phones Auto-backup feature more... Entertainment Create and edit ringtones Cut your videos Edit and resize your photos with our integrated Photo Editor Convert your music into various formats Install applications into your phone more... Making a call Make a call from your PC Receive a call and see who&#039;s calling from your PC Use virtual keyboard to control your phone from your PC more... Text messages Complete SMS management and printing Sort, read, and archive your SMS messages on your PC Compose a message from a PC keyboard Automatically stores them to Sent Items on the PC Backup or delete your old messages Handling of incoming SMS through MOBILedit! Automatic conversion of SMS characters into GSM compliant character set more... Manage data on SIM card SIM card status information (IMSI, ICCID, LAI, PIN, PUK, call costs) SIM phonebook, sent-received-draft SMS, call log SIM card reader support more... Phone Copier Transfer contacts, messages, files from other phones with a single click Intelligent or manual mapping of fields in phonebook Wipe and backup before you copy option SIM card data transfer available Copy data also to/from Outlook, a file, Inte.com Storage or Google contacts (Gmail) Copy from Offline Devices or local/transferred backup file</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/HzXgGimvnlI?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" gesture="media" allow="encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br>Full phone status information<br><ul><li> Picture of your phone<br></li><li> Name of the phone - manufacturer and model<br></li><li> Signal strength, battery status<br></li><li> Current.comwork operator, connection type, hardware and software revision<br></li><li> IMEI<br></li><li> SIM card information<br></li><li> Remaining storage space<br></li><li> Phone's display resolution<br></li><li> Phone's platform/OS<br></li></ul><br>Complete Phonebook management<br><ul><li> Robust editor of structured contacts, such as fax, more phones, email, addresses...<br></li><li> Contact photo support<br></li><li> Printing of whole phonebook is the best backup, especially for travelers<br></li><li> Full-text search across all contacts and messages<br></li><li> Comfortable internationalization - automatically adds prefix of selected country - great feature for travelers<br></li><li> Swap the first name for the last name with one click<br></li><li> Drag &amp; drop contacts between MOBILedit! and other programs like Word, Excel, etc.<br></li><li> Import and export of contacts into various formats<br></li><li> more...<br></li></ul><br>Easy connection via cable, Bluetooth, Wi-Fi or IrDA<br><ul><li> Wizard helps you to connect your phone explaining all the needed steps<br></li><li> Guides you through the step-by-step actions, making it easy even for a beginner<br></li><li> Installs all necessary drivers for your phone<br></li><li> Recognizes running applications that may block the phone communication channel<br></li><li> Having trouble connecting the phone to a PC? Use our mobile application to establish a connection over a Wi-Fi<br></li><li> more...<br></li></ul><br>Inte.com Storage<br><ul><li> New way of copying phones to the inte.com cloud<br></li><li> Access your backup from anywhere<br></li><li> Use our mobile app to upload/download and migrate your contacts and messages using our Inte.com Storage<br></li><li> Transfer your contacts wirelessly and import them to MOBILedit<br></li><li> more...<br></li></ul><br>Create a backup<br><ul><li> Never lose your data<br></li><li> Store your backup either locally on a PC or in inte.com storage<br></li><li> You can restore your backup later to other phones<br></li><li> Auto-backup feature<br></li><li> more...<br></li></ul><br>Entertainment<br><ul><li> Create and edit ringtones<br></li><li> Cut your videos<br></li><li> Edit and resize your photos with our integrated Photo Editor<br></li><li> Convert your music into various formats<br></li><li> Install applications into your phone<br></li><li> more...<br></li></ul><br>Making a call<br><ul><li> Make a call from your PC<br></li><li> Receive a call and see who's calling from your PC<br></li><li> Use virtual keyboard to control your phone from your PC<br></li><li> more...<br></li></ul><br>Text messages<br><ul><li> Complete SMS management and printing<br></li><li> Sort, read, and archive your SMS messages on your PC<br></li><li> Compose a message from a PC keyboard<br></li><li> Automatically stores them to Sent Items on the PC<br></li><li> Backup or delete your old messages<br></li><li> Handling of incoming SMS through MOBILedit!<br></li><li> Automatic conversion of SMS characters into GSM compliant character set<br></li><li> more...<br></li></ul><br>Manage data on SIM card<br><ul><li> SIM card status information (IMSI, ICCID, LAI, PIN, PUK, call costs)<br></li><li> SIM phonebook, sent-received-draft SMS, call log<br></li><li> SIM card reader support<br></li><li> more...<br></li></ul><br>Phone Copier<br><ul><li> Transfer contacts, messages, files from other phones with a single click<br></li><li> Intelligent or manual mapping of fields in phonebook<br></li><li> Wipe and backup before you copy option<br></li><li> SIM card data transfer available<br></li><li> Copy data also to/from Outlook, a file, Inte.com Storage or Google contacts (Gmail)<br></li><li> Copy from Offline Devices or local/transferred backup file<br></li></ul><br><img src="https://a248.e.akamai.com/f/248/5462/2d/images.element5.com/pimages/P300004360/THUMB/300004360.JPG" style="max-width:100%;" alt="MOBILedit! 9.2.0.22984 Forensic Express"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>AppyGEN 5.5</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/866-appygen.html</link>
<description>Name : AppyGEN Version : 5.5 - Dynamic OS : Windows Type : Mobile Marketing, Android Apk Creator Price : $97 Homepage : SalePage AppyGEN is a completely done for you system, that will make you the king of an empire of Android Apps, making you hundreds every Day for the rest of your lifetime. the AppyGEN System contains Multiple ebooks, video and a unique software The AppyGEN Software is loaded with various multipurpose templates that you can customize as you wish to make your App.Those are custom templates made specifically to cover everything you need to make your app the way you want it.All apps generated with AppyGEN includes full Admob M.comization banners and Interstitialss</description>
<category>Apps Builder</category>
<enclosure url="http://i2.minus.com/ibzQiTz8q4QOlc.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2016 02:11:07 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><div class="dlevideoplayer" style="width:100%;max-width:425px;"><ul data-theme="default" data-preload="metadata"><li data-title="" data-type="youtube" data-url="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1H_wz2ZrrfY"></li></ul></div></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><img src="http://i2.minus.com/ibzQiTz8q4QOlc.png" alt="AppyGEN 5.5"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>