<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>GB Requests - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>GB Requests - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>LeadPrimo + OTOs</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4532-leadprimo-otos.html</link>
<description>GB Name : LeadPrimo + OTOs Version : Last OS : Anything Type : Email Marketing Software GB Price : $47(FE) + $77(OTO1) + $97(OTO2) + $97(OTO3) + $324/y(OTO4) = $642 GB Cost : 32.4$/20 peoples + 2.6$ Fee GB Joined : 10/20 Peoples GB Status : Going Homepage : SalePage LeadPrimo is a All-In-One Email Marketing Software that makes everything simple and easy, you can enjoy maximum delivery, capture and import unlimited lists and make use of all other features that our IM space needs as it creates high converting lead pages, boost leads, commissions, webinar registrations and ultimately get more profits on complete autopilot. It is completely newbie friendly and enable your subscribers to get THOUSANDS of Leads, send UNLIMITED emails, as well as follow-up with all the leads automatically and manage them without any complex issues. They can also see the complete real-time activity of subscribers, and find out which particular campaigns are giving best results. So, provide your subscribers with the untapped power to turn leads into buyers to get best results from the Email Marketing activities. With LeadPrimo, it is a SIMPLE and EASY 3 step method that goes like this-</description>
<category>GB Requests</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 03:24:11 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FE - LeadPrimo Pro - $47 1. 20 eye-catchy templates to create high converting lead pages. 2. Get direct views and leads from Facebook by adding your page as page tab. 3. By default, 1 list – All Subscribers. 4. Add subscribers. 5. Subscriber management. 6. Newsletter. 7. 1 email template. 8. Google, Yahoo, Hotmail - FREE mailing. 9. SMTP Mailing - SMTP mailing setup allowed. 10. 5 web-form templates with editor – inline editor. 11. 1 Sub-Domain / Business only. 12. Unlimited mailing per month. 13. Stats and Much More. OTO1 - LeadPrimo Elite - $77 1. Get 30 extra, Inbuilt eye-catching lead page templates to maximize lead generation. 2. Multiple List. 3. Advanced Subscriber management – suppression list, message wise, bounce wise, export, create custom fields. 4. 20 email templates. 5. Advanced messages management – use message again. 6. 10 form templates with editor. 7. Integrations – Webinars. 8. API – Integrate with any software. 9. Media Library. OTO2 - LeadPrimo Enterprise - $97 1. Complete lead Page real time statistics. 2. Autoresponder. 3. Advance Statistics. 4. Bounce management. 5. Advanced List management. 6. Advance Subscriber management – copy &amp;amp; move contacts. 7. Integrations – CRM. 8. Team management up-to 5 members. 9. 30 email templates. 10. 15 form templates with editor. OTO3 - LeadPrimo Reseller - $97 This is a mind-blowing deal as we are providing RESELLER license to LeadPrimo, and now your subscribers can SELL LeadPrimo to anyone they want &amp;amp; they get to KEEP 100% of the PROFITS. They don&#039;t have to do anything, just collect their 100% profit and find a way to spend it. OTO4 - Premium Membership - $324/y 1. 5 Brand New Lead-Page Templates Every Month. 2. 10 brand new eye- catchy &amp;amp; premium email templates delivered every month. 3. 5 web form templates with editor each month. 4. Create Multiple autoresponders for multiple businesses. 5. Ultra-Fast Servers for faster mail delivery. 6. Premium support. 7. Regular Updates. 8. Unlimited members team management. 9. Library with UNLIMITED Hosting on FAST servers &amp;amp; 200GB bandwidth per month.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br><a href="https://www.leadprimo.com/jv/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>FE - LeadPrimo Pro - </b></a><br><ul><li> 1. 20 eye-catchy templates to create high converting lead pages.<br></li><li> 2. Get direct views and leads from Facebook by adding your page as page tab.<br></li><li> 3. By default, 1 list – All Subscribers.<br></li><li> 4. Add subscribers.<br></li><li> 5. Subscriber management.<br></li><li> 6. Newsletter.<br></li><li> 7. 1 email template.<br></li><li> 8. Google, Yahoo, Hotmail - FREE mailing.<br></li><li> 9. SMTP Mailing - SMTP mailing setup allowed.<br></li><li> 10. 5 web-form templates with editor – inline editor.<br></li><li> 11. 1 Sub-Domain / Business only.<br></li><li> 12. Unlimited mailing per month.<br></li><li> 13. Stats and Much More.<br></li></ul><br><a href="https://www.leadprimo.com/jv/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO1 - LeadPrimo Elite - </b></a><br><ul><li> 1. Get 30 extra, Inbuilt eye-catching lead page templates to maximize lead generation.<br></li><li> 2. Multiple List.<br></li><li> 3. Advanced Subscriber management – suppression list, message wise, bounce wise, export, create custom fields.<br></li><li> 4. 20 email templates.<br></li><li> 5. Advanced messages management – use message again.<br></li><li> 6. 10 form templates with editor.<br></li><li> 7. Integrations – Webinars.<br></li><li> 8. API – Integrate with any software.<br></li><li> 9. Media Library.<br></li></ul><br><a href="https://www.leadprimo.com/jv/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO2 - LeadPrimo Enterprise - </b></a><br><ul><li> 1. Complete lead Page real time statistics.<br></li><li> 2. Autoresponder. <br></li><li> 3. Advance Statistics.<br></li><li> 4. Bounce management.<br></li><li> 5. Advanced List management.<br></li><li> 6. Advance Subscriber management – copy &amp; move contacts.<br></li><li> 7. Integrations – CRM.<br></li><li> 8. Team management up-to 5 members.<br></li><li> 9. 30 email templates.<br></li><li> 10. 15 form templates with editor.<br></li></ul><br><a href="https://www.leadprimo.com/jv/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO3 - LeadPrimo Reseller - </b></a><br><ul><li> This is a mind-blowing deal as we are providing RESELLER license to LeadPrimo, and now your subscribers can SELL LeadPrimo to anyone they want &amp; they get to KEEP 100% of the PROFITS. They don't have to do anything, just collect their 100% profit and find a way to spend it.<br></li></ul><br><a href="https://www.leadprimo.com/jv/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO4 - Premium Membership - 4/y</b></a><br><ul><li> 1. 5 Brand New Lead-Page Templates Every Month.<br></li><li> 2. 10 brand new eye- catchy &amp; premium email templates delivered every month.<br></li><li> 3. 5 web form templates with editor each month.<br></li><li> 4. Create Multiple autoresponders for multiple businesses.<br></li><li> 5. Ultra-Fast Servers for faster mail delivery.<br></li><li> 6. Premium support.<br></li><li> 7. Regular Updates.<br></li><li> 8. Unlimited members team management.<br></li><li> 9. Library with UNLIMITED Hosting on FAST servers &amp; 200GB bandwidth per month.<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="LeadPrimo + OTOs"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>LetSlotio + OTOs</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4529-letslotio-otos.html</link>
<description>GB Name : LetSlotio + OTOs Version : Last OS : Anything Type : SaaS Web App GB Price : $47(FE) + $67(OTO1) + $67(OTO2) + $77(OTO3) = $258 GB Cost : 17.5$/15 peoples + 1.5$ Fee GB Joined : 10/15 Peoples GB Status : Going Homepage : SalePage Just like LetSpin.io, LetSlot.io is a Full Featured Lead Generation Platform (SaaS Web App) that Leverages the Power of Gamification to Use the Inherent Human Curiosity of Playing &amp;amp; Winning Gifts in a Slot Machine.</description>
<category>GB Requests</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 03:23:56 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FE - LetSlotio Elite - $47 Outcome Weightage (Intelligent Wheel) Fully Customizable Slot Machine Shopify Plugin Wordpress Plugin Express Shopify Checkout Plugin AutoResponders Integration Webinars Integration Basic Email Validation Customisable Form Builder Scarcity Bar and Countdown Timer 5 Domain License Unlimited Optins Built in Library Youzign Integration Zapier Integration Campaign Level Integration Slot Icon Pack Live Campaign/ Slot Machine Preview Advance Show up Conditions (On Page Load, On Exit, X Time on Page, X Percentage of Scroll) Display URL Targeting Mobile Optimised Slot Machine Multiple Action Types on Win (Redirect URL, Close Popup, Reirect URL in New Tab, Copy Coupon) Leads Export as CSV File In Depth Training Sound and Basic Animation GDPR Complaint OTO1 - LetSlotio Platinum - $67 Outsourcer License with Unlimited Users &amp;amp; Access Level Roles Reminder Widget Follow Up Widget Advanced Show Up Conditions for Desktop (After X Time on Page, After X % Scroll, Load Up Widget) Advanced Show Up Conditions for Mobile (After X Time on Page, After X % Scroll, Load Up Widget) Advanced Display URL Targeting (Exclude URL &amp;amp; Referral URL conditions) Detailed Reporting (Export as CSV and PDF) Show LetSlot Machine on Click and Load Up Widget Customizable Floating Widget One Click Clone Campaigns Campaign Specific Multi Action Automations Slot Machine Animations Daily/Weekly Email Reports Repeat Show up Conditions Lead Generation Masterclass OTO2 - LetSlotio Booster - $67 Lander Win on Multiple Spins Detailed Reporting and Stats (Booster) Social Share User Card Add any Retargeting Pixel OTO3 - LetSlotio Jacker - $77 Run LetSlot Campaigns on Any Third Party Website WhitelabelDomain Name Detailed Reporting and Stats (Jacker) Detailed Reporting and Stats (Jacker) Commercial License Unlimited Domain License Removable Branding FullContact Integration Facebook &amp;amp; other Social Media Sharing Customizable Emoji Integration Done for you Lead Ma.com Vault</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/73VKreV2S4Y?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><a href="http://jvpartners.letx.co/letslotio/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>FE - LetSlotio Elite - </b></a><br><ul><li> Outcome Weightage (Intelligent Wheel) <br></li><li> Fully Customizable Slot Machine<br></li><li> Shopify Plugin<br></li><li> Wordpress Plugin<br></li><li> Express Shopify Checkout Plugin<br></li><li> AutoResponders Integration<br></li><li> Webinars Integration<br></li><li> Basic Email Validation <br></li><li> Customisable Form Builder<br></li><li> Scarcity Bar and Countdown Timer<br></li><li> 5 Domain License<br></li><li> Unlimited Optins<br></li><li> Built in Library<br></li><li> Youzign Integration<br></li><li> Zapier Integration <br></li><li> Campaign Level Integration <br></li><li> Slot Icon Pack <br></li><li> Live Campaign/ Slot Machine Preview <br></li><li> Advance Show up Conditions (On Page Load, On Exit, X Time on Page, X Percentage of Scroll)<br></li><li> Display URL Targeting<br></li><li> Mobile Optimised Slot Machine<br></li><li> Multiple Action Types on Win (Redirect URL, Close Popup, Reirect URL in New Tab, Copy Coupon) <br></li><li> Leads Export as CSV File <br></li><li> In Depth Training<br></li><li> Sound and Basic Animation  <br></li><li> GDPR Complaint <br></li></ul><br><a href="http://jvpartners.letx.co/letslotio/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO1 - LetSlotio Platinum - </b></a><br><ul><li> Outsourcer License with Unlimited Users &amp; Access Level Roles<br></li><li> Reminder Widget<br></li><li> Follow Up Widget <br></li><li>  Advanced Show Up Conditions for Desktop (After X Time on Page, After X % Scroll, Load Up Widget)<br></li><li>  Advanced Show Up Conditions for Mobile (After X Time on Page, After X % Scroll, Load Up Widget)<br></li><li> Advanced Display URL Targeting (Exclude URL &amp; Referral URL conditions) <br></li><li> Detailed Reporting (Export as CSV and PDF) <br></li><li> Show LetSlot Machine on Click and Load Up Widget <br></li><li> Customizable Floating Widget<br></li><li> One Click Clone Campaigns<br></li><li> Campaign Specific Multi Action Automations <br></li><li>  Slot Machine Animations<br></li><li> Daily/Weekly Email Reports <br></li><li> Repeat Show up Conditions <br></li><li> Lead Generation Masterclass<br></li></ul><br><a href="http://jvpartners.letx.co/letslotio/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO2 - LetSlotio Booster - </b></a><br><ul><li> Lander <br></li><li> Win on Multiple Spins<br></li><li> Detailed Reporting and Stats (Booster)  <br></li><li> Social Share<br></li><li> User Card<br></li><li> Add any Retargeting Pixel<br></li></ul><br><a href="http://jvpartners.letx.co/letslotio/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO3 - LetSlotio Jacker - </b></a><br><ul><li> Run LetSlot Campaigns on Any Third Party Website <br></li><li> WhitelabelDomain Name  <br></li><li> Detailed Reporting and Stats (Jacker) <br></li><li> Detailed Reporting and Stats (Jacker) <br></li><li> Commercial License <br></li><li> Unlimited Domain License <br></li><li> Removable Branding  <br></li><li> FullContact Integration <br></li><li> Facebook &amp; other Social Media Sharing Customizable  <br></li><li> Emoji Integration  <br></li><li> Done for you Lead Ma.com Vault<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="LetSlotio + OTOs"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>EXplaindio Video ToolKit  + OTOs</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4520-explaindio-video-toolkit-otos.html</link>
<description>GB Name : EXplaindio Video ToolKit + OTOs Version : Last OS : Anything Type : Video ToolKit GB Price : $47(FE) + $59(OTO1) + $97(OTO2) = $106 GB Cost : 11$/10 eoples + 1$ Fee GB Joined : 6/10 Peoples GB Status : Going Homepage : SalePage The Explaindio Video FX software was created by the same team of people who previously created Explaindio Video Creator, which is now used by tens of thousands video marketers in their businesses. Ever since we have released the very first version of Explaindio Video Creator back in 2014, one of the most requested features, has been the ability to add video effects to any video clip by people without any experience in video effects creation or adding. After almost a year of development by the team of our top software engineers, the Explaindio Video FX was created, and now we can finally fulfill that request. Explaindio Video FX can be used for both stock video clips, or as a final step for already produced videos. There are many stock video websites on the market, where everybody can download video clips for almost any existing niche.</description>
<category>GB Requests</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 09:22:04 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FE - EXplaindio Video ToolKit - $47 Just Drag &amp;amp; Drop Video, Choose Visual Effect, And Click Start 40 Amazing Built-In Customizable Video Effects (pro) Turns Dull Video Into A Shining Attention Grabber Star Unlimited Source of Blurred Video Backgrounds No Experience Required - Super Easy To Use Commercial License To Produced Videos OTO1 - Explaindio Toolbox App Bundle - $59 The features, which are very hard to find in any other video are batch processing, ability to convert video to any custom width &amp;amp; height dimensions, which is must have for any multi picture-in-picture video clip, and video proportion change. Batch processing is an extremely useful feature our team uses very often. For example, we drag &amp;amp; drop hundreds of 4k videos into converter, start conversion, let software run through the night, and in the morning we have all converted videos ready. The conversion to any custom width &amp;amp; height dimensions is a must have if you work with any video clip which include multiple small videos. The exclusive feature of Explaindio Video Creator is the ability to convert any supported video file format and encoding into the video format required by Explaindio Video Creator 1.014. If you purchased Explaindio Video FX PRO, you already have Explaindio Video Creator 1.014 which is a free bonus for that version. To make it clear, Explaindio Video Converter is a completely stand alone application, and can be used with any video creation and editing software. Watch the demo below where I show how Video Converter works with custom width &amp;amp; height dimensions needed for any software producing picture-in-picture multi-video clips, and how easy it is to convert video files, with just a few clicks, including conversion to the video format required by Explaindio Video Creator 1.014. Explaindio Video Converter Explaindio Audio Converter Explaindio Video Marker Explaindio Video Split Screen Explaindio Watermark Maker Explaindio Video Cropper Explaindio Sketch Line Color Changer Explaindio Screen Recorder (PC only)</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/-qrztzvySMg?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><a href="http://explaindiofx.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>FE - EXplaindio Video ToolKit - </b></a><br><ul><li> Just Drag &amp; Drop Video, Choose Visual Effect, And Click Start<br></li><li> 40 Amazing Built-In Customizable Video Effects (pro)<br></li><li> Turns Dull Video Into A Shining Attention Grabber Star<br></li><li> Unlimited Source of Blurred Video Backgrounds<br></li><li> No Experience Required - Super Easy To Use<br></li><li> Commercial License To Produced Videos<br></li></ul><br><a href="http://explaindiofx.com/otojvs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO1 -  Explaindio Toolbox App Bundle - </b></a><br><ul><li> The features, which are very hard to find in any other video are batch processing, ability to convert video to any custom width &amp; height dimensions, which is must have for any multi picture-in-picture video clip, and video proportion change.<br></li><li> Batch processing is an extremely useful feature our team uses very often. For example, we drag &amp; drop hundreds of 4k videos into converter, start conversion, let software run through the night, and in the morning we have all converted videos ready.<br></li><li> The conversion to any custom width &amp; height dimensions is a must have if you work with any video clip which include multiple small videos.<br></li><li> The exclusive feature of Explaindio Video Creator is the ability to convert any supported video file format and encoding into the video format required by Explaindio Video Creator 1.014.<br></li><li> If you purchased Explaindio Video FX PRO, you already have Explaindio Video Creator 1.014 which is a free bonus for that version.<br></li><li> To make it clear, Explaindio Video Converter is a completely stand alone application, and can be used with any video creation and editing software.<br></li><li> Watch the demo below where I show how Video Converter works with custom width &amp; height dimensions needed for any software producing picture-in-picture multi-video clips, and how easy it is to convert video files, with just a few clicks, including conversion to the video format required by Explaindio Video Creator 1.014.<br></li><li> Explaindio Video Converter<br></li><li> Explaindio Audio Converter<br></li><li> Explaindio Video Marker<br></li><li> Explaindio Video Split Screen<br></li><li> Explaindio Watermark Maker<br></li><li> Explaindio Video Cropper<br></li><li> Explaindio Sketch Line Color Changer<br></li><li> Explaindio Screen Recorder (PC only)<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="EXplaindio Video ToolKit  + OTOs"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Clip Dramatizer + OTOs</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4519-clip-dramatizer-otos.html</link>
<description>GB Name : Clip Dramatizer + OTOs Version : Last OS : Anything Type : Dramatizer Video Creater Tool GB Price : $67(FE) + $149/y(OTO1) + $97(OTO2) = $313 GB Cost : 31.3$/10 Peoples + 2.7$ Fee GB Joined : 6/10 Peoples GB Status : Going Homepage : SalePage Turn dull videos &amp;amp; images intp visually striling blockbusters that bring more viewers, generate more leads, and move people to take action</description>
<category>GB Requests</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 09:21:26 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FE - Clip Dramatizer - $67 Quality product Our team is known for producing quality software. This software is no different and that is very same devs who coded our other great software Customer Support We now have 6 full time support team which is helping customers of our product so you known your buyers are in the good hands Attractive Audience This is the very same target andience as for a few other launch with combined over $3m sales Huge Commissions As will all our launches we are looking for above $11 across the funnel OTO1 - Clip Overlay Club - $149/y OTO2 - Enterprise Upgrade - $97</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/4DK-HrcduOM?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><a href="http://jv.clipdramatizer.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>FE - Clip Dramatizer - </b></a><br><ul><li> Quality product<br></li><li> Our team is known for producing quality software. This software is no different and that is very same devs who coded our other great software<br></li><li> Customer Support<br></li><li> We now have 6 full time support team which is helping customers of our product so you known your buyers are in the good hands<br></li><li> Attractive Audience<br></li><li> This is the very same target andience as for a few other launch with combined over m sales<br></li><li> Huge Commissions<br></li><li> As will all our launches we are looking for above  across the funnel<br></li></ul><br><a href="http://jv.clipdramatizer.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO1 -  Clip Overlay Club - 9/y</b></a><br><ul><li> <br></li></ul><br><a href="http://jv.clipdramatizer.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO2 - Enterprise Upgrade - </b></a><br><ul><li> <br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Clip Dramatizer + OTOs"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Clip To GiF + OTOs</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4518-clip-to-gif-otos.html</link>
<description>GB Name : Clip To GiF + OTOs Version : Last OS : Anything Type : Clip to GIF Creator GB Price : $37(FE) + $44(OTO1) + $78/y(OTO2) + $97(OTO3) = $256 GB Cost : 25.6$/10 Peoples + 2.4$ Fee GB Joined : 6/10 Peoples GB Status : Going Homepage : SalePage Powerful software leverages the world&#039;s largest social media platforms as your own personal traffic source, boost engagement and sales convrsion simply by leveraging new type of animated gif images</description>
<category>GB Requests</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 09:20:17 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FE - Clip To GiF - $37 Quality product Our team is known for producing quality software. This software is no different and that is very same devs who coded our other great software Customer Support We now have 6 full time support team which is helping customers of our product so you known your buyers are in the good hands Attractive Audience This is the very same target andience as for a few other launch with combined over $3m sales Huge Commissions As will all our launches we are looking for above $11 across the funnel OTO1 - Clip To GiF Pro - $44 Convert viral GIFs into videos for Facebook and Instagram posts. Emotionally charged GIFs to get incredible results like top marketers and social media celebrities use. Beat 1.7 second attention span Tap into massive number of raw GIFs already done Import any existing GIF into the software and apply all ClipToGIF engagement boosters to it. OTO2 - Animated Business Stickers Club - $78/y Generate More Leads, Move People To Action &amp;amp; Increase Profit. OTO3 - Clip To GiF Pro Enterprise - $97 Low Competition Sell GIFs for $100 A Pop Commercial License</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ZWzZRAE8rXw?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><a href="http://www.cliptogif.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>FE - Clip To GiF - </b></a><br><ul><li> Quality product<br></li><li> Our team is known for producing quality software. This software is no different and that is very same devs who coded our other great software<br></li><li> Customer Support<br></li><li> We now have 6 full time support team which is helping customers of our product so you known your buyers are in the good hands<br></li><li> Attractive Audience<br></li><li> This is the very same target andience as for a few other launch with combined over m sales<br></li><li> Huge Commissions<br></li><li> As will all our launches we are looking for above  across the funnel<br></li></ul><br><a href="http://www.cliptogif.com/oto1jvzoo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO1 - Clip To GiF Pro - </b></a><br><ul><li> Convert viral GIFs into videos for Facebook and Instagram posts.<br></li><li> Emotionally charged GIFs to get incredible results like top marketers and social media celebrities use.<br></li><li> Beat 1.7 second attention span<br></li><li> Tap into massive number of raw GIFs already done<br></li><li> Import any existing GIF into the software and apply all ClipToGIF engagement boosters to it.<br></li></ul><br><a href="http://www.cliptogif.com/oto2jvzoo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO2 - Animated Business Stickers Club - /y</b></a><br><ul><li> Generate More Leads, Move People To Action &amp; Increase Profit.<br></li></ul><br><a href="http://www.cliptogif.com/oto3jvzoo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO3 - Clip To GiF Pro Enterprise - </b></a><br><ul><li> Low Competition<br></li><li> Sell GIFs for 0 A Pop<br></li><li> Commercial License<br><br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Clip To GiF + OTOs"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Animatron Studio Bussiness Annual</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4469-animatron-studio-bussiness-annual.html</link>
<description>GB Name : Animatron Studio Bussiness Annual Version : Last OS : Anything Type : Animatron Studio GB Price : $360/y = $360 GB Cost : 36$/10 Peoples + 3$ Fee GB Joined : 0/10 Peoples GB Status : Going Homepage : SalePage ANIMATRON IS PERFECT FOR ARTISTS &amp;amp; ANIMATORS, BUSINESSES &amp;amp; STARTUPS, EDUCATION</description>
<category>GB Requests</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 08:26:42 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FE - Animatron Wave Agency Annual - $360/y Public projects : Unlimited Private/Unlisted projects : Unlimited Remove watermark Movie hosting bandwidth : 100GB storage, 1000GB/month Real-time collaboration Commercial rights : 3rd-party transfer rights Royalty-free pro video clips : 100,000 Royalty-free audio clips : 200,000 Royalty-free photos : 250,000 Royalty-free pre-animated objects : 2,200</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/zIdadgq7HIc?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><a href="https://www.animatron.com/studio/pricing" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>FE - Animatron Wave Agency Annual  - 0/y</b></a><br><ul><li> Public projects : Unlimited<br></li><li> Private/Unlisted projects : Unlimited<br></li><li> Remove watermark<br></li><li> Movie hosting bandwidth : 100GB storage, 1000GB/month<br></li><li> Real-time collaboration<br></li><li> Commercial rights : 3rd-party transfer rights<br></li><li> Royalty-free pro video clips : 100,000<br></li><li> Royalty-free audio clips : 200,000<br></li><li> Royalty-free photos : 250,000<br></li><li> Royalty-free pre-animated objects : 2,200<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Animatron Studio Bussiness Annual"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Animatron Wave Agency Annual</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4468-animatron-wave-agency-annual.html</link>
<description>GB Name : Animatron Wave Agency Annual Version : Last OS : Anything Type : Animation Video Creators GB Price : $600/y GB Cost : 60$/10 Peoples + 4.8$ Fee GB Joined : 6/10 Peoples GB Status : Going Homepage : SalePage Empowers businesses and individuals to be video and animation creators</description>
<category>GB Requests</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 08:25:58 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FE - Animatron Wave Agency Annual - $600/y Unlimited usage of 500,000 videos, images and sounds included in your plan 30+ video publishing formats Unlimited video projects Library of over 200,000,000 premium assets available for purchase Upload original video footage Custom watermark Custom brand presets : 150 brands Max video duration : 15 min 3rd party resale rights Upload custom fonts White label preview Priority customer support</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Hsb8Hnxnyyw?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><a href="https://www.animatron.com/wave/pricing" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>FE - Animatron Wave Agency Annual  - 0/y</b></a><br><ul><li> Unlimited usage of 500,000 videos, images and sounds included in your plan<br></li><li> 30+ video publishing formats<br></li><li> Unlimited video projects<br></li><li> Library of over 200,000,000 premium assets available for purchase<br></li><li> Upload original video footage<br></li><li> Custom watermark<br></li><li> Custom brand presets : 150 brands<br></li><li> Max video duration : 15 min<br></li><li> 3rd party resale rights<br></li><li> Upload custom fonts<br></li><li> White label preview<br></li><li> Priority customer support<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Animatron Wave Agency Annual"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>LIVEreel + OTOs</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4395-livereel-otos.html</link>
<description>GB Name : LIVEreel + OTOs Version : Last OS : Anything Type : Live Video Tool GB Price : $27(FE) + $67(OTO1) + $47(OTO2) + $47(OTO3) + $27(OTO4) = $215 GB Cost : 43$/5 Peoples + 3.5$ Fee GB Joined : 2/5 Peoples GB Status : Going Homepage : SalePage LIVEreel is a web based one-stop shop for going live on 15 different live platforms at once OR playing your pre-recorded videos as live on these 15 different, all at once! LIVEreel not only makes it so much easier and do-able for anyone to go live without actually being live but also lets your live videos reach out to much much bigger audience and gets you more views, engagement, traffic, leads and sales!</description>
<category>GB Requests</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2018 05:16:18 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FE - LIVEreel - $27 Go Live on 15 Social Networks Quickly and Easily Go Live on 15 different social.comworks. Use your pre-recorded video to do live-casting on all these social.comworks at once. Auto-Moderate Comments &amp;amp; Engage Using LIVEreel you can automatically moderate all the comments and engagement you’re getting on your live videos. Automatically reply to comments you’re getting, automatically send them private message and make sure they are engaged. Works great for giveaway or getting survey responses or special deals or coupon offers for ecom or digital products. Build a List Of Viewers &amp;amp; Reach Out Automatically With LIVEreel you can build a list of your viewers who have been engaging with you on Facebook and send them a private message every time you have an offer for them or when you go live to instantly start getting viewers to your live video Customize Your LIVE-CASTING Video Add lower third, background music from our library of 650+ music, choose from 100s of frames to add to your videos, add auto-captions in different language, mult-lingual support for caption and more! Go Live On Your Own Blog or Website Use LIVEreel to cast live videos on your own blogs or websites. Simply setup a live video campaign, select &quot;Own Website&quot; option, copy-paste the code on your website and now you’re live casting on your own blogs or websites. Schedule, Set-n-Forget With LIVEreel you truly don’t have to be live EVER! Simply select any video you want to use as live video, schedule it to go live at any date and time and sit back and relax. The app will automatically make sure video go live and do all the work for you, while you’re away from your computer. Ability to share on 15 Different Social Media sites Connect your accounts and start sharing all your live video links on 15 different traffic pack social media sites and start reaching out to a bigger, broader customer base. Schedule and Automation Our automation makes it a set-n-forget campaign for you. Simply create whatever you wish to share, schedule it to be publish at a specific time, logout, sit back and relax while LIVEreel does all the work for you. Start Ranking on #1 on YouTube &amp;amp; Google People love live videos and Google/YouTube/SocialMedia sites love live videos. This is the easiest way to start targeting tons of keywords in your niche and start getting ranked on YouTube and Google without crazy SEO or optimization. Advanced Tracking and Stats Track your data and see which social media site or which piece of live video is getting you more clicks, more traffic and more customers so you can replicate the same over and over again and scale. 100% Whitehat and Approved LIVEreel is a 100% whitehat live video distribution app and in no ways violates any TOS, making sure your accounts are fully safe. Cloud based app LIVEreel is a cloud based application. There’s nothing to download or install or configure. Simply login to your accounts and start going live and manaing your live video campaigns. Established &amp;amp; Evergreen Product With over 100s beta testers and 6 months in research and development, LIVEreel is a stable product that is here to stay for a long run and bring in recurring commissions for you. OTO1 - LIVEreel Advance Upgrade - $67 The LIVEreel Agency lets you do 10X more. It comes packed with: Agency License to help you sell live video casting, customer getting services for your clients Ability to Create Unlimited live video campaigns weekly (FE lets you do upto 50 live videos a week) Sub-users / Clients Access Feature Virtual Assistant Access Developers + Commercial License Ready-Made Agency Website with Paypal checkout and more Connect Unlimited Social Media Profile Accounts 100 Professionally Approved Fonts &amp;amp; Text Designs Live Video Income Mastery System (training) OTO2 - LIVEreel Club - $47 LIVEreel Club is a monthly membership offered to the early adopters of LIVEreel where users will get unparalleled access to 100s of brand new video templates to create amazing intro and outro videos, presentation videos, sales-videos, logo stringers and more. OTO3 - SyVID – Agency License - $47 With SyVID Video Syndication, all the videos you and your clients create and now be shared on 7 different video sharing platforms and 13 different social media websites. With LIVEreel and SyVID together, you can be getting 20X more traffic and viewers to your live and existing videos. SyVID helps you to instantly start sharing and generating more free traffic, leads and sales. OTO4 - ViralSoci – Agency License - $27 Add in a mix of different images and videos when using LIVEreel. With ViralSoci you’ll be able find and publish highly engaging and viral Images &amp;amp; Native Videos on your Facebook fan pages, groups and profiles with 100% Automation!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/hXkgpy2F400?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><a href="http://www.livereel.io/jv/"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer"><b>FE - LIVEreel - </b></a><br><ul><li> Go Live on 15 Social Networks<br></li><li> Quickly and Easily Go Live on 15 different social.comworks. Use your pre-recorded video to do live-casting on all these social.comworks at once.<br></li><li> Auto-Moderate Comments &amp; Engage<br></li><li> Using LIVEreel you can automatically moderate all the comments and engagement you’re getting on your live videos. Automatically reply to comments you’re getting, automatically send them private message and make sure they are engaged. Works great for giveaway or getting survey responses or special deals or coupon offers for ecom or digital products.<br></li><li> Build a List Of Viewers &amp; Reach Out Automatically<br></li><li> With LIVEreel you can build a list of your viewers who have been engaging with you on Facebook and send them a private message every time you have an offer for them or when you go live to instantly start getting viewers to your live video<br></li><li> Customize Your LIVE-CASTING Video<br></li><li> Add lower third, background music from our library of 650+ music, choose from 100s of frames to add to your videos, add auto-captions in different language, mult-lingual support for caption and more!<br></li><li> Go Live On Your Own Blog or Website<br></li><li> Use LIVEreel to cast live videos on your own blogs or websites. Simply setup a live video campaign, select "Own Website" option, copy-paste the code on your website and now you’re live casting on your own blogs or websites.<br></li><li> Schedule, Set-n-Forget<br></li><li> With LIVEreel you truly don’t have to be live EVER! Simply select any video you want to use as live video, schedule it to go live at any date and time and sit back and relax. The app will automatically make sure video go live and do all the work for you, while you’re away from your computer.<br></li><li> Ability to share on 15 Different Social Media sites<br></li><li> Connect your accounts and start sharing all your live video links on 15 different traffic pack social media sites and start reaching out to a bigger, broader customer base.<br></li><li> Schedule and Automation<br></li><li> Our automation makes it a set-n-forget campaign for you. Simply create whatever you wish to share, schedule it to be publish at a specific time, logout, sit back and relax while LIVEreel does all the work for you.<br></li><li> Start Ranking on #1 on YouTube &amp; Google<br></li><li> People love live videos and Google/YouTube/SocialMedia sites love live videos. This is the easiest way to start targeting tons of keywords in your niche and start getting ranked on YouTube and Google without crazy SEO or optimization.<br></li><li> Advanced Tracking and Stats<br></li><li> Track your data and see which social media site or which piece of live video is getting you more clicks, more traffic and more customers so you can replicate the same over and over again and scale.<br></li><li> 100% Whitehat and Approved<br></li><li> LIVEreel is a 100% whitehat live video distribution app and in no ways violates any TOS, making sure your accounts are fully safe.<br></li><li> Cloud based app<br></li><li> LIVEreel is a cloud based application. There’s nothing to download or install or configure. Simply login to your accounts and start going live and manaing your live video campaigns.<br></li><li> Established &amp; Evergreen Product<br></li><li> With over 100s beta testers and 6 months in research and development, LIVEreel is a stable product that is here to stay for a long run and bring in recurring commissions for you.<br></li></ul><br><a href="http://www.livereel.io/jv/"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer"><b>OTO1 - LIVEreel Advance Upgrade - </b></a><br><ul><li> The LIVEreel Agency lets you do 10X more. It comes packed with:<br></li><li> Agency License to help you sell live video casting, customer getting services for your clients<br></li><li> Ability to Create Unlimited live video campaigns weekly (FE lets you do upto 50 live videos a week)<br></li><li> Sub-users / Clients Access Feature<br></li><li> Virtual Assistant Access<br></li><li> Developers + Commercial License<br></li><li> Ready-Made Agency Website with Paypal checkout and more<br></li><li> Connect Unlimited Social Media Profile Accounts<br></li><li> 100 Professionally Approved Fonts &amp; Text Designs<br></li><li> Live Video Income Mastery System (training)<br></li></ul><br><a href="http://www.livereel.io/jv/"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer"><b>OTO2 - LIVEreel Club - </b></a><br><ul><li> LIVEreel Club is a monthly membership offered to the early adopters of LIVEreel where users will get unparalleled access to 100s of brand new video templates to create amazing intro and outro videos, presentation videos, sales-videos, logo stringers and more.<br></li></ul><br><a href="http://www.livereel.io/jv/"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer"><b>OTO3 - SyVID – Agency License - </b></a><br><ul><li> With SyVID Video Syndication, all the videos you and your clients create and now be shared on 7 different video sharing platforms and 13 different social media websites. With LIVEreel and SyVID together, you can be getting 20X more traffic and viewers to your live and existing videos. SyVID helps you to instantly start sharing and generating more free traffic, leads and sales.<br></li></ul><br><a href="http://www.livereel.io/jv/"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer"><b>OTO4 - ViralSoci – Agency License - </b></a><br><ul><li> Add in a mix of different images and videos when using LIVEreel. With ViralSoci you’ll be able find and publish highly engaging and viral Images &amp; Native Videos on your Facebook fan pages, groups and profiles with 100% Automation!<br></li></ul><br><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="LIVEreel + OTOs"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>TweetPush + OTOs</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4208-tweetpush-otos.html</link>
<description>GB Name : TweetPush + OTOs Version : Last OS : Anything Type : Tweet Marketing Tool GB Price : $37(FE) + $67(OTO1) + $97(OTO2) = $201 GB Cost : 13.4$/15 Peoples + 1.1$ Fee GB Joined : 10/15 Peoples GB Status : Going Homepage : SalePage Powerful SAAS gives you everything you need to turn Twitter into trafiic.</description>
<category>GB Requests</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2018 04:31:25 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FE - TweetPush - $37 Powerful SAAS gives you everything you need to turn Twitter into trafiic. OTO1 - TweetPush Pro - $67 The Pro version of Tweetpush gives you the power to work with multiple Twitter accounts, as well as unloacks advanced twitter marketing features that are not available in Elite version. OTO2 - Tweetpush Agency - $97 The Agency version of Tweetpush lets you create account for the customers you recruit and sell Tewwtpush as a service. OTO3 - ViralReach Pro - $47</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/7TJj-JPsn5A?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><a href="https://gettweetpush.in/jv"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer"><b>FE - TweetPush - </b></a><br><ul><li> Powerful SAAS gives you <br></li><li> everything you need to <br></li><li> turn Twitter into trafiic.<br></li></ul><br><a href="https://gettweetpush.in/jv"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer"><b>OTO1 - TweetPush Pro - </b></a><br><ul><li> The Pro version of Tweetpush gives you the power to work with multiple Twitter accounts, as well as unloacks advanced twitter marketing features that are not available in Elite version.<br></li></ul><br><a href="https://gettweetpush.in/jv"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer"><b>OTO2 - Tweetpush Agency - </b></a><br><ul><li> The Agency version of Tweetpush lets you create account for the customers you recruit and sell Tewwtpush as a service.<br></li></ul><br><a href="https://gettweetpush.in/jv"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer"><b>OTO3 - ViralReach Pro - </b></a><br><ul><li> <br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="TweetPush + OTOs "><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Lumen5 Pro Annual</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4122-lumen5-pro-annual.html</link>
<description>GB Name : Lumen5 Pro Annual Version : Last OS : Anything Type : Text to Video Creator GB Price : $470/y/(FE) = $470 GB Cost : $47/10 Peoples + $5 Fee GB Joined : 5/10 Peoples GB Status : Going Homepage : SalePage Social videos made easy Transform articles into videos in minutes</description>
<category>GB Requests</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 28 Apr 2018 09:30:50 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FE - Lumen5 Pro Annual - $470/y Text to Video Easily transform articles and blog posts into video content Enter a link Simply enter a link to an article or blog post and Lumen5 will automatically fetch the content and populate your storyboard. Copy &amp;amp; paste If your content is in an offline document, simply copy and paste the text into Lumen5 to begin building your video. RSS feeds For a more automated approach, simply plug in RSS feeds and have video templates created automatically everyday! Automated Workflow Create videos in minutes with the assistance of A.I. Scene length The length of each scene is dynamically determined by the system based on the amount of text in each segment. Text positioning The positioning of text is intelligently calculated based on the composition of the media file you&#039;ve chosen. Keyword highlighting Machine learning is applied to natural language processing to highlight important keywords within each sentence. Media Library Searchable library with millions of free media files Video clips Make your video come to life with countless professional grade video clips that can help you tell your story. Still images Easily access millions of photos available at your finger tips covering thousands of subject matters. Music library Choose from thousands of free audio files and background music tracks categorized by mood and genre. Branding Options Customize your videos to match the look and feel of your brand Brand colors Choose from one of our preset colors or enter your own hex code to get the perfect color. Logo &amp;amp; watermark Upload your own logo and display it at the end or throughout the video as a watermark. Font choices Choose from a collection of beauitful fonts or upload your own custom font file. Video formats Optimize every video to improve performance and conversion rates Video resolution You can choose to render your videos in 480p, 720p, or 1080p, giving you full control over video quality and file size. Aspect ratio Render your videos in standard 16:9 landscape format or 1:1 square format for specialized social platforms like Instagram. Letterbox style Enhance your messaging with a letterbox format which has been popularized by viral meme videos. Everything in Pro +Team permission settings +Multiple brand presets +1,000,000+ premium media files +1080p video quality +Letterbox videos +Upload your own music +Upload your own fonts</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br><a href="https://lumen5.com/pricing/"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer"><b>FE - Lumen5 Pro Annual - 0/y </b></a><br><ul><li> Text to Video<br></li><li> Easily transform articles and blog posts into video content<br></li><li> Enter a link<br></li><li> Simply enter a link to an article or blog post and Lumen5 will automatically fetch the content and populate your storyboard.<br></li><li> Copy &amp; paste<br></li><li> If your content is in an offline document, simply copy and paste the text into Lumen5 to begin building your video.<br></li><li> RSS feeds<br></li><li> For a more automated approach, simply plug in RSS feeds and have video templates created automatically everyday!<br></li><li> Automated Workflow<br></li><li> Create videos in minutes with the assistance of A.I.<br></li><li> Scene length<br></li><li> The length of each scene is dynamically determined by the system based on the amount of text in each segment.<br></li><li> Text positioning<br></li><li> The positioning of text is intelligently calculated based on the composition of the media file you've chosen.<br></li><li> Keyword highlighting<br></li><li> Machine learning is applied to natural language processing to highlight important keywords within each sentence.<br></li><li> Media Library<br></li><li> Searchable library with millions of free media files<br></li><li> Video clips<br></li><li> Make your video come to life with countless professional grade video clips that can help you tell your story.<br></li><li> Still images<br></li><li> Easily access millions of photos available at your finger tips covering thousands of subject matters.<br></li><li> Music library<br></li><li> Choose from thousands of free audio files and background music tracks categorized by mood and genre.<br></li><li> Branding Options<br></li><li> Customize your videos to match the look and feel of your brand<br></li><li> Brand colors<br></li><li> Choose from one of our preset colors or enter your own hex code to get the perfect color.<br></li><li> Logo &amp; watermark<br></li><li> Upload your own logo and display it at the end or throughout the video as a watermark.<br></li><li> Font choices<br></li><li> Choose from a collection of beauitful fonts or upload your own custom font file.<br></li><li> Video formats<br></li><li> Optimize every video to improve performance and conversion rates<br></li><li> Video resolution<br></li><li> You can choose to render your videos in 480p, 720p, or 1080p, giving you full control over video quality and file size.<br></li><li> Aspect ratio<br></li><li> Render your videos in standard 16:9 landscape format or 1:1 square format for specialized social platforms like Instagram.<br></li><li> Letterbox style<br></li><li> Enhance your messaging with a letterbox format which has been popularized by viral meme videos.<br></li><li> Everything in Pro<br></li><li> +Team permission settings<br></li><li> +Multiple brand presets<br></li><li> +1,000,000+ premium media files<br></li><li> +1080p video quality<br></li><li> +Letterbox videos<br></li><li> +Upload your own music<br></li><li> +Upload your own fonts<br></li></ul><br><br><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Lumen5 Pro Annual"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>