<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Live Stream Tools - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Live Stream Tools - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>Live Event Blaster 2.02 Pro Local</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1749-live-event-blaster.html</link>
<description>Name : Live Event Blaster Version : 2.02 Pro Local OS : Windows Type : Youtube Marketing Price : $99 Homepage : SalePage We Will Change The Way You Are CREATING – UPLOADING – RANKING Videos On YouTube Find Out Why The Top Video Marketers Are Calling This “The Ultimate YouTube Super Weapon”…</description>
<category>Live Stream Tools</category>
<enclosure url="http://i.imgur.com/QJ0L67F.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="http://liveblaster.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/04/features-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2018 13:32:07 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Step 1 : You schedule a live event, YouTube will already index your event, giving you higher rankings than videos… Step 2 : You start streaming your live event . YouTube promotes your event using it’s internal engine! Step 3 : When you finish streaming, your event TRANSFORMS INTO A VIDEO…but keeps its original event rankings!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/262629560?app_id=122963" width="425" height="239" frameborder="0" title="New Sales Video - LEB 2" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Step 1 : You schedule a live event, YouTube will already index your event, giving you higher rankings than videos…<br></li><li> Step 2 : You start streaming your live event .  YouTube promotes your event using it’s internal engine!<br></li><li> Step 3 : When you finish streaming, your event TRANSFORMS INTO A VIDEO…but keeps its original event rankings!<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://i.imgur.com/QJ0L67F.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Live Event Blaster 2.02 Pro Local"><br><img src="http://liveblaster.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/04/features-2.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Live Caster Agency 1.5.5</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3629-livecaster-pro.html</link>
<description>Name : LiveCaster + OTOs Version : 1.5.5 Pro OS : Windows Type : Youtube Live Stream Marketing, Facebook Live Stream Marketing Price : $545 Homepage : SalePage This is the best livecasting software made for Facebook &amp;amp; YouTube. Ultra simple to use, it supports scheduling, one-click live mode. Can Cast pre-recorded videos as live to Facebook Personal feed, Pages &amp;amp; even Groups. It can also livecast to YouTube!</description>
<category>Live Stream Tools</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 13:17:35 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Cast pre-recorded videos as live to Facebook Personal feed, Pages &amp;amp; even Groups.And also YouTube channels! Pick up any pre-recorded video and cast it ‘live’ on Facebook or YouTube. Supports scheduling. Cast your videos at any time you want without being there. Cast multiple videos at the same time. Two or even three videos simultaneously. Lets you select the playback quality you want so you can pick up optimum playback for your inte.com speed. Cast live videos to Facebook groups, Facebook pages, Facebook personal feeds and YouTube channels. Casts direct from your computer, gets you the best results for SEO and rankings. Super easy to use! You won’t be wasting time trying to figure out things. Supports &amp;amp; converts from a variety of video formats an sizes. Powerful Scheduling : Schedule your videos for any time, and even schedule multiple videos to run at the same time. Universal Compatibility : Works with Facebook Groups, Pages, Personal Feed &amp;amp; Even YouTube Easy to Use Interface : No need to go through a complicated course to understand it. Everything is just accessible Gets You Higher Rankings : People want to watch live-streamed videos and it&#039;s the best way to link up with trending keywords while providing desired content to your audience and boosting your ranks. Free Traffic From Facebook : Live videos generate high buzz among audience and get your FaceBook pages organic traffic in droves Go Live Whenever You Want : This monster app allows you to livecast any prerecorded videos as live events on YouTube and Facebook. Super Robust Engine : LiveCaster allows you to schedule as many videos as you want to be casted as live event. All you have to do is set it once, and have the App running, along with an inte.com connection. LiveCaster is robust enough to work round the clock, 24/7 to get you maximum engagement from your audience.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/3A3t0UwIMlQ?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><p><br></p><br><h3>Features</h3><br><p><br><ul><li> Cast pre-recorded videos as live to Facebook Personal feed, Pages &amp; even Groups.And also YouTube channels!<br></li><li> Pick up any pre-recorded video and cast it ‘live’ on Facebook or YouTube.<br></li><li> Supports scheduling. Cast your videos at any time you want without being there.<br></li><li> Cast multiple videos at the same time. Two or even three videos simultaneously.<br></li><li> Lets you select the playback quality you want so you can pick up optimum playback for your inte.com speed.<br></li><li> Cast live videos to Facebook groups, Facebook pages, Facebook personal feeds and YouTube channels.<br></li><li> Casts direct from your computer, gets you the best results for SEO and rankings.<br></li><li> Super easy to use! You won’t be wasting time trying to figure out things.<br></li><li> Supports &amp; converts from a variety of video formats an sizes.<br></li><li> Powerful Scheduling : Schedule your videos for any time, and even schedule multiple videos to run at the same time.<br></li><li> Universal Compatibility : Works with Facebook Groups, Pages, Personal Feed &amp; Even YouTube<br></li><li> Easy to Use Interface : No need to go through a complicated course to understand it. Everything is just accessible<br></li><li> Gets You Higher Rankings : People want to watch live-streamed videos and it's the best way to link up with trending keywords while providing desired content to your audience and boosting your ranks.<br></li><li> Free Traffic From Facebook : Live videos generate high buzz among audience and get your FaceBook pages organic traffic in droves<br></li><li> Go Live Whenever You Want : This monster app allows you to livecast any prerecorded videos as live events on YouTube and Facebook.<br></li><li> Super Robust Engine : LiveCaster allows you to schedule as many videos as you want to be casted as live event. All you have to do is set it once, and have the App running, along with an inte.com connection. LiveCaster is robust enough to work round the clock, 24/7 to get you maximum engagement from your audience.</p><br><p><br></li></ul></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Live Caster Agency 1.5.5"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Live Stream Alpha 2.21 BCE</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1738-live-stream-alpha.html</link>
<description>Name : Live Stream Alpha Version : Bulk Campaign Multiplier 2.21 OS : Windows Type : YouTube Live Events Bot - Facebook Live Bot - Daily Motion Live Bot Price : $400 Homepage : SalePage Live Stream Pre Recorded Videos To 3 Top Platforms For Fast Rankings &amp;amp; Traffic! Our New Tool Live Steams Existing Videos To YouTube Live Events, Daily Motion &amp;amp; Facebook! Connect With The Top 3 Popular Live Steaming Platforms! Live Stream &quot;Pre-Recorded&quot; Videos YouTube Live Events - Facebook Live - Daily Motion Live</description>
<category>Live Stream Tools</category>
<enclosure url="http://anthonyhayes.me/wp-content/uploads/Live-Stream-Alpha.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 23:30:15 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features YouTube Live Events : YouTube Live Events helps Your Videos Rank Faster. You Can Choose From Advanced Options Made Click Button Simple For Silos, Linkwheels &amp;amp; Tiered Linking Using Pre Recorded Videos! Daily Motion : Daily Motion is a High traffic Site that ranks REALLY well, and they also offer Live Streaming.Just Set Up Your Campaign And Stream Your Videos! Facebook Live Stream : Facebook Live Steam Is Typically Done Via Smart Phones, Now You Can Stream Right From Live Stream Alpha &amp;amp; Drive More Traffic With Facebook&#039;s New Live Steam Feature Effortlessly! Simplify Your Live Stream Video Marketing Campaign Today! Advanced Video SEO :We have built in advanced video SEO and made it as simple as checkboxing options when you are setting up your live stream campaigns. This is &quot;push button easy&quot; SEO made as effortless you will ever see!Choose from streaming as unlisted, public, add silos, linkwheel, tiered linking, instant pinging and Indexing just by ticking the checkboxes for each!You can even add different video intros and CTA outro&#039;s to every video in one click! Video Spinning &amp;amp; Bulk Upload : Want to figure out what keyword phrases rank with no backlinks?...Just load up one video to your campaign, add hundreds of prases, choose which youtube channels to use and click start.Each video will be a different size and you can even add difeent thumbnails to each in one click! Web 2.0 Video Embedding : We have added or web 2.0 one click bulk account creator that creates hundreds of web 2.0 accounts in minutes and posts using your live stream video embed code.Instant indexing and pinging as well as tiered linking, silos and linkwheels options added too! RSS Xtreme : Our RSS Xtreme tool pulls in 86 YouTube url versions and creates short urls from those also, mashes the urls into one feed and syndicates for powerful video sundication in just a few clicks! LongTail Buyer Keywords Generator : This tool uses the 3 key elements to any buyer intent keyword, combines them into hundreds of variations and a simple click can be added into titles, descriptions using automated spintax or shortcodes!This literally helps you dominate niches on demand. Auto Scheduling : Run everything on autopilot with multiple campaigns. This is a multi threaded tool to simplify your life and allow you to post with time delays, spin your titles and description, add different thumbnails to every video and keep every video unique! Unique Marketing Strategy Tools Built In... Traffic Redirect Tool : With this tool you can create a cloaked URL and change the destination of that cloaked URL using 301 Redirect. This means you can now effectively redirect your entire backlink campaigns in seconds.This is perfect if doing launch Jacking for example:) Expired Domain Finder : This tool searches YouTube for video with high traffic or rankings with domains that are no longer being used but are available to buy for around $10.00!This works by searching keywords in bulk, it will indicate if a URL is available to purchase the same second that it discovers the broken link!...This is a Major Time Saver! Amazon Affiliate Tool : This Tool Will Monitor Amazon for NEW Products &amp;amp; let you curate from the product description, specs reviews and find videos on Amazon product listing or or YouTube for this exact product, which you can then send to the live stream tool and upload for fast rankings with your affiliate ID and link added automatically! Some Quick Tips: YouTube Live Streaming... Please do not use proxies with YouTube live events or with Feedburner when using RSS X as Google will flag your location. Facebook Live Streaming... Do not spam facebook with your main facebook account, use facebook for your best quality videos only and focus on driving traffic to main money videos, do not use for creating multipleversions of the same video for the sake of backlinks on facebook or you may lose your facebook accounts! Always add retargeting to your facebook pages This tool works with multiple facebook pages but will upload only one at a time.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/3C_lL-3fnr0?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><p></p><br><h3>Features</h3><br><p><br><ul><li> YouTube Live Events : YouTube Live Events helps Your Videos Rank Faster. You Can Choose From Advanced Options Made Click Button Simple For Silos, Linkwheels &amp; Tiered Linking Using Pre Recorded Videos!<br></li><li> Daily Motion : Daily Motion is a High traffic Site that ranks REALLY well, and they also offer Live Streaming.Just Set Up Your Campaign And Stream Your Videos!<br></li><li> Facebook Live Stream : Facebook Live Steam Is Typically Done Via Smart Phones, Now You Can Stream Right From Live Stream Alpha &amp; Drive More Traffic With Facebook's New Live Steam Feature Effortlessly!<br></li></ul><br><b>Simplify Your Live Stream Video Marketing Campaign Today!</b><br><ul><li> Advanced Video SEO :We have built in advanced video SEO and made it as simple as checkboxing options when you are setting up your live stream campaigns. This is "push button easy" SEO made as effortless you will ever see!Choose from streaming as unlisted, public, add silos, linkwheel, tiered linking, instant pinging and Indexing just by ticking the checkboxes for each!You can even add different video intros and CTA outro's to every video in one click!<br></li><li> Video Spinning &amp; Bulk Upload : Want to figure out what keyword phrases rank with no backlinks?...Just load up one video to your campaign, add hundreds of prases, choose which youtube channels to use and click start.Each video will be a different size and you can even add difeent thumbnails to each in one click!<br></li><li> Web 2.0 Video Embedding : We have added or web 2.0 one click bulk account creator that creates hundreds of web 2.0 accounts in minutes and posts using your live stream video embed code.Instant indexing and pinging as well as tiered linking, silos and linkwheels options added too!<br></li><li> RSS Xtreme : Our RSS Xtreme tool pulls in 86 YouTube url versions and creates short urls from those also, mashes the urls into one feed and syndicates for powerful video sundication in just a few clicks!<br></li><li> LongTail Buyer Keywords Generator : This tool uses the 3 key elements to any buyer intent keyword, combines them into hundreds of variations and a simple click can be added into titles, descriptions using automated spintax or shortcodes!This literally helps you dominate niches on demand.<br></li><li> Auto Scheduling : Run everything on autopilot with multiple campaigns. This is a multi threaded tool to simplify your life and allow you to post with time delays, spin your titles and description, add different thumbnails to every video and keep every video unique!<br></li></ul><br><b>Unique Marketing Strategy Tools Built In...</b><br><ul><li> Traffic Redirect Tool : With this tool you can create a cloaked URL and change the destination of that cloaked URL using 301 Redirect. This means you can now effectively redirect your entire backlink campaigns in seconds.This is perfect if doing launch Jacking for example:)<br></li><li> Expired Domain Finder : This tool searches YouTube for video with high traffic or rankings with domains that are no longer being used but are available to buy for around .00!This works by searching keywords in bulk, it will indicate if a URL is available to purchase the same second that it discovers the broken link!...This is a Major Time Saver!<br></li><li> Amazon Affiliate Tool : This Tool Will Monitor Amazon for NEW Products &amp; let you curate from the product description, specs reviews and find videos on Amazon product listing or or YouTube for this exact product, which you can then send to the live stream tool and upload for fast rankings with your affiliate ID and link added automatically!<br></li></ul><br><br><b>Some Quick Tips:</b><br><u>YouTube Live Streaming...</u><br>Please do not use proxies with YouTube live events or with Feedburner when using RSS X as Google will flag your location.<br><br><u>Facebook Live Streaming...</u><br>Do not spam facebook with your main facebook account, use facebook for your best quality videos only and focus on driving traffic to main money videos, do not use for creating multipleversions of the same video for the sake of backlinks on facebook or you may lose your facebook accounts!<br>Always add retargeting to your facebook pages<br>This tool works with multiple facebook pages but will upload only one at a time.<br><br><img src="http://anthonyhayes.me/wp-content/uploads/Live-Stream-Alpha.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Live Stream Alpha 2.21 BCE"></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Telestream Wirecast Pro 9.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3644-telestream-wirecast-pro.html</link>
<description>Name : Telestream Wirecast Pro Version : 9.0 Type : Live Streaming Tools Price : $995 Homepage : SalePage Everything you need to stream live video from your desktop to the world! Wirecast lets you capture an unlimited number of input devices from live camera feeds, iOS cameras (coming soon), computer desktop, Web feeds, and more. Then add polish and professionalism to your broadcast with live switching, transitions, titles, lower thirds, and more.</description>
<category>Live Stream Tools</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2017 15:48:45 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Produce your show.Add polish and professionalism to your broadcast with live switching, transitions, titles, lower thirds and more. Stream it live.Use the built in multiformat encoding capabilities and easily stream to integrated streaming services and CDNs. Live Events / Entertainment : Live stream conferences, concerts, interviews and more. Wirecast provides everything you need to stream professional live events. Add multiple cameras, including iOS devices; create composite shots with graphics and transitions; and live encode and stream to your favorite streaming destination. News / Sports : For a fraction of the cost of traditional broadcast hardware, Wirecast allows you to quickly and easily broadcast breaking news and live sports. Carry Wirecast on a laptop for remote newsgathering and production. For sports, use integrated scoreboards and replay for high quality live streams. Education : Live stream your lectures, interviews, workshops for professional development or student instruction. Using Wirecast, anyone can now create professional live streamed broadcasts for sharing live or on-demand via the web with just a camera, a computer and an inte.com connection. Houses of Worship : Engage and expand your remote congregation with live streams of your services and events. Easily train volunteers to use Wirecast to switch between multiple cameras, add graphics and even record a version for on-demand viewing. Wirecast is a flexible software solution that can be used on existing hardware.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/TqxX2Y5VLkA?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Produce your show.Add polish and professionalism to your broadcast with live switching, transitions, titles, lower thirds and more.<br></li><li> Stream it live.Use the built in multiformat encoding capabilities and easily stream to integrated streaming services and CDNs.<br></li><li> Live Events / Entertainment : Live stream conferences, concerts, interviews and more. Wirecast provides everything you need to stream professional live events. Add multiple cameras, including iOS devices; create composite shots with graphics and transitions; and live encode and stream to your favorite streaming destination.<br></li><li> News / Sports : For a fraction of the cost of traditional broadcast hardware, Wirecast allows you to quickly and easily broadcast breaking news and live sports. Carry Wirecast on a laptop for remote newsgathering and production. For sports, use integrated scoreboards and replay for high quality live streams.<br></li><li> Education : Live stream your lectures, interviews, workshops for professional development or student instruction. Using Wirecast, anyone can now create professional live streamed broadcasts for sharing live or on-demand via the web with just a camera, a computer and an inte.com connection.<br></li><li> Houses of Worship : Engage and expand your remote congregation with live streams of your services and events. Easily train volunteers to use Wirecast to switch between multiple cameras, add graphics and even record a version for on-demand viewing. Wirecast is a flexible software solution that can be used on existing hardware.<br><br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Telestream Wirecast Pro 9.0"><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Live Face Caster 0.14.2</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1754-live-facebook-caster.html</link>
<description>Name : Live Face Caster Version : 0.14.2 OS : Windows Type : Facebook Live Stream Tools, Live Streaming Marketing Tools Price : $20 Homepage : SalePage Live Streaming on Facebook Just Got Easier, Faster and Better And We&#039;ll Show You How!! You can now use your PC or Mac to Live Stream on Facebook. No longer are you chained to your mobile device for Live Streaming! You&#039;ll have the latest training on how to use a FREE software that NO ONE else is talking about!! Presenting Live Face Caster!</description>
<category>Live Stream Tools</category>
<enclosure url="http://livefacecaster.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/05/castHeader-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2016 21:18:38 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Training to use a new simple FREE software with a few clicks. Focus on making money inside Facebook with Presentations &amp; Multi-Screen Recorded Videos. Create marketing videos for products, webinars, training &amp; more within seconds. You NEVER have to be on camera For PC or Mac - no longer tied to your mobile device for streaming.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/hx-ePz_DwDY?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Training to use a new simple FREE software with a few clicks. <br /></li><li> Focus on making money inside Facebook with Presentations & Multi-Screen Recorded Videos. <br /></li><li> Create marketing videos for products, webinars, training & more within seconds. <br /></li><li> You NEVER have to be on camera <br /></li><li> For PC or Mac - no longer tied to your mobile device for streaming. <br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://livefacecaster.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/05/castHeader-2.jpg" alt="Live Face Caster 0.14.2" title="Live Face Caster 0.14.2"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Live Face Caster 0.14.2" title="Live Face Caster 0.14.2"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>