<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>RSS Submissions - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>RSS Submissions - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>Submit RSS 2.0.1</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3798-submit-rss.html</link>
<description>Name : Submit RSS Version : 2.0.1 OS : Windows Type : RSS Submision Price : $15 Homepage : SalePage Submit RSS is a must have tool for blog and website owners to manage and promote your RSS feeds as it has a built-in RSS Pinger utility which allows you to automatically send your RSS Feed to more than 100 best RSS Directories and Engines. Submit RSS is created to be easy understandable and have intuitive interface so it is a convenient tool for both newbie and professional. Nowadays submitting your RSS feed to RSS Directories and RSS Engines is extremely important as it informs RSS Directories and Engines about your RSS feed. So when you add new content on your blog or website the RSS Directories and RSS Engines automatically notice it and bring new readers and subscribers to your resource.</description>
<category>RSS Submissions</category>
<enclosure url="http://i.imgur.com/7KmIJoc.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2017 21:22:18 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Automatic submission: 105 Semi automatic submission: 28 Fast processing Intuitive user interface Cheap Lifetime license</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Automatic submission: 105<br></li><li> Semi automatic submission: 28<br></li><li> Fast processing<br></li><li> Intuitive user interface<br></li><li> Cheap<br></li><li> Lifetime license<br></li></ul><br><br><img src="http://i.imgur.com/7KmIJoc.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Submit RSS 2.0.1"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>RSS Channel Writer 2.1.3</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3801-rss-channel-writer.html</link>
<description>Name : RSS Channel Writer Version : 2.1.3 OS : Windows Type : RSS Creation Price : $25 Homepage : SalePage RSS Channel Writer is a powerful, as well as user-friendly RSS feed creator, editor and submitter. RSS feed for your web site can be created and pinged to more than 105 RSS servers fast and easily attracting more visitors to your website. There is no need for XML syntax knowledge - all you need to know is how to use this user-friendly program and you will create RSS with no problem.</description>
<category>RSS Submissions</category>
<enclosure url="http://i.imgur.com/YhBvyBu.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2017 21:22:12 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Easily create RSS feed with simple wizard; iTunes RSS creator; Google products RSS creator; RSS Validator; Publish your feed - upload it to a server with a built-in FTP manager; Autocomplete option; WYSIWYG editor for descriptions; Built-in RPC pinger and RSS submitter to directories; HTML and XML preview; a very, very user-friendly interface; and many more ...</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Easily create RSS feed with simple wizard;<br></li><li> iTunes RSS creator;<br></li><li> Google products RSS creator;<br></li><li> RSS Validator;<br></li><li> Publish your feed - upload it to a server with a built-in FTP manager;<br></li><li> Autocomplete option;<br></li><li> WYSIWYG editor for descriptions;<br></li><li> Built-in RPC pinger and RSS submitter to directories;<br></li><li> HTML and XML preview;<br></li><li> a very, very user-friendly interface;<br></li><li> and many more ...<br></li></ul><br><br><img src="http://i.imgur.com/YhBvyBu.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt="RSS Channel Writer 2.1.3"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>RSS Submit 5.926 SEO Edition</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1860-rss-submit.html</link>
<description>Name : RSS Submit Version : 5.926 SEO Edition DB470 OS : Windows Type : RSS Submit Tools Price : $125 Homepage : SalePage Submit RSS feeds to over 140+ directories Fully Customizable, Accurate Results! RSS Submit is the most powerful RSS feed management and promotion tool available. The first of its kind for automatically submitting RSS feeds, it is the quickest and most reliable way to submit to the RSS search engines. RSS Submit has been has been completely re-developed from the ground-up. The latest brand new 2016 edition of RSS Submit 5 promotes your RSS feeds with even more power. Sporting profile management, a brand new interface, targeting the latest Windows 8 platform, and including fully customizable engines, RSS Submit is the easiest way to get more traffic to your site! RSS Submit is a fully automated solution for submitting your RSS feeds. With just a few clicks RSS Submit lets you automatically create accounts on the RSS directories, submit your feeds, populate captchas *, and view real-time screenshot results of each submission. RSS Submit contains built-in profile management, allowing you to create submission profiles per RSS directory. With this powerful feature you can specify account login details and web site information to submit your feed. After submitting, view screenshots of the actual submissions and verify the results. You can even browse a real-time log of each step in the submission process. Verify accuracy and track your results with the easiest RSS submission tool available.</description>
<category>RSS Submissions</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.dummysoftware.com/rsssubmit5-cap3.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2017 23:18:23 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Unlimited time usage of software. 6-month subscription to RSS directory updates. All search engines activated. Unlimited number of RSS feeds may be submitted. Submission of RSS feeds used for commercial purposes. Submission of feeds belonging to other businesses and clients.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/5O1WZNX1tig?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Unlimited time usage of software.<br></li><li> 6-month subscription to RSS directory updates.<br></li><li> All search engines activated.<br></li><li> Unlimited number of RSS feeds may be submitted.<br></li><li> Submission of RSS feeds used for commercial purposes.<br></li><li> Submission of feeds belonging to other businesses and clients.<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://www.dummysoftware.com/rsssubmit5-cap3.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="RSS Submit 5.926 SEO Edition"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>RSS AutoGen 1.5 SEO Edition</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1862-rss-autogen.html</link>
<description>Name : RSS AutoGen Version : 1.5 SEO Edition OS : Windows Type : RSS generate Tools Price : $85 Homepage : SalePage Convert web pages to RSS feeds - Automatically generate RSS feeds from links - Web2RSS, HTML2RSS, Links2RSS RSS AutoGen is a powerful tool for automatically converting web pages or a list of links into complete keyword-rich RSS feeds. RSS feeds created by RSS AutoGen are fully functional, human readable, and compatible with both web browsers and submitting to RSS search engines and directories. Generated RSS feeds include web page content, images, meta tags, and descriptive text. RSS AutoGen is extremely easy to use. Simply add your web page URLs or links into the software or use the Import feature to automatically load a list of URLs into the software. Click the Generate All button to automatically convert each web page into fully validating RSS feeds. The perfect Web2RSS, HTML2RSS, and Links2RSS conversion tool, RSS AutoGen makes it easy to generate RSS feeds to distribute your web content to the most users, allowing you to submit your RSS feeds, increase backlinks, and increase visibility!</description>
<category>RSS Submissions</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.dummysoftware.com/rssautogen_cap1.gif" type="image/gif" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2016 00:13:18 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Unlimited time usage of software. Unlimited number of RSS feeds may be generated. Generation of RSS feeds used for commercial purposes. Generation of feeds belonging to other businesses and clients.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/dL8gAiEfGv0?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Unlimited time usage of software.<br /></li><li> Unlimited number of RSS feeds may be generated.<br /></li><li> Generation of RSS feeds used for commercial purposes.<br /></li><li> Generation of feeds belonging to other businesses and clients.<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://www.dummysoftware.com/rssautogen_cap1.gif" alt="RSS AutoGen 1.5 SEO Edition" title="RSS AutoGen 1.5 SEO Edition"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="RSS AutoGen 1.5 SEO Edition" title="RSS AutoGen 1.5 SEO Edition"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>RSS Authority Sniper 2.22</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1213-rss-authority-sniper.html</link>
<description>Name : RSS Authority Sniper Version : 2.22 OS : Windows/MAC Type : Rss Submission Tools Price : $127 Homepage : SalePage RSS Authority Sniper is the content marketer and blogger’s solution to generating REAL human traffic to a blog, website, or affiliate site.</description>
<category>RSS Submissions</category>
<enclosure url="http://s3.amazonaws.com/la.slgraphics/ras2/WSO_03.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="http://s3.amazonaws.com/la.slgraphics/ras2/WSO_04.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 01:36:03 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Legally STEAL the authority of websites that are larger, more established and are already loved by Google to get higher rankings. QUICKLY rank naturally for hundreds of new longtail keywords, bringing even more visitors to your content. Get new content indexed and funneling search traffic to websites FAST</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/sqHFNBl18r0?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Legally STEAL the authority of websites that are larger, more established and are already loved by Google to get higher rankings.<br /></li><li> QUICKLY rank naturally for hundreds of new longtail keywords, bringing even more visitors to your content.<br /></li><li> Get new content indexed and funneling search traffic to websites FAST<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://s3.amazonaws.com/la.slgraphics/ras2/WSO_03.jpg" alt="RSS Authority Sniper 2.22" title="RSS Authority Sniper 2.22"  /><br /><img src="http://s3.amazonaws.com/la.slgraphics/ras2/WSO_04.jpg" alt="RSS Authority Sniper 2.22" title="RSS Authority Sniper 2.22"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="RSS Authority Sniper 2.22" title="RSS Authority Sniper 2.22"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>No Hands SEO 2.35.0.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1011-no-hands-seo.html</link>
<description>Name : No Hands SEO Version : 2.35.0.0 OS : Windows Type : Indexes | Searches | Posts | Checks Links | Submits RSS Feeds Price : $77 Homepage : SalePage !!! The first truly automated website promotion tool has just gotten a whole lot better !!! No Hands SEO is not just another &quot;automated&quot; tool that requires hours of setup or baby sitting to use or costs an arm and a leg every month. No Hands SEO is the only tool equipped to take your websites from not indexed to ranking on total auto pilot. With just a few minutes setup you can have your website indexed, backlink all inner pages, promote RSS feeds, submit sitemaps, create tiered profiles and much more on absolute auto-pilot. The best thing about No Hands SEO is that once you have your profiles input all you need to do is hit the start button and you can leave it running indefinitely. In the background it will constantly search for new targets and post backlinks to more than 80 platforms from a variety of platform types, getting your websites indexed incredibly quickly and increasing visitors to your website. On top of all of this automation you get automatic link checking and pinging / indexing to ensure all of the created link juice is maximised.</description>
<category>RSS Submissions</category>
<enclosure url="http://nohandsseo.com/images/MainScreen.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2015 00:42:19 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Very simple setup : Just three inputs to get started Multi-Threaded : Super fast searching and posting Generate PR links : You can set the quality of links you want to build Automatically Pings Links : Whenever a new link is created it is pinged automatically Promotes Inner Pages : NHSEO promotes your whole website not just the homepage Promote Unlimited Webpages : You can promote as many pages as you like at once Fast Website Indexing : Get any website indexed within hours Link Indexer Support : Supports multiple indexing services to get your new links indexed fast Integrate Content Spinners : Support all major content rewriters for quick comment writing Insane amount of link platforms : Post links to lots of different link platforms for unparalleled link variety. Extensive Proxy support : NHSEO has full support for private and public proxies Proxy Harvester : If you do not have your own proxies NHSEO will find them for you. Lifetime Updates : NHSEO is updated very regularly for free Built in Text Rewriter App : Makes it easy to make any content spinnable and see the output</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><div class="dlevideoplayer" style="width:100%;max-width:425px;"><ul data-theme="default" data-preload="metadata"><li data-title="" data-type="youtube" data-url="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=p9pLVSSo2ak"></li></ul></div></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Very simple setup : Just three inputs to get started<br /></li><li> Multi-Threaded : Super fast searching and posting<br /></li><li> Generate PR links : You can set the quality of links you want to build<br /></li><li> Automatically Pings Links : Whenever a new link is created it is pinged automatically<br /></li><li> Promotes Inner Pages : NHSEO promotes your whole website not just the homepage<br /></li><li> Promote Unlimited Webpages : You can promote as many pages as you like at once<br /></li><li> Fast Website Indexing : Get any website indexed within hours<br /></li><li> Link Indexer Support : Supports multiple indexing services to get your new links indexed fast<br /></li><li> Integrate Content Spinners : Support all major content rewriters for quick comment writing<br /></li><li> Insane amount of link platforms : Post links to lots of different link platforms for unparalleled link variety.<br /></li><li> Extensive Proxy support : NHSEO has full support for private and public proxies<br /></li><li> Proxy Harvester : If you do not have your own proxies NHSEO will find them for you.<br /></li><li> Lifetime Updates : NHSEO is updated very regularly for free<br /></li><li> Built in Text Rewriter App : Makes it easy to make any content spinnable and see the output<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://nohandsseo.com/images/MainScreen.png" alt="No Hands SEO 2.35.0.0" title="No Hands SEO 2.35.0.0"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="No Hands SEO 2.35.0.0" title="No Hands SEO 2.35.0.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>