<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Amazon Marketing - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Amazon Marketing - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>Jungle Scout 4.1.4 + Pro 2.1.6</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1169-jungle-scout.html</link>
<description>Name : Jungle Scout Lite + Jungle Scout Pro Version : 4.1.4 + Pro 2.1.6 OS : Windows Type : Amazon Research Tools, Amazon Seller Tools Price : $87 + $147 Homepage : SalePage Jungle Scout integrates into your Google Chrome browser, streamlining your product research. Extract rank, sales volume, estimated revenue and more without ever exiting your browser or entering an Amazon product page. Amazon product research made easy. Save hours uncovering product ideas and sales information.</description>
<category>Amazon Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-07/thumbs/1437434033_jungles.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 08:33:04 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Quickly See Best Seller Ranks : One click of the Jungle Scout favicon neatly lists all the best seller ranks and pertinent categories. Estimate Monthly Revenue : Using proprietary sales information, monthly unit sales and revenue are estimated for each product. Works with Mac and PC : One click seamless installation into your Chrome browser means it works with any operating system and runs lean. Uncover Product Review Stats : Product review statistics, including number of reviews and the average star rating are neatly displayed. Free Updates : Team members work tirelessly to improve Jungle Scout. Unlimited product updates are included for the next year at no extra cost. Export Results : With one click of a button you can export all your data to a .csv file. Proof Tester</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/WvYkxqzhz2g?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><p><br></p><br><h3>Features</h3><br><p><br><ul><li> Quickly See Best Seller Ranks : One click of the Jungle Scout favicon neatly lists all the best seller ranks and pertinent categories. <br></li><li> Estimate Monthly Revenue : Using proprietary sales information, monthly unit sales and revenue are estimated for each product. <br></li><li> Works with Mac and PC : One click seamless installation into your Chrome browser means it works with any operating system and runs lean. <br></li><li> Uncover Product Review Stats : Product review statistics, including number of reviews and the average star rating are neatly displayed. <br></li><li> Free Updates : Team members work tirelessly to improve Jungle Scout. Unlimited product updates are included for the next year at no extra cost. <br></li><li> Export Results : With one click of a button you can export all your data to a .csv file.<br></li></ul></p><br><h3>Proof Tester</h3><br><p><br><a href="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-07/1437434033_jungles.png" class="highslide" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-07/thumbs/1437434033_jungles.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=''></a></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Jungle Scout 4.1.4 + Pro 2.1.6"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>ASINspector 2.4.1 + Pro 2.4.12</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1233-asinspector.html</link>
<description>Name : ASINspector Version : 2.4.1 + Pro 2.4.12 OS : Windows/MAC/Linux Type : Amazon Marketing Tools Price : $127 + 97$/yearly Homepage : SalePage ASINspector Amazon Search Tool Researching Amazon Just Got A Whole Lot Easier! ASINspector integrates into your Google Chrome browser as an extension, streamlining your product research. Extract rank, sales volume, estimated revenue, find out where it is being sold on other sites, source product and more without ever exiting your browser. Simply type a product in on Amazon and instantly get results and do this in multiple countries. If you are selling, know someone who is selling products on Amazon you will not want to do it without this tool. This will save you hours of work and allow you to be able easily beat your competition. You can find niche products to easily rank on Amazon.</description>
<category>Amazon Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://asinspector.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/10/mobile_scanning_asinpro.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://asinspector.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/10/asin_tracker_pro.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://asinspector.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/07/ss.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 08:32:38 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Estimate Monthly Revenue Find Niche products quickly and easily Know what your competition is doing volume wise instantly Works in multiple countries Find the product on other sources and compare such as Alibaba, Ebay (co,uk, ca, fr), Walmart, Target, Etc Categories and Nodes where you will want your product coming up! Graph with history pricing! Easy to use with any screen size! Extract your data to Excel/CSV, no limit to the amount you can extract! Use the tool right from AMZ product page, category page and seller page Allows you to alter the pricing to see how the numbers will change based on different scenarios! Much, Much, More... Allows you to sort by any keyword, product, category and find what is selling the most on Amazon You can ethically “spy” on your Competition by Quickly gathering whatever Data You Choose Works with Mac or PC - One click seamless installation into your Chrome browser means it works with any operating system and runs lean. Works with any country you may be in. Allows you to see what other competing sites such as Ebay, Walmart, Etc to see what pricing they are offering if at all. Easily source it on Alibaba and Aliexpress to see what price you might get the product at. Find out instantly what the monthly revenue is for any product you want. Quickly sort by most revenue made with one click Know instantly what rank, reviews, ratings, price of any product, niche, category you want. Know instantly every keyword the product is listed under Pro Version Spy on your competitor with our keyword search and find too Mobile - Yes scan any item anywhere from any store on your ISO/Android device Effortlessly filter any category and or column and drill down to find exactly the parameters you are looking for ASINspector Product Tracker - Track pricing, margins, inventory, and so much more - $80/mo value Easily find sponsored link products Brainstorm - Not sure what to search click our magic light bulb and let ASINspector Pro find it for you Simply store and save your most favorite searches to easily with one click find them again. Import unlimited amount of ASIN&#039;s at once, then let ASIN Pro research them all (with filters as well) Easily get other related keywords for any product in Google + Google Trends Easily reverse search sites like WalMart and have ASIN pull the results. ...much, MUCH more! Screen Pro Version Screen Nomal Version Walk Through</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/133793653?app_id=122963" width="425" height="484" frameborder="0" title="ASINspector Chrome Extension" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><p><br></p><br><h3>Features</h3><br><p><br><ul><li> Estimate Monthly Revenue<br></li><li> Find Niche products quickly and easily<br></li><li> Know what your competition is doing volume wise instantly<br></li><li> Works in multiple countries<br></li><li> Find the product on other sources and compare such as Alibaba, Ebay (co,uk, ca, fr), Walmart, Target, Etc<br></li><li> Categories and Nodes where you will want your product coming up!<br></li><li> Graph with history pricing!<br></li><li> Easy to use with any screen size!<br></li><li> Extract your data to Excel/CSV, no limit to the amount you can extract!<br></li><li> Use the tool right from AMZ product page, category page and seller page<br></li><li> Allows you to alter the pricing to see how the numbers will change based on different scenarios!<br></li><li> Much, Much, More...<br></li><li> Allows you to sort by any keyword, product, category and find what is selling the most on Amazon<br></li><li> You can ethically “spy” on your Competition by Quickly gathering whatever Data You Choose<br></li><li> Works with Mac or PC - One click seamless installation into your Chrome browser means it works with any operating system and runs lean.<br></li><li> Works with any country you may be in.<br></li><li> Allows you to see what other competing sites such as Ebay, Walmart, Etc to see what pricing they are offering if at all.<br></li><li> Easily source it on Alibaba and Aliexpress to see what price you might get the product at.<br></li><li> Find out instantly what the monthly revenue is for any product you want.<br></li><li> Quickly sort by most revenue made with one click<br></li><li> Know instantly what rank, reviews, ratings, price of any product, niche, category you want.<br></li><li> Know instantly every keyword the product is listed under<br></li></ul></p><br><h3>Pro Version</h3><br><p><br><ul><li> Spy on your competitor with our keyword search and find too<br></li><li> Mobile - Yes scan any item anywhere from any store on your ISO/Android device<br></li><li> Effortlessly filter any category and or column and drill down to find exactly the parameters you are looking for<br></li><li> ASINspector Product Tracker - Track pricing, margins, inventory, and so much more - /mo value<br></li><li> Easily find sponsored link products<br></li><li> Brainstorm - Not sure what to search click our magic light bulb and let ASINspector Pro find it for you<br></li><li> Simply store and save your most favorite searches to easily with one click find them again.<br></li><li> Import unlimited amount of ASIN's at once, then let ASIN Pro research them all (with filters as well)<br></li><li> Easily get other related keywords for any product in Google + Google Trends<br></li><li> Easily reverse search sites like WalMart and have ASIN pull the results.<br></li><li> ...much, MUCH more!<br></li></ul></p><br><h3>Screen Pro Version</h3><br><p><br><img src="http://asinspector.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/10/mobile_scanning_asinpro.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="ASINspector 2.4.1 + Pro 2.4.12"><br><img src="http://asinspector.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/10/asin_tracker_pro.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""></p><br><h3>Screen Nomal Version</h3><br><p><br><img src="http://asinspector.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/07/ss.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><br></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br>Walk Through<br><div class="dlevideoplayer" style="width:100%;max-width:425px;">
			<ul data-theme="default" data-preload="metadata">
				<li data-title="conv_35uu3ipxixd6v" data-type="m4v" data-url="https://vidhosting-files.s3.amazonaws.com/conv_35uu3ipxixd6v.mp4" ></li>
			</ul>
		</div><br><div class="dlevideoplayer" style="width:100%;max-width:425px;">
			<ul data-theme="default" data-preload="metadata">
				<li data-title="user_3_de7c29a8ba060897438bc0940ff026e4c685dba5" data-type="m4v" data-url="https://www.vidhostingonline.com/_members/_video_files/converted/media_124/user_3_de7c29a8ba060897438bc0940ff026e4c685dba5.mp4" ></li>
			</ul>
		</div><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>SellerHacks 10 in 1 2.5</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4340-sellerhacks.html</link>
<description>Name : SellerHacks 10 in 1 Version : 2.5 OS : Windows/MAC/Linux Type : Amazon FB Tools Price : $2997 Homepage : SalePage We believe that following a live, real case study is the best way for YOU to learn and implement the hacks and strategies we&#039;re successfully using in our Amazon business</description>
<category>Amazon Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 06:22:28 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Everything in PREMIUM Plus... Instead of 3 months, you get 6 months of free access to SellerHacks Insiders - our monthly coaching program. (6 x $397 = $2,382 real value) Instead of 3 months of Software Access, you get free acess to all our software for the entire duration of the case study, which is at least 12 months! ($11,964+ real value) Exclusive access to our Ultimate Review Hacks program - 3 different strategies for getting more reviews. Consisting of 3 different live training webinars, along with 3 Q&amp;amp;A live webinars and 3 different software tools that make the 3 strategies easy to implement and use. These hacks are not available anywhere else and this is the only way to get access to these 3 super powerful hacks. If you need more, high quality reviews - you need to get this. ($1,997 real value)</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/RTxey-UP_l0?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Everything in PREMIUM Plus...<br></li><li> Instead of 3 months, you get 6 months of free access to SellerHacks Insiders - our monthly coaching program. (6 x 7 = ,382 real value)<br></li><li> Instead of 3 months of Software Access, you get free acess to all our software for the entire duration of the case study, which is at least 12 months! (,964+ real value)<br></li><li> Exclusive access to our Ultimate Review Hacks program - 3 different strategies for getting more reviews. Consisting of 3 different live training webinars, along with 3 Q&amp;A live webinars and 3 different software tools that make the 3 strategies easy to implement and use. These hacks are not available anywhere else and this is the only way to get access to these 3 super powerful hacks. If you need more, high quality reviews - you need to get this. (,997 real value)<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="SellerHacks 10 in 1 2.5"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Amasuite 5.0.1.4</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/992-amasuite-4.html</link>
<description>Name : Amasuite (Ama Keyword Generator + Ama Top Product Analyzer+ Ama Search Analyzer + Ama Review Analyzer) Version : 5.0.1.4 (5.0.1.1 + 5.0.1.4 + 5.0.1.1 + 5.0.0.9) OS : Windows/MAC Type : Amazon Marketing Price : $297 Homepage : SalePage AmaSuite 5 is the collection of five powerful software tools designed to help solve some of the most important aspects of succeeding on Amazon. A totally re-invented version of AmaSuite with more powerful features than ever before</description>
<category>Amazon Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://20028-presscdn.pagely.comdna-cdn.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/top-product-analyzer-boxset-1.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://20028-presscdn.pagely.comdna-cdn.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/search-analyzer-boxset-3.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://20028-presscdn.pagely.comdna-cdn.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/keyword-generator-boxset-1.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://20028-presscdn.pagely.comdna-cdn.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/review-analyzer-boxset-1.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://20028-presscdn.pagely.comdna-cdn.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/ali-inspector-box-combo-2.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://20028-presscdn.pagely.comdna-cdn.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/sellers-training-course-set-600.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://20028-presscdn.pagely.comdna-cdn.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/affiliate-training-course-set-600.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 18:45:59 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Amasuite Top Product Analyzer Find hidden profitable niches to avoid the worry to releasing unsuccessful products Find hot selling items that you know will convert well when people click over to Amazon Amasuite Search Analyzer Go beyond the top 100 and take advantage of competitive info, like massively discounted productsAmasuite 5 Search Analyzer Amasuite Keyword Generator Out do the competition by finding what people are actually searching for when wanting to buy Find the perfect keywords for your product listing to show up and sell moreAmaSuite 5 Review Amasuite Review Analyzer Differentiate your product from the competition to increase sales &amp;amp; conversions Find new product ideas to private label on AmazonAmasuite 5 Review Analyzer Ali Inspector Find dropship products you can test on Amazon &amp;amp; then private label for your own business Analyze thousands of products on AliExpress in just minutes Amazon Sellers Training Course Module 1 – Introduction to selling on Amazon Module 2 – How to pick the right product to sell Module 3 – How to find a supplier Module 4 – How to get sales on Amazon Module 5 – How to get reviews on Amazon Module 6 – How to scale your from one product to many Module 7 – Customer Q&amp;amp;A – December 2016 Amazon Affiliate Training Course Module 1 – How To Research An Amazon Niche Module 2 – How to setup an Amazon web-site Module 3 – Should you build niche or authority web-sites Module 4 – Why Amazon review web-sites work the best Module 5 – How to write content for an Amazon web-site Module 6 – How to use AmaSync to cut down content creation times Module 7 – How to make Cash with Amazon websites Module 8 – How to get traffic to an Amazon web-site Module 9 – How to buy Amazon web-sites</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/y2bVeIXXlbo?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><img src="http://20028-presscdn.pagely.comdna-cdn.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/top-product-analyzer-boxset-1.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Amasuite 5.0.1.4"><br><b>Amasuite Top Product Analyzer</b><br><ul><li> Find hidden profitable niches to avoid the worry to releasing unsuccessful products<br></li><li> Find hot selling items that you know will convert well when people click over to Amazon<br></li></ul><br><br><img src="http://20028-presscdn.pagely.comdna-cdn.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/search-analyzer-boxset-3.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><b>Amasuite Search Analyzer</b><br><ul><li> Go beyond the top 100 and take advantage of competitive info, like massively discounted productsAmasuite 5 Search Analyzer<br></li></ul><br><br><img src="http://20028-presscdn.pagely.comdna-cdn.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/keyword-generator-boxset-1.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><b>Amasuite Keyword Generator</b><br><ul><li> Out do the competition by finding what people are actually searching for when wanting to buy<br></li><li> Find the perfect keywords for your product listing to show up and sell moreAmaSuite 5 Review<br></li></ul><br><br><img src="http://20028-presscdn.pagely.comdna-cdn.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/review-analyzer-boxset-1.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><b>Amasuite Review Analyzer</b><br><ul><li> Differentiate your product from the competition to increase sales &amp; conversions<br></li><li> Find new product ideas to private label on AmazonAmasuite 5 Review Analyzer<br></li></ul><br><br><img src="http://20028-presscdn.pagely.comdna-cdn.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/ali-inspector-box-combo-2.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><b>Ali Inspector</b><br><ul><li> Find dropship products you can test on Amazon &amp; then private label for your own business<br></li><li> Analyze thousands of products on AliExpress in just minutes<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://20028-presscdn.pagely.comdna-cdn.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/sellers-training-course-set-600.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><br><b>Amazon Sellers Training Course</b><br><ul><li> Module 1 – Introduction to selling on Amazon<br></li><li> Module 2 – How to pick the right product to sell<br></li><li> Module 3 – How to find a supplier<br></li><li> Module 4 – How to get sales on Amazon<br></li><li> Module 5 – How to get reviews on Amazon<br></li><li> Module 6 – How to scale your from one product to many<br></li><li> Module 7 – Customer Q&amp;A – December 2016<br></li></ul><br><br><img src="http://20028-presscdn.pagely.comdna-cdn.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/affiliate-training-course-set-600.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><b>Amazon Affiliate Training Course</b><br><ul><li> Module 1 – How To Research An Amazon Niche<br></li><li> Module 2 – How to setup an Amazon web-site<br></li><li> Module 3 – Should you build niche or authority web-sites<br></li><li> Module 4 – Why Amazon review web-sites work the best<br></li><li> Module 5 – How to write content for an Amazon web-site<br></li><li> Module 6 – How to use AmaSync to cut down content creation times<br></li><li> Module 7 – How to make Cash with Amazon websites<br></li><li> Module 8 – How to get traffic to an Amazon web-site<br></li><li> Module 9 – How to buy Amazon web-sites<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Amazon Keyword Generator 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3996-amazon-keyword-generator.html</link>
<description>Name : Amazon Keyword Generator Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Amazon Keyword Tool Price : $59 Homepage : SalePage Amazon Keyword Tool is a keyword software tool that allows users to generate unlimited long tail keywords from Amazon auto search suggest. Amazon auto search suggest keywords are generated when an Amazon user enters any characters. For example if they enter cooking then a list of auto complete suggestions will be generated.</description>
<category>Amazon Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 03:19:40 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features The tool simply fires requests off to Amazon in the background and scrapes the results to automatically to find long tail variants of your niches keywords that Amazon users are searching for when buying items from Amazon. You simply enter your inital niches keyword(s) then configure the depth of long tails you want to generate and click start.. For example if your niche/main keyword is gaming, you would simply enter gaming and click generate long tails and the software would bring back hundreds of gaming related long tail keywords to give you a better insight into what Amazon customers in your niche are searching for. This will also help you optimise your Amazon listings so they appear higher up in Amazon search results.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/CYEnR1xeFh4?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> The tool simply fires requests off to Amazon in the background and scrapes the results to automatically to find long tail variants of your niches keywords that Amazon users are searching for when buying items from Amazon. You simply enter your inital niches keyword(s) then configure the depth of long tails you want to generate and click start.. For example if your niche/main keyword is gaming, you would simply enter gaming and click generate long tails and the software would bring back hundreds of gaming related long tail keywords to give you a better insight into what Amazon customers in your niche are searching for. This will also help you optimise your Amazon listings so they appear higher up in Amazon search results.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Amazon Keyword Generator 1.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Amazon Link Checker 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4133-amazon-link-checker.html</link>
<description>Name : Amazon Link Checker Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Amazon Check Link Tool Price : $50 Homepage : SalePage Amazon Link Checker is a desktop tool that will crawl your Amazon affiliate website checking all your outbound links to Amazon for out of stock, unavailable, 404, missing affiliate tracking IDs and more. You simply enter your website&#039;s address and click &quot;Start check&quot; and it will check every webpage on your website for Amazon affiliate links with any issues.</description>
<category>Amazon Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 06:17:23 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Using advanced crawling technology you don&#039;t need to tell this tool about every page on your website you simply enter your homepage and it will go page to page searching for outbound links to Amazon. Once it finds one it can check for any of the following issues. - Check product score - You may write an amazon review for a newly launched product that you think is going to be amazing but once people get hold of it they may give it negative reviews. This check will tell you if the average review score is below a certain threshold. With that information you can switch products you are promoting or stop promoting that product with negative reviews. - Out of stock - This simple check will tell you if an Amazon product is out of stock. - Check for affiliate code - This mode will check if your tracking ID (affiliate code) is present in the link to the Amazon product. - Check for 404 - This mode will check for pages you are linking to that no longer exist (or maybe didn&#039;t ever) by checking the server HTTP response code. Examples of server HTTP response codes that will cause issues with your links are 404 (page not found) and 500 (internal server error). - Check for unavailable - This mode will check if the product you are linking to is still available and actually being sold.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/UHHRLRWfnjY?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Using advanced crawling technology you don't need to tell this tool about every page on your website you simply enter your homepage and it will go page to page searching for outbound links to Amazon. Once it finds one it can check for any of the following issues.<br></li><li> - Check product score - You may write an amazon review for a newly launched product that you think is going to be amazing but once people get hold of it they may give it negative reviews. This check will tell you if the average review score is below a certain threshold. With that information you can switch products you are promoting or stop promoting that product with negative reviews.<br></li><li> - Out of stock - This simple check will tell you if an Amazon product is out of stock.<br></li><li> - Check for affiliate code - This mode will check if your tracking ID (affiliate code) is present in the link to the Amazon product.<br></li><li> - Check for 404 - This mode will check for pages you are linking to that no longer exist (or maybe didn't ever) by checking the server HTTP response code. Examples of server HTTP response codes that will cause issues with your links are 404 (page not found) and 500 (internal server error).<br></li><li> - Check for unavailable - This mode will check if the product you are linking to is still available and actually being sold.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Amazon Link Checker 1.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Amazon Ripper 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3728-amazon-ripper.html</link>
<description>Name : Amazon Ripper Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Scrape Amazon products Price : $0 Homepage : SalePage Amazon ripper is a simply free desktop application that allows you to add Amazon items categories and it will scrape / rip all the products from your selected category.</description>
<category>Amazon Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 05:28:08 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>[media=https://youtu.be/NS6MpvdXN5E] Features What information does it scrape / rip? Amazon ripper can scrape the item url, item title, item review count and item price. Why should I use Amazon Ripper? When searching for new Amazon products to review if you are a member of the Amazon affiliate program you can use Amazon Ripper to scrape all products in a category and sort by review count (indicating purchase quanity) and price giving you a much better idea about what products to promote rather than checking each item in a category individually. How does Amazon Ripper work? HTTP requests are simply sent from the desktop application you download (100% free and full, no trial etc) and the HTML is parsed and the items are extracted out for you to browse or export. Will Amazon ban my IP address? By default the application sends requests at a speed that will not cause your IP address to get banned. However if you want to scrape Amazon products and items even faster Amazon Ripper does support an unlimited number of proxies.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;">[media=https://youtu.be/NS6MpvdXN5E]</div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br>What information does it scrape / rip?<br>Amazon ripper can scrape the item url, item title, item review count and item price.<br><br>Why should I use Amazon Ripper?<br>When searching for new Amazon products to review if you are a member of the Amazon affiliate program you can use Amazon Ripper to scrape all products in a category and sort by review count (indicating purchase quanity) and price giving you a much better idea about what products to promote rather than checking each item in a category individually.<br><br>How does Amazon Ripper work?<br>HTTP requests are simply sent from the desktop application you download (100% free and full, no trial etc) and the HTML is parsed and the items are extracted out for you to browse or export.<br><br>Will Amazon ban my IP address?<br>By default the application sends requests at a speed that will not cause your IP address to get banned. However if you want to scrape Amazon products and items even faster Amazon Ripper does support an unlimited number of proxies.<br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Amazon Ripper 1.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Easy Amazon 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3663-easy-amazon.html</link>
<description>Name : Easy Amazon Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Scrape Amazon products Price : $0 Homepage : SalePage Easy Amazon allows you to find items and products sold on Amazon that have zero review competition on Google. If you are a member of the Amazon affiliate program this tool can seriously boost your traffic and commissions.</description>
<category>Amazon Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 05:27:43 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>[media=https://youtu.be/Q08lHSdHRmQ] Features How does Easy Amazon work? Once you enter your Amazon category Easy Amazon will crawl each page scraping all the items and products. For every item it will check if people are searching for reviews on Google using the Google suggest API. If people are searching for reviews for the chosen product / item then easy Amazon will send the search query of &quot;product name + review&quot;. For each result that is returned for this search query Easy Amazon checks if they are promoting Amazon products. This allows you to find products and items that have literally zero compition on Google for item / product reviews. Why should I use Easy Amazon? Easy Amazon can save you literally hours, even days of Amazon product / item keyword research. How many times have you seen a great item in your niche you&#039;d like to review only to see that Google is stuffed full of highly targeted results for reviews for that item / product.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;">[media=https://youtu.be/Q08lHSdHRmQ]</div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br>How does Easy Amazon work?<br>Once you enter your Amazon category Easy Amazon will crawl each page scraping all the items and products. For every item it will check if people are searching for reviews on Google using the Google suggest API. If people are searching for reviews for the chosen product / item then easy Amazon will send the search query of "product name + review". For each result that is returned for this search query Easy Amazon checks if they are promoting Amazon products. This allows you to find products and items that have literally zero compition on Google for item / product reviews.<br><br>Why should I use Easy Amazon?<br>Easy Amazon can save you literally hours, even days of Amazon product / item keyword research. How many times have you seen a great item in your niche you'd like to review only to see that Google is stuffed full of highly targeted results for reviews for that item / product.<br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Easy Amazon 1.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>LionCow 1.1.9</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1835-lioncow.html</link>
<description>Name : LionCow Version : 1.1.9 OS : Windows Type : Plugin Review Price : $0 Homepage : SalePage RESOLVE NEGATIVE REVIEWS &amp;amp; GIVE CUSTOMERS A REASON TO RECOMMEND YOUR BRAND AGAIN YOUR DATA IS SECURE (WE CAN’T SEE IT) US UK DE FR IT ES MARKETPLACES SUPPORTED VIRTUAL ASSISTANT FRIENDLY</description>
<category>Amazon Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 00:14:15 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features NEW. SIMPLE. ESSENTIAL! OFTEN THE FIRST INSTANCE YOU FIND OUT ABOUT A CUSTOMER ISSUE IS THROUGH A NEGATIVE REVIEW. IT’S A LOSE-LOSE SITUATION. YOUR SALES ARE AFFECTED AND THE CUSTOMER IS LEFT FEELING FRUSTRATED WITH THEIR SHOPPING EXPERIENCE. YOU HAVE THE OPTION TO “RESOLVE” SELLER FEEDBACK… …AND THE SAME IS AVAILABLE FOR REVIEWS TOO. IT’S JUST NOT AS OBVIOUS. THAT’S WHY WE CREATED LIONCOW – THE CUSTOMER EXCELLENCE PLUGIN. LIONCOW MATCHES REVIEWS TO CUSTOMER ORDERS. ALLOWING YOU TO RESOLVE CUSTOMER ISSUES LEFT AS PRODUCT REVIEWS. OFTEN THE FIRST INSTANCE YOU FIND OUT ABOUT A CUSTOMER ISSUE IS THROUGH A NEGATIVE REVIEW. IT’S A LOSE-LOSE SITUATION. YOUR SALES ARE AFFECTED AND THE CUSTOMER IS LEFT FEELING FRUSTRATED WITH THEIR SHOPPING EXPERIENCE. YOU HAVE THE OPTION TO “RESOLVE” SELLER FEEDBACK… …AND THE SAME IS AVAILABLE FOR REVIEWS TOO. IT’S JUST NOT AS OBVIOUS. THAT’S WHY WE CREATED LIONCOW – THE CUSTOMER EXCELLENCE PLUGIN. LIONCOW MATCHES REVIEWS TO CUSTOMER ORDERS. ALLOWING YOU TO RESOLVE CUSTOMER ISSUES LEFT AS PRODUCT REVIEWS. The LionCow plugin adds a new locate order button next to all of your reviews. Click it and LionCow get’s to work locating the order associated to your chosen review. Next you’ll get a pop-up showing the order details including the Amazon Order ID and customer name, plus a view order button so that you can go straight to the order in seller central with one click. Once you know who the customer is who left you that negative review you can go and give them a taste of your awesome customer service and wow them into updating their review. LionCow members have access to our proven strategies for delivering amazing customer service which can often lead to the customer wanting to update their review – without ever asking them to do so. We advocate amazing customer service not incentivizing customers to change their reviews. LEAVING YOUR CUSTOMER WITH A BAD EXPERIENCE IS VERY POOR CUSTOMER SERVICE SURE, THE CUSTOMER COULD RETURN THE ITEM FOR A REFUND AND BUY A NEW ONE BUT THAT IS A TIME CONSUMING PROCESS FOR THEM AND NOT SOMETHING WE THINK ANY CUSTOMER SHOULD HAVE TO GO THROUGH. JOIN US IN OUR CAMPAIGN AGAINST POOR CUSTOMER SERVICE AND START AMAZING YOUR CUSTOMERS TODAY. LIONCOW SPY WANT TO KNOW YOUR COMPETITORS EXACT BACKEND SEARCH TERMS? WITH LIONCOW SPY YOU’RE ONLY EVER 60 SECONDS AWAY… HOW IT WORKS 1. Step 1 Select the marketplace you want to do the lookup in 2. Step 2 List the ASINs to extract backend keywords from 3. Step 3 Pay for your order securely via Stripe Step 4 Instant download of your keyword CSV file</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/tk-udL8MZ90?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br>NEW. SIMPLE. ESSENTIAL!<br>OFTEN THE FIRST INSTANCE YOU FIND OUT ABOUT A CUSTOMER ISSUE IS THROUGH A NEGATIVE REVIEW.<br><br>IT’S A LOSE-LOSE SITUATION.<br><br>YOUR SALES ARE AFFECTED AND THE CUSTOMER IS LEFT FEELING FRUSTRATED WITH THEIR SHOPPING EXPERIENCE.<br><br>YOU HAVE THE OPTION TO “RESOLVE” SELLER FEEDBACK…<br><br>…AND THE SAME IS AVAILABLE FOR REVIEWS TOO.<br><br>IT’S JUST NOT AS OBVIOUS.<br><br>THAT’S WHY WE CREATED LIONCOW – THE CUSTOMER EXCELLENCE PLUGIN.<br><br>LIONCOW MATCHES REVIEWS TO CUSTOMER ORDERS.<br><br>ALLOWING YOU TO RESOLVE CUSTOMER ISSUES LEFT AS PRODUCT REVIEWS.<br><br>OFTEN THE FIRST INSTANCE YOU FIND OUT ABOUT A CUSTOMER ISSUE IS THROUGH A NEGATIVE REVIEW.<br><br>IT’S A LOSE-LOSE SITUATION.<br><br>YOUR SALES ARE AFFECTED AND THE CUSTOMER IS LEFT FEELING FRUSTRATED WITH THEIR SHOPPING EXPERIENCE.<br><br>YOU HAVE THE OPTION TO “RESOLVE” SELLER FEEDBACK…<br><br>…AND THE SAME IS AVAILABLE FOR REVIEWS TOO.<br><br>IT’S JUST NOT AS OBVIOUS.<br><br>THAT’S WHY WE CREATED LIONCOW – THE CUSTOMER EXCELLENCE PLUGIN.<br><br>LIONCOW MATCHES REVIEWS TO CUSTOMER ORDERS.<br><br>ALLOWING YOU TO RESOLVE CUSTOMER ISSUES LEFT AS PRODUCT REVIEWS.<br><br>The LionCow plugin adds a new locate order button next to all of your reviews.<br>Click it and LionCow get’s to work locating the order associated to your chosen review.<br>Next you’ll get a pop-up showing the order details including the Amazon Order ID and customer name, plus a view order button so that you can go straight to the order in seller central with one click.<br>Once you know who the customer is who left you that negative review you can go and give them a taste of your awesome customer service and wow them into updating their review.<br><br>LionCow members have access to our proven strategies for delivering amazing customer service which can often lead to the customer wanting to update their review – without ever asking them to do so.<br>We advocate amazing customer service not incentivizing customers to change their reviews.<br><br>LEAVING YOUR CUSTOMER WITH A BAD EXPERIENCE IS VERY POOR CUSTOMER SERVICE<br><br>SURE, THE CUSTOMER COULD RETURN THE ITEM FOR A REFUND AND BUY A NEW ONE BUT THAT IS A TIME CONSUMING PROCESS FOR THEM AND NOT SOMETHING WE THINK ANY CUSTOMER SHOULD HAVE TO GO THROUGH.<br><br>JOIN US IN OUR CAMPAIGN AGAINST POOR CUSTOMER SERVICE AND START AMAZING YOUR CUSTOMERS TODAY.<br><br>LIONCOW SPY<br>WANT TO KNOW YOUR COMPETITORS EXACT BACKEND SEARCH TERMS?<br><br>WITH LIONCOW SPY YOU’RE ONLY EVER 60 SECONDS AWAY…<br><br><b>HOW IT WORKS</b><br>1. Step 1<br>Select the marketplace you want to do the lookup in<br><br>2. Step 2<br>List the ASINs to extract backend keywords from<br><br>3. Step 3<br>Pay for your order securely via Stripe<br><br>Step 4<br>Instant download of your keyword CSV file<br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="LionCow 1.1.9"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>AMZing PRO 2.1.4</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3763-amzing-pro.html</link>
<description>Name : AMZing PRO Version : 2.1.4 OS : Windows/MAC/Linux Type : FBA Keyword Tools Price : $39 Homepage : SalePage Fast and accurate Amazon Ebay and Aliexpress Keywords Scraper, desktop application which will scrape Central E-commerce Sites for REAL Keywords That People Are Typing Into The Main Search Box and download into convenient, CSV file. AMZing PRO Scraper Support international E-commerce Sites for the United States, United Kingdom and Ireland, France,Canada, Germany, Italy,Spain,Netherlands,Australia, Brazil, Japan, China, India, and Mexico.</description>
<category>Amazon Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 22:08:27 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features You can search by a keywords, such as “Cat Toys&quot; and pull up all products that People are interested in. This process will help you reveal the most successful Target Products, so that you can create profitable campaigns in no time! Millions of people are using Amazon, Ebay &amp;amp; AliExpress to find and buy products that they are interested in. AMZing PRO Keyword Suggestions Scraper helps you to figure out what those products are. AMZing PRO Keyword Suggestions Scraper is using E-commerce Sites autocomplete or search suggestion feature to generate a big number of relevant keywords that can be used for Amazon or Ebay keyword optimization or any other purpose. AMZing PRO helps you to generate relevant long-tail keywords using Sites search suggest function. Every time a person types something into the Site search box, he or she starts seeing search suggestions. E-commerce Sites Sites use sophisticated algorithms to try and predict what products would be the best match for the entered keyword. Explode Your Profits With Targets Products Strategy. AMZing PRO is a strong and beneficial tool which provides you with highly valuable information that can be used to develop and deliver a strategic approach to your ad campaigns Discover Opportunities Quickly . Marketing is about adapting to changes while taking advantage of what’s trending. AMZing PRO provides an excelent insights so that you can become aware of the hottest niches as well as find Products who are starting to gain a presence. When you want to maximize your ROIs, stay on top of this opportunity and know what’s going on AMZing PRO Keyword Suggestions Scraper uses this Sites feature to generate hundreds of long-tails keywords for Amazon keyword optimization in seconds. Keyword Tool takes the seed keyword that you specify, places it into the Sites search box and appends it with different letters and numbers. Then Keyword Tool pulls all the keyword suggestions generated by Sites and presents it to you in a straightforward and elegant manner. All the processes happen behind the scenes and take mere seconds. To start the search you will need to provide a seed keyword that will be used to generate the Site keywords for you. After pressing the Extract button, you will be able to see hundreds of long-tail keywords that are pulled from Sites Data in seconds. You can easily copy or download the generated keywords and use them for any purpose you have in mind. One of the worst things has to be when you dedicate a lot of time and resources to an advertiser who ends up not converting as expected. Instead of wasting your time taking blind leaps of faith, entrust AMZing PRO to find the Products which are already converting well. Handcrafted by experts ! AMZing PRO was built by professionals with more than ten years of software Dev. experience. With AMZing PRO, we have used our experience from countless IM software projects and designed a tool that fits perfectly into the workflow of both professionals and novices Optimized for speed and time AMZing PRO contains the fastest process mining algorithms, and the most efficient search engine framework. On top of that, you get an obsessively streamlined user experience allowing you to move fast. Because what counts is performance from start to finish. Designed for humans Software should serve the user, not the other way around. You are already a marketing expert, and you shouldn&#039;t need to become an expert in using process mining software. With AMZING PRO, you don&#039;t need to, because we made it intelligent, sane, and fun. Step-by-Step &quot;how to&quot; Tutorial. AMZing PRO is one of the simplest and most intuitive IM software you will ever use and you probably will not have any questions... But just in case you do, each and every feature is covered in full detail, in the help section. AMZing PRO goal is that you are completely satisfied with your &quot;purchase&quot; :-) &quot;. If for any reason you aren&#039;t satisfied we will be at your service please let us know by: Emailing a request to yossi@roi.im For Windows * Mac * Chromebook * Linux * Commodore 64 You don&#039;t need to be Log-In to Any Sites to use AMZing PRO! AMZing PRO Scraper Support Amazon / Ebay Sites for the United States, United Kingdom and Ireland, France,Canada, Germany, Italy, Spain, Netherlands,Australia, Brazil, Japan, China, India, and Mexico. Important : Amzing PRO Keyword Suggestions Scraper presents keywords in exactly the same order as they were pulled from the Site autocomplete. Usually, E-commerce Sites will place more relevant and popular keywords above the less popular keywords. Unfortunately, E-commerce Sites does not provide keyword search volume data. That&#039;s why you should use Google Keyword Planner search volume for your keywords results to help you estimate their relative popularity.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/BW9kEGUQg3E?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> You can search by a keywords, such as “Cat Toys"  and pull up all products that People are interested in. This process will help you reveal the most successful Target Products, so that you can create profitable campaigns in no time!<br></li><li> Millions of people are using Amazon, Ebay &amp; AliExpress to find and buy products that they are interested in. AMZing PRO Keyword Suggestions Scraper<br></li><li> helps you to figure out what those products are. <br></li><li> AMZing PRO Keyword Suggestions Scraper is using E-commerce Sites autocomplete or search suggestion feature to generate a big number of relevant keywords that can be used for Amazon or Ebay keyword optimization or any other purpose.<br></li><li> AMZing PRO  helps you to generate relevant long-tail keywords using Sites search suggest function. Every time a person types something into the Site search box, he or she starts seeing search suggestions. E-commerce Sites Sites use sophisticated algorithms to try and predict what products would be the best match for the entered keyword. <br></li><li> Explode Your Profits With Targets Products Strategy. <br></li><li> AMZing PRO  is a strong and beneficial tool which provides you with highly valuable information that can be used to develop and deliver a strategic approach to your ad campaigns<br></li><li> Discover Opportunities Quickly . Marketing is about adapting to changes while taking advantage of what’s trending. <br></li><li> AMZing PRO provides an excelent insights  so that you can become aware of the hottest niches as well as find Products who are starting to gain a presence. When you want to maximize your ROIs, stay on top of this opportunity and know what’s going on<br></li><li> AMZing PRO  Keyword Suggestions Scraper uses this Sites feature to generate hundreds of long-tails keywords for Amazon keyword optimization in seconds. Keyword Tool takes the seed keyword that you specify, places it into the Sites search box and appends it with different letters and numbers. Then Keyword Tool pulls all the keyword suggestions generated by Sites and presents it to you in a straightforward and elegant manner. All the processes happen behind the scenes and take mere seconds.<br></li><li> To start the search you will need to provide a seed keyword that will be used to generate the Site keywords for you. After pressing the Extract button, you will be able to see hundreds of long-tail keywords that are pulled from Sites Data in seconds. You can easily copy or download the generated keywords and use them for any purpose you have in mind.<br></li><li> One of the worst things has to be when you dedicate a lot of time and resources to an advertiser who ends up not converting as expected. Instead of wasting your time taking blind leaps of faith, entrust AMZing PRO  to find the Products which are already converting well.<br></li><li> Handcrafted by experts ! AMZing PRO  was built by professionals with more than ten years of software Dev. experience. With AMZing PRO, we have used our experience from countless IM software projects and designed a tool that fits perfectly into the workflow of both professionals and novices<br></li><li> Optimized for speed and time AMZing PRO contains the fastest process mining algorithms, and the most efficient search engine framework. On top of that, you get an obsessively streamlined user experience allowing you to move fast. Because what counts is performance from start to finish.<br></li><li> Designed for humans Software should serve the user, not the other way around. You are already a marketing expert, and you shouldn't need to become an expert in using process mining software. With AMZING PRO, you don't need to, because we made it intelligent, sane, and fun.<br></li><li> Step-by-Step "how to" Tutorial. AMZing PRO is one of the simplest and most intuitive IM software you will ever use and you probably will not have any questions... But just in case you do, each and every feature is covered in full detail, in the help section.<br></li><li> AMZing PRO goal is that you are completely satisfied with your "purchase" :-) ". If for any reason you aren't satisfied we will be at your service please let us know by: Emailing a request to yossi@roi.im<br></li><li> For Windows  *  Mac  * Chromebook  * Linux  * Commodore 64<br></li><li> You don't need to be Log-In to Any Sites to use AMZing PRO!<br></li><li> AMZing PRO Scraper Support Amazon / Ebay  Sites  for the United States, United Kingdom and Ireland, France,Canada, Germany, Italy, Spain, Netherlands,Australia, Brazil, Japan, China, India, and Mexico.<br></li><li> Important : Amzing PRO  Keyword Suggestions Scraper presents keywords in exactly the same order as they were pulled from the Site autocomplete. Usually, E-commerce Sites will place more relevant and popular keywords above the less popular keywords. Unfortunately, E-commerce Sites does not provide keyword search volume data. That's why you should use Google Keyword Planner search volume for your keywords results to help you estimate their relative popularity.  <br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="AMZing PRO 2.1.4"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>