<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Youtube Marketing - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Youtube Marketing - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>VidIQ Vision EnterPrise 2.68.5</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4474-vidiq-vision.html</link>
<description>Name : VidIQ Vision EnterPrise Version : 2.68.5 OS : Windows Type : Video YouTube Tool Price : $39/m Homepage : SalePage Uncover YouTube video success secrets vidIQ Vision for Google Chrome helps you understand why videos are promoted in Related Videos, Search, and Recommended Videos</description>
<category>Youtube Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 11:09:51 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Rank The vidIQ Score helps judge the likelihood of a video being promoted in Related Videos, Search, and Recommended Videos. Discover Success on YouTube is about more than just views — Vision keeps you focused on the metrics that matter. Optimize Use what you learn to drive better decision making for your own content.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/y_AzfqVG8Jw?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Rank<br></li><li> The vidIQ Score helps judge the likelihood of a video being promoted in Related Videos, Search, and Recommended Videos.<br></li><li> Discover<br></li><li> Success on YouTube is about more than just views — Vision keeps you focused on the metrics that matter.<br></li><li> Optimize<br></li><li> Use what you learn to drive better decision making for your own content.<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="VidIQ Vision EnterPrise 2.68.5"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Playinator 7.10</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1751-playinator.html</link>
<description>Name : Playinator Version : 7.10 OS : Windows Type : Youtube Marketing Price : $69 Homepage : SalePage &quot;Tired of Getting Just a Few YouTube Video Views? Are your videos always remaining unseen by the rest of the world?&quot; Well, the solution is here... Playinator is an easy, efficient and fully automated software to increase YouTube views - that will increase the views in all of your videos, and will NOT freeze them at the 300 views mark!</description>
<category>Youtube Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.playinator.com/images/playinator_v6_website_11.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://www.playinator.com/screen_v6.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 16:24:12 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/oC080H67sAs?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><img src="http://www.playinator.com/images/playinator_v6_website_11.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Playinator 7.10"><br><img src="http://www.playinator.com/screen_v6.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Channel Authority Builder Pro 1.4</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1379-channel-authority-builder-pro.html</link>
<description>Name : Channel Authority Builder Pro Version : 1.4 OS : Youtube Type : Youtube Marketing Tools Price : $97 Homepage : SalePage A Next Generation Video Marketing System That Helps You To Unlock The Power Of YouTube &amp;amp; Generate Millions Of Views To Your YouTube channel By Discovering Strategies Used By Market Leaders.. This Is The First YouTube Software That Is Focused Totally On Helping Marketers Build Authority Or Target YouTube’s Content Discovery Mechanisms. Most Of The Competing Products Just Go After Keywords Or Search. Channel Authority Builder is a tool which helps people in content planning to create strategic content that is relevant, targets other videos and can get people long term organic traffic, not from search but from YouTube’s content discovery. This is the strategy you need to unlock 80% of the traffic that you’re not getting targeting only keywords, and to create long-term authority channels.</description>
<category>Youtube Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 13:18:20 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Keyword Rank Tracker - Well, it comes with a keyword rank tracker that lets you monitor how your other videos are ranking for keywords on YouTube over time. Video Stats Monitor - Video stats monitor features lets you monitor all the current statistics of any video on YouTube on a daily basis. Channel Stats Monitor - It helps you to monitor all the current statistics for a channel on everyday basis. Latest Videos From Monitored Channels - Well, this is another innovative feature that lets you discover all the latest videos from all those channels you are monitoring. Sidebar Monitor - Lets you find whether you are appearing on a video&#039;s sidebar and the trends there. Related Channels Finder - with this feature you can quickly find all those channels that is related to a YouTube Channel. Trending Tags Finder - Here you can discover what new tags your competitors are targeting right now for the business to boost their videos. Popular Videos Finder - You can find what new videos from your competitors have actually become popular.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/nT5U9y5Mr8c?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Keyword Rank Tracker - Well, it comes with a keyword rank tracker that lets you monitor how your other videos are ranking for keywords on YouTube over time.<br></li><li> Video Stats Monitor - Video stats monitor features lets you monitor all the current statistics of any video on YouTube on a daily basis.<br></li><li> Channel Stats Monitor - It helps you to monitor all the current statistics for a channel on everyday basis.<br></li><li> Latest Videos From Monitored Channels - Well, this is another innovative feature that lets you discover all the latest videos from all those channels you are monitoring.<br></li><li> Sidebar Monitor - Lets you find whether you are appearing on a video's sidebar and the trends there.<br></li><li> Related Channels Finder - with this feature you can quickly find all those channels that is related to a YouTube Channel.<br></li><li> Trending Tags Finder - Here you can discover what new tags your competitors are targeting right now for the business to boost their videos.<br></li><li> Popular Videos Finder - You can find what new videos from your competitors have actually become popular.<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Channel Authority Builder Pro 1.4"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Tube Rank Jeet 4.2 Pro</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/945-tuberank-jeet.html</link>
<description>Name : Tuberank Jeet 3 Pro Version : 4.2 OS : Windows Type : Youtube Marketing Price : $67 Homepage : SalePage Rank Your YouTube Videos on Page #1! This revolutionary video optimization tool is your secret weapon to help you create killer video campaigns that spell DEFEAT for your competition. What are the places you get traffic from right now? Facebook? Google? Is YouTube of one of them? If all your traffic is coming only from Facebook and Google, you’re leaving a big empty hole in your strategy. It’s like running a car with one tyre flat. You’re moving, but it’s not fast enough, and you’re forced to watch all those other guys zip by. You see, YouTube is the third most popular website of the world with 1.3 billion active users, and over 1 billion video views per day. Yes, the world is watching YouTube and if you cannot be found there, you’re letting too much money escape!</description>
<category>Youtube Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://tuberankjeet.com/Content/salesimg/product.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 13:16:33 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Tells you what is the traffic and ranking potential for absolutely any keyword. Analyzes existing videos ranking for your niche or keyword and finds out what you need to beat them. Finds you three levels of keywords a) Long-tail for easy ranking, b) Medium value for traffic with minimal effort and c) High value for top quality traffic. Viewer sentiment analysis tells you what exactly people feel about your niche or keyword telling you where the market is headed. Grab stats and tags from any video you want, appear on its related videos bar. Proven algorithm gives you the ranking-recipe, telling you exactly what you need to do to rank. Everything right at your fingertips to make optimization a 2-minute process. Save your time! Uploads videos directly to YouTube, Vimeo (Pro Version) or Dailymotion (Pro Version)</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/W6dmHzPXEFQ?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Tells you what is the traffic and ranking potential for absolutely any keyword.<br></li><li> Analyzes existing videos ranking for your niche or keyword and finds out what you need to beat them.<br></li><li> Finds you three levels of keywords a) Long-tail for easy ranking, b) Medium value for traffic with minimal effort and c) High value for top quality traffic.<br></li><li> Viewer sentiment analysis tells you what exactly people feel about your niche or keyword telling you where the market is headed.<br></li><li> Grab stats and tags from any video you want, appear on its related videos bar.<br></li><li> Proven algorithm gives you the ranking-recipe, telling you exactly what you need to do to rank.<br></li><li> Everything right at your fingertips to make optimization a 2-minute process. Save your time!<br></li><li> Uploads videos directly to YouTube, Vimeo (Pro Version) or Dailymotion (Pro Version)<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://tuberankjeet.com/Content/salesimg/product.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Tube Rank Jeet 4.2 Pro"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Easy YouTube Traffic 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4174-easy-youtube-traffic.html</link>
<description>Name : Easy YouTube Traffic Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : YouTube Research Tool Price : $59 Homepage : SalePage Easy YouTube Traffic is a dekstop software tool that allows users to find YouTube videos with massive views that are unm.comized and not linked with a business in anyway. These videos can be used to generate huge amounts of niche targeted traffic from YouTube.</description>
<category>Youtube Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 03:23:24 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features You simply enter your keywords into the tool and it will go off and in the background scrape Youtube for videos related to your keywords. These videos are then checked for certain configurable criteria to assess if they are currently being monitised in any way by the user who uploaded the video. If they are not being monitised currently, you can reach out to the vieo uploader and offer something in return for your link being inserted in the description. Easy, white hat, safe, cheap traffic! Tool options - The options below allow you to tune the search for unmonitised videos. - Exclude verified channels - This option will exclude any videos from any channels that are verified. Verified channel will be monitising their videos. - Exclude channels with links on about - This option will exclude any videos from uploaders that have links on their about page, which businesses normally do. - Exclude videos with links in description - This option will exclude any videos with links in their description as they are probably being monitised - Exclude if channel has custom thumb nail - If the uploader has a custom thumb nail they may be a business (this can be on/off depending on your results) - Mine more keywords from keywords - This option will use the auto suggest feature on YouTube search to find long tail variants of your entered keywords. Turning 1 keyword into hundreds. - Use proxies (dedicated) - Use proxies for faster scraping, please use dedicated high quality proxies. - Min Views - The minimum amount of views a video should have before its showm in the results grid - Max Subs - If an uploader has over &quot;Max subs&quot; value then exclude the video as this is an indication of a monitised video/channel</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/QLbLPBWX3kY?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> You simply enter your keywords into the tool and it will go off and in the background scrape Youtube for videos related to your keywords. These videos are then checked for certain configurable criteria to assess if they are currently being monitised in any way by the user who uploaded the video. If they are not being monitised currently, you can reach out to the vieo uploader and offer something in return for your link being inserted in the description. Easy, white hat, safe, cheap traffic!<br></li><li> Tool options<br></li><li> - The options below allow you to tune the search for unmonitised videos.<br></li><li> - Exclude verified channels - This option will exclude any videos from any channels that are verified. Verified channel will be monitising their videos.<br></li><li> - Exclude channels with links on about - This option will exclude any videos from uploaders that have links on their about page, which businesses normally do.<br></li><li> - Exclude videos with links in description - This option will exclude any videos with links in their description as they are probably being monitised<br></li><li> - Exclude if channel has custom thumb nail - If the uploader has a custom thumb nail they may be a business (this can be on/off depending on your results)<br></li><li> - Mine more keywords from keywords - This option will use the auto suggest feature on YouTube search to find long tail variants of your entered keywords. Turning 1 keyword into hundreds.<br></li><li> - Use proxies (dedicated) - Use proxies for faster scraping, please use dedicated high quality proxies.<br></li><li> - Min Views - The minimum amount of views a video should have before its showm in the results grid<br></li><li> - Max Subs - If an uploader has over "Max subs" value then exclude the video as this is an indication of a monitised video/channel<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Easy YouTube Traffic 1.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>YouTube Comment Bot 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4014-youtube-comment-bot.html</link>
<description>Name : YouTube Comment Bot Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : YouTube Comment Bot Price : $59 Homepage : SalePage YouTube Comment Bot is a software tool used for commenting on videos, it allows users to automatically poster comments on YouTube videos that match set keywords for your niche. For example if someone uploads a video about cooking with a certain type of cooker/ingredient (bacon perhaps) then it will search for &quot;cooking with bacon&quot; every few minutes and comment on the video with your chosen marketing message for your brand or product.</description>
<category>Youtube Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 03:22:13 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features YouTube Comment Bot uses its own built in web browser to browse YouTube and comment on videos. Once it finds one matching your keyword(s) it will comment then move onto the next video or next keyword. You can use the Log Viewer feature to always see what its doing. NOTE: I&#039;ve recently had some questions/confusion about why its sorting by video upload date. There are two modes for tool can run in... - Comment on new videos - This mode works by searching for the newest page of videos so you can just leave it running and forget about it. So it will comment on all recent videos then new videos then repeat this process so its set and forget. - Comment on existing videos - For each of your keywords (targets) this will comment on every video it can find starting from page 1 onwards then stop.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/250673368?app_id=122963" width="425" height="239" frameborder="0" title="youtube-comment-bot" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> YouTube Comment Bot uses its own built in web browser to browse YouTube and comment on videos. Once it finds one matching your keyword(s) it will comment then move onto the next video or next keyword. You can use the Log Viewer feature to always see what its doing. <br></li><li> NOTE: I've recently had some questions/confusion about why its sorting by video upload date. There are two modes for tool can run in...<br></li><li> - Comment on new videos - This mode works by searching for the newest page of videos so you can just leave it running and forget about it. So it will comment on all recent videos then new videos then repeat this process so its set and forget.<br></li><li> - Comment on existing videos - For each of your keywords (targets) this will comment on every video it can find starting from page 1 onwards then stop.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="YouTube Comment Bot 1.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>YouTube View Bot 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3970-youtube-view-bot.html</link>
<description>Name : YouTube View Bot Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : YouTube View Bot Price : $59 Homepage : SalePage YouTube View Bot is a software tool used for increasing the amount of views your videos have. By increasing the amount of views your videos have not only will your vidoes look more popular (thus getting more views naturally) they will also rank higher, so again they will get more natural views and engagement.</description>
<category>Youtube Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 03:20:36 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features YouTube View Bot uses web browsers installed on your machine such as Chrome and IE with proxies or a VPN to load and play your chosen video. The software can run in a infinite loop constantly increasing the videos views in a set and forget manner or just a single run. There are three different modes this software can run in. - VPN connection proxy - This mode will make use of HideMyAss.com VPN software to get a fresh new IP address for the view bot to use. Or you can simply use your own installed VPN solution and supply the bot with new fresh IP addresses. - Private proxy - Here you simply enter your own private proxies (semi or dedicated) and the bot will use these private proxies to send views to your video. - Rotating proxy - Here you simply enter your rotating proxy IP and port and the bot will monitor for IP address changes through the rotating proxy. Once one has been detected it will be connected through to watch your video.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/WDau7OjIVBg?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> YouTube View Bot uses web browsers installed on your machine such as Chrome and IE with proxies or a VPN to load and play your chosen video. The software can run in a infinite loop constantly increasing the videos views in a set and forget manner or just a single run. There are three different modes this software can run in. <br></li><li> - VPN connection proxy - This mode will make use of HideMyAss.com VPN software to get a fresh new IP address for the view bot to use. Or you can simply use your own installed VPN solution and supply the bot with new fresh IP addresses.<br></li><li> - Private proxy - Here you simply enter your own private proxies (semi or dedicated) and the bot will use these private proxies to send views to your video.<br></li><li> - Rotating proxy - Here you simply enter your rotating proxy IP and port and the bot will monitor for IP address changes through the rotating proxy. Once one has been detected it will be connected through to watch your video.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="YouTube View Bot 1.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Mass Video Blaster Pro 2.48 Full Modules</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/904-mass-video-blaster-pro.html</link>
<description>Name :Mass Video Blaster Pro + Mass Video Downloader + 301 Views Pumper Version : 2.48 + 1.39 + 1.09 OS : Windows Type : Youtube Marketing Price : $97 Homepage : SalePage Upload your videos like a real PRO The leading YouTube Marketing Software: 12,698 clients rely on Mass Video Blaster to upload their videos. Mass Video Blaster let you upload videos from YouTube, whether it&#039;s about the hottest video game to hit the market, some sweet a** music video, the newest diet or weight loss product on the market, latest movie trailers , or any video that you can think of, dosen&#039;t matter.</description>
<category>Youtube Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-08/1440613760_mvb.previews.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 11:40:39 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Multi Threaded Uploader you will be able to upload up to 5 videos in the same time Multiple Account Support you can add as many youtube accounts as you want. Each account will be checked and you will be notified if any account has problems or got removed Proxy Support you can assign to each account a different proxy. Auto ReUploader if one video gets removed , Mass Video Blaster will auto ReUpload it creating a nightmare to the flaggers Video Dashboard manage all your videos from a single dashboard , see how many views each video has &amp;amp; how well it is ranked . Disable/Enable Comments/Ratings Unlist/List Videos this way you will always have a fresh video when you need it Trick YouTube duplicate filter you will be able to upload 100 times the same video and we guarantee you won&#039;t see any duplicate video screens Upload type MVB pro supports both YouTube API and fully supports WebBrowser simulation Custom API Key Enter your custom API Key and APP Name so you know you don&#039;t leave traces on YouTube Image/Text watermark You can either create your watermark in your favorite image editor or MVB pro can make it for you Watermark options You can specify the final size of the watermark (in percentage with the video size) and also the position (top left,top middle, top right, bottom left etc...) Proxy scrapper [new] Scrape thousands of proxies in seconds from various public proxy lists Views Statistics [new] Trace your views and see how your campaigns progress Schedule [new] You can now schedule videos or campaigns. You can tell MVB Pro to pick random dates when to upload/list/disable comments/add annotations/add captions. Change thumbnail [new] After the video is processed on YouTube MVB Pro can now change the thumbnail for a video Custom annotation settings [new] Start time of annotation, end time, text and background color + link Simulate human behavior [new] Before doing actions or uploading MVB Pro has the option to simulate human behavior (like browsing, subscribing, etc....) Subscribe to channel [new] Right after login you can tell MVB Pro to randomly subscribe to a channel Change audio with description [new] MVB Pro can turn your text description to audio and add it to the video Integrated HMA [new] Simply select the HideMyAss installation folder and before each login, MVB Pro will reconnect HMA to get a new fresh IP Accounts Mass Import - Import accounts from a text file in various formats Check accounts [new] - Verify if your accounts are up and running Refresh accounts [new] - Retrieve the number of channel views/videos from a specific YouTube account Delete videos [new] - Mass delete all videos from an account, directly on YouTube Multi threading [new] - All features (check, verify, delete) are multi threading. You can use up to eight threads at a time. Easy to manage - Double-click on a campaign to assign accounts, double-click on an account to assign a proxy. Proxy support - Manually assign or randomly assign proxies to selected accounts Proxy scrapper [new] - Scrape thousands of proxies in seconds from various public proxy lists Export - You can export valid accounts and their assigned proxies with ease Proxy checker [new] - Check to see if the proxies are valid. If the proxies are broken, they won&#039;t be used in MVB Pro. Delete suspended accounts - Simple feature that will remove all disabled accounts from your MVB Pro accounts list. Statistics Mass Import - Import accounts from a text file in various formats Views [new] - Trace your views and see how your campaigns progress Videos [new] - View the number of videos you had in a campaign (or all campaigns) Deleted accounts [new] - Track the number of disabled accounts per days Custom time frame [new] - Generate statistics on custom time frames (select a start and end date) For individual campaign [new] - You can generate statistics for 1 campaign or for all your MVB pro campaigns Easy navigation [new] - Navigate easy through your statistics with quick zoom and pan features Adding videos Mass Import - Import accounts from a text file in various formats Add from PC - Add video files from your PC and fill in title/description/tags Mass import - Import videos from a text file using various formats Mass import from MVD - Use Mass Video Downloader (bonus) to download files and then import them to Mass Video Blaster PRO Export videos - Use custom formats while exporting, export what you want (title, link, original author, file, etc....) Duplicate videos [new] - You can now duplicate a video multiple times with a single click Move videos to other campaigns - If you think that the video does not fit your current campaign, simply move it to another one with this easy feature On screen info - Always see how many videos you have in your list, and how many videos are ready for upload Duplicate campaign [new] - Duplicate the entire campaign and upload it again to YouTube Spin syntax - MVB Pro fully supports spyntax and nested spyntax like Alex} Upload videos Mass Import - Import accounts from a text file in various formats Auto assign accounts [new] - Before uploading you can easily assign the accounts so you will know how the videos will be uploaded Manually assign accounts - Right click on a video to assign manually an account to it Multiple actions - Do multiple actions at a time (like, unlist, disable comments, add annotation, add captions) Mutliple steps - Check, Assign and Upload. This are the three main action of the upload module. Selected items - If you want, you can do actions only on selected items Continous loop - If you have multiple campaigns, when MVB Pro finishes uploading one campaign, it will automatically move on to the next Schedule [new] - You can now schedule videos or campaigns. You can tell MVB Pro to pick random dates when to upload/list/disable comments/add annotations/add captions. More actions [new] - This is the list of actions that can be done in MVB Pro: check videos, assign accounts, upload videos, list, unlist, disable comments, disable ratings, add annotations, generate and add captions, change thumbnail. Change thumbnail [new] - After the video is processed on YouTube MVB Pro can now change the thumbnail for a video Tags - Use tags so you know you have unique video details. Tags like #D#, #T#, #A#, #K# will be replaced with the original video details (of the downloaded video). Random numbers - Append random numbers with the unique random tags #R1#,#R5# so you obtain original titles/description/tags Use tag combinations like #T# #R4# Other Detachable log [new] - Whenever a warning or problem appears in MVB Pro, you will be notified in the log window Detachable browser [new] - View how the login process goes on YouTube by watching the integrated web browser Custom colors - When MVB Pro is uploading a video, the color of the text will be green. If the video is deleted, the color will turn red. Custom annotation settings [new] - Start time of annotation, end time, text and background color + link Import data from mass Video Blaster 2.0 [new] - 1 Click import. Do you have all your accounts, campaigns and videos in MVB 2.0? Than simply import all of them in Mass Video Blaster Pro. Upload type - MVB pro supports both YouTube API and fully supports WebBrowser simulation Custom API Key - Enter your custom API Key and APP Name so you know you don&#039;t leave traces on YouTube User agents [new] - MVB Pro support about five different user agents for every popular browser (Inte.com explorer, explorer, firefox, chrome, opera). You can also specify to use a random user agent. Simulate human behavior [new] - Before doing actions or uploading MVB Pro has the option to simulate human behavior (like browsing, subscribing, etc....) Subscribe to channel [new] - Right after login you can tell MVB Pro to randomly subscribe to a channel Disable comments/unlist - You can upload a video unlisted and with the comments disabled Google position [new] - MVB Pro can now check to see if your video is ranked on Google Multiple google domains - MVB Pro supports any google country (.com, .de, .it, .ro etc...) Delay after login - After MVB Pro will loggin to an account, it will wait for a random amount of seconds before continuing with upload Delay after upload - After MVB Pro uploads a video, it will wait for a random amount of seconds Number of videos/account - When assigning accounts to videos, this option will alow MVB Pro to only upload X Videos/account (and than move on to the next account) Use the least used accounts - Use this option to assign &quot;least used accounts&quot; first, and than move on to other accounts Hide passwords in all forms and lists - If you are doing a recording, this will surely help protect your passwords Change audio from folder - You can change the audio of the video by picking a random audio file from a local directory Change audio with description [new] - MVB Pro can turn your text description to audio and add it to the video Image/Text watermark - You can either create your watermark in your favorite image editor or MVB pro can make it for you Watermark options - You can specify the final size of the watermark (in percentage with the video size) and also the position (top left,top middle, top right, bottom left etc...) Colors - Change the text/background color of the watermark Cut from the start [new] - MVB Pro can cut random seconds from the start of the video Cut from the end [new] - MVB Pro can cut random seconds from the end of the video Video quality - If you want the encoding process to be faster, you can low the video quality of the final video Append intro [new] - You can specify an intro video and MVB pro will append that video to your video file before uploading to YouTube Live preview [new] - Whenever you do a change in the video editor settings, you have a quick preview button to see how the final video file will look Captcha window - If you want to manually enter the captcha, this option will help you do just that DeathByCaptcha - Whenever a captcha appears, MVB Pro with the help of DeathByCaptcha service will auto fill the image verification Proxy error handling - If a proxy is broken you can tell MVB Pro to auto assign another proxy or simply skip that account Send emails - Whenever you have X disabled accounts, MVB Pro can send you an email to notify you about your current campaign status. Integrated HMA [new] - Simply select the HideMyAss installation folder and before each login, MVB Pro will reconnect HMA to get a new fresh IP Integrated PPOE Connection [new] - Enter the connection name of your PPOE and before each login, MVB Pro will reconnect your default IP Custom .bat file [new] - Select a .bat file that you want MVB Pro to run before logging in to an account :::Free Members 2.22::: http://mir.cr/0O8SL21B Password : www.tgmember.com :::ViP Only:::</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/8rz-SJlrOMQ?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><p><br></p><br><h3>Features</h3><br><p><br><ul><li> Multi Threaded Uploader you will be able to upload up to 5 videos in the same time<br></li><li> Multiple Account Support you can add as many youtube accounts as you want. Each account will be checked and you will be notified if any account has problems or got removed<br></li><li> Proxy Support you can assign to each account a different proxy.<br></li><li> Auto ReUploader if one video gets removed , Mass Video Blaster will auto ReUpload it creating a nightmare to the flaggers<br></li><li> Video Dashboard manage all your videos from a single dashboard , see how many views each video has &amp; how well it is ranked .<br></li><li> Disable/Enable Comments/Ratings<br></li><li> Unlist/List Videos this way you will always have a fresh video when you need it<br></li><li> Trick YouTube duplicate filter you will be able to upload 100 times the same video and we guarantee you won't see any duplicate video screens<br></li><li> Upload type MVB pro supports both YouTube API and fully supports WebBrowser simulation<br></li><li> Custom API Key Enter your custom API Key and APP Name so you know you don't leave traces on YouTube<br></li><li> Image/Text watermark You can either create your watermark in your favorite image editor or MVB pro can make it for you<br></li><li> Watermark options You can specify the final size of the watermark (in percentage with the video size) and also the position (top left,top middle, top right, bottom left etc...)<br></li><li> Proxy scrapper [new] Scrape thousands of proxies in seconds from various public proxy lists<br></li><li> Views Statistics [new] Trace your views and see how your campaigns progress<br></li><li> Schedule [new] You can now schedule videos or campaigns. You can tell MVB Pro to pick random dates when to upload/list/disable comments/add annotations/add captions.<br></li><li> Change thumbnail [new] After the video is processed on YouTube MVB Pro can now change the thumbnail for a video<br></li><li> Custom annotation settings [new] Start time of annotation, end time, text and background color + link<br></li><li> Simulate human behavior [new] Before doing actions or uploading MVB Pro has the option to simulate human behavior (like browsing, subscribing, etc....)<br></li><li> Subscribe to channel [new] Right after login you can tell MVB Pro to randomly subscribe to a channel<br></li><li> Change audio with description [new] MVB Pro can turn your text description to audio and add it to the video<br></li><li> Integrated HMA [new] Simply select the HideMyAss installation folder and before each login, MVB Pro will reconnect HMA to get a new fresh IP<br></li></ul><br><b>Accounts</b><br><ul><li> Mass Import - Import accounts from a text file in various formats<br></li><li> Check accounts [new] - Verify if your accounts are up and running<br></li><li> Refresh accounts [new] - Retrieve the number of channel views/videos from a specific YouTube account<br></li><li> Delete videos [new] - Mass delete all videos from an account, directly on YouTube<br></li><li> Multi threading [new] - All features (check, verify, delete) are multi threading. You can use up to eight threads at a time.<br></li><li> Easy to manage - Double-click on a campaign to assign accounts, double-click on an account to assign a proxy.<br></li><li> Proxy support - Manually assign or randomly assign proxies to selected accounts<br></li><li> Proxy scrapper [new] - Scrape thousands of proxies in seconds from various public proxy lists<br></li><li> Export - You can export valid accounts and their assigned proxies with ease<br></li><li> Proxy checker [new] - Check to see if the proxies are valid. If the proxies are broken, they won't be used in MVB Pro.<br></li><li> Delete suspended accounts - Simple feature that will remove all disabled accounts from your MVB Pro accounts list.<br></li></ul><br><br><b>Statistics</b><br><ul><li> Mass Import - Import accounts from a text file in various formats<br></li><li> Views [new] - Trace your views and see how your campaigns progress<br></li><li> Videos [new] - View the number of videos you had in a campaign (or all campaigns)<br></li><li> Deleted accounts [new] - Track the number of disabled accounts per days<br></li><li> Custom time frame [new] - Generate statistics on custom time frames (select a start and end date)<br></li><li> For individual campaign [new] - You can generate statistics for 1 campaign or for all your MVB pro campaigns<br></li><li> Easy navigation [new] - Navigate easy through your statistics with quick zoom and pan features<br></li></ul><br><br><b>Adding videos</b><br><ul><li> Mass Import - Import accounts from a text file in various formats<br></li><li> Add from PC - Add video files from your PC and fill in title/description/tags<br></li><li> Mass import - Import videos from a text file using various formats<br></li><li> Mass import from MVD - Use Mass Video Downloader (bonus) to download files and then import them to Mass Video Blaster PRO<br></li><li> Export videos - Use custom formats while exporting, export what you want (title, link, original author, file, etc....)<br></li><li> Duplicate videos [new] - You can now duplicate a video multiple times with a single click<br></li><li> Move videos to other campaigns - If you think that the video does not fit your current campaign, simply move it to another one with this easy feature<br></li><li> On screen info - Always see how many videos you have in your list, and how many videos are ready for upload<br></li><li> Duplicate campaign [new] - Duplicate the entire campaign and upload it again to YouTube<br></li><li> Spin syntax - MVB Pro fully supports spyntax and nested spyntax like Alex}<br></li></ul><br><br><b>Upload videos</b><br><ul><li> Mass Import - Import accounts from a text file in various formats<br></li><li> Auto assign accounts [new] - Before uploading you can easily assign the accounts so you will know how the videos will be uploaded<br></li><li> Manually assign accounts - Right click on a video to assign manually an account to it<br></li><li> Multiple actions - Do multiple actions at a time (like, unlist, disable comments, add annotation, add captions)<br></li><li> Mutliple steps - Check, Assign and Upload. This are the three main action of the upload module.<br></li><li> Selected items - If you want, you can do actions only on selected items<br></li><li> Continous loop - If you have multiple campaigns, when MVB Pro finishes uploading one campaign, it will automatically move on to the next<br></li><li> Schedule [new] - You can now schedule videos or campaigns. You can tell MVB Pro to pick random dates when to upload/list/disable comments/add annotations/add captions.<br></li><li> More actions [new] - This is the list of actions that can be done in MVB Pro: check videos, assign accounts, upload videos, list, unlist, disable comments, disable ratings, add annotations, generate and add captions, change thumbnail.<br></li><li> Change thumbnail [new] - After the video is processed on YouTube MVB Pro can now change the thumbnail for a video<br></li><li> Tags - Use tags so you know you have unique video details. Tags like #D#, #T#, #A#, #K# will be replaced with the original video details (of the downloaded video).<br></li><li> Random numbers - Append random numbers with the unique random tags #R1#,#R5# so you obtain original titles/description/tags Use tag combinations like #T# #R4#<br></li></ul><br><br><b>Other</b><br><ul><li> Detachable log [new] - Whenever a warning or problem appears in MVB Pro, you will be notified in the log window<br></li><li> Detachable browser [new] - View how the login process goes on YouTube by watching the integrated web browser<br></li><li> Custom colors - When MVB Pro is uploading a video, the color of the text will be green. If the video is deleted, the color will turn red.<br></li><li> Custom annotation settings [new] - Start time of annotation, end time, text and background color + link<br></li><li> Import data from mass Video Blaster 2.0 [new] - 1 Click import. Do you have all your accounts, campaigns and videos in MVB 2.0? Than simply import all of them in Mass Video Blaster Pro.<br></li><li> Upload type - MVB pro supports both YouTube API and fully supports WebBrowser simulation<br></li><li> Custom API Key - Enter your custom API Key and APP Name so you know you don't leave traces on YouTube<br></li><li> User agents [new] - MVB Pro support about five different user agents for every popular browser (Inte.com explorer, explorer, firefox, chrome, opera). You can also specify to use a random user agent.<br></li><li> Simulate human behavior [new] - Before doing actions or uploading MVB Pro has the option to simulate human behavior (like browsing, subscribing, etc....)<br></li><li> Subscribe to channel [new] - Right after login you can tell MVB Pro to randomly subscribe to a channel<br></li><li> Disable comments/unlist - You can upload a video unlisted and with the comments disabled<br></li><li> Google position [new] - MVB Pro can now check to see if your video is ranked on Google<br></li><li> Multiple google domains - MVB Pro supports any google country (.com, .de, .it, .ro etc...)<br></li><li> Delay after login - After MVB Pro will loggin to an account, it will wait for a random amount of seconds before continuing with upload<br></li><li> Delay after upload - After MVB Pro uploads a video, it will wait for a random amount of seconds<br></li><li> Number of videos/account - When assigning accounts to videos, this option will alow MVB Pro to only upload X Videos/account (and than move on to the next account)<br></li><li> Use the least used accounts - Use this option to assign "least used accounts" first, and than move on to other accounts<br></li><li> Hide passwords in all forms and lists - If you are doing a recording, this will surely help protect your passwords<br></li><li> Change audio from folder - You can change the audio of the video by picking a random audio file from a local directory<br></li><li> Change audio with description [new] - MVB Pro can turn your text description to audio and add it to the video<br></li><li> Image/Text watermark - You can either create your watermark in your favorite image editor or MVB pro can make it for you<br></li><li> Watermark options - You can specify the final size of the watermark (in percentage with the video size) and also the position (top left,top middle, top right, bottom left etc...)<br></li><li> Colors - Change the text/background color of the watermark<br></li><li> Cut from the start [new] - MVB Pro can cut random seconds from the start of the video<br></li><li> Cut from the end [new] - MVB Pro can cut random seconds from the end of the video<br></li><li> Video quality - If you want the encoding process to be faster, you can low the video quality of the final video<br></li><li> Append intro [new] - You can specify an intro video and MVB pro will append that video to your video file before uploading to YouTube<br></li><li> Live preview [new] - Whenever you do a change in the video editor settings, you have a quick preview button to see how the final video file will look<br></li><li> Captcha window - If you want to manually enter the captcha, this option will help you do just that<br></li><li> DeathByCaptcha - Whenever a captcha appears, MVB Pro with the help of DeathByCaptcha service will auto fill the image verification<br></li><li> Proxy error handling - If a proxy is broken you can tell MVB Pro to auto assign another proxy or simply skip that account<br></li><li> Send emails - Whenever you have X disabled accounts, MVB Pro can send you an email to notify you about your current campaign status.<br></li><li> Integrated HMA [new] - Simply select the HideMyAss installation folder and before each login, MVB Pro will reconnect HMA to get a new fresh IP<br></li><li> Integrated PPOE Connection [new] - Enter the connection name of your PPOE and before each login, MVB Pro will reconnect your default IP<br></li><li> Custom .bat file [new] - Select a .bat file that you want MVB Pro to run before logging in to an account<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-08/1440613760_mvb.previews.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Mass Video Blaster Pro 2.48 Full Modules"></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><span style="font-size:12pt;"><b><span style="color:#006600;">:::Free Members 2.22:::</span></b></span><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><a href="http://mir.cr/0O8SL21B"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer"><a href="http://mir.cr/0O8SL21B" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><a href="http://mir.cr/0O8SL21B"  target="_blank">http://mir.cr/0O8SL21B</a></a></a><br>Password : www.tgmember.com<br></div></div><br><p><br><br></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><span style="font-size:12pt;"><b><span style="color:#ff0000;">:::ViP Only:::</span></b></span><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Tube Engage Pro 1.7</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1230-tube-engage-pro.html</link>
<description>Name : Tube Engage Pro Version : 1.7 OS : Windows Type : Youtube Inbox Tools, Youtube Marketing Tools Price : $47 Homepage : SalePage The Secret Weapon That Will Take Your Toughest Competition’s Youtube Rankings And Makes THEIR Followers Come Running To YOU ! This is a software that has no parallels. It helps you engage your viewers, AND those of your competition, to keep them coming back again and again, research your niche, and gives you a direct spyline into any YouTube channel you want. It’s your personal YouTube inbox.</description>
<category>Youtube Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/tbengagepro/sales/sales_box.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 11:37:19 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Windows desktop software - Works on Mac when running Windows Parallels Desktop... Pulls in the comments from ALL of your Youtube channels AND your compeition&#039;s, so you can reply to them from ONE interface and create more engagement with your audience... Grabs your biggest competition&#039;s latest conversations and videos, so you can find out what&#039;s the buzz there...and you can take action to steal their rankings ! Engage with your competitor&#039;s audience DIRECTLY, infiltrate and steal their leads... Spy on your biggest competition&#039;s youtube channel, steal their strategy and make them work for YOU ! Direct engagement with your own AND your competitor&#039;s audience turns them all into YOUR loyal followers. The FASTEST STEP to make them put money on YOUR table ! Easily discover what any audience is looking for, so you can profit from it ! And more...</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/hqQwcSa2-3g?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Windows desktop software - Works on Mac when running Windows Parallels Desktop...<br></li><li> Pulls in the comments from ALL of your Youtube channels AND your compeition's, so you can reply to them from ONE interface and create more engagement with your audience...<br></li><li> Grabs your biggest competition's latest conversations and videos, so you can find out what's the buzz there...and you can take action to steal their rankings !<br></li><li> Engage with your competitor's audience DIRECTLY, infiltrate and steal their leads...<br></li><li> Spy on your biggest competition's youtube channel, steal their strategy and make them work for YOU !<br></li><li> Direct engagement with your own AND your competitor's audience turns them all into YOUR loyal followers. The FASTEST STEP to make them put money on YOUR table !<br></li><li> Easily discover what any audience is looking for, so you can profit from it !<br></li><li> And more...<br></li></ul><br><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/tbengagepro/sales/sales_box.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Tube Engage Pro 1.7"><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Tube Inspector Jeet 3.1</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1960-tube-inspector-jeet.html</link>
<description>Name : Tube Inspector Jeet Version : 3.1 OS : Windows Type : Youtube Keyword Tools Price : $12 Homepage : SalePage M.comize the most profitable keywords for your YouTube business. The best software resource to find the most effective keywords for your video and Pay per click campaigns. This software application allows you to export keywords from Google keywords tool for your video campaigns. Import them to Tube Inspector Jeet and run a comprehensive analysis to maximise your earnings.</description>
<category>Youtube Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://teknikforce.com/assets/scrennshot/tijimagessort/3l.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 11:36:42 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Sources upto 800 keywords from Google Keywords Tool. Allows you to m.comize your content by analyzing the profitability of targeted keywords in your niche. Identifies various criterions like rankabilty, popularity and most searched videos, to help you select the right keywords. Facilitates better decision making so you can plan the content better and m.comize it optimally. 1.Extracts an extensive list of niche keywords from Google Keyword Tool. 2.Conducts a comprehensive analysis of hundreds of video keywords based on various success criterions. 3.Custom algorithm identifies cashable keywords on the basis of competition, popularity, views and profitability. 4.Applicable to all niches .</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/8UNdFNKLtEs?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Sources upto 800 keywords from Google Keywords Tool. <br></li><li> Allows you to m.comize your content by analyzing the profitability of targeted keywords in your niche.<br></li><li> Identifies various criterions like rankabilty, popularity and most searched videos, to help you select the right keywords. <br></li><li> Facilitates better decision making so you can plan the content better and m.comize it optimally.<br></li><li> 1.Extracts an extensive list of niche keywords from Google Keyword Tool.<br></li><li> 2.Conducts a comprehensive analysis of hundreds of video keywords based on various success criterions.<br></li><li> 3.Custom algorithm identifies cashable keywords on the basis of competition, popularity, views and profitability.<br></li><li> 4.Applicable to all niches .<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://teknikforce.com/assets/scrennshot/tijimagessort/3l.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Tube Inspector Jeet 3.1"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>