<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Instagram Marketing - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Instagram Marketing - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>Instabot PW 1.0.62 Pro</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1177-instabot-pw.html</link>
<description>Name : Instabot PW Version : 1.0.62 Pro OS : Windows Type : Instagram Marketing Bot Price : $45 Homepage : SalePage Use our instagram bot to get your target audience! Instabot.pw will promote your profile, your product or service 24 hours a day. You only need to specify the desirable settings. Follows, likes, comments - dozens of settings according to different criteria.</description>
<category>Instagram Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2018 13:31:27 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features unlimit likes per hour unlimit follow per hour unlimit unfollow per hour unlimit comments per hour proxy support multiply accounts</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/110780293?app_id=122963" width="425" height="239" frameborder="0" title="Carbongram Bot short overview - The best Instagram bot ever made" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> unlimit likes per hour<br></li><li> unlimit follow per hour<br></li><li> unlimit unfollow per hour<br></li><li> unlimit comments per hour<br></li><li> proxy support<br></li><li> multiply accounts<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Instabot PW 1.0.62 Pro"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Instadub 3.412</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1025-insta-dub.html</link>
<description>Name : Instadub - ISG Bot Version : 3.412 OS : Windows Type : Instagram Marketing Bot Price : $67 Homepage : SalePage The Ultimate Instagram Automation bot. Increase your followers, auto follow, auto like, auto comment and more! Increase your followers and profile popularity using Instadub...</description>
<category>Instagram Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 12:58:05 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Search And Follow Users / Unfollow : Search for users, community members, community contributors, authors of posts returned by search and follow them automatically. Following users is a great way to get followers as most users will follow you back. But better than this is getting users to follow you back who are interested in the same niche as yourself, so the Instagram bot from rootjazz allows you to find users to follow by searching keywords / hashtags and numerous scrape functionality Search And Post Comments : Search for images and add comments automatically. Posting messages to a post is a great way to engage the user and to get them to check your profile / pages Search And Like Images : Search for images, process all images for a user, search by hashtag, geolocation, images of followers, images of users who liked or commented and more. Instagram bot allows you to find images to Like by searching keywords / hashtags with the option to use advanced filters so you can find targeted images to like. Liking an images adds your profile URL to the post and is another way for users browsing Instagram to stumble across your profile Full Accounts Support : Run an unlimited number of accounts in instadub. No limits or hidden charges for extra accounts! Instagram Scraper : Scrape lists of images / users to file Import / Export : All your data belongs to you. You can import / export everything for your promotions Database Storage : Instadub stores your data in a database structure. If you want to shut down the application, it can restart all processes currently queued up for processing. All processes can be redone, retried if failed, paused or cancelled. Captcha API Support : Death by Captcha, By Pass Captcha, Human Coder, Decaptcher</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/125337741?app_id=122963" width="425" height="270" frameborder="0" title="instagram like bot instadub" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Search And Follow Users / Unfollow : Search for users, community members, community contributors, authors of posts returned by search and follow them automatically. Following users is a great way to get followers as most users will follow you back. But better than this is getting users to follow you back who are interested in the same niche as yourself, so the Instagram bot from rootjazz allows you to find users to follow by searching keywords / hashtags and numerous scrape functionality<br></li><li> Search And Post Comments : Search for images and add comments automatically. Posting messages to a post is a great way to engage the user and to get them to check your profile / pages<br></li><li> Search And Like Images : Search for images, process all images for a user, search by hashtag, geolocation, images of followers, images of users who liked or commented and more. Instagram bot allows you to find images to Like by searching keywords / hashtags with the option to use advanced filters so you can find targeted images to like. Liking an images adds your profile URL to the post and is another way for users browsing Instagram to stumble across your profile<br></li><li> Full Accounts Support : Run an unlimited number of accounts in instadub. No limits or hidden charges for extra accounts!<br></li><li> Instagram Scraper : Scrape lists of images / users to file<br></li><li> Import / Export : All your data belongs to you. You can import / export everything for your promotions<br></li><li> Database Storage : Instadub stores your data in a database structure. If you want to shut down the application, it can restart all processes currently queued up for processing. All processes can be redone, retried if failed, paused or cancelled.<br></li><li> Captcha API Support : Death by Captcha, By Pass Captcha, Human Coder, Decaptcher<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Instadub 3.412"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Insta Money Bot 2.1.5</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1459-insta-money-bot.html</link>
<description>Name : Insta Money Bot Version : 2.1.5 OS : Windows Type : Instagram Marketing Tools Price : $4 Homepage : SalePage Insta Money Bot has been released, it is the instagram edition of Twitter Money Bot v3! Hurry up and get this great instagram marketing software!INSTAGRAM BOT</description>
<category>Instagram Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://twittermoneybot.com/Screenshots/Insta_Money_Bot.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 11:11:45 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Auto follow users from search results or txt files Follow other people’s followers or followings Unfollow users who don’t follow you back Like photos automatically from search results with your custom hashtags or keywords Comment on photos automatically from search results with your custom hashtags or keywords Mass Account Statistics Checker Direct Message Sender Various Scrapers To Scrape Various Infos From Instagram Username scraper and manager – you can remove users with no avatar! You can add unlimited accounts, and you can work with multiple accounts and projects at the same time! Proxy Support – Public And Private Proxies! Scheduler – Just Set Up Your Campaign To The Task Table And Leave It To The Scheduler, It Will Start Your Tasks In The List Automatically Random Delay Feature White List – The unfollower will never unfollow people who are in your white list… Mass Photo Downloader – Scrape photos with your custom hashtags, or download all the photos of a specific user on instagram! Hashtag scraper, generate thousands of hashtags in a few minutes! Proxy Tester! And more!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/E0GoZ7WqnYE?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Auto follow users from search results or txt files<br></li><li> Follow other people’s followers or followings<br></li><li> Unfollow users who don’t follow you back<br></li><li> Like photos automatically from search results with your custom hashtags or keywords<br></li><li> Comment on photos automatically from search results with your custom hashtags or keywords<br></li><li> Mass Account Statistics Checker<br></li><li> Direct Message Sender<br></li><li> Various Scrapers To Scrape Various Infos From Instagram<br></li><li> Username scraper and manager – you can remove users with no avatar!<br></li><li> You can add unlimited accounts, and you can work with multiple accounts and projects at the same time!<br></li><li> Proxy Support – Public And Private Proxies!<br></li><li> Scheduler – Just Set Up Your Campaign To The Task Table And Leave It To The Scheduler, It Will Start Your Tasks In The List Automatically<br></li><li> Random Delay Feature<br></li><li> White List – The unfollower will never unfollow people who are in your white list…<br></li><li> Mass Photo Downloader – Scrape photos with your custom hashtags, or download all the photos of a specific user on instagram!<br></li><li> Hashtag scraper, generate thousands of hashtags in a few minutes!<br></li><li> Proxy Tester!<br></li><li> And more!<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://twittermoneybot.com/Screenshots/Insta_Money_Bot.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Insta Money Bot 2.1.5"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Ninja Gram 5.4.9</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1023-ninja-gram.html</link>
<description>Name : NinjaGram Instagram Bot Version : 5.4.9 OS : Windows Type : Instagram Marketing Bot Price : $27 Homepage : SalePage Welcome to NinjaGram, the world’s #1 Instagram bot. This proprietary and versatile marketing software handles all of the repetitive grunt work, SAVES you large amounts of time, gets you thousands of followers, and helps you generate more profit from this wildly popular image sharing website!</description>
<category>Instagram Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 07:06:59 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Target users/photos by keyword search, tag search, user’s followers, user’s friends, your feed, URL, recent comments or likes. Auto follow (you can also monitor a tag and like any users making new posts, thereby ensuring you are only following active accounts). Auto unfollow (you can exclude users you followed less than X days ago or users who haven’t followed you back). Auto like (you can also monitor your feed or a tag search and like any new photos). SUPERLIKE! Like targeted users’ last 5 photos. Extremely effective method to gain more followers. Auto comment from a list of comments (spintax allowed). Like a person’s most recent photo when following them. Time delay feature to keep your account safe. Blacklist Proxy support Import/export accounts from text file. Image resizer And more!!!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/QceDS4I2aCM?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><p><br></p><br><h3>Features</h3><br><p><br><ul><li> Target users/photos by keyword search, tag search, user’s followers, user’s friends, your feed, URL, recent comments or likes.<br></li><li> Auto follow (you can also monitor a tag and like any users making new posts, thereby ensuring you are only following active accounts).<br></li><li> Auto unfollow (you can exclude users you followed less than X days ago or users who haven’t followed you back).<br></li><li> Auto like (you can also monitor your feed or a tag search and like any new photos).<br></li><li> SUPERLIKE! Like targeted users’ last 5 photos. Extremely effective method to gain more followers.<br></li><li> Auto comment from a list of comments (spintax allowed).<br></li><li> Like a person’s most recent photo when following them.<br></li><li> Time delay feature to keep your account safe.<br></li><li> Blacklist<br></li><li> Proxy support<br></li><li> Import/export accounts from text file.<br></li><li> Image resizer<br></li><li> And more!!!<br></li></ul><br><br></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Ninja Gram 5.4.9"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>GramDominator 2.5.0.43</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1176-gram-dominator.html</link>
<description>Name : Gramdominator Version : 2.5.0.43 OS : Windows Type : Instagram Marketing Bot Price : $499 Homepage : SalePage Gramdominator lets you target with precision, connect directly with your audience, spread your message throughout the day, manage campaigns and do much more to make sure you achieve your marketing goal. There’s no doubt that Instagram, with its more than 600 million users, has become a great marketing tool for business today. With growing targeting, analytics, promotional tactics and marketing tools provided by Instagram, it’s definitely a great arsenal in your digital marketing tool kit. Now Brands have been opening Instagram accounts thick and fast like you, but how confident are you of obtaining real results, and are you able to measure the impact of their messaging on the microblogging.comwork? So the difficulty remains: Who will you reach on Instagram? How will you reach them? How effectively are you using this tool? How can you tell if you’ve done a good job? etc.</description>
<category>Instagram Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 06:05:16 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Follower : Increase followers of any Specific username or upload a custom list of usernames. Photo Like : Send Likes and unlikes to the loaded Photo and videos with ease. Unfollower : Unfollow users who are not following you back to get a good and infl.comial Follow:Following ratio. Comment : Comment on Photos of your desire, you just need to upload a Custom list of photo Urls. Scrape Users : Scrape targetted users from Keywords or hashtags to jump start your campaigns. Scrape Image URLs : Lacking photo urls, No worries use scrape image urls and get loaded with plenty of images that match your needs. Hash Tags : Auto follow, Like &amp;amp; comment just via hashtags and everything on autopilot. Scrape Followers : Scrape Followers of influential or niche related Users to get started with any campaign.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/UJbunDu3xfg?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Follower : Increase followers of any Specific username or upload a custom list of usernames.<br></li><li> Photo Like : Send Likes and unlikes to the loaded Photo and videos with ease.<br></li><li> Unfollower : Unfollow users who are not following you back to get a good and infl.comial Follow:Following ratio.<br></li><li> Comment : Comment on Photos of your desire, you just need to upload a Custom list of photo Urls.<br></li><li> Scrape Users : Scrape targetted users from Keywords or hashtags to jump start your campaigns.<br></li><li> Scrape Image URLs : Lacking photo urls, No worries use scrape image urls and get loaded with plenty of images that match your needs.<br></li><li> Hash Tags : Auto follow, Like &amp; comment just via hashtags and everything on autopilot.<br></li><li> Scrape Followers : Scrape Followers of influential or niche related Users to get started with any campaign.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="GramDominator 2.5.0.43"><br><div class="quote"><br><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>GSupremacy 1.232 Ultimate</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1302-gsupremacy.html</link>
<description>Name : GSupremacy Version : 1.232 OS : Windows Type : Instagram Marketing Bot Price : $80 Homepage : SalePage GSupremacy is multi-threaded, proxy enabled Instagram account management and marketing software.</description>
<category>Instagram Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="https://i.imgur.com/fsNLq00.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2018 09:17:04 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Instagram - Repost - Comment - Like - Follow - Unfollow - Manager - Filters - Nonfollowers - Scraper Other - Multi-Threaded - Proxy Enabled - Schedules - Auto Pilots - Advanced Settings - Console Logs - Task Reports - Clear Design</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Instagram<br></li><li> - Repost<br></li><li> - Comment<br></li><li> - Like<br></li><li> - Follow<br></li><li> - Unfollow<br></li><li> - Manager<br></li><li> - Filters<br></li><li> - Nonfollowers<br></li><li> - Scraper<br></li><li> Other<br></li><li> - Multi-Threaded<br></li><li> - Proxy Enabled<br></li><li> - Schedules<br></li><li> - Auto Pilots<br></li><li> - Advanced Settings<br></li><li> - Console Logs<br></li><li> - Task Reports<br></li><li> - Clear Design<br></li></ul><br><img src="https://i.imgur.com/fsNLq00.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="GSupremacy 1.232 Ultimate"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Instagram Registration Tool 1.0.0.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1632-instagram-registration-tool.html</link>
<description>Name : Instagram Registration Tool Version : 1.0.0.0 OS : Windows Type : Instagram Marketing Tools Price : $97 Homepage : SalePage Instagram Registration Tool help u register Instagram Account Fast and safely</description>
<category>Instagram Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://i.imgur.com/ZuMlFPb.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 03:39:17 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Instagram Registration Tool Proxy Support</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Instagram Registration Tool <br></li><li> Proxy Support<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://i.imgur.com/ZuMlFPb.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Instagram Registration Tool 1.0.0.0"><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>4K Stogram 2.6.12.1567</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1166-4kstogram.html</link>
<description>Name : 4kstogram Version : 2.6.12.1567 OS : Windows Type : Instagram Viewer and Downloader Tool Price : $19.90 Homepage : SalePage 4K Stogram is an Instagram Viewer and Downloader for PC, macOS and Linux. Download photos, videos and stories from your friends’ public and private Instagram accounts, backup your Instagram profile and import your list of Instagram subscriptions. Get started for free!</description>
<category>Instagram Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 00:17:52 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>(function(d, s, id) { var js, fjs = d.getElementsByTagName(s)[0]; if (d.getElementById(id)) return; js = d.createElement(s); js.id = id; js.src = &#039;https://connect.facebook.com/en_US/sdk.js#xfbml=1&amp;version=v2.12&#039;; fjs.parentNode.insertBefore(js, fjs); }(document, &#039;script&#039;, &#039;facebook-jssdk&#039;)); CultofMac on 4K Stogram: &amp;quot;4K Stogram is an Instagram viewer that offers a way to get behind the locked box of Instagram’s app. The program gives you options to export, download and back up your Instagram photos and videos — or anybody else’s. Available for Mac, PC or Linux, the software affords you the option to download and save content from any account.&amp;quot; - http://snip.ly/pufql Get 4K Stogram for your Windows, Mac, or Linux now: http://snip.ly/sfn6vPosted by 4k Download on Friday, June 9, 2017 Features - Download Instagram Stories Save short-living daily images and videos from any Instagram account for good. - Download video posts Grab videos in MP4 format from Instagram accounts, hashtags and locations after enabling this handy feature. - Backup your account in seconds It takes one click to download all photos from your Instagram account. - Follow your subscriptions in one click Press ‘Subscribe to Accounts I’m Following’ and all accounts you follow on Instagram will be automatically added to 4K Stogram and downloaded. - Comments and hashtags meta data All downloaded images contain information about comments and hashtags in their metadata. - Export and import subscriptions Keep your subscriptions database safely: export it and import after major computer reinstallations, so no images and accounts are lost.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><div id="fb-root"></div>
<script>(function(d, s, id) {
  var js, fjs = d.getElementsByTagName(s)[0];
  if (d.getElementById(id)) return;
  js = d.createElement(s); js.id = id;
  js.src = 'https://connect.facebook.com/en_US/sdk.js#xfbml=1&version=v2.12';
  fjs.parentNode.insertBefore(js, fjs);
}(document, 'script', 'facebook-jssdk'));</script><div class="fb-video" data-href="https://www.facebook.com/4kdownload/videos/1585271271513949/?t=20" data-width="425"><blockquote cite="https://www.facebook.com/4kdownload/videos/1585271271513949/" class="fb-xfbml-parse-ignore"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/4kdownload/videos/1585271271513949/" rel="external noopener noreferrer"></a><p>CultofMac on 4K Stogram:
&quot;4K Stogram is an Instagram viewer that offers a way to get behind the locked box of Instagram’s app. The program gives you options to export, download and back up your Instagram photos and videos — or anybody else’s. Available for Mac, PC or Linux, the software affords you the option to download and save content from any account.&quot; - http://snip.ly/pufql
Get 4K Stogram for your Windows, Mac, or Linux now: http://snip.ly/sfn6v</p>Posted by <a href="https://www.facebook.com/4kdownload/" rel="external noopener noreferrer">4k Download</a> on Friday, June 9, 2017</blockquote></div></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br> - Download Instagram Stories<br>Save short-living daily images and videos from any Instagram account for good.<br><br> - Download video posts<br>Grab videos in MP4 format from Instagram accounts, hashtags and locations after enabling this handy feature.<br><br> - Backup your account in seconds<br>It takes one click to download all photos from your Instagram account.<br><br> - Follow your subscriptions in one click<br>Press ‘Subscribe to Accounts I’m Following’ and all accounts you follow on Instagram will be automatically added to 4K Stogram and downloaded.<br><br> - Comments and hashtags meta data<br>All downloaded images contain information about comments and hashtags in their metadata.<br><br> - Export and import subscriptions<br>Keep your subscriptions database safely: export it and import after major computer reinstallations, so no images and accounts are lost.<br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="4K Stogram 2.6.12.1567"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Gram MultiTool 2.6.2</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3851-gram-multitool.html</link>
<description>Name : Gram MultiTool Version : 2.6.2 OS : Windows Type : Instagram Marketing Tools Price : $120/y Homepage : SalePage Gram MultiTool (or GMT) is a tool to fulfill all of your Instagram needs. It everything you could think off, ranging from interacting with followers to scheduling posts. With GMT you will be able to grow your follower base and engagement in a matter of weeks, without having to lift a finger!</description>
<category>Instagram Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="https://i.imgur.com/A2UpdmU.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 09:02:44 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features The first Bulk platform for WhatsApp Users, called WHATSAPP Marketing, provides the ability to create contact lists of potential customers mobile phones and send text messages with photos, pictures and viral videos to an unlimited number of recipients Supported: Text, Image, Audio, Video, vCard, Location. Even multiple messages sending option. Delivery Report Export in Text file. Built-in Whatsapp Number Filter, and Number Generator. Can filter 1 million in just few minutes. Multi Languages: Arabic, English, Portuguese, Chines, Russian.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/KRe695SyrL4?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> The first Bulk platform for WhatsApp Users, called WHATSAPP Marketing, provides the ability to create contact lists of potential customers mobile phones and send text messages with photos, pictures and viral videos to an unlimited number of recipients <br></li><li> Supported: Text, Image, Audio, Video, vCard, Location.<br></li><li> Even multiple messages sending option.<br></li><li> Delivery Report Export in Text file.<br></li><li> Built-in Whatsapp Number Filter, and Number Generator. Can filter 1 million in just few minutes. <br></li><li> Multi Languages: Arabic, English, Portuguese, Chines, Russian. <br></li></ul><br><img src="https://i.imgur.com/A2UpdmU.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Gram MultiTool 2.6.2"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>HimmelGram 4.4.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3804-himmelgram.html</link>
<description>Name : HimmelGram Version : 4.4.0 OS : Windows/ Type : Instagram Marketing Bot Price : $340 Homepage : SalePage HimmelGram have Awesome Features! Follow, Unfollow, Comment, Like, Upload Images, Remove Images, Rip Images, Account Creator, Mass Promoter , Profile updater</description>
<category>Instagram Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 22:01:13 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Instagram Follow Users : Auto-follow users; follow a user&#039;s followers/following, users discussing a topic (by keywords/hashtags), by location/language, custom list of users (your own list); Follow back your followers; Follow by follower to following ratio... Instagram Unfollow Users : Auto-Unfollow users, unfollow users not following back after some days, limit unfollow per run or day, white list users that should not be unfollowed, unfollow by follower to following ratio... Instagram Share Photos/Videos : Keep your Instagram profiles active, engaging and interesting. Automatically share or upload photos and videos to your Instagram accounts directly from your computer; Schedule photo and video sharing/uploading; Limit photo and video sharing/uploading... Instagram Like Photos : Auto-like photos; Like photos posted by a user; Like custom list of photos (your own list)... Instagram Unlike Photos : Auto-unlike photo, unlike photos liked after some days, set unlike photo limit with each run, delay unlike to look more natural... Instagram Comment on Photos : Auto-comment on photos; Comment on a user&#039;s photos; Comment on custom list of photos (your own list)... Instagram Send Direct Messages : Communicate with your followers directly and keep them informed. Automatically send direct messages to your followers, send thank you messages to new followers... Instagram User Search : Auto-find users to follow based on keywords, other user&#039;s followers/following and location. It has the ability to remove results of users that only have a default profile picture... Instagram Photo Search : Auto-find photos to be liked and com.comed based on keyword/hashtag choices, other user&#039;s photos... Instagram Search Followers/Following : Search people&#039;s followers and following to be used by other module like follow,unfollow and send message etc. You can also save the searched data directly. Instagram Search The Un-Followback Users : Search the un-followback users. Instagram Search Photos By User : Search photos by user. Instagram Get The Post&#039;s Author : Get the post&#039;s author. Instagram Get The Users Associated With Me : Get the users associated with me. Instagram Home Like : Home Like.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/LqPeLVw680o?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><ul><li> Instagram Follow Users : Auto-follow users; follow a user's followers/following, users discussing a topic (by keywords/hashtags), by location/language, custom list of users (your own list); Follow back your followers; Follow by follower to following ratio...<br></li><li> Instagram Unfollow Users : Auto-Unfollow users, unfollow users not following back after some days, limit unfollow per run or day, white list users that should not be unfollowed, unfollow by follower to following ratio...<br></li><li> Instagram Share Photos/Videos : Keep your Instagram profiles active, engaging and interesting. Automatically share or upload photos and videos to your Instagram accounts directly from your computer; Schedule photo and video sharing/uploading; Limit photo and video sharing/uploading...<br></li><li> Instagram Like Photos : Auto-like photos; Like photos posted by a user; Like custom list of photos (your own list)...<br></li><li> Instagram Unlike Photos : Auto-unlike photo, unlike photos liked after some days, set unlike photo limit with each run, delay unlike to look more natural...<br></li><li> Instagram Comment on Photos : Auto-comment on photos; Comment on a user's photos; Comment on custom list of photos (your own list)...<br></li><li> Instagram Send Direct Messages : Communicate with your followers directly and keep them informed. Automatically send direct messages to your followers, send thank you messages to new followers...<br></li><li> Instagram User Search : Auto-find users to follow based on keywords, other user's followers/following and location. It has the ability to remove results of users that only have a default profile picture...<br></li><li> Instagram Photo Search : Auto-find photos to be liked and com.comed based on keyword/hashtag choices, other user's photos...<br></li><li> Instagram Search Followers/Following : Search people's followers and following to be used by other module like follow,unfollow and send message etc. You can also save the searched data directly.<br></li><li> Instagram Search The Un-Followback Users : Search the un-followback users.<br></li><li> Instagram Search Photos By User : Search photos by user.<br></li><li> Instagram Get The Post's Author : Get the post's author.<br></li><li> Instagram Get The Users Associated With Me : Get the users associated with me.<br></li><li> Instagram Home Like : Home Like.<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="HimmelGram 4.4.0"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>