<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Bot Creation - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Bot Creation - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>BotChief Runner Elite Developer 4.2.1</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1068-botchief-runner.html</link>
<description>Name : BotChief Runner Version : Elite Developer 4.2.1 OS : Windows Type : Bot Creator Price : $147 Homepage : SalePage Run your custom bots to automate any task , create from BotChief Editor Anything you do online can be automated with BotChief. You can create your own custom bot, you can also can use our system bots. There are already many system bots available like yahoo creator, gmail creator, hotmail creator, twitter creator, pinterest creator, etc.</description>
<category>Bot Creation</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.botchief.com/images/projects/7b.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 13:02:52 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Run your bots with proxies. Run your bots with multi-threads.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/0Cgr9OKFOnw?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><p><br></p><br><h3>Features</h3><br><p><br><ul><li> Run your bots with proxies.<br></li><li> Run your bots with multi-threads.<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://www.botchief.com/images/projects/7b.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="BotChief Runner Elite Developer 4.2.1"></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>BotChief Editor Developer 4.7.4</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1072-botchief-editor.html</link>
<description>Name : BotChief Editor Version : Elite Developer 4.7.4 OS : Windows Type : Bot Creator Price : $297 Homepage : SalePage Create your custom bots to automate any task Anything you do online can be automated with BotChief. You can create your own custom bot, you can also can use our system bots. There are already many system bots available like yahoo creator, gmail creator, hotmail creator, twitter creator, pinterest creator, etc.</description>
<category>Bot Creation</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-08/thumbs/1440789447_s0cdpul.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 13:02:32 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Create any bot in minutes by yourself to automate your any task. Run your bots with proxies. Run your bots with multi-threads. Use system bots directly (we add more system bots daily). Contains all functions in the Elite User Version. Create self-extracting installation packages for your customers and clients. Whitelabel your software by removing the BotChief brand. Customize/design your software&#039;s unique interfaces. Use our integrated auto-update system to update your bots for your customers. Use our integrated license system to manage your orders and users.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ThAGX2wglt4?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><p><br></p><br><h3>Features</h3><br><p><br><ul><li> Create any bot in minutes by yourself to automate your any task.<br></li><li> Run your bots with proxies.<br></li><li> Run your bots with multi-threads.<br></li><li> Use system bots directly (we add more system bots daily).<br></li><li> Contains all functions in the Elite User Version.<br></li><li> Create self-extracting installation packages for your customers and clients.<br></li><li> Whitelabel your software by removing the BotChief brand.<br></li><li> Customize/design your software's unique interfaces.<br></li><li> Use our integrated auto-update system to update your bots for your customers.<br></li><li> Use our integrated license system to manage your orders and users.<br></li></ul><br><a href="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-08/1440789447_s0cdpul.jpg" class="highslide" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-08/thumbs/1440789447_s0cdpul.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt=''></a></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="BotChief Editor Developer 4.7.4"><br><div class="quote"><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>WinAutomation Pro Plus 7.0.2.4549</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1356-winautomation.html</link>
<description>Name : WinAutomation Version : Pro 7.0.2.4549 OS : Windows Type : Macro Recorder Price : $285 Homepage : SalePage WinAutomation is the most advanced Windows Automation app, featuring a Macro Recorder and a Web Recorder With WinAutomation you can teach your computer to perform your repetitive tasks automatically</description>
<category>Bot Creation</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-10/1444931939_dummy_slide02.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2018 22:04:00 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Automatically fill and submit web forms with data from local files. Web Scraping and data extraction from any web page into Excel or text files. Prerecord mouse clicks and keystrokes via auto clicker, mouse recorder and keyboard macro recorder sent to any desktop application. Retrieve and parse your emails and update a database with the data contained in the emails. Copy, move, edit, rename, compress, uncompress and manage files and folders in any possible way. Automate your FTP transfers: Download and upload files or entire folders at schedule. Launch applications, move, resize, close and manipulate windows, take screenshots. Read and write data to automate Excel files, connect to SQL databases and manipulate text files. Include logic to automate even the most complex tasks. Convert your tasks into your very own applications that you can share with others, with the press of a button. Run any task using the built-in advanced task scheduler, when you press a hotkey, when a file is created or deleted, when your site is down or when you receive an email. Combine all the above to design custom tasks for your specific needs.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/78j6M_j4fQ8?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Automatically fill and submit web forms with data from local files.<br></li><li> Web Scraping and data extraction from any web page into Excel or text files.<br></li><li> Prerecord mouse clicks and keystrokes via auto clicker, mouse recorder and keyboard macro recorder sent to any desktop application.<br></li><li> Retrieve and parse your emails and update a database with the data contained in the emails.<br></li><li> Copy, move, edit, rename, compress, uncompress and manage files and folders in any possible way.<br></li><li> Automate your FTP transfers: Download and upload files or entire folders at schedule.<br></li><li> Launch applications, move, resize, close and manipulate windows, take screenshots.<br></li><li> Read and write data to automate Excel files, connect to SQL databases and manipulate text files.<br></li><li> Include logic to automate even the most complex tasks.<br></li><li> Convert your tasks into your very own applications that you can share with others, with the press of a button.<br></li><li> Run any task using the built-in advanced task scheduler, when you press a hotkey, when a file is created or deleted, when your site is down or when you receive an email.<br></li><li> Combine all the above to design custom tasks for your specific needs.<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-10/1444931939_dummy_slide02.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt="WinAutomation Pro Plus 7.0.2.4549"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>FileMaker Pro Advanced 16 v16.0.4.403</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3938-filemaker-pro-advanced-16.html</link>
<description>Name : FileMaker Pro Advanced 16 Version : 16.0.4.403 OS : Windows/MAC Type : Software Create Custom Apps Price : $500 Homepage : SalePage FileMaker Pro Advanced includes all of the features of FileMaker Pro plus a set of advanced development and customization tools. Get features to design and develop custom apps faster and easier. Plus, get robust analysis capabilities, powerful diagnostic tools, and much more. If you want to build more powerful and flexible apps for your business, then FileMaker Pro Advanced is for you.</description>
<category>Bot Creation</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 06:40:45 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features New! Enhanced Data Viewer: Increase your productivity with auto-complete for function names in the Data Viewer. Plus, automatically evaluate results for functions and resize the Edit Expression window to easily view all results. New! OAuth 2.0 support for accounts Use your existing Amazon, Google, or Microsoft Azure account credentials to log in to your FileMaker-based custom apps. Get started quickly Choose from a variety of predesigned Starter Solutions to manage contacts, inventory, projects, and more. Import existing dаta: Bring your existing data into FileMaker Pro, including .CSV, Tab, XML, ODBC, and Microsoft Excel files. Customize with ease Use flexible design tools to make your layouts look and work just the way you want — without extensive development experience or IT skills. Built-in reporting tools: Easy-to-use reporting and charting tools make it easy to make summary reports, colorful charts, and executive dashboards with a few clicks. Share with your team: Create custom apps that work together seamlessly across iPad, iPhone, Windows, Mac, and the web. Learn more about sharing information with your team. Integrate with other programs Exchange and interact with data from other applications. Plus, create live, 2-way connections with Microsoft SQL Server, Oracle and MySQL data sources. Multiple Table Import: Build or modify apps faster by importing multiple tables at once. Script Debugger Instantly pinpoint problem areas in scripts and Script Triggers directly in the Script Workspace. Turn off Script Triggers when debugging to fine tune the troubleshooting process. Data Viewer Monitor fields, variables, and calculations while troubleshooting. Enable Database Encryption: Enable AES 256-bit encryption with FileMaker Pro Advanced to protect data on a FileMaker client or on FileMaker Server. Custom Menus: Create, change, or delete specific menu items or entire menu sets. Custom Functions: Build your own functions and copy, paste, or import them into any FileMaker file. Database Design Report: Run comprehensive reports on all elements of your database schema. Kiosk Mode: Build applications where all menus are hidden.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> New! Enhanced Data Viewer:	Increase your productivity with auto-complete for function names in the Data Viewer. Plus, automatically evaluate results for functions and resize the Edit Expression window to easily view all results.		<br></li><li> New! OAuth 2.0 support for accounts	Use your existing Amazon, Google, or Microsoft Azure account credentials to log in to your FileMaker-based custom apps.		<br></li><li> Get started quickly	Choose from a variety of predesigned Starter Solutions to manage contacts, inventory, projects, and more.		<br></li><li> Import existing dаta:	Bring your existing data into FileMaker Pro, including .CSV, Tab, XML, ODBC, and Microsoft Excel files.		<br></li><li> Customize with ease	Use flexible design tools to make your layouts look and work just the way you want — without extensive development experience or IT skills.		<br></li><li> Built-in reporting tools:	Easy-to-use reporting and charting tools make it easy to make summary reports, colorful charts, and executive dashboards with a few clicks.		<br></li><li> Share with your team:	Create custom apps that work together seamlessly across iPad, iPhone, Windows, Mac, and the web. Learn more about sharing information with your team.		<br></li><li> Integrate with other programs	Exchange and interact with data from other applications. Plus, create live, 2-way connections with Microsoft SQL Server, Oracle and MySQL data sources.		<br></li><li> Multiple Table Import:	Build or modify apps faster by importing multiple tables at once.		<br></li><li> Script Debugger	Instantly pinpoint problem areas in scripts and Script Triggers directly in the Script Workspace. Turn off Script Triggers when debugging to fine tune the troubleshooting process.		<br></li><li> Data Viewer	Monitor fields, variables, and calculations while troubleshooting.		<br></li><li> Enable Database Encryption:	Enable AES 256-bit encryption with FileMaker Pro Advanced to protect data on a FileMaker client or on FileMaker Server.		<br></li><li> Custom Menus:	Create, change, or delete specific menu items or entire menu sets.		<br></li><li> Custom Functions:	Build your own functions and copy, paste, or import them into any FileMaker file.		<br></li><li> Database Design Report:	Run comprehensive reports on all elements of your database schema.		<br></li><li> Kiosk Mode:	Build applications where all menus are hidden.		<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="FileMaker Pro Advanced 16 v16.0.4.403"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Advanced Mouse Auto Clicker 4.1.8</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3939-advanced-mouse-auto-clicker.html</link>
<description>Name : Advanced Mouse Auto Clicker Version : 4.1.8 OS : Windows Type : Automatic Mouse Clicking Utility Price : $0 Homepage : SalePage Advanced Mouse Auto Clicker is a powerful yet easy-to-use tool with many more features that can free your hands and save your time. it&#039;s an inexpensive automatic mouse clicking utility. it&#039;s used to automate screen mouse clicks at specified intervals and any location on the screen.</description>
<category>Bot Creation</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 06:40:45 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Advanced Mouse Auto Clicker Main Features - With many features that can free your hands and save your time. - Support click on fixed point,and define action after that,back to the original location or not. - Repeat Single Click at specified intervals and any location on the screen. - Support click at specified color block,search color point on full screen or part of it. - Version 4.0 new feather: random interval.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Advanced Mouse Auto Clicker Main Features<br></li><li> - With many features that can free your hands and save your time.<br></li><li> - Support click on fixed point,and define action after that,back to the original location or not.<br></li><li> - Repeat Single Click at specified intervals and any location on the screen.<br></li><li> - Support click at specified color block,search color point on full screen or part of it.<br></li><li> - Version 4.0 new feather: random interval.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Advanced Mouse Auto Clicker 4.1.8"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>AutoPlay Media Studio 8.5.2.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3933-autoplay-media-studio.html</link>
<description>Name : AutoPlay Media Studio Version : 8.5.2.0 OS : Windows Type : Software AutoPlay Media Studio Price : $995 Homepage : SalePage AutoPlay Media Studio delivers on the promise of rapid application development. It’s perfect for making anything from autoplay CD/DVD/USB menus and utilities to games and interactive multimedia applications – complete with web interaction, database connectivity, video playback and much more.</description>
<category>Bot Creation</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 00:05:57 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Easy To Use. No Training Needed : This easy-to-use software development tool allows you to create your own custom software in a visual drag and drop workspace. Make anything from CD/DVD/USB autorun menus and interactive presentations to complete multimedia software programs – quickly and easily! Simply drag and drop to create amazing Windows software applications. The Original! Trusted Since 1997 : Since 1997 we have been the autorun menu and rapid application builder of choice for thousands of software developers worldwide. With millions of autorun menus and applications distributed, you simply cannot find a more robust and well tested tool in this category than Autoplay Media Studio. Drag and Drop Development : Quickly turn your ideas into fully functioning applications. With a wide range of actions and objects to choose from, all the most popular functionality is right at your fingertips. Simply drag and drop to visually build your app! Powerful Scripting System : Users without any coding experience can simply click to add actions from the library to build up functionality, from basic screen controls to advanced operating system commands. Advanced coders will instantly feel at home hand coding in the familiar Lua-based environment. Target Any Version of Windows : From Windows XP right up to Windows 10, we’ve got you covered. You can be completely confident that your applications and menus are fully compatible. There’s no worrying about operating system compatibility or runtime issues. Just click and go! Licensing That Makes Sense : As developers ourselves, we understand the challenges you face. Our objective was to keep the costs of single-user licenses low enough for individuals to afford, yet provide deep enough multi-user discounts to make sense for full development teams.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/tkobtGx98GI?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Easy To Use. No Training Needed : This easy-to-use software development tool allows you to create your own custom software in a visual drag and drop workspace. Make anything from CD/DVD/USB autorun menus and interactive presentations to complete multimedia software programs – quickly and easily! Simply drag and drop to create amazing Windows software applications.<br></li><li> The Original! Trusted Since 1997 : Since 1997 we have been the autorun menu and rapid application builder of choice for thousands of software developers worldwide. With millions of autorun menus and applications distributed, you simply cannot find a more robust and well tested tool in this category than Autoplay Media Studio.<br></li><li> Drag and Drop Development : Quickly turn your ideas into fully functioning applications. With a wide range of actions and objects to choose from, all the most popular functionality is right at your fingertips. Simply drag and drop to visually build your app!<br></li><li> Powerful Scripting System : Users without any coding experience can simply click to add actions from the library to build up functionality, from basic screen controls to advanced operating system commands. Advanced coders will instantly feel at home hand coding in the familiar Lua-based environment.<br></li><li> Target Any Version of Windows : From Windows XP right up to Windows 10, we’ve got you covered. You can be completely confident that your applications and menus are fully compatible. There’s no worrying about operating system compatibility or runtime issues. Just click and go!<br></li><li> Licensing That Makes Sense : As developers ourselves, we understand the challenges you face. Our objective was to keep the costs of single-user licenses low enough for individuals to afford, yet provide deep enough multi-user discounts to make sense for full development teams.<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="AutoPlay Media Studio 8.5.2.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>RoboTask 6.9.0.925 Business</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2049-robotask.html</link>
<description>Name : RoboTask Version : 6.9.0.925 Business OS : Windows Type : Bot Creator Price : $57 Homepage : SalePage RoboTask - automate any series of tasks on your computer!RoboTask enables you to automate any combination of tasks on your computer, ranging from simply launching applications, to checking email, moving or backing up files to uploading or downloading, sending email and much more. The program allows to easily create simple task, as well as highly complex automations, involving conditional IF/ELSE statements, loops, custom variables and other advanced options.</description>
<category>Bot Creation</category>
<enclosure url="http://robotask.com/images/mainwin.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2017 15:49:05 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Runs applications and open documents. Manages automatic backups. Alerts you of any changes in your folders. Shuts down Windows and powers off your computer triggered by any event you choose. Processes files and folders (copies, moves, renames, deletes). Works with FTP and Web servers (downloads, uploads, etc). Sends letters and files by e-mail. Starts and stops Windows NT services. Sends.comwork messages as WinPopup’s. Acts as an alarm clock. and much more!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/UXGJZiXroA0?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Runs applications and open documents.<br></li><li> Manages automatic backups.<br></li><li> Alerts you of any changes in your folders.<br></li><li> Shuts down Windows and powers off your computer triggered by any event you choose.<br></li><li> Processes files and folders (copies, moves, renames, deletes).<br></li><li> Works with FTP and Web servers (downloads, uploads, etc).<br></li><li> Sends letters and files by e-mail.<br></li><li> Starts and stops Windows NT services.<br></li><li> Sends.comwork messages as WinPopup’s.<br></li><li> Acts as an alarm clock.<br></li><li> and much more!<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://robotask.com/images/mainwin.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="RoboTask 6.9.0.925 Business"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>UBot Studio 5.9.50 Developer Edition</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/956-ubot-studio-developer-edition.html</link>
<description>Name : UBot Studio Version : 5.9.50 Developer Edition OS : Windows Type : Bot Creation Price : $1200 Homepage : SalePage Automate common tasks and boost your inte.com marketing potential. Anything you do online can be automated with UBot Studio.</description>
<category>Bot Creation</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2017 01:22:13 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Visual Scripting Language : Use the Visual Scripting Language to build drag-and-drop automation products. Visual UI Designer : Create unique, beautiful user interfaces for your software with a simple, WYSIWYG visual UI designer. Record and Playback : Record actions inside your browser and automatically convert them into scripts that you can then edit however you&#039;d like. Search and Save : Search and save any web page content (including hidden HTML, jаvascript, and CSS data). Emails : Send, receive, and scan emails for important data instantly, and automatically click links inside. Auto-fill Forms : Auto-fill forms on any website with important or randomized data. Solve CAPTCHAs : Solve captchas manually or remotely with built-in third-party service integration. Proxies : Quickly use and switch private, public, and secure proxies. Randomize Content : Randomize content easily with a built-in Spintax editor and integration with the most popular text spinning services. Compile Scripts : Compile your scripts into executable software that anyone can install, even if they don&#039;t have UBot Studio. The Bot Bank : Start automating from Day 1 with our pre-programmed library scripts, the Bot Bank. Smart Apps : Create smart apps with conditionals and if-then statements. Custom Commands : Create your own custom commands and reuse them again and again. Data Manipulation : Handle advanced data manipulation with easy-to-use variables, lists and tables. Debug : Debug your scripts quickly and easily with UBot Studio&#039;s built-in debugger. RegEx - Powerful Regex Builder : Scrape text with a built-in, powerful Regex builder that includes common patterns for finding emails, addresses, and more. Web Inspector : Analyze websites&#039; source code with the built in Web Inspector. CSV : Read and write text CSV files for easy data management. Windows Automation : Type &amp;amp; click anywhere on your PC with Windows automation. Shell Commands : Quickly open other applications using shell commands. SQL - SQL Database Integration : Connect to, update, and grab data from any MySQL, SQLite, and SQL Server databases. Multi-Threading : Unlimited multi-threading and socket features let you control rendering and build lightning-fast apps. Professional Code View : Professional Code View lets you switch between Visual Scripting and a simple text language, for fast and easy editing. Image Recognition : Use Image Recognition to interact with Flash, Java and other web content automatically. Socket Interaction : Interact with web pages without rendering images or jаvascript, or connect directly through their HTTP protocol and supercharge your automation. Scheduling : Set recurring or timed events for your whole program or just individual parts, and leave the job to UBot Studio. Advanced UI Editor : Create entirely custom interfaces for your products with HTML5 using a specialized, advanced UI editor. Whitelabel Applications : Remove the UBot Studio logo and process information from all compiled software. Built-in Installer : Build tidy packages containing everything your customer will need to use your software.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/LC2QoT7ySR4?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li>Visual Scripting Language : Use the Visual Scripting Language to build drag-and-drop automation products.<br></li><li>Visual UI Designer : Create unique, beautiful user interfaces for your software with a simple, WYSIWYG visual UI designer.<br></li><li>Record and Playback : Record actions inside your browser and automatically convert them into scripts that you can then edit however you'd like.<br></li><li>Search and Save : Search and save any web page content (including hidden HTML, jаvascript, and CSS data).<br></li><li>Emails : Send, receive, and scan emails for important data instantly, and automatically click links inside.<br></li><li>Auto-fill Forms : Auto-fill forms on any website with important or randomized data.<br></li><li>Solve CAPTCHAs : Solve captchas manually or remotely with built-in third-party service integration.<br></li><li>Proxies : Quickly use and switch private, public, and secure proxies.<br></li><li>Randomize Content : Randomize content easily with a built-in Spintax editor and integration with the most popular text spinning services.<br></li><li>Compile Scripts : Compile your scripts into executable software that anyone can install, even if they don't have UBot Studio.<br></li><li>The Bot Bank : Start automating from Day 1 with our pre-programmed library scripts, the Bot Bank.<br></li><li>Smart Apps : Create smart apps with conditionals and if-then statements.<br></li><li>Custom Commands : Create your own custom commands and reuse them again and again.<br></li><li>Data Manipulation : Handle advanced data manipulation with easy-to-use variables, lists and tables.<br></li><li>Debug : Debug your scripts quickly and easily with UBot Studio's built-in debugger.<br></li><li>RegEx - Powerful Regex Builder : Scrape text with a built-in, powerful Regex builder that includes common patterns for finding emails, addresses, and more.<br></li><li>Web Inspector : Analyze websites' source code with the built in Web Inspector.<br></li><li>CSV : Read and write text CSV files for easy data management.<br></li><li>Windows Automation : Type &amp; click anywhere on your PC with Windows automation.<br></li><li>Shell Commands : Quickly open other applications using shell commands.<br></li><li>SQL - SQL Database Integration : Connect to, update, and grab data from any MySQL, SQLite, and SQL Server databases.<br></li><li>Multi-Threading : Unlimited multi-threading and socket features let you control rendering and build lightning-fast apps.<br></li><li>Professional Code View : Professional Code View lets you switch between Visual Scripting and a simple text language, for fast and easy editing.<br></li><li>Image Recognition : Use Image Recognition to interact with Flash, Java and other web content automatically.<br></li><li>Socket Interaction : Interact with web pages without rendering images or jаvascript, or connect directly through their HTTP protocol and supercharge your automation.<br></li><li>Scheduling : Set recurring or timed events for your whole program or just individual parts, and leave the job to UBot Studio.<br></li><li>Advanced UI Editor : Create entirely custom interfaces for your products with HTML5 using a specialized, advanced UI editor.<br></li><li>Whitelabel Applications : Remove the UBot Studio logo and process information from all compiled software.<br></li><li>Built-in Installer :  Build tidy packages containing everything your customer will need to use your software.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="UBot Studio 5.9.50 Developer Edition"><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>iMacros 11.5.499.3066 Enterprise Edition</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1128-imacros.html</link>
<description>Name : iMacros Version : 11.5.499.3066 Enterprise Edition OS : Windows Type : Bot Creator Price : $995 Homepage : SalePage AUTOMATE TASKS ACROSS ALL MAJOR BROWSERS INCLUDING INTE.COM EXPLORER, FIREFOX AND CHROME iMacros makes it easy for you to record and replay repetitious work and it’s the only web automation software that works with every website.</description>
<category>Bot Creation</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 16:00:01 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Playback Manual iMacro Playback Playback Unencrypted Macros Playback Encrypted Macros iMacros Playback via API Create Custom Passwords for Encrypted Macros Scripting / Recording Macro Recording Macro Editing (Unencrypted Macros) Macro Editing (Encrypted Macros) Inte.com Explorer: Automate via API Firefox: Automate via API Chrome: Automate via API Password Encryption Popup Manager Support Flash, Silverlight, Java, Flex Image Search / Recognition DirectScreen Automation &amp;amp; Testing Website Response Time Measurement Use of Variables Command Line Interface Task Scheduling Batch File Support Runs in Background (Tray) Scripting Interface (API) Windows Scripting Host Support (API) MS Office, Excel VBA Scripting MS .COM Support (VB.COM, C#, J#, ASP.COM) (API) API Supports All Scripting/Programming Languages Data Input Use CSV as input to iMacros Read data from text files as input to iMacros Read data from databases (API) Read / Write XML files (API) Web Page Data Extraction Extract Webpage Data Save data as CSV file Use of iMacros API Service / Support Expert Technical Support :::Free Members ::: Download Now Password : www.tgmember.com :::ViP Only:::</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/oh7T96fCu9g?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br>Playback 		<br><ul><li> Manual iMacro Playback 	 	 	<br></li><li> Playback Unencrypted Macros 	 	 	<br></li><li> Playback Encrypted Macros 			<br></li><li> iMacros Playback via API 			<br></li><li> Create Custom Passwords for Encrypted Macros 	<br></li></ul>		<br>Scripting / Recording 	<br><ul><li> Macro Recording 	 	 	<br></li><li> Macro Editing (Unencrypted Macros) 	 	 	<br></li><li> Macro Editing (Encrypted Macros) 			<br></li><li> Inte.com Explorer: Automate via API 			<br></li><li> Firefox: Automate via API 			<br></li><li> Chrome: Automate via API 			<br></li><li> Password Encryption 	 	 	<br></li><li> Popup Manager 	 	 	<br></li><li> Support Flash, Silverlight, Java, Flex 		 	<br></li><li> Image Search / Recognition 		 	<br></li><li> DirectScreen 	<br></li></ul>	 	<br>Automation &amp; Testing 	<br><ul><li> Website Response Time Measurement 	 	 	<br></li><li> Use of Variables 	 	 	<br></li><li> Command Line Interface 		 	<br></li><li> Task Scheduling 		 	<br></li><li> Batch File Support 		 	<br></li><li> Runs in Background (Tray) 		 	<br></li><li> Scripting Interface (API) 			<br></li><li> Windows Scripting Host Support (API) 			<br></li><li> MS Office, Excel VBA Scripting 			<br></li><li> MS .COM Support (VB.COM, C#, J#, ASP.COM) (API) 			<br></li><li> API Supports All Scripting/Programming Languages 	<br></li></ul>		<br>Data Input 		<br><ul><li> Use CSV as input to iMacros 	 	 	<br></li><li> Read data from text files as input to iMacros 	 	 	<br></li><li> Read data from databases (API) 			<br></li><li> Read / Write XML files (API) 		<br></li></ul>	<br>Web Page Data Extraction 	<br><ul><li> Extract Webpage Data 	 	 	<br></li><li> Save data as CSV file 	 	 	<br></li><li> Use of iMacros API 	<br></li></ul>		<br>Service / Support 	<br><ul><li> Expert Technical Support<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><span style="font-size:12pt;"><b><span style="color:#006600">:::Free Members :::</span></b></span><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="iMacros 11.5.499.3066 Enterprise Edition"><br><div class="quote"><br><a href="http://31.220.48.156/engine/go.php?url=aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9jbG91ZGRyaXZlL3NoYXJlL3ozRnB2SFBRTks5VGc2SXNHbUJlNG1LVEg0S2NWa2JoNEFQNEgyM2V3MUk%2FcmVmXz1jZF9zaGFyZV9saW5rX2NvcHk%3D"  target="_blank">Download Now</a><br>Password : www.tgmember.com<br></div><br></div><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><span style="font-size:12pt;"><b><span style="color:#FF0000">:::ViP Only:::</span></b></span><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Master Shorty 2.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1816-master-shorty.html</link>
<description>Name : Mastery Shorty Version : 2.0 OS : Windows Type : Bot Creator Price : $7 Homepage : SalePage This software provides a series of little tools that we never find and think about. Why we need them and we don’t have them yet. Usually you should spend your time to do a simple task but it is a boring work for you and seize your thousands time everyday.</description>
<category>Bot Creation</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2016 17:33:40 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features And the software that you use eat your more time. Now, Master Shorty presents, you have your own copy this software you will never end up to break your flow that make you stuck on some little task and useless. With Master Shorty you will keep moving forward at full speed. You will move without consume your precious time. And today you can develop your business with full speed and of course you will get many visitors and making money everyday.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/6VWXpyYrhQI?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /> And the software that you use eat your more time. Now, Master Shorty presents, you have your own copy this software you will never end up to break your flow that make you stuck on some little task and useless. With Master Shorty you will keep moving forward at full speed. You will move without consume your precious time. And today you can develop your business with full speed and of course you will get many visitors and making money everyday.<br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Master Shorty 2.0" title="Master Shorty 2.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>