<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Tumblr Marketing - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Tumblr Marketing - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>TumblingJazz 1.912</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/947-tumblingjazz.html</link>
<description>Name : TumblingJazz Version : 1.912 OS : Windows Type : Social Marketing, Tumblr Marketing Price : $77 Homepage : SalePage Tumbling Jazz - The Ultimate Tumblr Bot Tumblr is one of the most popular social media blogging websites around at the moment. Millions of users with millions of blogs use the site EVERY DAY. With the use of TumblingJazz, the world&#039;s leading Tumblr automation bot, you can harness this power for your own needs. The TumblingJazz tumblr bot can fully automate all actions and interactions of the Tumblr.com site, hands free!. Harness The Huge Amount Of Users And Traffic On Tumblr Using TumblingJazz it is a walk in the park to generate tonnes of traffic to your Tumblr blog and then onto your money sites. Due to the multi capacity, multi-threaded, raw socket implementation you can really let the bot rip, doing what it does best. All hands free. Set it up, schedule it, repeat it. Site back and watch the traffic FLOOD in. Be The Master Of Puppets (Pulling Strings) Everything you can do on the Tumblr website has been automated. This means you have full control over your accounts. Let the bots run on repeat and your accounts will grow rapidly destroying all before them, but most importantly they will grow naturally and organically. The TumblingJazz automation bot gives you the full command at your fingertips, nothing is restricted, we are here to help your realise your Tumblr domination dreams.</description>
<category>Tumblr Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 13:08:51 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Automatic Following Automatic Liking Automatic Reblogging Automatic Reblogging Articles Automatic Reblogging Images Automatic Reblogging Quotes Automatic Reblogging Converstations Automatic Reblogging Links Automatic Posting Articles Post Articles from RSS feed automatically - fully customisable to work with ANY RSS feed Automatic Posting Images with watermark options Post Images from RSS feed automatically - fully customisable to work with ANY RSS feed Post Images as a photoshoot, up to 10 images per post Automatic Posting YouTube Videos Post Videos from RSS feed automatically - fully customisable to work with ANY RSS feed Pinterest Image Scraper Tumblr Blog Image Scraper Tumblr Tagged Search Image scraper FULL Tumblr search functionality, tags / blogs / recent / popular Tumblr search filters (audio / links / text / video etc) Full Secondary blog support Watch folder automatic image uploader - Automatically upload images that are put into a specific folder Syndicate posted content to Wordpress and Blogger - Before posting your content to Tumblr, post it to any wordpress / blogger blog then insert the syndicated link to your Tumblr post! Account creation and automatic email verification Manage an unlimited amount of accounts, unlike other softwares we do not charge you a monthly fee nor limit the amount of accounts you can use. Account Verification Update account names / titles / description / avatar / theme easily Fully socket implemented. No webbrowser / WYSIWYG bot here. TumblingJazz is a lean, mean fighting machine *Create accounts uses a browser rendered to memory for high success rate Get your accounts / content trending by utilizing our MASS features, Mass Like, Mass Reblog, Mass Follow. Better yet, how about MASS INCEST TRENDING. Use your accounts to create a social web of likes / reblogs / follows. Proxy scraper Proxy verification Auto content spinning control Content creation tool with custom synonum files for ease of content creation Full Spintax support Supports Tokens in content posting Control all aspects of the application via Settings Schedule all actions for Drip Feeding potential. Time delay between actions when posting Repeat all actions for constant blog updates Post all content immediately or to your Tumblr queue Run SEO improvements to your blog theme with one click Frequent updates High quality support via multiple systems Full Captcha API support All processes are stored so can be restarted in case of power failure Detailed logs of all processes Import/Export features for profiles, proxies. It is your data to take and do what you want with Redo / retry / pause / cancel any action</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/B9G_F6-8Br0?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><br><ul><li> Automatic Following<br></li><li> Automatic Liking<br></li><li> Automatic Reblogging<br></li><li> Automatic Reblogging Articles<br></li><li> Automatic Reblogging Images<br></li><li> Automatic Reblogging Quotes<br></li><li> Automatic Reblogging Converstations<br></li><li> Automatic Reblogging Links<br></li><li> Automatic Posting Articles<br></li><li> Post Articles from RSS feed automatically - fully customisable to work with ANY RSS feed<br></li><li> Automatic Posting Images with watermark options<br></li><li> Post Images from RSS feed automatically - fully customisable to work with ANY RSS feed<br></li><li> Post Images as a photoshoot, up to 10 images per post<br></li><li> Automatic Posting YouTube Videos<br></li><li> Post Videos from RSS feed automatically - fully customisable to work with ANY RSS feed<br></li><li> Pinterest Image Scraper<br></li><li> Tumblr Blog Image Scraper<br></li><li> Tumblr Tagged Search Image scraper<br></li><li> FULL Tumblr search functionality, tags / blogs / recent / popular<br></li><li> Tumblr search filters (audio / links / text / video etc)<br></li><li> Full Secondary blog support<br></li><li> Watch folder automatic image uploader - Automatically upload images that are put into a specific folder<br></li><li> Syndicate posted content to Wordpress and Blogger - Before posting your content to Tumblr, post it to any wordpress / blogger blog then insert the syndicated link to your Tumblr post!<br></li><li> Account creation and automatic email verification<br></li><li> Manage an unlimited amount of accounts, unlike other softwares we do not charge you a monthly fee nor limit the amount of accounts you can use.<br></li><li> Account Verification<br></li><li> Update account names / titles / description / avatar / theme easily<br></li><li> Fully socket implemented. No webbrowser / WYSIWYG bot here. TumblingJazz is a lean, mean fighting machine *Create accounts uses a browser rendered to memory for high success rate<br></li><li> Get your accounts / content trending by utilizing our MASS features, Mass Like, Mass Reblog, Mass Follow. Better yet, how about MASS INCEST TRENDING. Use your accounts to create a social web of likes / reblogs / follows.<br></li><li> Proxy scraper<br></li><li> Proxy verification<br></li><li> Auto content spinning control<br></li><li> Content creation tool with custom synonum files for ease of content creation<br></li><li> Full Spintax support<br></li><li> Supports Tokens in content posting<br></li><li> Control all aspects of the application via Settings<br></li><li> Schedule all actions for Drip Feeding potential.<br></li><li> Time delay between actions when posting<br></li><li> Repeat all actions for constant blog updates<br></li><li> Post all content immediately or to your Tumblr queue<br></li><li> Run SEO improvements to your blog theme with one click<br></li><li> Frequent updates<br></li><li> High quality support via multiple systems<br></li><li> Full Captcha API support<br></li><li> All processes are stored so can be restarted in case of power failure<br></li><li> Detailed logs of all processes<br></li><li> Import/Export features for profiles, proxies. It is your data to take and do what you want with<br></li><li> Redo / retry / pause / cancel any action<br><br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="TumblingJazz 1.912"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Tumble Ninja 2.5.5</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1022-tumble-ninja.html</link>
<description>Name : TumbleNinja Tumblr Bot Version : 2.5.5 OS : Windows Type : Tumblr Marketing Bot Price : $27 Homepage : SalePage Welcome to TumbleNinja, the world’s #1 Tumblr bot. This proprietary and versatile marketing software handles all of the repetitive grunt work, SAVES you large amounts of time, gets you thousands of followers, and helps you generate more profit from this incredibly popular social media blogging platform!</description>
<category>Tumblr Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 12:53:24 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Auto-follow blogs Auto-unfollow blogs Auto-message blog owners Auto-like blog posts Auto-reblog Schedule reblogs in advance Monitor keywords to automatically like or reblog new posts The ability to carefully target who you want to reach</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/SAQmDaqtBEg?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><br><ul><li> Auto-follow blogs<br></li><li> Auto-unfollow blogs<br></li><li> Auto-message blog owners<br></li><li> Auto-like blog posts<br></li><li> Auto-reblog<br></li><li> Schedule reblogs in advance<br></li><li> Monitor keywords to automatically like or reblog new posts<br></li><li> The ability to carefully target who you want to reach<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Tumble Ninja 2.5.5"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Almighty Tumbly Hog 1.0.6</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1988-almighty-tumbly-hog.html</link>
<description>Name : Almighty Tumbly Hog Version : 1.0.6 OS : Windows Type : Tumblr Tools Price : $97 Homepage : SalePage The ONLY PUSH-BUTTON TRAFFIC SOFTWARE On The Market Taking Advantage of the Tumblr Platform!</description>
<category>Tumblr Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.thealmightyhog.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/12/HeaderLogo.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 02:13:59 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features ONE-CLICK SIMPLICITY – Easily drive insane amounts of traffic to any offer, website, or video with a click of a button. TEST CONVERSIONS FREE – Need to test your conversion rate for your landing page or sales page? Quickly send free targeted and quality traffic to your page to test it without having to pay a dime for paid traffic. BUILD YOUR FOLLOWERS – Get tons of followers to your Tumbler account and start using it for your business. EASY TO IMPLEMENT – The software is so easy to use, anyone can become a traffic maverick overnight! TRAFFIC FOR YOUR CLIENTS – Send quality traffic to your clients websites over and over again, and get paid for it. =) FULL MEMBERS AREA TRAINING – Full training by Megan on how to use the software. M.COMIZE YOUR TRAFFIC – Get Megan’s Ebook on how to effectively m.comize Tumblr traffic. TARGETED TRAFFIC – Quickly targets specific keywords to find the BEST relative blog posts to repost. This way you get very targeted audiences to visit your page. PROGRAM WORKS FOR YOU WHILE YOU SLEEP – Literally posts FOR YOU in your sleep. Wake up in the morning with your visitor stats sky rocketing. CHOOSE WHAT TO REPOST – Post just text ads, video ads or only ads with images? ADD IMAGES TO TEXT POSTS – Ads images based off of keywords so your text posts NEVER look boring! SHORTEN LONG POSTS SO YOUR LINKS ARE VISIBLE – This software will even shorten the text ads and put YOUR LINK right in front of TARGETED traffic! MULTIPLE BLOG &amp; ACCOUNTS – You can easily setup multiple blogs and accounts for different niches so you can post relative content to each niche. The Ultimate All-In-One Free Traffic Resource Has Finally Arrived for 2016!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/FxUcTuFDTeA?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> ONE-CLICK SIMPLICITY – Easily drive insane amounts of traffic to any offer, website, or video with a click of a button.<br /></li><li> TEST CONVERSIONS FREE – Need to test your conversion rate for your landing page or sales page? Quickly send free targeted and quality traffic to your page to test it without having to pay a dime for paid traffic.<br /></li><li> BUILD YOUR FOLLOWERS – Get tons of followers to your Tumbler account and start using it for your business.<br /></li><li> EASY TO IMPLEMENT – The software is so easy to use, anyone can become a traffic maverick overnight!<br /></li><li> TRAFFIC FOR YOUR CLIENTS – Send quality traffic to your clients websites over and over again, and get paid for it. =)<br /></li><li> FULL MEMBERS AREA TRAINING – Full training by Megan on how to use the software.<br /></li><li> M.COMIZE YOUR TRAFFIC – Get Megan’s Ebook on how to effectively m.comize Tumblr traffic.<br /></li><li> TARGETED TRAFFIC – Quickly targets specific keywords to find the BEST relative blog posts to repost. This way you get very targeted audiences to visit your page.<br /></li><li> PROGRAM WORKS FOR YOU WHILE YOU SLEEP – Literally posts FOR YOU in your sleep. Wake up in the morning with your visitor stats sky rocketing.<br /></li><li> CHOOSE WHAT TO REPOST – Post just text ads, video ads or only ads with images?<br /></li><li> ADD IMAGES TO TEXT POSTS – Ads images based off of keywords so your text posts NEVER look boring!<br /></li><li> SHORTEN LONG POSTS SO YOUR LINKS ARE VISIBLE – This software will even shorten the text ads and put YOUR LINK right in front of TARGETED traffic!<br /></li><li> MULTIPLE BLOG & ACCOUNTS – You can easily setup multiple blogs and accounts for different niches so you can post relative content to each niche.<br /></li><li> The Ultimate All-In-One Free Traffic Resource Has Finally Arrived for 2016!<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://www.thealmightyhog.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/12/HeaderLogo.png" alt="Almighty Tumbly Hog 1.0.6" title="Almighty Tumbly Hog 1.0.6"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Almighty Tumbly Hog 1.0.6" title="Almighty Tumbly Hog 1.0.6"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>PR Traffic Booster 1.0.0.58</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1700-pr-traffic-booster.html</link>
<description>Name : PR Traffic Booster + PRHarvester + PRPixelMagick Version : 1.0.0.58 + 1.0.0.13 + 1.0.0.0 OS : Windows Type : Tumblr Marketing Tools Price : $97 Homepage : SalePage Still struggling to Get Visitors and your Website Ranked? Sick and Tired of relying on Google Rankings and Wasting Money on Expensive Traffic that Doesn&#039;t Work? Brand New Software Taps into Over 118 Million Visitors Funnelling Targeted Traffic and High PR links to Any Url of your Choice Leveraging 118 Million Visitors a Month on Auto Pilot while Driving Targeted Traffic, Gaining higher SERPS, Backlinks, and even pocketing Ca$h What I&#039;m about to share with you is a strategy I stumbled across by accident. A strategy that actually had me slapping myself. Thinking why didn&#039;t I come across it earlier!? This strategy was a method that not only hundreds of fellow marketers are banking cash from on a daily bases but a method that has been overlooked by many. Brand New Software Gets Targeted Traffic and High PR DO-Follow Backlinks It’s a method that not only allowed me to gain targeted traffic, High PR do follow backlinks which I controlled, but a method that also increased my websites rankings. Introducing</description>
<category>Tumblr Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.prtrafficbooster.com/group1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2016 00:07:30 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Account Signup email verification and customization (includes adding avatar, theme, blog title) Reblogs - also ability to change description, add tags and click through link (HTML Supported) Likes posts with ability to add random delays Follows users Auto follows users that follow you Unfollows users that do not follow back after X days Posts articles, images, quotes and videos. You can publish now or add to queue with the ability to add description, tags and clickthorugh links for each post. Group Niche management - Allows you to manage multiple accounts niche specific Collects Blog stats Checks account status Works with threads Works with proxies Works with Tor Works with HMA VPN Allows spinned syntax Works with death by captcha and decaptcha Works with bit.ly api to shorten links Runs whilst minimized Uploads images from url or hard drive Ability to import already created accounts</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/gcdBSSzqv9g?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Account Signup email verification and customization (includes adding avatar, theme, blog title)<br /></li><li> Reblogs - also ability to change description, add tags and click through link (HTML Supported)<br /></li><li> Likes posts with ability to add random delays<br /></li><li> Follows users<br /></li><li> Auto follows users that follow you<br /></li><li> Unfollows users that do not follow back after X days<br /></li><li> Posts articles, images, quotes and videos. You can publish now or add to queue with the ability to add description, tags and clickthorugh links for each post.<br /></li><li> Group Niche management - Allows you to manage multiple accounts niche specific<br /></li><li> Collects Blog stats<br /></li><li> Checks account status<br /></li><li> Works with threads<br /></li><li> Works with proxies<br /></li><li> Works with Tor<br /></li><li> Works with HMA VPN<br /></li><li> Allows spinned syntax<br /></li><li> Works with death by captcha and decaptcha<br /></li><li> Works with bit.ly api to shorten links<br /></li><li> Runs whilst minimized<br /></li><li> Uploads images from url or hard drive<br /></li><li> Ability to import already created accounts<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://www.prtrafficbooster.com/group1.jpg" alt="PR Traffic Booster 1.0.0.58" title="PR Traffic Booster 1.0.0.58"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="PR Traffic Booster 1.0.0.58" title="PR Traffic Booster 1.0.0.58"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Tum Demon 1.16</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1188-tumdemon.html</link>
<description>Name :Tum Demon – The Ultimate Tumblr Bot Version : 1.16 OS : Windows Type : Tumblr Marketing Bot Price : $299 Homepage : SalePage Using Tum Demon, you can save lots of time and money. The whole process can be done quickly with just a few setups. What you get from Tum Demon: creating multiple accounts, posting content, scheduling, blasting, searching users, following, searching posts, liking, reblogging, and more… All are done automatically and systematically. It is completely hand free! All you need to do is set up tasks and manage the report. Tum Demon has user-friendly interface which allows you to run and control everything easily.</description>
<category>Tumblr Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://smmbots.com/screenshots/tum/tum.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://smmbots.com/screenshots/tum/avatar-editor.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2016 01:26:13 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Modules Follow/Unfollow Modules Video uploader Modules images uploader Modules Text poster Modules Liker Modules Reblogtor Modules Send Messages Modules Mass liker/Reblogtor Modules Scraper Modules Account Statistic Modules Theme Editor Modules Avatar Editor Modules Captcha Sloving Modules Proxies</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/bzuR1RBvzcY?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Modules Follow/Unfollow<br></li><li> Modules Video uploader<br></li><li> Modules images uploader<br></li><li> Modules Text poster<br></li><li> Modules Liker<br></li><li> Modules Reblogtor<br></li><li> Modules Send Messages<br></li><li> Modules Mass liker/Reblogtor<br></li><li> Modules Scraper<br></li><li> Modules Account Statistic<br></li><li> Modules Theme Editor<br></li><li> Modules Avatar Editor<br></li><li> Modules Captcha Sloving<br></li><li> Modules Proxies<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://smmbots.com/screenshots/tum/tum.png" alt="Tum Demon 1.16"><br><img src="http://smmbots.com/screenshots/tum/avatar-editor.png" alt=""><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>