<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>GPlus Marketing - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>GPlus Marketing - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>GPlusDominator 2.0.11</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/885-gplusdominator.html</link>
<description>Name :GPlus Dominator Agency Version : 2.0.11 OS : Windows Type : Google Plus Marketing Price : $499 Homepage : SalePage GPlusDominator offers you features to simplify any task on Google+. From managing circles and connections to posting content, from tracking a post&#039;s performance to comparing with others; from knowing your follower growth to tracking the activity of popular users GPlusDominator is your one-stop solution to trust. No doubt Google+ has emerged as a relatively new social.comworking player. It has, however, evolved continually to offer business communities an amazing platform with unique features and important SEO capabilities that no marketer can afford to overlook. A research shows that if your business has 100 followers with active engagement, your Google search engine results position can improve by at least 14 spots. With instant Indexing, SEO and an array of amazing services from videos, maps, books, analytics etc. to hangouts and apps unlike Facebook, Twitter or any other social.comworking site, Google+ can make or break a brand&#039;s presence online along with impacting traffic, leads and sales incredibly. But as both bouquet and range of Google+ services continue to grow by the day, both individuals and brands are looking for comprehensive yet easy tools to make the most of their digital marketing move on Google+.</description>
<category>GPlus Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 13:06:18 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Account Like Increaser Text Community People Photos Pages Circles Profile</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/YdmOj73BDVs?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Account<br></li><li> Like Increaser<br></li><li> Text<br></li><li> Community<br></li><li> People<br></li><li> Photos<br></li><li> Pages<br></li><li> Circles<br></li><li> Profile<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="GPlusDominator 2.0.11"><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Google Plus Bot 1.176</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/884-google-plus-bot.html</link>
<description>Name : Google Plus Bot by RootJazz Version : 1.176 OS : Windows Type : Google + Marketing Price : $77 Homepage : SalePage Google Plus Bot - The Ultimate In Google Plus Automation The Ultimate Google Plus Automation bot. Increase followers, auto post, auto Plus one, auto follow, join communities, scrape and more</description>
<category>GPlus Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2017 05:54:58 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Automatic Following Automatic unfollowing Automatic Liking Automatic Commenting Full account support, works with profiles and pages (business / secondary pages) RSS posting text / images / links / audio / videos Automatic posting of new items to RSS feeds Action on all posts in community Action on all community members Action on all community contributers Full search support Action via search via authors or post Filter search via recent or popular Post links Post videos Post text Post Audio Post to communities Join Communities GPlus List Scraper Manage an unlimited amount of accounts. Account Verification Full Spintax support Schedule all actions for Drip Feeding potential. Time delay between actions to appear realistic Repeat all actions for constant promotions hands free! Frequent updates Good quality support via multiple systems Full Captcha API support All processes are stored so can be restarted in case of power failure Detailed logs of all processes Import / Export features for profiles, proxies. It is your data to take and do what you want with Redo / retry / pause / cancel any action</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3>
<p><br><ul><li> Automatic Following<br></li><li> Automatic unfollowing<br></li><li> Automatic Liking<br></li><li> Automatic Commenting<br></li><li> Full account support, works with profiles and pages (business / secondary pages)<br></li><li> RSS posting text / images / links / audio / videos<br></li><li> Automatic posting of new items to RSS feeds<br></li><li> Action on all posts in community<br></li><li> Action on all community members<br></li><li> Action on all community contributers<br></li><li> Full search support<br></li><li> Action via search via authors or post<br></li><li> Filter search via recent or popular<br></li><li> Post links<br></li><li> Post videos<br></li><li> Post text<br></li><li> Post Audio<br></li><li> Post to communities<br></li><li> Join Communities<br></li><li> GPlus List Scraper<br></li><li> Manage an unlimited amount of accounts.<br></li><li> Account Verification<br></li><li> Full Spintax support<br></li><li> Schedule all actions for Drip Feeding potential.<br></li><li> Time delay between actions to appear realistic<br></li><li> Repeat all actions for constant promotions hands free!<br></li><li> Frequent updates<br></li><li> Good quality support via multiple systems<br></li><li> Full Captcha API support<br></li><li> All processes are stored so can be restarted in case of power failure<br></li><li> Detailed logs of all processes<br></li><li> Import / Export features for profiles, proxies. It is your data to take and do what you want with<br></li><li> Redo / retry / pause / cancel any action<br></li></ul></p>
<div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Google Plus Bot 1.176"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Gplus 4.7.13 Pro</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1657-gplus.html</link>
<description>Name : Gplus Version : 4.7.13 Pro OS : Windows Type : Gplus Marketing Tools Price : $100 Homepage : SalePage Increase +1 and marketing online</description>
<category>GPlus Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://autogoogleplus.com/frontend/img/plus24h_screen.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2016 17:49:00 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Plus all the information on the homepage Google+ : Auto plus one, no more hand fatigue and still clicks hundreds of thousands of public community. Auto Share Link and post to the group : Auto Share link, posting to the communities. Comment to posts : Auto comment on posts you plus one. Auto add profile to circles : Auto find and add profile to your circles Auto comment on YouTube video : Search youtube video by keyword or loaded from file and then auto comment on the video in the list. Auto comment upvote comments Youtube : Using list account and list chanel to comment and like comment youtube Join communities : Find groups by keyword and automatically join the group found.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><div class="dlevideoplayer" style="width:100%;max-width:425px;"><ul data-theme="default" data-preload="metadata"><li data-title="" data-type="youtube" data-url="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Vsm2DUYUVqg"></li></ul></div></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Plus all the information on the homepage Google+ : Auto plus one, no more hand fatigue and still clicks hundreds of thousands of public community.<br></li><li> Auto Share Link and post to the group : Auto Share link, posting to the communities.<br></li><li> Comment to posts : Auto comment on posts you plus one.<br></li><li> Auto add profile to circles : Auto find and add profile to your circles<br></li><li> Auto comment on YouTube video : Search youtube video by keyword or loaded from file and then auto comment on the video in the list.<br></li><li> Auto comment upvote comments Youtube : Using list account and list chanel to comment and like comment youtube<br></li><li> Join communities : Find groups by keyword and automatically join the group found.<br><br></li></ul><br><img src="http://autogoogleplus.com/frontend/img/plus24h_screen.png" alt="Gplus 4.7.13 Pro"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Google Plus Marketing 2016 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2033-google-plus-marketing.html</link>
<description>Name : Google Plus Marketing 2016 Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Google Plus Tools Price : $57 Homepage : SalePage Google Plus, Post Multi Text, Multi Link + Email sharing</description>
<category>GPlus Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://i.imgur.com/KiDSPy8.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2016 12:35:49 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Google Plus Marketing - How to choose people on YouTube videos or Google Plus Posts and submit comments on your posts and also by mail using Google Plus only Did you know that you can remove all the people who have commented on a video to send posts and emails to all of them. Did you notice in the picture above we took any amount of ids (people) who commented on the post, now we will comment threads them all on Google Plus. Now see that our COMMENT program with your message all threads of all these people. Note the message.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/v6EXuIY4v2Q?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br />Google Plus Marketing - How to choose people on YouTube videos or Google Plus Posts and submit comments on your posts and also by mail using Google Plus only<br /> <br />Did you know that you can remove all the people who have commented on a video to send posts and emails to all of them.<br /> <br /> <br />Did you notice in the picture above we took any amount of ids (people) who commented on the post, now we will comment threads them all on Google Plus.<br />Now see that our COMMENT program with your message all threads of all these people.<br /><br />Note the message.<br /><img src="http://i.imgur.com/KiDSPy8.png" alt="Google Plus Marketing 2016 1.0" title="Google Plus Marketing 2016 1.0"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Google Plus Marketing 2016 1.0" title="Google Plus Marketing 2016 1.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Google Plus Add 2016 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2032-google-plus-add.html</link>
<description>Name : Google Plus Add 2016 Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : GPlus Marketing Tools Price : $57 Homepage : SalePage Google Plus Add - Add people to your Google Plus 2016</description>
<category>GPlus Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://i.imgur.com/CcnzYDH.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2016 12:30:21 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Import ID List to Add ADD TO MULTIPLE TEXT : This feature enables users to drag and drop soup custom font position, font, in bold, in italics, font size, alignment 2 pm and 4 pm, centered, text color, border, height, width of Chu, bla bla ..... ADD TO BE MORE PICTURES : You may add the past tense changes in the text image you imported to help you save time. EXPORT FORM ultrafast : Will help you with software the lightning speed output formats .png accordance with the size of the art file Watch coordinates glue tha : Help you solve the scale 1 promptly. PLUS ANOTHER VIETNAM many advantages : HELPING YOUR PROBLEM SOLVING HUMAN LARGE</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/2Mee7ayL4tc?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Import ID List to Add<br /></li><li> ADD TO MULTIPLE TEXT : This feature enables users to drag and drop soup custom font position, font, in bold, in italics, font size, alignment 2 pm and 4 pm, centered, text color, border, height, width of Chu, bla bla .....<br /></li><li> ADD TO BE MORE PICTURES : You may add the past tense changes in the text image you imported to help you save time.<br /></li><li> EXPORT FORM ultrafast : Will help you with software the lightning speed output formats .png accordance with the size of the art file<br /></li><li> Watch coordinates glue tha : Help you solve the scale 1 promptly.<br /></li><li> PLUS ANOTHER VIETNAM many advantages : HELPING YOUR PROBLEM SOLVING HUMAN LARGE<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://i.imgur.com/CcnzYDH.png" alt="Google Plus Add 2016 1.0" title="Google Plus Add 2016 1.0"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Google Plus Add 2016 1.0" title="Google Plus Add 2016 1.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Google + Email Sender 2016 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2014-google-plus-email-sender.html</link>
<description>Name : Google + Email Sender Version : 2016 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Google Plus Marketing Tools Price : $50 Google Plus Email Sender, sending bulk email using Google Plus 2016</description>
<category>GPlus Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://i.imgur.com/3D2GYOK.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2016 02:33:42 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Google Plus Marketing - How to choose people on YouTube videos or Google Plus Posts and submit comments on your posts and also by mail using Google Plus only Did you know that you can remove all the people who have commented on a video to send posts and emails to all of them, see the image of our removing program Did you notice in the picture above we took in 1293 ids (people) who commented on the post, now we will comment threads them all on Google Plus. Now see that our COMMENT program with your message all threads of all these people. - Custom Message - List of Email to Send</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/AdNR72cU0Uw?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br />Google Plus Marketing - How to choose people on YouTube videos or Google Plus Posts and submit comments on your posts and also by mail using Google Plus only<br />Did you know that you can remove all the people who have commented on a video to send posts and emails to all of them, see the image of our removing program<br />Did you notice in the picture above we took in 1293 ids (people) who commented on the post, now we will comment threads them all on Google Plus.<br />Now see that our COMMENT program with your message all threads of all these people.<br />- Custom Message<br />- List of Email to Send<br /><img src="http://i.imgur.com/3D2GYOK.png" alt="Google + Email Sender 2016 1.0" title="Google + Email Sender 2016 1.0"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Google + Email Sender 2016 1.0" title="Google + Email Sender 2016 1.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>G Plus Adder 3.0.36</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/883-g-plus-adder.html</link>
<description>Name :G Plus Adder Version : 3.0.36 OS : Windows Type : Google Plus Marketing Price : $19 Homepage : SalePage GOOGLE PLUS ADDER is a software designed to bring about an instant positive impact on your online marketing. It has been crafted to boost marketing on Google + without having to sluggishly and agonizingly figure out the whole thing from scratch them self! Google Plus Adder can justifiably be called as &quot;Google plus friend adder&quot; because it increases your targeted followers within the Google+ social.comwork. When your circle gets expanded, you will have more traffic to your site and this will help you in boosting your sales. And, all of this will happen instantly. Both start-ups and experienced Inte.com marketers can use the Google Plus Friend Adder software to find their potential customers instantly. Even successful businesses are using this tool because success motivates them to crave for more. Google Plus Bot Friends Adder will help you find the right user profiles within the.comwork. You can therefore build the potential audience you have been targeting so that you can achieve the higest conversion rate. Put your best foot forward and start utilizing the Google Plus Friend Adder software, so that you don’t spend hours manually trying to expand your.comwork. You can systematically grow your circle and this will ultimately result in phenomenal increase in your sales. Isn’t that amazing?</description>
<category>GPlus Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-_bY2THbUXKg/VLXL4AjgDaI/AAAAAAAAA58/b2y0QoClsVk/s1600/6.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2016 05:00:26 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Collect Google Plus user profiles by keywords. Collect communities by keywords. Retrieve communities user profiles list. Add automatically all collected users to one or more than one selected circle in your Business Pages Add automatically all collected users to one or more than one selected circle in your personal profile. Option to pause and continue at the point where it left off. Bypass the j&amp;#097;vascript filters searching for communities. Now the software collect unlimited communities targeted by keywords. Full control of time and limits. Protection to avoid to follow already followed profiles Support unlimited accounts Save accounts in projects in the software You can add, edit or delete unlimited projects You can browse any selected user profile or community You can remove any selected user profile or community You can clear all the list of users or communities collected.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/ow4osYybWC4?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Collect Google Plus user profiles by keywords.<br /></li><li> Collect communities by keywords.<br /></li><li> Retrieve communities user profiles list.<br /></li><li> Add automatically all collected users to one or more than one selected circle in your Business Pages<br /></li><li> Add automatically all collected users to one or more than one selected circle in your personal profile.<br /></li><li> Option to pause and continue at the point where it left off.<br /></li><li> Bypass the j&#097;vascript filters searching for communities. Now the software collect unlimited communities targeted by keywords.<br /></li><li> Full control of time and limits.<br /></li><li> Protection to avoid to follow already followed profiles<br /></li><li> Support unlimited accounts<br /></li><li> Save accounts in projects in the software<br /></li><li> You can add, edit or delete unlimited projects<br /></li><li> You can browse any selected user profile or community<br /></li><li> You can remove any selected user profile or community<br /></li><li> You can clear all the list of users or communities collected.<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-_bY2THbUXKg/VLXL4AjgDaI/AAAAAAAAA58/b2y0QoClsVk/s1600/6.png" alt="G Plus Adder 3.0.36" title="G Plus Adder 3.0.36"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="G Plus Adder 3.0.36" title="G Plus Adder 3.0.36"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Maps Mentor 2.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1378-maps-mentor.html</link>
<description>Name : Maps Mentor Version : 2.0 OS : Windows/MAC Type : GoogleMaps Marketing Tools Price : $197 Homepage : SalePage I’ve kept this software close to the chest for a long time… but I know that if you’re just starting out, finding clients can be the most challenging thing… So imagine if you had software that spit out PERFECT clients who have money to invest, are WILLING AND READY to invest, and who NEED YOUR SERVICE… Do you think it’d be easier to get the 8 clients you need to reach 6-figures a year?</description>
<category>GPlus Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.mapsmentor.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/mockupdesigns_transparentbackground.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2015 11:47:50 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features How To Get Your First Client TODAY: Even if you have no experience, no website of your own, and no results to show. How is this possible? You’ll leverage other people’s proof to gain trust… Then you’ll use the exact closing words I give you that will get even skeptical business owners to pull out their credit cards and pay you. You’ll never need to make a phone call, film a video, or struggle with cheap clients if you don&#039;t want to… the training inside Maps Mentor is SO powerful that all you have to do is implement it and you will get paid! How To Rank ANY Client Fast: Follow the unique strategies inside Maps Mentor to get any website to the top of Google local listings in days. Your clients’ jaws will drop with the flood of new business they receive thanks to your service. Heck, you may even surprise yourself with just how easy it is! That means your clients will happily pay you $1,000.00 a month, AND send you countless referrals so that your business grows without you ever having to pitch. Some of these strategies are so groundbreaking and secretive that I know you’ll be shocked about the REAL way to rank locally. All “Technical” Stuff Made Easy Enough For an 8 Year Old: With your step-by-step video training, you will NEVER be confused or worried about the tech stuff. I’ve made it so simple that an 8 year old could follow the instructions and get ANY website ranked in days.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/3_9cljOnuLg?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> How To Get Your First Client TODAY: Even if you have no experience, no website of your own, and no results to show. How is this possible? You’ll leverage other people’s proof to gain trust… Then you’ll use the exact closing words I give you that will get even skeptical business owners to pull out their credit cards and pay you. You’ll never need to make a phone call, film a video, or struggle with cheap clients if you don't want to… the training inside Maps Mentor is SO powerful that all you have to do is implement it and you will get paid!<br /></li><li> How To Rank ANY Client Fast: Follow the unique strategies inside Maps Mentor to get any website to the top of Google local listings in days. Your clients’ jaws will drop with the flood of new business they receive thanks to your service. Heck, you may even surprise yourself with just how easy it is! That means your clients will happily pay you ,000.00 a month, AND send you countless referrals so that your business grows without you ever having to pitch. Some of these strategies are so groundbreaking and secretive that I know you’ll be shocked about the REAL way to rank locally.<br /></li><li> All “Technical” Stuff Made Easy Enough For an 8 Year Old: With your step-by-step video training, you will NEVER be confused or worried about the tech stuff. I’ve made it so simple that an 8 year old could follow the instructions and get ANY website ranked in days.<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://www.mapsmentor.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/mockupdesigns_transparentbackground.png" alt="Maps Mentor 2.0" title="Maps Mentor 2.0"  /><br /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Maps Mentor 2.0" title="Maps Mentor 2.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>