<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Request - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Request - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>iqualif</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4296-request-software.html</link>
<description>hello cant you crack this software ? in french and english , thanks</description>
<category>Request</category>
<pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2018 06:58:49 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>https://www.iqualif.com/en/</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div class="quote"><a href="https://www.iqualif.com/en/"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">https://www.iqualif.com/en/</a></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Flashstuffer</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3975-flashstuffer.html</link>
<description>Flashstuffer can perform FIVE types of cookie-stuffing: Forum stuffing - and YES, it can even blank the referrer! Own page stuffing - stuff cookies using Flash on your own pages, almost impossible to detect. Can even spoof the referrer! 3rd party page stuffing - stuff cookies on other websites that allow you to embed Flash! Can also send a spoofed referrer. Favicon stuffing - a little known stuffing technique that doesn&#039;t require ANY cookie-stuffing code on your page...even sends a blank referrer! Mobile stuffing (BETA) - stuff mobile devices (cellphones, tablets) without Flash.</description>
<category>Request</category>
<pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 15:30:49 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>http://www.flashstuffer.com/specs/</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div class="quote"><a href="http://www.flashstuffer.com/specs/"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">http://www.flashstuffer.com/specs/</a></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Google Site Creator Software</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3787-google-site-creator-software.html</link>
<description>Salespage http://beta.petestrafficsuite.com/trial/ Software will create google sites for SEO rankings.</description>
<category>Request</category>
<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 05:41:19 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Download:</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[Download:<br>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Facebook Messages Manager</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3772-facebook-messages-manager.html</link>
<description>Facebook Page Messages Management Manage all messages in one stream, search &amp;amp; filter for specific individual. Add notes, apply a label for message thread. View messages statistics and analytic. Send messages to all Facebook Page Fans (Likes) with one click. Use this application when you launching a sales promotion, inform a new product, take care of customers, follow up potential client, closing sales. This could help to bring people back to your page and get more value from existing customers (remarketing &amp;amp; retargeting). Messages Manager gives your business a fast and convenient way to connect people. It allows you to build personal connections with your customers. You can easy to keep tracks of conversation between your business and your prospective customer. View all messages. View all messages of Page from beginning until now. Support view full messages of conversation or just the last message. Quick Reply &amp;amp; Reply All. Manual reply, quick reply and reply all helps to send bulk messages or send one by one. Search and Filter. Search for specific individual message, visitor, tags, created date, from date.. to date.. Filter and sorted by alphabetical order, export selected data to file. Manage Labels and Notes. Manage labels and notes in bulk or one by one. For example, assign one label for all selected conversations, filter a group of conversations based on the labels. Facebook Remarketing for FREE. Bring people back to your page and get more value from existing customers (remarketing &amp;amp; retargeting) for free.. 100% Safe &amp;amp; Secure. Using Messages Manager to send messages is 100% safe and secure for your Facebook Page. Common Usage Sending news, productivity updates Sending brand advertising, newsletters, announcements or spam Sending customer support messages Up-selling or cross-selling products or services Confirming bookings, purchases, orders, etc.</description>
<category>Request</category>
<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2017 15:24:42 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text></yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div class="quote"></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Rivercleaner Extension - Amazon Tool</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3768-rivercleaner-extension-amazon-tool.html</link>
<description>Awesome Amazon plugin: RiverCleaner Can you please get this extension, work your magic and crack it for us?</description>
<category>Request</category>
<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 01:19:35 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text></yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div class="quote"></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Power Suggest Pro</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3761-powersuggestpro.html</link>
<description>The Ultimate Keyword &amp;amp; Market Research Tool Uncover far more keywords using 6 major search engines Identify profitable opportunities, niches and product ideas Reveal the desires, needs and pains of any target audience Discover products and services people are looking to buy Generate endless ideas for contents that attract traffic</description>
<category>Request</category>
<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 15:02:18 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text></yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div class="quote"></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Easy Mandala Generator</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1867-easy-mandala-generator.html</link>
<description>Haven’t Heard of the Adult Coloring Book Craze? Here’s a Quick Rundown: 5 MILLION adult coloring books sold in 2015 100k/month Google searches for “adult coloring book” The positives of adult coloring books covered by CNN, The Atlantic, Huffington Post, MSNBC and every other major news outlet Adult coloring books consistently make the “best seller” lists on Amazon, Barnes and Noble, Wal-Mart, Google Play and the iTunes Store</description>
<category>Request</category>
<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 21:02:47 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text></yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div class="quote"></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Lead Finder jack</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1854-biz-lead-finder-9.html</link>
<description>Local Business owners pay this source (a $200 million company) thousands of dollars each and every month to get new customers. This source is a website that lists thousands of local businesses. It is a paid business listing directory and thousands businesses spend between $30 and $100 for each and every referred customer. Biz Lead Finder - THe MAPS ERROR Feature Finds in ONE click thousands Google Maps Errors from those super hot leads. PS: To protect this $200 Million leads source we can&#039;t reveal it here.</description>
<category>Request</category>
<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 20:52:03 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text></yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div class="quote"></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>SMS ilimitado</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3700-sms-ilimitado.html</link>
<description>SMS em Massa Ilimitado Ligue-nos e compre a vers?o correta para o seu neg?cio, n?s te ajudaremos escolher! SMS Simples, com 1, 2 ou at? 20 modens SMS com nome e outras vari?veis para avisos e cobran?as em geral SMS Marketing usando Celulares com Android, envie de qualquer lugar SMS com ?udio, liga, passa e passa o ?udio SMS separado por Operadoras Tim, Oi, Claro, Vivo Pesquisa por SMS com relat?rios em tempo real Escolha o seu e COMPRE AGORA</description>
<category>Request</category>
<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 23:22:40 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text></yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div class="quote"><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>dataenginesoft</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3699-dataenginesoft.html</link>
<description>Justdial Lead Extractor Price INR 5499/Year DownloadBuy Here Demo VideoMore... Justdial Lead Extractor Justdial Lead Extractor Tool can Intelligently Collect Bulk Customer Data for Marketing Purpose. Users Can Collects Thousands of Leads in One Click. Targeted Search for Email Addresses &amp;amp; Contact Number Using Keywords Continue... Indiamart Lead Extractor Indiamart Lead Extractor Price INR 4999/Year DownloadBuy Here Demo VideoMore... Indiamart Lead Extractor Indiamart Lead Extractor Tool can Intelligently Collect Bulk Customer Data for Marketing Purpose. Users Can Collects Thousands of Leads in One Click. Targeted Search for Contact Number Using Keywords Continue... GoogleMap Lead Extractor GoogleMap Lead Extractor Price INR 4999/Year DownloadBuy Here Demo VideoMore... GoogleMap Lead Extractor GoogleMap Lead Extractor Tool can Intelligently Collect Bulk Customer Data for Marketing Purpose. Users Can Collects Thousands of Leads in One Click. Targeted Search for Email Addresses &amp;amp; Contact Number Using Keywords Continue... Sulekha Lead Extractor Sulekha Lead Extractor Price INR 5499/Year DownloadBuy Here Demo VideoMore... Sulekha Lead Extractor Sulekha Lead Extractor Tool can Intelligently Collect Bulk Customer Data for Marketing Purpose. Users Can Collects Thousands of Leads in One Click. Targeted Search for Email Addresses &amp;amp; Contact Number Using Keywords Continue... Whois Lead Extractor Whois Lead Extractor Price INR 4999/Year DownloadBuy Here Demo VideoMore... Whois Lead Extractor Whois Lead Extractor Tool can Intelligently Collect Bulk Customer Data for Marketing Purpose. Users Can Collects Thousands of Leads in One Click. Targeted Search for Email Addresses &amp;amp; Contact Number Using Keywords Continue... Email Verifier Email Verifier Price INR 4999/Year DownloadBuy Here Demo VideoMore... Email Verifier Email Verifier Tool can Intelligently Verify Bulk Email Addresses for Marketing Purpose. Users Can Verify Thousands of Leads in One Click. Targeted Verification of Email Addresses. Your Mail Will Reach Its Destination. More Opens, Clicks, and Sales Continue... Global Lead Extractor Global Lead Extractor Price INR 8999/Year DownloadBuy Here Demo VideoMore... Global Lead Extractor Global Lead Extractor Tool can Intelligently Collect Bulk Customer Data for Marketing Purpose. Users Can Collects Thousands of Leads From Multiple Source in One Click. Targeted Search for Leads Using Keywords Continue... Web Lead Extractor Web Lead Extractor Price INR 4999/Year DownloadBuy Here Demo VideoMore... Web Lead Extractor Web Lead Extractor Tool can Intelligently Collect Bulk Customer Data for Marketing Purpose. Users Can Collects Thousands of Leads in One Click. Targeted Search for Email Addresses &amp;amp; Contact Number Using Keywords Continue... YellowPages Lead Extractor YellowPages Lead Extractor Price INR 4999/Year DownloadBuy Here Demo VideoMore... YellowPages Lead Extractor YellowPages Lead Extractor Tool can Intelligently Collect Bulk Customer Data for Marketing Purpose. Users Can Collects Thousands of Leads in One Click. Targeted Search for Contact Number Using Keywords Continue... Zomatoo Lead Extractor Zomatoo Lead Extractor Price INR 4999/Year DownloadBuy Here Demo VideoMore... Zomatoo Lead Extractor Zomatoo Lead Extractor Tool can Intelligently Collect Bulk Customer Data for Marketing Purpose. Users Can Collects Thousands of Leads in One Click. Targeted Search for Contact Number Using Keywords Continue... Email Extractor File Email Extractor File Price INR 3999/Year DownloadBuy Here Demo VideoMore... Email Extractor File Email Extractor File Tool can Intelligently Extract Bulk Email Addresses for Marketing Purpose. Users Can Extract Thousands of Leads or Customer Email Addresses in One Click. Tool Can Extract Email Addresses From Files Like .CSV .TXT .PDF Continue... Email Extractor Web Email Extractor Web Price INR 4999/Year DownloadBuy Here Demo VideoMore... Email Extractor Web Email Extractor Web Tool can Intelligently Extract Bulk Email Address for Marketing Purpose. Users Can Collects Thousands of Leads or Customer Email Addresses in One Click. Targeted Based Extraction of Email Addresses From Inte.com Continue... Email Sender Bulk Email Sender Bulk Price INR 8999/Year DownloadBuy Here Demo VideoMore... Email Sender Bulk Email Sender Bulk Tool can Send Bulk Emails For Marketing Purpose. Users Can Send Thousands of Emails in One Click. Tool Have Option To Import File Continue... Email Styler Pro Email Styler Pro Price INR 3999/Year DownloadBuy Here Demo VideoMore... Email Styler Pro Email Styler Pro Tool can Help You To Design Email Newsletter Easily. Create Perfect Email Templates with an Intuitive Drag &amp;amp; Drop Editor. No HTML/CSS Skills Required To Create Continue... Mobile Number Generator Mobile Number Generator Price INR 3999/Year DownloadBuy Here Demo VideoMore... Mobile Number Generator Mobile Number Generator Tool can Generate Thousands of Mobile Number for Marketing Purpose. Users Can Generate Thousands of Mobile Numbers in One Click. Tool Can Generate Mobile Numbers With Various Length Like 10 Digit,12 Digit,15 Digit Continue... Mobile Number Checker Mobile Number Checker Price INR 4999/Year DownloadBuy Here Demo VideoMore... Mobile Number Checker Mobile Number Checker Tool can Intelligently Check Network Provider Name, State for Marketing Purpose. Users Can Check Thousands of Mobile Number in One Click. Tool Have Option To Save Processed Mobile Numbers into CSV File Continue... Mobile Number Extractor Web Mobile Number Extractor Web Price INR 4999/Year DownloadBuy Here Demo VideoMore... Mobile Number Extractor Web Mobile Number Extractor Web Tool can Extract Thousands of Mobile Number for Marketing Purpose. Users Can Extract Thousands of Mobile Numbers in One Click. Tool Can Extract Mobile Numbers From Web Continue... Mobile Number Extractor File Mobile Number Extractor File Price INR 3999/Year DownloadBuy Here Demo VideoMore... Mobile Number Extractor File Mobile Number Extractor File Tool can Extract Mobile Numbers For Marketing Purpose. Users Can Extract Thousands of Mobile Numbers in One Click. Tool Have Option To Import File Continue... SMS Sender Bulk SMS Sender Bulk Price INR 6999/Year DownloadBuy Here Demo VideoMore... SMS Sender Bulk SMS Sender Bulk Tool can Intelligently Send Bulk SMS To Recipient. Users Can Send Thousands of SMS in One Click. Tool Have Option To Import File Continue... Proxy Grabber Proxy Grabber Price INR 3999/Year DownloadBuy Here Demo VideoMore... Proxy Grabber Proxy Grabber Tool can Intelligently Collect Proxy Addresses From Multiple Sources. Users Can Collect Thousands of Proxy Addresses in One Click. Tool Also Help You to Filter Active Proxy Continue... Youtube Ranker Youtube Ranker Price INR 5999/Year DownloadBuy Here Demo VideoMore... Youtube Ranker Youtube Ranker Tool can Create Perfectly Optimized Video Titles,Descriptions &amp;amp; Tags for Your Videos. Helps You Select the Right Keywords,Best Description &amp;amp; Tags to Get You Perfect Optimization Every Time. Tool Have Intelligent Scoring System &amp;amp; Suggestions Based Makes Highly Optimized Videos Continue... Youtube Traffic Pro Youtube Traffic Pro Price INR 6999/Year DownloadBuy Here Demo VideoMore... Youtube Traffic Pro Youtube Traffic Pro Tool can Able to Address Very Specific &amp;amp; Compelling Problems That You Need to Resolve On A Daily Basis. Users Have Total Control Over Youtube Channels And Monitor How Your Videos And Continue... Youtube Engage Pro Youtube Engage Pro Price INR 5999/Year DownloadBuy Here Demo VideoMore... Youtube Engage Pro Youtube Engage Pro Tool can Help You to Engaging Your Users And Your Competitor&#039;S Userbase. Monitor An Exhaustive List Of Channels,Videos &amp;amp; Comments With An Easy Scroll Continue... SEO Keywords Pro SEO Keywords Pro Price INR 6999/Year DownloadBuy Here Demo VideoMore... SEO Keywords Pro SEO Keywords Pro Tool Helps You Find The Keywords That People Are Typing Into Google Search Box. Determine Keyword Profitability with New Rank Value Feature. Help You to Keyword Competitiveness Score &amp;amp;</description>
<category>Request</category>
<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2017 23:57:25 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text></yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div class="quote"></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>