<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Backlink Checker - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Backlink Checker - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>Keyword Link Spy 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4223-keyword-link-spy.html</link>
<description>Name : Keyword Link Spy Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Keyword Link Spy Tool Price : $59 Homepage : SalePage Keyword Link Spy is a desktop tool that will allow users to find the backlinks that your top 100 competitors are using to rank for specific keywords. Simply enter your keyword such as &quot;dog training&quot; and Keyword Link Spy will show you all the backlinks linking to the organic results for &quot;dog training&quot;.</description>
<category>Backlink Checker</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2018 21:52:42 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features When you click &quot;Start Search&quot; Keyword Link Spy takes all your entered keyword(s) and goes off to Google and searches these keywords, it then takes each of the results (up to 100 results / webpages) and sees what backlinks are linking directly to each of these organic search results. This backlink search on the Google results is powered by the MOZ API, you simply need to enter your MOZ API key. Which is 100% free to obtain, you simply create an account with them and click generate API keys.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/oLvIomLEVA0?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> When you click "Start Search" Keyword Link Spy takes all your entered keyword(s) and goes off to Google and searches these keywords, it then takes each of the results (up to 100 results / webpages) and sees what backlinks are linking directly to each of these organic search results. This backlink search on the Google results is powered by the MOZ API, you simply need to enter your MOZ API key. Which is 100% free to obtain, you simply create an account with them and click generate API keys.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Keyword Link Spy 1.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Backlink Checker 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4229-backlink-checker.html</link>
<description>Name : Backlink Checker Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Backlink Tool Price : $59 Homepage : SalePage Backlink Checker is a desktop tool the allows website owners or SEO&#039;s to check a websites backlink profile. It is powered through the MOZ API (which is free to use). You simply enter the web properties (domains / webpages) you want to see the backlinks for and the tool will fire off requests to the MOZ API fetching all the known websites / webpages linking to those web properties.</description>
<category>Backlink Checker</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2018 21:51:26 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features This tool is powered by the MOZ backlink crawler. Which current has around 190 Billion URLs, 317 Million Domains and 2 Trillion Links in its index. When you click start in the background the tool fires off requests to the MOZ API which returns all the links for your entered web properties. Web properties are just webpages and domains. Once we get a response back from the MOZ API we display the results in the results grid. There are a few options that we&#039;ll explain below. Tool options - Fetch MOZ DA and PA - With this setting the tool will also query the moz api for the backlink&#039;s domain authority (DA) and page authority (PA) so you can assess how much of an impact its having on ranking the target web property (webpage or website). - Fetch NoFollow links - By default this tool will fetch only dofollow links, however if this option is selected it will return all links regardless of their nofollow / dofollow link attributes - Fetch links for entire domain - By detault if you were to enter www.supagrowth.com this tool would only return links pointing to the root domain (www.supagrowth.com) however if you select this option it will return all links pointing to the domain regardless of their target URL. For example links pointing to www.supagrowth.com/about would be returned as well as any links pointing to www.supagrowth.com.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/jkkYSourutA?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> This tool is powered by the MOZ backlink crawler. Which current has around 190 Billion URLs, 317 Million Domains and 2 Trillion Links in its index. When you click start in the background the tool fires off requests to the MOZ API which returns all the links for your entered web properties. Web properties are just webpages and domains. Once we get a response back from the MOZ API we display the results in the results grid. There are a few options that we'll explain below.<br></li><li> Tool options<br></li><li> - Fetch MOZ DA and PA - With this setting the tool will also query the moz api for the backlink's domain authority (DA) and page authority (PA) so you can assess how much of an impact its having on ranking the target web property (webpage or website).<br></li><li> - Fetch NoFollow links - By default this tool will fetch only dofollow links, however if this option is selected it will return all links regardless of their nofollow / dofollow link attributes<br></li><li> - Fetch links for entire domain - By detault if you were to enter www.supagrowth.com this tool would only return links pointing to the root domain (www.supagrowth.com) however if you select this option it will return all links pointing to the domain regardless of their target URL. For example links pointing to www.supagrowth.com/about would be returned as well as any links pointing to www.supagrowth.com.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Backlink Checker 1.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Bad Neighborhood Checker 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3726-bad-neighborhood-checker.html</link>
<description>Name : Bad Neighborhood Checker Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Backlink Checker Price : $0 Homepage : SalePage When you host a website your domaain name has to resolve to an IP address so your computer can connect to that IP address and load the websites contents. If you host your website on shared hosting then you will be sharing the same IP with serveral other websites. Anywhere from 10-10000. Also even if you don&#039;t have shared hosting there is a strong chance that the dedicated IP address will of been used by a website your hosting provider was using before you used it for your website. How do you know these websites weren&#039;t hosting Malware or spammy websites that have been deindexed by Google? This is what Bad Neighborhood Checker can tell you. How much do you know about the websites you&#039;re sharing an IP address with? Probably very little. Are they hosting malware? Are they hosting thousands of auto generated spun content? Have they been deindexed by Google? Bad Neighborhood Checker can provide you with the valuable information you need about your IP address neighbors to decide if you need to move or not.</description>
<category>Backlink Checker</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 05:27:16 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>[media=https://youtu.be/u2akhaX46m8] Features How Bad Neighborhood Checker works Everytime the search engine Bing crawls a website it remembers the IP address its hosted on. Using advanced search modifiers we can scrape a list of websites that are sharing the same IP address as your website currently does. Once we have this information we can then run checks on the website to see if you really want to be sharing an IP address with that website. For example Bad Neighborhood Checker will check the website for malware, foreign content, spammy content farm, cloaking and if its been deindexed by Google. Why should I use Bad Neighborhood Checker? You never know who you&#039;re sharing an IP address with or who owned it before you if its a brand new website. So its always best to check. For example you may of just thought you got a great deal on some super cheap hosting but so did someone who wants to host their PBN there. So you end up sharing an IP address with 30 PBN websites. Now when they all get deindexed there is a strong chance Google may decide to automatically deindex your website too! Unfair I know, but Google is very &quot;proactive&quot; in its anti-spam algorithms these days. So why take the chance?</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;">[media=https://youtu.be/u2akhaX46m8]</div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br>How Bad Neighborhood Checker works<br>Everytime the search engine Bing crawls a website it remembers the IP address its hosted on. Using advanced search modifiers we can scrape a list of websites that are sharing the same IP address as your website currently does. Once we have this information we can then run checks on the website to see if you really want to be sharing an IP address with that website. For example Bad Neighborhood Checker will check the website for malware, foreign content, spammy content farm, cloaking and if its been deindexed by Google.<br><br>Why should I use Bad Neighborhood Checker?<br>You never know who you're sharing an IP address with or who owned it before you if its a brand new website. So its always best to check. For example you may of just thought you got a great deal on some super cheap hosting but so did someone who wants to host their PBN there. So you end up sharing an IP address with 30 PBN websites. Now when they all get deindexed there is a strong chance Google may decide to automatically deindex your website too! Unfair I know, but Google is very "proactive" in its anti-spam algorithms these days. So why take the chance?<br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Bad Neighborhood Checker 1.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Broken Link Finder 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3717-broken-link-finder.html</link>
<description>Name : Broken Link Finder Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Link Finder Price : $0 Homepage : SalePage We all know links power your website up the search engine rankings and its very tempting to break the Google webmaster guidelines and buy links or spam links. However this can very risky and may get your website delisted on Google. So if you&#039;re looking for a legit whitehat risk free way of getting links to your website a broken link campaign is a great option.</description>
<category>Backlink Checker</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 07:12:51 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>[media=https://youtu.be/7GOL_g9RmGk] Features What are broken links? Broken links are website hyperlinks that do not find their chosen website target. For example, a link on bbc.co.uk that points to boref.com instead of bored.com would be a broken backlink as boref.com does not exist. Another example would be if a website on bbc.co.uk was pointing to google.com/missingWebPage.html. If missingWebPage.html has been removed by Google then this would result in a 404 error and another broken backlink. How does a broken link campaign work? Once you find a broken backlink on a website that you like the look of you simply email the website owner and inform them that they have a broken link and that you have some relevant content to replace this link. You won&#039;t always get a nice new shiny link but over time you will get good results and whats more important is these types of links are safe, you haven&#039;t broken the Google webmaster guidelines in anyway. How does broken link finder work? You have two options in broken backlink finder. Firstly you can enter a single website or list of websites that you want to crawl and try and find broken links on. Or secondly you can enter your keywords you&#039;re trying to rank for and the software will grab as many websites ranking for those search terms as you want and then crawl those.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;">[media=https://youtu.be/7GOL_g9RmGk]</div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br>What are broken links?<br>Broken links are website hyperlinks that do not find their chosen website target. For example, a link on bbc.co.uk that points to boref.com instead of bored.com would be a broken backlink as boref.com does not exist. Another example would be if a website on bbc.co.uk was pointing to google.com/missingWebPage.html. If missingWebPage.html has been removed by Google then this would result in a 404 error and another broken backlink.<br><br>How does a broken link campaign work?<br>Once you find a broken backlink on a website that you like the look of you simply email the website owner and inform them that they have a broken link and that you have some relevant content to replace this link. You won't always get a nice new shiny link but over time you will get good results and whats more important is these types of links are safe, you haven't broken the Google webmaster guidelines in anyway.<br>How does broken link finder work?<br>You have two options in broken backlink finder. Firstly you can enter a single website or list of websites that you want to crawl and try and find broken links on. Or secondly you can enter your keywords you're trying to rank for and the software will grab as many websites ranking for those search terms as you want and then crawl those.<br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Broken Link Finder 1.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Link Monitor 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3718-link-monitor.html</link>
<description>Name : Link Monitor Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : BackLink Monitor Price : $0 Homepage : SalePage Link Monitor automates the tasks of checking if your backlinks have been changed/deleted or new ones have being placed on specified webpages.</description>
<category>Backlink Checker</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 07:10:44 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>[media=https://youtu.be/AAqYV06daB0] Features How does Link Monitor work? Once your website URL and the URL of pages where your backlinks exist have been added to Link Monitor you can check the status of every single link to your website with the click of a single button. When that single button is clicked Link Monitor will download the HTML for each page and check your links. You can even schedule checks to automatically check for you at set times or intervals. Any different types of notification are included such as tray balloons, audio notifications and URL loads. Why should I use Link Monitor? Cloud based services such as ahrefs and MOZ will check your websites backlink profile but they will not check daily. So if you&#039;ve purchased a nice expensive powerful link and the webmaster accidentally removes it you may not be notified by these cloud crawlers for weeks and by then this change could of damaged your websites rankings. Link Monitor can check every few minutes. Not to mention the cost savings! Link Monitor is 100% free. Missing links to your website New links to your website Changed links to your website (nofollow and many others) Outbound link increases/decreases on pages</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;">[media=https://youtu.be/AAqYV06daB0]</div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br>How does Link Monitor work?<br>Once your website URL and the URL of pages where your backlinks exist have been added to Link Monitor you can check the status of every single link to your website with the click of a single button. When that single button is clicked Link Monitor will download the HTML for each page and check your links. You can even schedule checks to automatically check for you at set times or intervals. Any different types of notification are included such as tray balloons, audio notifications and URL loads.<br>Why should I use Link Monitor?<br>Cloud based services such as ahrefs and MOZ will check your websites backlink profile but they will not check daily. So if you've purchased a nice expensive powerful link and the webmaster accidentally removes it you may not be notified by these cloud crawlers for weeks and by then this change could of damaged your websites rankings. Link Monitor can check every few minutes. Not to mention the cost savings! Link Monitor is 100% free.<br>Missing links to your website<br>New links to your website<br>Changed links to your website (nofollow and many others)<br>Outbound link increases/decreases on pages<br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Link Monitor 1.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Outbound Link Checker 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3724-outbound-link-checker.html</link>
<description>Name : Outbound Link Checker Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Backlink Checker Price : $59 Homepage : SalePage Outbound Link Checker crawls your entire website checking all your outbound links for any reason you wouldn&#039;t want to link to any of your outbound websites. Checks include adult, foreign, cloaking, deindexed or servering up malware and much more. Linking to these types of websites can seriously damage your rankings. Outbound Link Checker is a very simple tool to use. You simply enter your websites domain and it will crawl every page looking for outbound links. Once it has an outbound link it will check for any reason you might not want to be linking to this website. For example has it being hacked and its serving up Malware? Has it being deindexed by Google?</description>
<category>Backlink Checker</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 07:05:48 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>[media=https://youtu.be/R4Nu01iXdRc] Features Why should I use Outbound Link Checker? Google is smart and when you consider how much money they invest in maintaining quality search results do you think they&#039;re going to want to server up your website when you&#039;re linking to a hacked website hosting malware or linking to a website they&#039;ve just deinxeded because its part of a PBN. Have you checked all those webstes you&#039;re linking with to see if they&#039;ve expired and being turned into a spammy PBN? Probably not, because thats a massive task. But with Outbound Link Checker it takes about 3 seconds to start the you just let it run and investigate anything it flags up.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;">[media=https://youtu.be/R4Nu01iXdRc]</div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br>Why should I use Outbound Link Checker?<br>Google is smart and when you consider how much money they invest in maintaining quality search results do you think they're going to want to server up your website when you're linking to a hacked website hosting malware or linking to a website they've just deinxeded because its part of a PBN. Have you checked all those webstes you're linking with to see if they've expired and being turned into a spammy PBN? Probably not, because thats a massive task. But with Outbound Link Checker it takes about 3 seconds to start the you just let it run and investigate anything it flags up.<br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Outbound Link Checker 1.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Bad Link Buster 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3725-bad-link-buster.html</link>
<description>Name : Bad Link Buster Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : BackLink Checker Price : $0 Homepage : SalePage Bad Link Buster checks your baclink profile for any websites that you wouldn&#039;t want a link from. These websites might be adult, foreign, cloaking, deindexed or servering up malware. Simply load in your backlink profile and Bad Link Buster will start doing all the hard work for you. Bad Link Buster is a free tool that allows you to find baclinks in your backlink profile that might be damaging your search engine rankings.</description>
<category>Backlink Checker</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 07:05:00 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>[media=https://youtu.be/L6dC0NK9mpg] Features How Bad Link Buster works Bad Link Buster is very simple to use. You simply enter your domain name then load in a line seperated list of your backlinks and bad link buster will check each link for any issues that might be causing you problems. These include Malware websites, deindexed websites, foreign websites, content farms, cloaking websites and more. Why should I use Bad Link Buster? There are many ways you may have ended up with bad links in your backlink profile. Purchased an expired domain name that has bad links already pointing at it A Negative SEO attack on your website Purchased blackhat SEO services All of these can cause major issues. You may even end up with your website being deindexed if a negative SEO attack is not dealt with swiftly. Maintaining a clean high quality backlink profile says to google &quot;This is a website you can trust&quot;.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;">[media=https://youtu.be/L6dC0NK9mpg]</div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br>How Bad Link Buster works<br>Bad Link Buster is very simple to use. You simply enter your domain name then load in a line seperated list of your backlinks and bad link buster will check each link for any issues that might be causing you problems. These include Malware websites, deindexed websites, foreign websites, content farms, cloaking websites and more.<br><br>Why should I use Bad Link Buster?<br>There are many ways you may have ended up with bad links in your backlink profile.<br><br>Purchased an expired domain name that has bad links already pointing at it<br>A Negative SEO attack on your website<br>Purchased blackhat SEO services<br>All of these can cause major issues. You may even end up with your website being deindexed if a negative SEO attack is not dealt with swiftly. Maintaining a clean high quality backlink profile says to google "This is a website you can trust".<br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Bad Link Buster 1.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Inspyder Backlink Monitor 5.1.5</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1683-inspyder-backlink-monitor.html</link>
<description>Name : Inspyder Backlink Monitor Version : 5.1.5 Standard OS : Windows Type : Backlink Management Tool Price : $79 Homepage : SalePage Backlink Monitor 5 - The world&#039;s only multi-tier backlink management software! Tracking your tiers couldn&#039;t be easier. Backlink Monitor is the easiest way to track and manage your website backlinks. Just enter your backlink URLs and let Backlink Monitor check the status, anchor text, IP address and PageRank for you. It couldn’t be easier. Best of all, Backlink Monitor works with multiple backlink tiers! Stop working hard and start working smart with Backlink Monitor. Backlink Monitor is designed to be used along side your day-to-day link building activities. As you build backlinks you’ll paste the new links into the main Backlink URLs list. You always want to be adding to this list (never remove from it directly, except by using the “Remove Dead Backlinks” option). This way, it becomes your master list of working backlinks that have an SEO influence. It becomes particularly valuable during multi-tier link building because it finds and removes broken tiers, so you won’t waste time building new links to pages that don’t influence your website’s ranking.</description>
<category>Backlink Checker</category>
<enclosure url="https://www.inspyder.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/backlink-monitor-screenshot-2.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2017 05:03:15 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Easy to Use : Just enter your website URL, your backlink URLs and click “Go”. It couldn’t be easier! Multi-Tier Backlink Checking : Enter all your backlink URLs and let Backlink Monitor sort out the hierarchy Check PageRank : Backlink Monitor automatically determines Google PageRank for each domain and backlink page Check Indexed Status : Backlink Monitor can also check in Google’s index to see if your backlinks are included Low Cost, No Limits : Backlink Monitor has a low one-time cost, no matter how many backlinks you have or how often you use it! Indexing Service Integration : Submit your backlinks to the most popular indexing services directly from Backlink Monitor Scheduled Reports : Configure Backlink Monitor to check-up your backlinks daily, weekly or monthly and email you the results CSV Reports : Export Backlink Monitor’s results to CSV for Excel or input into other SEO tools Backlink Index Checker Backlink PageRank Checker Bulk Backlink Checker Monitor Website Backlinks</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><div class="dlevideoplayer" style="width:100%;max-width:425px;"><ul data-theme="default" data-preload="metadata"><li data-title="" data-type="youtube" data-url="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=C2Wce84tIqQ"></li></ul></div></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Easy to Use : Just enter your website URL, your backlink URLs and click “Go”. It couldn’t be easier!<br></li><li> Multi-Tier Backlink Checking : Enter all your backlink URLs and let Backlink Monitor sort out the hierarchy<br></li><li> Check PageRank : Backlink Monitor automatically determines Google PageRank for each domain and backlink page<br></li><li> Check Indexed Status : Backlink Monitor can also check in Google’s index to see if your backlinks are included<br></li><li> Low Cost, No Limits : Backlink Monitor has a low one-time cost, no matter how many backlinks you have or how often you use it!<br></li><li> Indexing Service Integration : Submit your backlinks to the most popular indexing services directly from Backlink Monitor<br></li><li> Scheduled Reports : Configure Backlink Monitor to check-up your backlinks daily, weekly or monthly and email you the results<br></li><li> CSV Reports : Export Backlink Monitor’s results to CSV for Excel or input into other SEO tools<br></li><li> Backlink Index Checker<br></li><li> Backlink PageRank Checker<br></li><li> Bulk Backlink Checker<br></li><li> Monitor Website Backlinks<br></li></ul><br><img src="https://www.inspyder.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/backlink-monitor-screenshot-2.png" alt="Inspyder Backlink Monitor 5.1.5"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>RA BackLink Checker 1.1</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1957-ra-backlink-checker.html</link>
<description>Name : RA BackLink Checker Version : 1.1 OS : Windows Type : BackLink Checker Tools Price : $30 Homepage : SalePage RA BackLink Checker is used to get / check your backlinks info which includes Backlink Url, Host Status, Inbound Link, Outbound Links, Follow Status, PageRank, Anchor Text, Backlink IP, Google Index Status and so on. You can easily export the extracted backlink information into CSV or TSV. RA BackLink Checker is light weight, designed &amp; developed with user friendly interface which everyone can use without guidance. Every search engine analyst must aware that the backbone of search engine optimization is building quality backlink especially for major search engine share holder Google. By monitoring your backlink details with this RA BackLink Checker for your domain periodically you can modify your backlink strategy and also it will help to customize for your backlink techniques. RA BackLink Checker was specially designed for every search engine analyst, search engine marketer and all online marketers who looking for smart backlink analyzer.</description>
<category>Backlink Checker</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.reverseapps.com/backlink-checker/screenshots/main-window.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2016 18:01:44 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Import from text file or Clipboard Automatic Backlink Duplicate &amp; Invalid URL Product Support Proxy Settings Update Notification Export</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/29cUXdgrwTY?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Import from text file or Clipboard 			<br /></li><li> Automatic Backlink 			<br /></li><li> Duplicate & Invalid URL 			<br /></li><li> Product Support 			<br /></li><li> Proxy Settings 			<br /></li><li> Update Notification 			<br /></li><li> Export <br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://www.reverseapps.com/backlink-checker/screenshots/main-window.png" alt="RA BackLink Checker 1.1" title="RA BackLink Checker 1.1"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="RA BackLink Checker 1.1" title="RA BackLink Checker 1.1"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Fast Link Checker 2.2 Build.608</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1014-fast-link-checker.html</link>
<description>Name : Fast Link Checker Version : 2.2 Build.608 OS : Windows Type : Misc Price : $99 Homepage : SalePage Fast Link Checker is a tool used for searching sites for broken links. It begins checking from the starting page and goes through all pages one by one until it checks all links on the site. If Fast Link Checker finds a broken link, it shows its position in the document, the cause why it does not work and a hint how it can be fixed. Fast Link Checker can check links to all pages both on current and external sites, the availability of documents, images, scripts, style sheets and other objects linked to pages. It can check links on the entire site, on one of its pages or in one directory. Fast Link Checker can check links in files available via the HTTP, HTTPS, FTP, FTPS and RTSP protocols on sites hosted by any properly configured web server. Furthermore, Fast Link Checker supports password-protected sites and FILE protocol, which allows checking links in HTML files without accessing a web server</description>
<category>Backlink Checker</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2015 00:43:35 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Small and easy to use : Yes. Fast Link Checker doesn&#039;t take much of server&#039;s resources. It can be run as a standalone application without any user&#039;s interference. The scope of its activities includes link checking internal and external websites. Each component such as script, image or stylesheet can be checked separately. Fast Link Checker is utilizing a one of a kind algorithm which allows multi-threading tasks at the same time. This results in faster processing and drastically improves effectiveness. Provides user-friendly reports on found broken links : Everything given like on a tray! Fast Link Checker saves detailed reports about numerous things. Everything regarding performed scan. Reports can be remotely saved in various file formats. From excel through xml to plain text. Reports can be generated for the entire website or just single pages. Generates Site Layout or Site Map during site check activities : Fast Link Checker saves special site layout or site map which helps end-user in understanding the content structure as well as improves better understanding of broken link directory. Allows saving reports to a file or sending them by email : Fast Link Checker offers diversity in the way user wants the reports to be generated. When the software finishes the scanning process it generates a report which then can be saved on user&#039;s computer or sent to a specified email adress. The reports come in multiple file formats such as html files, excel files, tables with advanced filtering system or just plain text. Checks links to pages on both current and external sites : Our software can scan the inbound links within website as well as hyperlinks to external resources or websites. All that just on a single snap of your fingers. Checks links on the entire site, on one of its pages or in one directory : When we were designing Fast Link Checker, our aim was to create a software elastic and effective. We&#039;re proud to announce that both of these goals have been achieved. Fast Link Checker allows users to pick only particular directories, one of the website&#039;s pages or entire website during the scanning process. Checks all static and dynamic HTML pages : It doesn&#039;t matter if your webpage is a static page with never changing content or a one with dynamically generated elements, Fast Link Checker will take care of all the hard work. Checks links in files available via the HTTP, HTTPS, FTP and FILE protocols : Fast Link Checker can check links available via the HTTP, HTTPS, FTP, FTPS and RTSP protocols on sites hosted by any properly configured web server. This means increased flexibility. Checks links in password-protected files and directories : Password protected sites are not a problem for Fast Link Checker. It supports the several HTTP authorization methods. Checks links to media content broadcasted through RTSP protocol : Videos, images, sliders and other media content can be easily scanned by Fast Link Checker through special RTSP protocol. Downloads and checks several pages at a time : Multi-threading is one of the best parts of Fast Link Checker. Sophisticated algorithm guards the fast processing time as well as allows the program to perform multiple scanning operations at the same time. Supports lots of the most common charsets : Fast Link Checker is characterized by it&#039;s ability to easily adapt to different scanning situations. It&#039;s ready to handle most common charsets. Customizable user-agent identification, identifies itself in the user-agent field so you can see its visits in your log : No more confusion! See when Fast Link Checker have performed a broken link scan as well as determine what directories did he scanned. Obeys voluntary robot guidelines, including the robots.txt standard for exclusion of files : The software understands and respects the guidelines included in robots.txt file which means that it won&#039;t scan those directories that are excluded from indexing. Supports HTTP and SOCKS proxy servers : Fast Link Checker can work through proxy servers. It supports HTTP and SOCKS type of proxy servers. Includes command line tool that can be launched from the command line or from batch files : Our program can work as a standalone application or be triggered from batch files. It&#039;s command line tool preserves server&#039;s resources. Free Basic Technical Support by email : Our free support won&#039;t let you down. We&#039;re avaible at any time, whenever a problem occurs. Software update and additional support services are provided on the subscription basis.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/Oa8nihC5LYw?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> <b>Small and easy to use</b> : Yes. Fast Link Checker doesn't take much of server's resources. It can be run as a standalone application without any user's interference. The scope of its activities includes link checking internal and external websites. Each component such as script, image or stylesheet can be checked separately. Fast Link Checker is utilizing a one of a kind algorithm which allows multi-threading tasks at the same time. This results in faster processing and drastically improves effectiveness.<br /></li><li> <b>Provides user-friendly reports on found broken links</b> : Everything given like on a tray! Fast Link Checker saves detailed reports about numerous things. Everything regarding performed scan. Reports can be remotely saved in various file formats. From excel through xml to plain text. Reports can be generated for the entire website or just single pages.<br /></li><li> <b>Generates Site Layout or Site Map during site check activities</b> : Fast Link Checker saves special site layout or site map which helps end-user in understanding the content structure as well as improves better understanding of broken link directory. <br /></li><li> <b>Allows saving reports to a file or sending them by email</b> : Fast Link Checker offers diversity in the way user wants the reports to be generated. When the software finishes the scanning process it generates a report which then can be saved on user's computer or sent to a specified email adress. The reports come in multiple file formats such as html files, excel files, tables with advanced filtering system or just plain text. <br /></li><li> <b>Checks links to pages on both current and external sites</b> : Our software can scan the inbound links within website as well as hyperlinks to external resources or websites. All that just on a single snap of your fingers. <br /></li><li> <b>Checks links on the entire site, on one of its pages or in one directory</b> : When we were designing Fast Link Checker, our aim was to create a software elastic and effective. We're proud to announce that both of these goals have been achieved. Fast Link Checker allows users to pick only particular directories, one of the website's pages or entire website during the scanning process. <br /></li><li> <b>Checks all static and dynamic HTML pages</b> : It doesn't matter if your webpage is a static page with never changing content or a one with dynamically generated elements, Fast Link Checker will take care of all the hard work.<br /></li><li> <b>Checks links in files available via the HTTP, HTTPS, FTP and FILE protocols</b> : Fast Link Checker can check links available via the HTTP, HTTPS, FTP, FTPS and RTSP protocols on sites hosted by any properly configured web server. This means increased flexibility. <br /></li><li> <b>Checks links in password-protected files and directories</b> : Password protected sites are not a problem for Fast Link Checker. It supports the several HTTP authorization methods. <br /></li><li> <b>Checks links to media content broadcasted through RTSP protocol</b> : Videos, images, sliders and other media content can be easily scanned by Fast Link Checker through special RTSP protocol. <br /></li><li> <b>Downloads and checks several pages at a time</b> : Multi-threading is one of the best parts of Fast Link Checker. Sophisticated algorithm guards the fast processing time as well as allows the program to perform multiple scanning operations at the same time. <br /></li><li> <b>Supports lots of the most common charsets</b> : Fast Link Checker is characterized by it's ability to easily adapt to different scanning situations. It's ready to handle most common charsets. <br /></li><li> <b>Customizable user-agent identification, identifies itself in the user-agent field so you can see its visits in your log</b> : No more confusion! See when Fast Link Checker have performed a broken link scan as well as determine what directories did he scanned. <br /></li><li> <b>Obeys voluntary robot guidelines, including the robots.txt standard for exclusion of files</b> : The software understands and respects the guidelines included in robots.txt file which means that it won't scan those directories that are excluded from indexing.<br /></li><li> <b>Supports HTTP and SOCKS proxy servers</b> : Fast Link Checker can work through proxy servers. It supports HTTP and SOCKS type of proxy servers.<br /></li><li> <b>Includes command line tool that can be launched from the command line or from batch files</b> : Our program can work as a standalone application or be triggered from batch files. It's command line tool preserves server's resources. <br /></li><li> <b>Free Basic Technical Support by email</b> : Our free support won't let you down. We're avaible at any time, whenever a problem occurs. Software update and additional support services are provided on the subscription basis.<br /></li></ul><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Fast Link Checker 2.2 Build.608" title="Fast Link Checker 2.2 Build.608"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>