<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>AutoBlog Plugins - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>AutoBlog Plugins - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>Wordpress Automatic 3.37.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/835-wordpress-automatic.html</link>
<description>Name : Wordpress Automatic Plugin Version : 3.37.0 Type : AutoBlog Plugin Price : $17 Homepage : SalePage Wordpress automatic plugin posts quality targeted articles, Amazon Products, Clickbank Products, Youtube Videos, Feeds posts, eBay auctions and Flicker images on auto-pilot. just install and leave, it will work 24/7* to blog for you .</description>
<category>AutoBlog Plugins</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 16:04:22 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Auto post articles to wordpress. plugin can search ezinearticles.com for your specified keywords &amp;amp; post quality matched articles on auto-pilot. Auto post content from Feeds. plugin can check your specified feeds regularly &amp;amp; post every new feed item as a new post. Fetch full content from summary feeds. Wordpress automatic can convert truncated feeds to full content posts with a big success ratio . Extract specific parts of original feeds posts. Wordpress automatic can extract two specified parts of the original post by id or class concat them to post to your wordpress. Auto post amazon products to wordpress. wordpress automatic can search amazon.com or amazon.co.uk , amazon.ca , amazon.de , amazon.fr and amazon.jp for products matching your keywords, post them and add your affiliate links automatically so you can make commissions from products sold via your referrals. just visit findbrowsenodes.com and get the node id.add your specified node and the plugin will limit searching on this node. Auto post Clickbank products to wordpress. wordpress automatic plugin can search clickbank.com for products matching your specified keywords, post to your blog and add your affiliate links automatically. Auto post Youtube videos to wordpress. wordpress automatic can search youtube.com for videos matching your keywords and post them to your wordpress blog* (all languages now supported) Auto post videos from specific youtube channel/user to wordpress . you can automatically add channel videos to wordpress. you have the option to add videos from a specific user/channel by searching for specific keywords or without filtering. Auto post eBay auctions to wordpress. wordpress automatic plugin can post ebay.com auctions for keywords you specify. you can also post from a specific eBay seller by searching his items for specified keywords or even without filtering. - Supported ebay sites: US, IE, AT, AU, BE, CA, FR, IT, DE, ES, CH , UK , NL Auto post Flicker images to wordpress. wordpress automatic plugin can post flicker.com images for keywords you specify. it also can post from a specific flicker user by searching this user items for specified keywords or without filtering. Automatic ads insertion. you can specify two ads slots to be inserted automatically to the posts. Campaign based. you can setup unlimited number of campaigns with different keywords &amp;amp; different post options and these campaigns will work together to post to your site. Post to specific category. you can set what category to add the new posts to one category per campaign. Post using a specific author. you can choose the new post author one author per campaign. Post keywords as tags. plugin can post keywords as wordpress tags. Custom post types support . plugin can post to your custom post type like woo-commerce product. Auto hyperlink keywords . plugin can automatically hyperlink specified keywords with your affiliate link or any specified link. Automatically set wordpress featured image. plugin can auto set post featured image from the first image in the post content. Cache images to your server. plugin can cache images to the server and change their links to your site link. Choose must exist words and phrases. you can specify words that must be in the wordpress post content. Execlude words and phrases. you can set words and phrases that must not be in the wordpress post content. Translate the content before posting . you can set the plugin to automatically translate the content before posting using Google translate. You can set it to translate it twice. Automatically add custom fields to new posts . you can set the plugin to add custom fields to the posted posts automatically these fields can contain any info from the post added like title, author ,content , image , price , rating .. etc . Allowed tags are listed automatically to choose from and differs for each campaign type. Auto search and replace support. The plugin can search the content before posting for your specified words and replace them. keyword suggestion. Writing the first letters of the keyword lists all keywords starting with this letter to choose from. Support for automatic content spin using the best spinner. the best spinner (thebestspinner.com) takes the article and replace synonyms using it&#039;s synonyms database to create 100% unique article. Support posts templates. the content of the post can be formed in different formats by using tags like [post_content] , [post_title],[product_price].. etc. supported tags differ for each campaign and listed atutomatically to choose from. set &amp;amp; forget cron job. to post every specific interval you specify for each campaign in the form of (days/hours/minutes). Internal cron job. wordpress automatic supports posting automatically based on the internal wordpress cron job. Two post status. you can set new post status to draft or published. Unlimited keywords. you can add unlimited keywords per campaign. when the campaign start being processed these keywords will be used one by one to get the content so if the first keyword is exhaused or no more having matches the second one will be used. Automatic keyword hyper-linking. automatic hyper-link matched keyword with specified link Spintax enabled. like awesome. you can use this form in the post content and only one word will be chosen in the final article randomly. Automatic link stripping. option to strip all links from the original content before posting. Wordpress multi-site.comwork support. plugin can be installed in multi-site wordpress installation and function properly in each zombie blog. proxy support.web proxies can be used by the plugin on the form ip:port Wordpress.Automatic.Plugin.3.27.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Wordpress.Automatic.Plugin.3.27.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Wordpress.Automatic.Plugin.3.27.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Wordpress.Automatic.Plugin.3.27.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Wordpress.Automatic.Plugin.3.27.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<p><br></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/flkTFMS4tXI?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><p><br></p><br><h3>Features</h3><br><p><br><ul><li> Auto post articles to wordpress. plugin can search ezinearticles.com for your specified keywords &amp; post quality matched articles on auto-pilot.<br></li><li> Auto post content from Feeds. plugin can check your specified feeds regularly &amp; post every new feed item as a new post.<br></li><li> Fetch full content from summary feeds. Wordpress automatic can convert truncated feeds to full content posts with a big success ratio .<br></li><li> Extract specific parts of original feeds posts. Wordpress automatic can extract two specified parts of the original post by id or class concat them to post to your wordpress.<br></li><li> Auto post amazon products to wordpress. wordpress automatic can search amazon.com or amazon.co.uk , amazon.ca , amazon.de , amazon.fr and amazon.jp for products matching your keywords, post them and add your affiliate links automatically so you can make commissions from products sold via your referrals.<br></li><li> just visit findbrowsenodes.com and get the node id.add your specified node and the plugin will limit searching on this node. <br></li><li> Auto post Clickbank products to wordpress. wordpress automatic plugin can search clickbank.com for products matching your specified keywords, post to your blog and add your affiliate links automatically.<br></li><li> Auto post Youtube videos to wordpress. wordpress automatic can search youtube.com for videos matching your keywords and post them to your wordpress blog* (all languages now supported)<br></li><li> Auto post videos from specific youtube channel/user to wordpress . you can automatically add channel videos to wordpress. you have the option to add videos from a specific user/channel by searching for specific keywords or without filtering.<br></li><li> Auto post eBay auctions to wordpress. wordpress automatic plugin can post ebay.com auctions for keywords you specify. you can also post from a specific eBay seller by searching his items for specified keywords or even without filtering. <br></li><li> - Supported ebay sites: US, IE, AT, AU, BE, CA, FR, IT, DE, ES, CH , UK , NL<br></li><li> Auto post Flicker images to wordpress. wordpress automatic plugin can post flicker.com images for keywords you specify. it also can post from a specific flicker user by searching this user items for specified keywords or without filtering.<br></li><li> Automatic ads insertion. you can specify two ads slots to be inserted automatically to the posts.<br></li><li> Campaign based. you can setup unlimited number of campaigns with different keywords &amp; different post options and these campaigns will work together to post to your site.<br></li><li> Post to specific category. you can set what category to add the new posts to one category per campaign.<br></li><li> Post using a specific author. you can choose the new post author one author per campaign.<br></li><li> Post keywords as tags. plugin can post keywords as wordpress tags.<br></li><li> Custom post types support . plugin can post to your custom post type like woo-commerce product.<br></li><li> Auto hyperlink keywords . plugin can automatically hyperlink specified keywords with your affiliate link or any specified link.<br></li><li> Automatically set wordpress featured image. plugin can auto set post featured image from the first image in the post content.<br></li><li> Cache images to your server. plugin can cache images to the server and change their links to your site link.<br></li><li> Choose must exist words and phrases. you can specify words that must be in the wordpress post content.<br></li><li> Execlude words and phrases. you can set words and phrases that must not be in the wordpress post content.<br></li><li> Translate the content before posting . you can set the plugin to automatically translate the content before posting using Google translate. You can set it to translate it twice.<br></li><li> Automatically add custom fields to new posts . you can set the plugin to add custom fields to the posted posts automatically these fields can contain any info from the post added like title, author ,content , image , price , rating .. etc . Allowed tags are listed automatically to choose from and differs for each campaign type.<br></li><li> Auto search and replace support. The plugin can search the content before posting for your specified words and replace them.<br></li><li> keyword suggestion. Writing the first letters of the keyword lists all keywords starting with this letter to choose from.<br></li><li> Support for automatic content spin using the best spinner. the best spinner (thebestspinner.com) takes the article and replace synonyms using it's synonyms database to create 100% unique article.<br></li><li> Support posts templates. the content of the post can be formed in different formats by using tags like [post_content] , [post_title],[product_price].. etc. supported tags differ for each campaign and listed atutomatically to choose from.<br></li><li> set &amp; forget cron job. to post every specific interval you specify for each campaign in the form of (days/hours/minutes).<br></li><li> Internal cron job. wordpress automatic supports posting automatically based on the internal wordpress cron job.<br></li><li> Two post status. you can set new post status to draft or published.<br></li><li> Unlimited keywords. you can add unlimited keywords per campaign. when the campaign start being processed these keywords will be used one by one to get the content so if the first keyword is exhaused or no more having matches the second one will be used.<br></li><li> Automatic keyword hyper-linking. automatic hyper-link matched keyword with specified link<br></li><li> Spintax enabled. like awesome. you can use this form in the post content and only one word will be chosen in the final article randomly.<br></li><li> Automatic link stripping. option to strip all links from the original content before posting.<br></li><li> Wordpress multi-site.comwork support. plugin can be installed in multi-site wordpress installation and function properly in each zombie blog.<br></li><li> proxy support.web proxies can be used by the plugin on the form ip:port<br><br></li></ul><br><br></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Wordpress Automatic 3.37.0"><br><div class="quote"><br><br><a href="https://clicknupload.link/pcsjfbfel7t6"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Wordpress.Automatic.Plugin.3.27.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://dailyuploads.com/slash1rgmtgx"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Wordpress.Automatic.Plugin.3.27.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://uploadocean.com/1zfm18msrqhq"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Wordpress.Automatic.Plugin.3.27.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://uplod.ws/1kc914kmf0oq"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Wordpress.Automatic.Plugin.3.27.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://userscloud.com/9at82t7x3nt4"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Wordpress.Automatic.Plugin.3.27.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br></div></div><br><p><br></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""> <br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Woozone 9.0.5.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/834-woocommerce-amazon-affiliates.html</link>
<description>Name : Woozone - WooCommerce Amazon Affiliates - Wordpress Plugin Version : 9.0.5.0 Type : Amazon Plugin Price : $33 Homepage : SalePage Advertise Amazon products on your Woocommerce website and earn advertising fees from Qualifying Purchases. You can also receive advertising fees from all products your visitors buy, visit, not just the products you advertise thanks to our 90 days cookie feature. Also, our On Site Cart feature allows your customers to checkout with multiple products on Amazon, and that means multiple commissions for you!</description>
<category>AutoBlog Plugins</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.aa-team.com/public/livedemo/woozone/mainfeatures.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 19:06:31 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Works as plugin on any WordPress Install. Compatible with any WordPress / Woocommerce Theme You can have Amazon Products and Simple Woocommerce Products on the Store in the Same Time (we&#039;ve made a special verification and the products don&#039;t conflict into the Cart Checkout Page) Choose from any Amazon Location - Worldwide, Amazon Germany, Amazon United Kingdom, Amazon Canada, Amazon France, Amazon Japan, Amazon India, Amazon Italy, Amazon China, Amazon Spain. 90 days cookies feature On Site Cart feature! Prices setup Products Variations Default publishing- import the products as Published or Draft. Select how many images to import for each product Select if you wish to display shipping availability Select if you wish to display Coupones - special offers &amp;amp; discounts Image Import type Automatically Content Spinner ASIN GRABBER Module Products into Posts Products Stats Images names - Product title or Random number - This is great for SEO Cross Selling Items Images gallery in product description Amazon Reviews Tab Setup Amazon Access Key ID and Secret Access Key Setup your affiliate ID&#039;s Setup Main Affiliate ID One second import! Mass Import products using the CSV module. Keep products updated using the Synchronisation Module, you can update Prices, Titles , Reviews, Buy Urls, Descriptions and SKU Setup / Backup Module 9.0.3.2 Wooamazonaffilates.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Wooamazonaffilates.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Wooamazonaffilates.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Wooamazonaffilates.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Wooamazonaffilates.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar 9.0.3 Woo.Zone.9.0.3.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Woo.Zone.9.0.3.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Woo.Zone.9.0.3.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Woo.Zone.9.0.3.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Woo.Zone.9.0.3.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/CoEMb3wRTDY?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li>Works as plugin on any WordPress Install.<br></li><li>Compatible with any WordPress / Woocommerce Theme<br></li><li>You can have Amazon Products and Simple Woocommerce Products on the Store in the Same Time (we've made a special verification and the products don't conflict into the Cart Checkout Page)<br></li><li>Choose from any Amazon Location - Worldwide, Amazon Germany, Amazon United Kingdom, Amazon Canada, Amazon France, Amazon Japan, Amazon India, Amazon Italy, Amazon China, Amazon Spain.<br></li><li>90 days cookies feature<br></li><li>On Site Cart feature!<br></li><li>Prices setup<br></li><li>Products Variations<br></li><li>Default publishing- import the products as Published or Draft.<br></li><li>Select how many images to import for each product<br></li><li>Select if you wish to display shipping availability<br></li><li>Select if you wish to display Coupones - special offers &amp; discounts<br></li><li>Image Import type<br></li><li>Automatically Content Spinner<br></li><li>ASIN GRABBER Module<br></li><li>Products into Posts<br></li><li>Products Stats<br></li><li>Images names - Product title or Random number - This is great for SEO<br></li><li>Cross Selling Items<br></li><li>Images gallery in product description<br></li><li>Amazon Reviews Tab<br></li><li>Setup Amazon Access Key ID and Secret Access Key<br></li><li>Setup your affiliate ID's<br></li><li>Setup Main Affiliate ID<br></li><li>One second import!<br></li><li>Mass Import products using the CSV module.<br></li><li>Keep products updated using the Synchronisation Module, you can update Prices, Titles , Reviews, Buy Urls, Descriptions and SKU<br></li><li>Setup / Backup Module<br></li></ul><br><br><img src="http://www.aa-team.com/public/livedemo/woozone/mainfeatures.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Woozone 9.0.5.0"><br><br> <div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br>9.0.3.2<br><a href="https://clicknupload.link/u3iuljlopzcn"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Wooamazonaffilates.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://dailyuploads.com/g67xwzcfe7j2"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Wooamazonaffilates.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://uploadocean.com/7ubvhx24zjfg"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Wooamazonaffilates.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://uplod.ws/k3rzzaj5ngut"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Wooamazonaffilates.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://userscloud.com/gm3fg8r593gu"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Wooamazonaffilates.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br>9.0.3<br><a href="https://clicknupload.link/of0rn94ec3b5"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Woo.Zone.9.0.3.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://dailyuploads.com/tsj90hfbb3wt"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Woo.Zone.9.0.3.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://uploadocean.com/kexp2bprlp37"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Woo.Zone.9.0.3.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://uplod.ws/sfu0t5jtl97f"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Woo.Zone.9.0.3.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://userscloud.com/f5cz0h0ewstl"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Woo.Zone.9.0.3.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><br></div><br><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>FBVidMatic 5.0 Elite</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1472-fbvidmatic.html</link>
<description>Name : FBVidMatic Version : 5.0 Elite Type : Auto Facebook Video Plugin Price : $27 Homepage : SalePage FB Vidmatic Is A 1 Click Video Site Builder Plugin That Pulls Video’s From FB Fan Pages…</description>
<category>AutoBlog Plugins</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2017 10:32:33 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FB Vidmatic Is A 1 Click Video Site Builder Plugin That Pulls Video’s From Facebook Fan Pages… You Can Make Totally Passive Income From Your Blogs Leveraging FBVidmatic… Can Create A Fully Blown Video Site In Literally Minutes… It Also Includes The Ability To Place Leadbox Ads Under Every Video On The Blog With 1 Click… Extremely Easy To Use And Install… Built In Leadbox Ad Editor That Allows You To Create &amp;amp; Edit Leadbox Ads So You Can M.comize The Site From Within The Plugin……</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/VHX-G9X2UL4?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> FB Vidmatic Is A 1 Click Video Site Builder Plugin That Pulls Video’s From Facebook Fan Pages…<br></li><li> You Can Make Totally Passive Income From Your Blogs Leveraging FBVidmatic…<br></li><li> Can Create A Fully Blown Video Site In Literally Minutes…<br></li><li> It Also Includes The Ability To Place Leadbox Ads Under Every Video On The Blog With 1 Click…<br></li><li> Extremely Easy To Use And Install…<br></li><li> Built In Leadbox Ad Editor That Allows You To Create &amp; Edit Leadbox Ads So You Can M.comize The Site From Within The Plugin……<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="FBVidMatic 5.0 Elite"><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>WP Video Sites 1.3.81 Enterprise</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3654-wp-video-sites.html</link>
<description>Name : WP Video Sites Version : 1.3.81 Enterprise Type : Auto Video Blog Price : $39 Homepage : SalePage WpVideoSites is a WordPress plugin that allows you to create Independent Video Sites that run alongside your current blog. The Video sites are designed to Send Targeted Traffic, Increase Engagement and Boost the Search Engine Rankings for your main WordPress site. It does this by creating Fully Optimized &amp;amp; Specially crafted Video posts that revolve around your Topics and Keywords.</description>
<category>AutoBlog Plugins</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2017 03:45:59 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Boost Search Engine Rankings Get Targeted Traffic &amp;amp; Visitors Rank Content for More Keywords Boost internal Links &amp;amp; Diversify Anchor text Search and Use Any Youtube Video in your Posts Scrape Video Transcripts to Build Content Rich Posts Works with ANY WP install &amp;amp; Theme GET INSTANT ACCESS TO WP VIDEO SITES Create a Fully Fledged Viral Video Blog within Minutes &amp;amp; Increase Traffic Search for YouTube videos using ANY Keyword &amp;amp; in ANY Niche Auto Add Relevant Content in ANY Language &amp;amp; Rank for more terms using video transcripts 1 click social media syndication for increasing links and Exposure Fully SEO Optimized Video posts using Schema Mark-up for accelerated Rankings RSS Sitemaps and Video feeds for Rapid indexing and syndication services Fully optimized Desktop and Mobile Theme Layout to match any WP site Fully integrated with Spin rewriter and The best spinner for content auto rewrites Fully integrated with Article builder for adding Additional Niche Specific content Supports proxies and allows you to control what IP’s are used for requests Schedule posts for months to come or Publish them immediately Works with ANY WP Install &amp;amp; ANY WP Theme -RANK in Google for More Terms &amp;amp; Increase your Search Engine Rankings + Link Internally, Diversify Anchor Text + And RANK Even Higher Auto Content Generation using Transcripts &amp;amp; Video Data + Syndicate Video Posts to Top Social Media Sites for Even More Exposure &amp;amp; Links -Generate SEO Friendly Video RSS Feeds &amp;amp; Sitemaps for Rapid Indexing &amp;amp; Syndication + WpVideoSites Generates Multiple Feeds and is Fully Silo Compliant. + Accelerated Rankings Using Fully Optimized Video Posts &amp;amp; Schema Mark-up -WP Video Sites Puts You in Full Control +Fully Customizable Desktop and Mobile Theme to Match ANY Blog +Show Targeted Offers using Advanced Banner Management, Control and Rotation +Google Mobile First Index Optimized for an even better Ranking &amp;amp; Experience +Increase Fresh Factor Scores &amp;amp; Rank Even Higher in Google</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ZaCUjB9_wvY?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><br><ul><li> Boost Search Engine Rankings<br></li><li> Get Targeted Traffic &amp; Visitors<br></li><li> Rank Content for More Keywords<br></li><li> Boost internal Links &amp; Diversify Anchor text<br></li><li> Search and Use Any Youtube Video in your Posts<br></li><li> Scrape Video Transcripts to Build Content Rich Posts<br></li><li> Works with ANY WP install &amp; Theme<br></li><li> GET INSTANT ACCESS TO WP VIDEO SITES<br></li><li> Create a Fully Fledged Viral Video Blog within Minutes &amp; Increase Traffic <br></li><li> Search for YouTube videos using ANY Keyword &amp; in ANY Niche <br></li><li> Auto Add Relevant Content in ANY Language &amp; Rank for more terms using video transcripts <br></li><li> 1 click social media syndication for increasing links and Exposure <br></li><li> Fully SEO Optimized Video posts using Schema Mark-up for accelerated Rankings <br></li><li> RSS Sitemaps and Video feeds for Rapid indexing and syndication services <br></li><li> Fully optimized Desktop and Mobile Theme Layout to match any WP site <br></li><li> Fully integrated with Spin rewriter and The best spinner for content auto rewrites <br></li><li> Fully integrated with Article builder for adding Additional Niche Specific content <br></li><li> Supports proxies and allows you to control what IP’s are used for requests  <br></li><li> Schedule posts for months to come or Publish them immediately<br></li><li> Works with ANY WP Install &amp; ANY WP Theme<br></li></ul><br><b>-RANK in Google for More Terms &amp; Increase your Search Engine Rankings</b><br>+ Link Internally, Diversify Anchor Text<br>+ And RANK Even Higher Auto Content Generation using Transcripts &amp; Video Data<br>+ Syndicate Video Posts to Top Social Media Sites for Even More Exposure &amp; Links<br><br><b>-Generate SEO Friendly Video RSS Feeds &amp; Sitemaps for Rapid Indexing &amp; Syndication</b><br>+ WpVideoSites Generates Multiple Feeds and is Fully Silo Compliant.<br>+ Accelerated Rankings Using Fully Optimized Video Posts &amp; Schema Mark-up<br><br><b>-WP Video Sites Puts You in Full Control</b>       <br>+Fully Customizable Desktop and Mobile Theme to Match ANY Blog<br>+Show Targeted Offers using Advanced Banner Management, Control and Rotation<br>+Google Mobile First Index Optimized for an even better Ranking &amp; Experience<br>+Increase Fresh Factor Scores &amp; Rank Even Higher in Google<br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="WP Video Sites 1.3.81 Enterprise"><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>WordPress Video Robot Plugin 1.8.9</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3548-wordpress-video-robot-plugin-189.html</link>
<description>Name :WordPress Video Robot Plugin Version : 1.8.9 OS : Linux Type : Media Price : 36 Homepage : SalePage Free WP Video Robot is the ultimate WordPress solution for creating automated and standalone video websites. It is a complete and yet easy premium WordPress plugin with a schedule import system that makes sure your site stays fresh and up to date with the latest or most popular videos online. You can import videos from Youtube. Dailymotion, Vimeo, TED and Youku. Millions of videos are now within reach of a click.</description>
<category>AutoBlog Plugins</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2017 00:58:35 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features unlimited sources detailed logs testing videos automatic updates video thumbnail full control video curation no duplicate videos manual import high performances auto clean mode automatic tagging importing &amp;amp; exporting randomization completely legal international no coding needed complete integration shortcode Wordpress.Video.Robot.Plugin1.8.9.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Wordpress.Video.Robot.Plugin1.8.9.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Wordpress.Video.Robot.Plugin1.8.9.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Wordpress.Video.Robot.Plugin1.8.9.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Wordpress.Video.Robot.Plugin1.8.9.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<p><br><b>Features</b><br><ul><li>unlimited sources<br></li><li>detailed logs<br></li><li>testing videos<br></li><li>automatic updates<br></li><li>video thumbnail<br></li><li>full control<br></li><li>video curation<br></li><li>no duplicate videos<br></li><li>manual import<br></li><li>high performances<br></li><li>auto clean mode<br></li><li>automatic tagging<br></li><li>importing &amp; exporting<br></li><li>randomization<br></li><li>completely legal<br></li><li>international<br></li><li>no coding needed<br></li><li>complete integration<br></li><li>shortcode<br></li></ul><br><br></p>
<div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="WordPress Video Robot Plugin 1.8.9"><br><div class="quote"><br><br><a href="https://clicknupload.link/1s4vku30n6qn" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer external">Wordpress.Video.Robot.Plugin1.8.9.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://dailyuploads.com/4gefuoycp2su" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer external">Wordpress.Video.Robot.Plugin1.8.9.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://uploadocean.com/ulo60lfzicf9" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer external">Wordpress.Video.Robot.Plugin1.8.9.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://uplod.ws/r3hduwqkf4eu" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer external">Wordpress.Video.Robot.Plugin1.8.9.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://userscloud.com/n7qp9zqe4k0a" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer external">Wordpress.Video.Robot.Plugin1.8.9.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br></div><br><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>WP Indeed Importer 1.0 - WordPress Plugin</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3547-wp-indeed-importer-10-wordpress-plugin.html</link>
<description>Name :WP Indeed Importer - WordPress Plugin Version : 1.0 OS : Linux Type : add-ons Price : 17 Homepage : SalePage Have you ever thought of creating a wordpress Jobsite, which posts jobs according to your own needs and where you do not have to send the visitors to some other sites, so you can post your own ads and make full money for yourself? If yes, then you have just purchased the right plugin for your own Jobsite. WordPress WP Indeed Importer is a plugin, which imports the jobs from Indeed.com. We support Indeed.com, Indeed.ca, Indeed.co.uk, Indeed.es, Indeed.fr, Indeed.de at this moment. You can use the settings screen to select the source of your job imports.</description>
<category>AutoBlog Plugins</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2017 00:58:31 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Scraping Source Post Ads Post by Category Search Panel Indeedimporter.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Indeedimporter.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Indeedimporter.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Indeedimporter.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Indeedimporter.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<p><br><b>Features</b><br><ul><li>Scraping Source<br></li><li>Post Ads<br></li><li>Post by<br></li><li>Category<br></li><li>Search Panel<br></li></ul><br><br></p>
<div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="WP Indeed Importer 1.0 - WordPress Plugin"><br><div class="quote"><br><a href="https://clicknupload.link/oex8x79lx3wt" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer external">Indeedimporter.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://dailyuploads.com/pubrh4c6521f" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer external">Indeedimporter.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://uploadocean.com/dbxnhmrnyz6b" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer external">Indeedimporter.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://uplod.ws/njiux08d5my0" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer external">Indeedimporter.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://userscloud.com/pukdr3xskz5s" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer external">Indeedimporter.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br></div><br><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>WP IMDB Automator 7.0 - WordPress Plugin</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3546-wp-imdb-automator-70-wordpress-plugin.html</link>
<description>Name :WP IMDB Automator - WordPress Plugin Version : 7.0 OS : Linux Type : add-ons Price : 19 Homepage : SalePage Free WP IMDB automator is a WordPress plugin designed for the WordPress platform which 100% automates the process of running a media specific blog. If you ever wanted a movie blog which features content for latest movies, short films, TV Shows this is your chance to have it.</description>
<category>AutoBlog Plugins</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2017 00:58:27 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Import more than 1 million movies from IMDB. Blog Posting Schedule Import Movie Poster Import Movie Plot Import Director Name Import Release Data Import Run Time Import Country Import Genre Import Tagline Import Trivia Import Goofs Save title as Title or Title (Year) for SEO as your choice Youtube HD Trailers Automatically Posted Import reviews Post reviews on every post using IMDB comments Automatically post reviews using Multiple Users Automatically Schedule or Post immediately Save titles as Tags for SEO of website Automatically locally saved Posters Wp.Imdb.Automator.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Wp.Imdb.Automator.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Wp.Imdb.Automator.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Wp.Imdb.Automator.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Wp.Imdb.Automator.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<br><b>Features</b><br><ul><li>Import more than 1 million movies from IMDB.<br></li><li>Blog Posting Schedule<br></li><li>Import Movie Poster<br></li><li>Import Movie Plot<br></li><li>Import Director Name<br></li><li>Import Release Data<br></li><li>Import Run Time<br></li><li>Import Country<br></li><li>Import Genre<br></li><li>Import Tagline<br></li><li>Import Trivia<br></li><li>Import Goofs<br></li><li>Save title as Title or Title (Year) for SEO as your choice<br></li><li>Youtube HD Trailers Automatically Posted<br></li><li>Import reviews<br></li><li>Post reviews on every post using IMDB comments<br></li><li>Automatically post reviews using Multiple Users<br></li><li>Automatically Schedule or Post immediately<br></li><li>Save titles as Tags for SEO of website<br></li><li>Automatically locally saved Posters<br></li></ul><br><br> <div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="WP IMDB Automator 7.0 - WordPress Plugin"><br><div class="quote"><br><br><a href="https://clicknupload.link/19jpzzt6w1u6"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Wp.Imdb.Automator.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://dailyuploads.com/1z1dal0kiazx"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Wp.Imdb.Automator.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://uploadocean.com/ylafcj8wu2wx"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Wp.Imdb.Automator.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://uplod.ws/jixa09ilj3q7"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Wp.Imdb.Automator.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://userscloud.com/3k6acsvjp5qo"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Wp.Imdb.Automator.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br></div><br><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>WP HyperShift 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3545-wp-hypershift-10.html</link>
<description>Name : WP HyperShift Version : 1.0 OS : Linux Type : Content Builder Price : 28 Homepage : SalePage Want More Time To Focus On The Good Stuff? Fed Up of Tiresome, Time-Consuming, Tedious Tasks?&quot; &quot;So Put All That Behind You - Push Just One Button And Have Your Entire Blog Set Up For You Automatically. In Just 7 Seconds&quot;</description>
<category>AutoBlog Plugins</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2017 00:58:23 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Setup your about us, contact us, legal pages,blog settings,floating bar and favicon in just a few clicks. Import WP Settings and WP Plugins from the other sites. Export WP Settings and WP Plugins from your site. Install and manage multiple plugins at once. Blog Settings: Change default category from &quot;uncategorized&quot; to user specified text. Add up to 5 additional categories. Change permalink structure to custom structure. Delete default &quot;hello world&quot; post and default comment and sample page. Change default tagline from &quot;just another wordpress blog&quot; to custom user specified tagline. Delete all links in Blogroll. Google Analytics integration. Create Google XML Sitemap for the blog. WP.Hypershift.1.0.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar WP.Hypershift.1.0.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar WP.Hypershift.1.0.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar WP.Hypershift.1.0.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar WP.Hypershift.1.0.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<br><div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/tEEeG81_Fno?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><b>Features</b><br><ul><li> Setup your about us, contact us, legal pages,blog settings,floating bar and favicon in just a few clicks.<br></li><li> Import WP Settings and WP Plugins from the other sites.<br></li><li> Export WP Settings and WP Plugins from your site.<br></li><li> Install and manage multiple plugins at once.<br></li></ul><br>Blog Settings:<br><ul><li> Change default category from "uncategorized" to user specified text.<br></li><li> Add up to 5 additional categories.<br></li><li> Change permalink structure to custom structure.<br></li><li> Delete default "hello world" post and default comment and sample page.<br></li><li> Change default tagline from "just another wordpress blog" to custom user specified tagline.<br></li><li> Delete all links in Blogroll.<br></li><li> Google Analytics integration.<br></li><li> Create Google XML Sitemap for the blog.<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="WP HyperShift 1.0"><br><div class="quote"><br><a href="https://clicknupload.link/rr8izy55mrn9"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">WP.Hypershift.1.0.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://dailyuploads.com/xenc5cwckoiq"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">WP.Hypershift.1.0.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://uploadocean.com/rnctpqzyw08d"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">WP.Hypershift.1.0.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://uplod.ws/6dlpawevjzqz"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">WP.Hypershift.1.0.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://userscloud.com/6og5846pxgpb"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">WP.Hypershift.1.0.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><br></div><br></div><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>WP Crawler 1.1.3 - Grab Any Website Content To WordPress</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3544-wp-crawler-113-grab-any-website-content-to-wordpress.html</link>
<description>Name :WP Crawler - Grab Any Website Content To WordPress Version : 1.1.3 OS : Linux Type : WOrdPress Price : 22 Homepage : SalePage Free WP Crawler WordPress plugin helps you to create WordPress content effortlessly. Nulled WP Crawler WordPress plugin lets you grab content from any website, then insert them into WordPress.</description>
<category>AutoBlog Plugins</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2017 00:58:19 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Get data (text/images) from other website via HTML Selectors and Attributes Support insert data as Custom Taxonomies and Custom Fields Manage unlimited websites source to get data Import/Export website settings Duplicate checking via source&#039;s URL Set post status, post type, post category for each post Schedule crawling hourly, twice daily and daily Detailed documentation Ready to translate (.pot file) Wp.Crawler.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Wp.Crawler.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Wp.Crawler.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Wp.Crawler.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Wp.Crawler.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<br><b>Features</b><br><ul><li>Get data (text/images) from other website via HTML Selectors and Attributes<br></li><li>Support insert data as Custom Taxonomies and Custom Fields<br></li><li>Manage unlimited websites source to get data<br></li><li>Import/Export website settings<br></li><li>Duplicate checking via source's URL<br></li><li>Set post status, post type, post category for each post<br></li><li>Schedule crawling hourly, twice daily and daily<br></li><li>Detailed documentation<br></li><li>Ready to translate (.pot file)<br></li></ul><br><br> <div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="WP Crawler 1.1.3 - Grab Any Website Content To WordPress"><br><div class="quote"><br><br><a href="https://clicknupload.link/indjmdh96wl3"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Wp.Crawler.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://dailyuploads.com/r7oav1bkzanw"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Wp.Crawler.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://uploadocean.com/90p2bch68lj0"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Wp.Crawler.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://uplod.ws/dwon611qmnh4"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Wp.Crawler.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://userscloud.com/gi4kwfkj3a7s"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Wp.Crawler.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br></div><br><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>WordPress Post Planner Plugin 1.5</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3543-wordpress-post-planner-plugin-15.html</link>
<description>Name :WordPress Post Planner Plugin Version : 1.5 OS : Linux Type : Miscellaneous Price : 25 Homepage : SalePage Free Post Planner WordPress Plugin is a fully-featured WordPress plugin for made just for you.</description>
<category>AutoBlog Plugins</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2017 00:58:15 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Assign Planners to Users - chose what roles show up in the assignment drop-down Set Due Dates for Planners - using a popup date picker Set and Assign Custom Statuses - including setting a color for each status for the dashboard widget A Standard Checklist for Every Planner - you set the checklist items Chose the Post Type for Each Planner - set what post types you want to chose from Comments on Each Planner - so you can discuss each planner with fellow authors Add and Insert References (links) - link title, url, target, nofollow Add and Insert Files - file title, url, and is integrated with the media uploader Add and Insert Images and Set Featured Image - image title, alt, url, and is integrated with the media uploader Easily integrate planners with new or existing posts - create a new post from the planner or select an existing post Email Assignments to Assigned Users - optional feature with configurable email messages Post.Planner.Codecanyon.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Post.Planner.Codecanyon.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Post.Planner.Codecanyon.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Post.Planner.Codecanyon.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Post.Planner.Codecanyon.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<br><b>Features</b><br><ul><li>Assign Planners to Users - chose what roles show up in the assignment drop-down<br></li><li>Set Due Dates for Planners - using a popup date picker<br></li><li>Set and Assign Custom Statuses - including setting a color for each status for the dashboard widget<br></li><li>A Standard Checklist for Every Planner - you set the checklist items<br></li><li>Chose the Post Type for Each Planner - set what post types you want to chose from<br></li><li>Comments on Each Planner - so you can discuss each planner with fellow authors<br></li><li>Add and Insert References (links) - link title, url, target, nofollow<br></li><li>Add and Insert Files - file title, url, and is integrated with the media uploader<br></li><li>Add and Insert Images and Set Featured Image - image title, alt, url, and is integrated with the media uploader<br></li><li>Easily integrate planners with new or existing posts - create a new post from the planner or select an existing post<br></li><li>Email Assignments to Assigned Users - optional feature with configurable email messages<br></li></ul><br><br> <div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="WordPress Post Planner Plugin 1.5"><br><div class="quote"><br><br><a href="https://clicknupload.link/z8otze2qz13d"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Post.Planner.Codecanyon.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://dailyuploads.com/83jrxzha30o2"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Post.Planner.Codecanyon.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://uploadocean.com/f7rnux29mphr"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Post.Planner.Codecanyon.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://uplod.ws/vbkc2xn8ypxp"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Post.Planner.Codecanyon.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://userscloud.com/02faat5s6swe"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Post.Planner.Codecanyon.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br></div><br><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>