<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>SEO Training - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>SEO Training - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>6 Tips to dominate Local Search Market</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1897-6-tips-to-dominate-local-search-market.html</link>
<description>This is Guest Post by Sahil Kakkar Have a craving for pizza? Don&amp;rsquo;t know where you can find the nearest store? All you have to do is run a quick Google search &amp;ldquo;Pizza delivery near me&amp;rdquo;. Thanks to the Inte.com and the growing technologies! Almost 98% of the customers now use search engines to find local products and services. Also, 87% of customers who search for a local business visit or call the store within a day. With multiple options available online for their desired service or product, how do you ensure that they choose your business? Local SEO is pacing fast in terms of helping you gain market share, online visibility and ultimately, customers. In order to dominate the hyper-competitive local search engine results, you need to optimize your business, website and strategies. You need to accommodate the needs of mobile-focused, modern and tech-savvy customers. Those days are gone when you could simply get a location, put up ads all around and wait for the customers to get in your stores. Your hyper-focused marketing efforts shouldn&amp;rsquo;t only be aimed at showing up in the search results, but dominate them in the sea of competitors. If you want to stand out of the crowd in your respective niche or category, you need to turn to some fundamental local practices. I&amp;rsquo;ve made a list of 6 actionable tips that can help you dominate local search market. Let&amp;rsquo;s get started.</description>
<category>SEO Training</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2016-07/thumbs/1469822329_local-website-review.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2016 02:57:00 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Content You knew this one, didn&amp;rsquo;t you? But content is not simply content, we are talking about local content here. It also does not mean information about your products and services. Each blog post is another web page indexed by Google, which can also be seen as an opportunity to get ranked on the Google local SERPs for the targeted keyword and location. In order to make your content as a traffic driving tool, you need to make it local, relevant and useful. Let&amp;rsquo;s say you are a business that sells organic food, your content can talk about the benefits of consuming organic food, how it affects your health, the best organic food to have, how to strike the balance between taste and health, where can you find organic food in your locality, and likewise. Also, you should parallelly keep working on other ways to engage the community &amp;ndash; cover local events, local news, news within your industry, sponsor local events or charities and write about it. You can also write about complementary local services. If you sell wedding gowns, you can write about the best wedding planners in the locality. This will also help you establish goodwill with local businesses and probably an inbound link soon. Do not forget to optimize your content for your targeted keywords &amp;ndash; try to include your City/Region in the title tag, H1 tag and URL. Do a thorough keyword research and cover all the long tail keywords which people might use to search for a business in your community. If you have a hard time figuring out what geo-targeted content you should focus on, then try writing about your customer success stories or case studies. Reviews Reviews are an absolute essential for every local business, whether or not they sell online. They clearly affect local search engine rankings, click-through rate and consumer purchasing decisions. I ran a quick search for Italian Restaurants in Pasadena, take a look at the result: The first results clearly stand out having a rating of 4.3 with 37 and 35 reviews respectively. Reviews account for roughly 10% of the local ranking factors. Also, review sites like Yelp drive a great deal of traffic and rank extremely well in the search results. But I think it goes much beyond this, reviews are a strong trust signal for the potential customers. They give reassurance to users that they will be taking the right decision if they choose your business. That is why great ratings and awesome reviews give people an extra push to make their purchase. Acquiring reviews is not a cakewalk. Even your most loyal customers wouldn&amp;rsquo;t seem to take the time to log in and write reviews for you. Try to incorporate reviews in the sales process &amp;ndash; give out flyers explaining them how to leave reviews, offer some token of appreciations, ask them how was their experience with you and if they would like to write about it, explain how your previous customers had a thrilling experience using your product/service, print some reviews and hang it in your store. Put a big &amp;ldquo;review us&amp;rdquo; tab on your website. Take out some time every day to reply to your reviews, particularly the bad ones. Thank your customers for the positive feedback. Directories There is no point in having a business if no one knows about it. Directories across the web can help you expand your web estate. There is no denying the fact that it is mandatory for every local business to be present over major local search directories like Google+ , Yahoo and Bing. Apart from these, review sites (such as Yelp), generic, industry-specific directories also help distribute data points to the search engines. Start by creating your Google My Business Profile . Make sure you enter accurate and consistent business details in your profile and claim it. Once you are done with this, you can start with getting listed in Top national generic directories ( Bing Places, Yahoo local, Yelp and so on), Industry specific directories (Tripadvisor for hotels, wellness for health sector) and locally relevant directories (Chamber of Commerce). Make sure your accurate business information is listed across all these websites. Consistent NAP Accurate and consistent citations can get you a great deal of targeted traffic. Citations are simply mentions of your business across the web, irrespective of whether they are linked to you or not. The number of accurate and consistent citations of your business is directly proportional to your online visibility. Consistent citations across relevant web directories increase the authenticity of your business in the eyes of Google, improves search engine rankings, provides more backlinks, enhances conversion rates and opens scope for getting reviewed on important web properties. Now, there are several reasons for the discrepancy in your NAP &amp;ndash; the physical location of your business might have changed over time, it might have used tracking numbers at some point of time or your local phone number might have changed, data aggregators might have accumulated inaccurate information about your business and so on. But, how do you clean this mess? To begin with, start with fixing your information with the major players &amp;ndash; Data Aggregators (InfoGroup, Acxiom, Localeze, Factual). Once this is done, you can start by checking your business details over other authoritative websites like Google+, Yahoo, Bing, Yelp and likewise. Then, run through your citations over generic and niche specific directories like Foursquare , CitySearch etc. Practically speaking, it can turn out to be a mess if you manually go and check all of your listings for accuracy and consistency. Needless to say, hell lot of time and effort. The best option here would be to go with automated tools. These tools pull out all your mentions across the web and list the inaccurate ones under a separate head. Local RankWatch not only lists your inaccurate citations, but also offers to correct them, saving a lot of your time. Optimized website Your website probably marks your potential customer&amp;rsquo;s&amp;rsquo; first impression of your business. So, you need to make sure that it is optimized for your local keywords. It&amp;rsquo;s best to focus on the fundamental things and let go of the little odds. Here are the things you should take care of: Domain name &amp;ndash; Try to get a domain name that reflects your business and location. Also, try to keep it as short as possible. NAP &amp;ndash; Put your business name, phone number, city, address and ZIP on every page possible. Copy &amp;ndash; Treat this as your sales pitch. As mentioned above, try to include as much of local content as you can. Use local jargon &amp;ndash; it will help you connect with your audience. Also, use the white space appropriately. Too many words will make the page look boring. Make sure the content is readable. Use keywords &amp;ndash; Try to include as many locally targeted keywords you can, but keep it natural. Mobile optimized &amp;ndash; Local search and mobile search are complementary in nature. People like to get their information on the go. Make sure your website is completely mobile-friendly. It will enable the users to easily check out your reviews, directions, contact information and so on. Link building Local link building can go a long way in attracting local attention. Also, it offers scope for developing relationships with the local community, improves search engine rankings and gets you more targeted and relevant traffic. The more local links you have, the better it is. To begin, get into local directories (Google Local, Bing Places, Yahoo Local, Yelp, Angie&amp;rsquo;s list etc), resource lists (Local Chamber of Commerce, local newspapers and magazines, city-based directories) and review sites (BBB.org, Yelp, CitySearch, MerchantCircle). Create a team of local strategic partners. How? Start contacting local business or companies who offer complementary products or services to your business. For example, if you are a wedding planner, you can probably partner with a business that sells wedding gowns. Leverage such relationships, keep sharing each other&amp;rsquo;s content and earn great links. Local sponsorship (sponsoring conferences, talk shows, fests, fairs) is another great option for building links. Generate local resources like a local map for tourist attractions, a local guide which talks about the best activities in town, cultural attractions, best pubs or hotels or a local event calendar which mentions the local sports events, festivals, etc. Local SEO is not a one-time thing. In order to establish your presence over the local SERPs in the long run, you need to constantly work for it. Go through this checklist, follow each step and see the results in your online visibility. I would love to hear any other tip I am missing on in the comments below. Author Bio: Sahil Kakkar is the CEO and Founder of RankWatch &amp;ndash; a platform, which helps companies and brands stay ahead with their SEO efforts in the ever growing inte.com landscape. Sahil likes making creative products that can help in automation of mundane tasks and he can spend endless nights implementing new technologies and ideas. You can connect with him and the Rankwatch team on Facebook or Twitter.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h2><strong>Content</strong></h2>
<p>You knew this one, didn&rsquo;t you?</p>
<p>But content is not simply content, we are talking about local content here. It also does not mean information about your products and services.</p>
<p>Each blog post is another web page indexed by Google, which can also be seen as an opportunity to get ranked on the <strong>Google local SERPs</strong> for the targeted keyword and location.</p>
<p>In order to make your content as a traffic driving tool, you need to make it local, relevant and useful.</p>
<p>Let&rsquo;s say you are a business that sells organic food, your content can talk about the benefits of consuming organic food, how it affects your health, the best organic food to have, how to strike the balance between taste and health, where can you find organic food in your locality, and likewise.</p>
<p>Also, you should parallelly keep working on other ways to engage the community &ndash; <strong>cover local events, local news, news within your industry, sponsor local events or charities</strong> and write about it.</p>
<p>You can also write about complementary local services. If you sell wedding gowns, you can write about the best wedding planners in the locality. This will also help you establish goodwill with local businesses and probably an inbound link soon.</p>
<p>Do not forget to <a href="rss.xml" target="_blank">optimize your content</a> for your targeted keywords &ndash; try to include your City/Region in the title tag, H1 tag and URL. Do a thorough keyword research and cover all the long tail keywords which people might use to search for a business in your community.</p>
<p>If you have a hard time figuring out what geo-targeted content you should focus on, then try writing about your customer success stories or case studies.</p>
<h2><strong>Reviews</strong></h2>
<p>Reviews are an absolute essential for every <strong>local business</strong>, whether or not they sell online.</p>
<p>They clearly affect <strong>local search engine rankings</strong>, click-through rate and consumer purchasing decisions.</p>
<p>I ran a quick search for Italian Restaurants in Pasadena, take a look at the result:</p>
<p><a href="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2016-07/1469822329_local-website-review.png" rel="highslide" class="highslide" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2016-07/thumbs/1469822329_local-website-review.png" alt='6 Tips to dominate Local Search Market' title='6 Tips to dominate Local Search Market'  /></a>
</p>
<p>The first results clearly stand out having a rating of 4.3 with 37 and 35 reviews respectively.</p>
<p>Reviews account for roughly 10% of the local ranking factors. Also, review sites like Yelp drive a great deal of traffic and rank extremely well in the search results.</p>
<p>But I think it goes much beyond this, reviews are a strong trust signal for the potential customers. They give reassurance to users that they will be taking the right decision if they choose your business. That is why great ratings and awesome reviews give people an extra push to make their purchase.</p>
<p>Acquiring reviews is not a cakewalk. Even your most loyal customers wouldn&rsquo;t seem to take the time to log in and write reviews for you.</p>
<p>Try to incorporate reviews in the sales process &ndash; give out flyers explaining them how to leave reviews, offer some token of appreciations, ask them how was their experience with you and if they would like to write about it, explain how your previous customers had a thrilling experience using your product/service, print some reviews and hang it in your store. Put a big &ldquo;review us&rdquo; tab on your website.</p>
<p>Take out some time every day to reply to your reviews, particularly the bad ones. Thank your customers for the positive feedback.</p>
<h2><strong>Directories</strong></h2>
<p>There is no point in having a business if no one knows about it. Directories across the web can help you expand your web estate.</p>
<p>There is no denying the fact that it is mandatory for every local business to be present over <strong>major local search directories</strong> like <strong><a href="https://plus.google.com/"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Google+</a></strong>, <strong>Yahoo</strong> and <strong>Bing</strong>. Apart from these, review sites (such as <strong>Yelp</strong>), generic, industry-specific directories also help distribute data points to the search engines.</p>
<p>Start by creating your <strong><a href="https://www.google.com/business/befound.html"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Google My Business Profile</a></strong>. Make sure you enter accurate and consistent business details in your profile and claim it. Once you are done with this, you can start with getting listed in <strong>Top national generic directories</strong> (<strong><a href="https://www.bingplaces.com"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Bing Places</a>, <a href="https://local.yahoo.com"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Yahoo local</a>, Yelp</strong> and so on), <strong>Industry specific directories</strong> (Tripadvisor for hotels, wellness for health sector) and <strong>locally relevant directories</strong> (<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chamber_of_commerce"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Chamber of Commerce</a>).</p>
<p>Make sure your accurate business information is listed across all these websites.</p>
<h2><strong>Consistent NAP</strong></h2>
<p>Accurate and consistent citations can get you a great deal of targeted traffic. Citations are simply mentions of your business across the web, irrespective of whether they are linked to you or not.</p>
<p>The number of accurate and consistent citations of your business is directly proportional to your online visibility. Consistent citations across relevant web directories increase the authenticity of your business in the eyes of Google, improves search engine rankings, provides more backlinks, enhances conversion rates and opens scope for getting reviewed on important web properties.</p>
<p>Now, there are several reasons for the discrepancy in your <strong>NAP</strong> &ndash; the physical location of your business might have changed over time, it might have used tracking numbers at some point of time or your local phone number might have changed, data aggregators might have accumulated inaccurate information about your business and so on.</p>
<p>But, how do you clean this mess? To begin with, start with fixing your information with the major players &ndash; Data Aggregators (InfoGroup, Acxiom, Localeze, Factual). Once this is done, you can start by checking your business details over other authoritative websites like Google+, Yahoo, Bing, Yelp and likewise. Then, run through your citations over generic and niche specific directories like <a href="https://foursquare.com"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer"><strong>Foursquare</strong></a>, <strong>CitySearch</strong> etc.</p>
<p>Practically speaking, it can turn out to be a mess if you manually go and check all of your listings for accuracy and consistency. Needless to say, hell lot of time and effort.</p>
<p>The best option here would be to go with automated tools. These tools pull out all your mentions across the web and list the inaccurate ones under a separate head. <a class="seoquake-nofollow" href="http://local.rankwatch.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow external noopener noreferrer">Local RankWatch</a> not only lists your inaccurate citations, but also offers to correct them, saving a lot of your time.</p>
<h2><strong>Optimized website </strong></h2>
<p>Your website probably marks your potential customer&rsquo;s&rsquo; first impression of your business. So, you need to make sure that it is optimized for your local keywords. It&rsquo;s best to focus on the fundamental things and let go of the little odds. Here are the things you should take care of:</p>
<ul>
  <li><strong>Domain name</strong> &ndash; Try to get a domain name that reflects your business and location. Also, try to keep it as short as possible.</li>
  <li><strong>NAP</strong> &ndash; Put your business name, phone number, city, address and ZIP on every page possible.</li>
  <li><strong>Copy</strong> &ndash; Treat this as your sales pitch. As mentioned above, try to include as much of local content as you can. Use local jargon &ndash; it will help you connect with your audience. Also, use the white space appropriately. Too many words will make the page look boring. Make sure the content is readable.</li>
  <li><strong>Use keywords</strong> &ndash; Try to include as many locally targeted keywords you can, but keep it natural.</li>
  <li><strong>Mobile optimized</strong> &ndash; Local search and mobile search are complementary in nature. People like to get their information on the go. Make sure your website is completely mobile-friendly. It will enable the users to easily check out your reviews, directions, contact information and so on.</li>
</ul>
<h2><strong>Link building </strong></h2>
<p><strong>Local link building</strong> can go a long way in attracting local attention. Also, it offers scope for developing relationships with the local community, improves search engine rankings and gets you more targeted and relevant traffic. The more local links you have, the better it is.</p>
<p>To begin, get into local directories (<strong>Google Local, Bing Places, Yahoo Local, <a href="http://www.yelp.com"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Yelp</a>, Angie&rsquo;s</strong> list etc), resource lists (Local Chamber of Commerce, local newspapers and magazines, city-based directories) and review sites (BBB.org, Yelp, CitySearch, MerchantCircle).</p>
<p>Create a team of local strategic partners. How? Start contacting local business or companies who offer complementary products or services to your business. For example, if you are a wedding planner, you can probably partner with a business that sells wedding gowns. Leverage such relationships, keep sharing each other&rsquo;s content and earn great links.</p>
<p>Local sponsorship (sponsoring conferences, talk shows, fests, fairs) is another great option for building links.</p>
<p>Generate <strong>local resources</strong> like a <strong>local map</strong> for tourist attractions, a <strong>local guide</strong> which talks about the best activities in town, cultural attractions, best pubs or hotels or a local event calendar which mentions the local sports events, festivals, etc.</p>
<p><strong>Local SEO</strong> is not a one-time thing. In order to establish your presence over the local SERPs in the long run, you need to constantly work for it.</p>
<p>Go through this checklist, follow each step and see the results in your online visibility.</p>
<p>I would love to hear any other tip I am missing on in the comments below.</p>
<h4><strong>Author Bio:</strong></h4>
<p><strong>Sahil Kakkar </strong>is the CEO and Founder of <strong><a href="https://www.rankwatch.com/"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">RankWatch</a></strong> &ndash; a platform, which helps companies and brands stay ahead with their SEO efforts in the ever growing inte.com landscape.</p>
<p><strong>Sahil </strong>likes making creative products that can help in automation of mundane tasks and he can spend endless nights implementing new technologies and ideas. You can connect with him and the Rankwatch team on <a class="seoquake-nofollow" href="https://www.facebook.com/RankWatch/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow external noopener noreferrer">Facebook</a> or <a class="seoquake-nofollow" href="https://twitter.com/RankWatch" target="_blank" rel="nofollow external noopener noreferrer">Twitter</a>.</p>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Top 6 Most Powerful Latest SEO Strategies 2016</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1896-top-6-most-powerful-latest-seo-strategies-2016.html</link>
<description></description>
<category>SEO Training</category>
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2016 02:52:09 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Any digital marketer knows the importance of having an effective SEO strategy &amp;ndash;using a few clever tactics to ensure your business ranks well when people are searching for your niche online- and search engines are a powerful tool if you know how to use them, by becoming more and more aligned with how we naturally would want to find things on the inte.com. While this is fantastic for the search engine user, this constant evolution of search engines means that we must be ahead of the curve with our search engine optimization- but if this is the first time you&amp;rsquo;ve sat down and really thought about your SEO strategies this year (or ever!), then don&amp;rsquo;t stress! A team of digital marketing gurus have compiled this fun, handy little infographic to get your search-engine optimization strategy prepared for 2016, so you know all the new algorithms and parameters to cater to. From on-page to off-page, long tail keywords to fresh and exciting content, and all the industry tips and tricks in between, scroll down and see what might be useful to you and your digital campaigns, and let us know how you go! Top 6 Most Powerful Latest SEO Strategies 2016 This infographic is Courtesy of &amp;ldquo;Dilate Digital &amp;ldquo;Perth, Western Australia</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<p>Any digital marketer knows the importance of having an <strong>effective SEO strategy</strong> &ndash;using a few clever tactics to ensure your business ranks well when people are searching for your niche online- and search engines are a powerful tool if you know how to use them, by becoming more and more aligned with how we naturally would want to find things on the inte.com.</p><br /><br /><p>While this is fantastic for the search engine user, this constant evolution of search engines means that we must be ahead of the curve with our search engine optimization- but if this is the first time you&rsquo;ve sat down and really thought about your <strong>SEO strategies</strong> this year (or ever!), then don&rsquo;t stress! A team of digital marketing gurus have compiled this fun, handy little infographic to get your search-engine optimization strategy prepared for 2016, so you know all the new algorithms and parameters to cater to.</p><br /><p>From <strong>on-page</strong> to <strong>off-page</strong>, long tail keywords to fresh and exciting content, and all the industry tips and tricks in between, scroll down and see what might be useful to you and your digital campaigns, and let us know how you go!</p><br /><p><strong><a href="https://www.dilate.com.au/blog/top-6-most-powerful-latest-seo-strategies-2016/" target="_blank">Top 6 Most Powerful Latest SEO Strategies 2016</a><br /> </strong></p><br /><p><strong>This infographic is Courtesy of &ldquo;Dilate Digital &ldquo;Perth, Western Australia</strong></p>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Tutorials7.com SEO Full Video Course Pro</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1550-tutorials7.com-seo-full-video-course-pro.html</link>
<description>Name : Tutorials7.com SEO Full Video Course Pro Version : 2016 Update Type : ScrapeBox Tutorials, Senuke Tutorials, SEO Tutorials Price : $97 Homepage : SalePage SEO Tutorials Full Course PRO – from Beginner to SEO Master! check7 Modules and 80 High-Definition (HD) Video Lessons check11 Hours 05 Minutes and 02 Seconds checkOn Page and Off Page SEO secrets revealed! checkCLICK HERE to download real customers’ SEO reports</description>
<category>SEO Training</category>
<enclosure url="http://tutorials7.com/wp-content/slideshow/seo/gallery/seo-tips-for-beginners-screenshot.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 08:03:54 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Module 1 – What is On-page and Off-page SEO? Module 2 – On Page SEO Lessons Keyword research option in Google Keyword Tool – 06m 52s How to create well-optimized articles. Basic settings. Meta tags and other essential on page SEO elements – 09m 55s SEO for images. Inner backlinking – 10m 26s On page SEO suggestions – 10m 07s Module 3 – Our On-Page SEO is Ready! Now What? Submitting your site to Google Web Tools – 08m 26s XML sitemap creation and submission – 04m 04s Robots.txt – 05m 51s Submitting your site to Google Analytics. Options – 07m 30s Validator. Checking for errors and warnings of your site – 03m 55s Backlinking process and strategy. White, Gray and Black Hat SEO. Rules. Link velocity. GEO targeting. IP Diversity – 09m 02s Finding backlinks from your niche. Authority sites-.edu and .gov sites. Social Networks – Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest, etc. – 08m 02s Module 4 – Off Page SEO SEO programs and tools – 07m 11s The Best Spinner (TBS) – excellent article spinner. Settings – 14m 16s Get Article. Find niche related articles – 05m 30s Captcha services – 08m 32s Captcha Sniper – captcha solving software solution – 02m 57s Article Marketing Robot (AMR) – article submitter. Basic settings and author creation – 16m 08s Article creation. Settings – 14m 02s Article directory submission – 10m 32s Power Submitter – simple directory submitter. Basic settings – 07m 06s Directory submission – 09m 19s AllSubmitter- advanced directory submitter. Overview – 05m 57s AllSubmitter settings – 19m 08s Directory submission – 13m 50s The results of our work – 08m 17s Other SEO tools – Sick Submitter and WikiNuke – 09m 08s Research tools. Market Samurai – quick overview – 06m 56s Inspyder Rank Reporter. Basic setting. Track your SERPs – 19m 39s Module 5 – SeNuke XCr Full Course – 30 Lessons SeNuke XCr lessons Module 6 – Scrapebox Full Course – 14 Lessons scrapebox seo Module 7 – SEO Campaigns’ Blueprints. Connecting All of the Dots Mozilla SEO Quake add-on – (4:42) Recommended services for your SEO campaigns – (13:38) Outsourcing your SEO work. Who wants to do some SEO work for me and my clients? – (16:51) SEO Mini Package. Step by step blueprint – (7:55) SEO ULTIMATE Package. Step by step blueprint – (9:06) SEO MEGA ULTIMATE Package. Step by step blueprint – (21:57) Final SEO thoughts. SEO tips and tricks – (6:04)</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/lWxr4j8sh3Q?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br />Module 1 – What is On-page and Off-page SEO?<br /><br />Module 2 – On Page SEO Lessons<br /><br />Keyword research option in Google Keyword Tool – 06m 52s<br />How to create well-optimized articles. Basic settings. Meta tags and other essential on page SEO elements – 09m 55s<br />SEO for images. Inner backlinking – 10m 26s<br />On page SEO suggestions – 10m 07s<br />Module 3 – Our On-Page SEO is Ready! Now What?<br /><br />Submitting your site to Google Web Tools – 08m 26s<br />XML sitemap creation and submission – 04m 04s<br />Robots.txt – 05m 51s<br />Submitting your site to Google Analytics. Options – 07m 30s<br />Validator. Checking for errors and warnings of your site – 03m 55s<br />Backlinking process and strategy. White, Gray and Black Hat SEO. Rules. Link velocity. GEO targeting. IP Diversity – 09m 02s<br />Finding backlinks from your niche. Authority sites-.edu and .gov sites. Social Networks – Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest, etc. – 08m 02s<br />Module 4 – Off Page SEO<br /><br />SEO programs and tools – 07m 11s<br />The Best Spinner (TBS) – excellent article spinner. Settings – 14m 16s<br />Get Article. Find niche related articles – 05m 30s<br />Captcha services – 08m 32s<br />Captcha Sniper – captcha solving software solution – 02m 57s<br />Article Marketing Robot (AMR) – article submitter. Basic settings and author creation – 16m 08s<br />Article creation. Settings – 14m 02s<br />Article directory submission – 10m 32s<br />Power Submitter – simple directory submitter. Basic settings – 07m 06s<br />Directory submission – 09m 19s<br />AllSubmitter- advanced directory submitter. Overview – 05m 57s<br />AllSubmitter settings – 19m 08s<br />Directory submission – 13m 50s<br />The results of our work – 08m 17s<br />Other SEO tools – Sick Submitter and WikiNuke – 09m 08s<br />Research tools. Market Samurai – quick overview – 06m 56s<br />Inspyder Rank Reporter. Basic setting. Track your SERPs – 19m 39s<br />Module 5 – SeNuke XCr Full Course – 30 Lessons<br /><br /><br />SeNuke XCr lessons<br /><br />Module 6 – Scrapebox Full Course – 14 Lessons<br /><br /><br />scrapebox seo<br /><br />Module 7 – SEO Campaigns’ Blueprints. Connecting All of the Dots<br /><br />Mozilla SEO Quake add-on – (4:42)<br />Recommended services for your SEO campaigns – (13:38)<br />Outsourcing your SEO work. Who wants to do some SEO work for me and my clients? – (16:51)<br />SEO Mini Package. Step by step blueprint – (7:55)<br />SEO ULTIMATE Package. Step by step blueprint – (9:06)<br />SEO MEGA ULTIMATE Package. Step by step blueprint – (21:57)<br />Final SEO thoughts. SEO tips and tricks – (6:04)<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://tutorials7.com/wp-content/slideshow/seo/gallery/seo-tips-for-beginners-screenshot.jpg" alt="Tutorials7.com SEO Full Video Course Pro" title="Tutorials7.com SEO Full Video Course Pro"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Tutorials7.com SEO Full Video Course Pro" title="Tutorials7.com SEO Full Video Course Pro"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Brian Dean - SEO That Works 2018</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1484-brian-dean-seo-that-works-2016.html</link>
<description>HDRips | MP4/AVC, ~2500 kb/s | 1280x720 | Duration: N/A | English: AAC, 128 kb/s (2 ch) Audio CDs in MP3 / English: MP3, 128 kb/s (2 ch) | Duration: N/A | ISBN-10: N/A PDF Guides Size: 6.08 GB | Genre: Business, Job How to get higher rankings with a step-by-step blueprint. - Learn advanced link building and content promotion strategies - Watch real-life case studies of people achieving first page rankings - Follow a proven step-by-step SEO system Now that you’ve seen that SEO That Works gets results in nearly any industry or niche, it’s time to learn what you’ll get when you enroll today:</description>
<category>SEO Training</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2016 21:12:23 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Module 1: Fast Track SEO Success This module is all about putting you on the fast track to SEO success. You’ll learn how to rank a new site — or an existing site — in record time. These are the exact first steps I take whenever I launch a new site or take on a new client. Module 2: How to Publish Content that Attracts Links, Traffic and Customers By the end of this module you’ll be able to generate content that you can leverage for authority backlinks and targeted traffic over and over again. How? By tapping into my 7 proven Content Frameworks. Module 3: How to promote your content and get backlinks from authority sites You may remember that I mentioned that I was able to get links from national news outlets, online magazines, and leading industry blogs on demand…without any connections. Module 4: SEO Energizers In the final module I’ll unveil my secret stash of advanced on and off-page SEO strategies that get results (FAST). These are the same tactics I turn to whenever I need to give one of my sites a quick — but significant — boost. This is a Complete SEO System for Ranking in Any Niche! Then it’s Time to Take Your Game to a Whole New Level Here’s a snapshot of what you’ll receive: Session 1 - Small Business PR Secrets Session 2 - Social Media Domination Session 3 - Local SEO Mastery Session 4 - How To Turn Traffic Into Customers Session 5 - Outsourcing Secrets</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[Module 1: Fast Track SEO Success<br>This module is all about putting you on the fast track to SEO success. You’ll learn how to rank a new site — or an existing site — in record time. These are the exact first steps I take whenever I launch a new site or take on a new client.<br><br>Module 2: How to Publish Content that Attracts Links, Traffic and Customers<br>By the end of this module you’ll be able to generate content that you can leverage for authority backlinks and targeted traffic over and over again. How? By tapping into my 7 proven Content Frameworks.<br><br>Module 3: How to promote your content and get backlinks from authority sites<br>You may remember that I mentioned that I was able to get links from national news outlets, online magazines, and leading industry blogs on demand…without any connections.<br><br>Module 4: SEO Energizers<br>In the final module I’ll unveil my secret stash of advanced on and off-page SEO strategies that get results (FAST). These are the same tactics I turn to whenever I need to give one of my sites a quick — but significant — boost.<br><br>This is a Complete SEO System for Ranking in Any Niche!<br><br>Then it’s Time to Take Your Game to a Whole New Level<br><br>Here’s a snapshot of what you’ll receive:<br><br>Session 1 - Small Business PR Secrets<br>Session 2 - Social Media Domination<br>Session 3 - Local SEO Mastery<br>Session 4 - How To Turn Traffic Into Customers<br>Session 5 - Outsourcing Secrets<br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Brian Dean - SEO That Works 2018"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>How To Find Super Profitable Rank-In-A-Week Keywords with Longtail Pro</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1222-how-to-find-super-profitable-rank-in-a-week-keywords-with-longtail-pro.html</link>
<description>How To Find Thousands Of Super Profitable Rank-In-A-Week Keywords In Foreign and High End Lead Selling Niches (AKA The Easiest Money Maker In SEO) Yes These Claims Are Outrageous, Lets Us Prove It To You Below</description>
<category>SEO Training</category>
<pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 23:39:40 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text></yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/GyMyrxLNucw?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>How to Find Profitable Keywords with Market Samurai</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1125-how-to-find-profitable-keywords-with-market-samurai.html</link>
<description>This tut is by matthewwoodward, it is very helpful, so i copy it, member can read directly A lot of niche bloggers and web site builders, simply don’t have the time to do thorough research before creating killer content and money pages. Quite often we end up targeting keywords that are either too competitive or not searched for enough. To me, a profitable keyword is one with a significant amount of searches and minimal competition. When you combine multiple profitable keywords on the same page, your search engine rankings and sales skyrocket. What You Will Learn Two word keywords vs. Long tail keywords vs. Money keywords Niche sites vs. Affiliate Blogs How to make keyword research easy 2 methods to find as many profitable keywords as you want</description>
<category>SEO Training</category>
<enclosure url="http://cdn.matthewwoodward.co.uk/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/samurai-features.jpg-618x393.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="http://cdn.matthewwoodward.co.uk/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/market-samurai-keyword-generation-618x392.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="http://cdn.matthewwoodward.co.uk/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/keywords-seo-movie-review-618x417.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://cdn.matthewwoodward.co.uk/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/semrush-keywords-618x224.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2015 21:03:09 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Two word keywords vs. Long tail keywords vs. Money keywords It is important that you understand the differnece between the types of keywords you can target and why that can make a difference between profit or failure. Two word keywords While some may think these are bringing the most traffic, they’re the worst to target for reasons you’ll find in a minute. Examples: v***** pills Credit cards Cheap shoes Birthday cards You get the idea. Two word keyterms used to be (very) profitable keywords and easy to rank back in 2000. Today, competition is fierce, and you’ll probably have to spend thousands of dollars every month to rank on page #1 for these terms – yet, attract less targeted visitors and buyers. It won’t make sense to go after such keywords anymore. Specific, long tail key phrases and money words is where the gold is. Long tail keywords 80% of most peoples’ organic traffic is generated by visitors typing in a combination of four, five or more words in Google. Long tail keywords are the rage in today’s competitive world. Yet, not all long-tail keywords are profitable. Often, long-tail keywords have little or no search volume according to Google’s Keyword Tool. Or they attract the wrong crowd of people. That’s why we have to aim only for certain long tail keywords and key phrases. Top 10 Long Tail Keywords to Target Best long tail keywords to target are the ones including: reviews review tutorials tutorial best ___ top ___ latest ___ script(s) template(s) download(s) Yet, they are not the best money makers. Money Keywords These are buying intent keywords. Best to target. What happens when you use them is simple: you start attracting buyers. People with credit cards in hand. Paypal accounts holders. Men and women actively looking for a solution to their problems. Top 20 Money Keywords To Focus On These keywords are usually made up of your main niche keyterm or product name followed by money words like.. discount buy order purchase trial coupon deal bargain bonus cheap delivery price promotion rent save shop sale shipping voucher wholesale Examples: Buy Thesis Market Samurai Trial Rent Toyota Highlander Hybrid Clothes Shop With Free Delivery The Body Shop Free Delivery Discount Code Niche sites vs. Affiliate Blogs Most people confuse affiliate blogs and niche sites, but they are actually 2 very different things. Niche sites are relevant to a particular category of people or related to a specific problem. Example: Weight loss after pregnancy Dating for seniors Blogging for dummies Niche sites can promote affiliate products and one’s own info products, services and programs. It’s like a boutique. Affiliate blogs are usually product review sites where the owner does not promote his own stuff but other people’s products. An affiliate blog can also be a niche site if it’s tailored to a specific market or problem. Any niche site can be easily turned into an affiliate blog, just like any affiliate blog can be upgraded to a niche site. Before starting your keyword research, ensure you know the type of site or blog you want to build. It can be a mix – niche affiliate blogs are everywhere these days and this very blog is a great example of that. Keyword Research Made Easy Free One of Matthew’s favourite IM tactics, especially if you are just starting out or have a limited budget is to take advantage of the world of free trials available. You see companies are deseperate to acquire new paying users and more often then not, you can get full access to their toolset free of charge for x amount of days. Even to this day Matthew takes advantage of this to string together with campaigns while keeping costs as close to zero as possible. Market Samurai does exactly that &amp;amp; will gives you instant access to a truck load of golden money terms that help build your niche sites and money pages. In short Market Samurai, is more than a keyword research tool because it also.. Monitors your page ranking in Google, Yahoo and Bing Uncovers less competitive markets in the SERPs Discovers easy link building opportunities Finds the most profitable affiliate offers Saves you time and money, by allowing you to automate all the manual tasks How To Find Those Golden Keywords So lets’ take a look at how to take full advantage of the trial to squeeze as many golden keywords out of it as we can! Step #1 – Google Integration Market Samurai integrates with Google Keyword Planner to help pull additional data. All you need is a free Google Adwords account which you can then link into Market Samurai. If you don’t have an account there is a link to create one in the software. Just head over to settings and input your account details! Step #2 – Creating Your Project Now you need to create your first project. This is where you enter the keyword you’d like to inspect. Never worry about keyword competition at this point. We’re just testing the waters. For this example, I’m going to be using the keyword phrase “portrait photography” to show you how this works. (Image credit – Kyle Larson) Starting The Keyword Gold Rush Click “Generate Keywords” and you’ll get your list of keywords for inspection or removal. Remember: you need to be signed in to your Google account in order for this tool to “fetch the keywords” along with their search counts. If you already have a list of keywords from another source, you can manually input your keyword(s) or import a list directly from your computer. Step #3 – Keyword Analysis Once you click on the ‘Keyword Analysis’ button, you will be taken to a new screen and all your keywords will be ready to be analysed. This is where Market Samurai reveals it’s true magic. A mega time saver. It generates all this info for the top 10 search results in Google for your targeted keyword at the click of a button. Best part — it takes less than a minute. If you had to access this data manually, you’d expect to spend at least 30 minutes per keyword and know how to do it. The software does everything on your behalf, and in the background – while you can do something else. Here’s an example of the type of data for “movie review” keyword (image credit – IMTips.in) Don’t be scared with the plethora of parameters Market Samurai gives you. We’ll just focus on the key ones- SEOT represents the maximum daily clicks that a #1 ranked site for your chosen keyword could potentially achieve. PBR indicateds the percentage of phrase-match searches out of broad-match searches per keyword. SEO Comp (SEOC) gives the total number of web pages globally that mention a specific keyword term, in the same (phrase) word order, in Google’s index. (as written by Kristoffer Sandven @ JoomlaBlogger) Trends shows monthly traffic trends for a particular keyword. Other important parameters to check: Total Searches gives the average number of daily searches for your keyword. OCI points the posibility that someone searching for a keyword is looking to buy as opposed to just looking for information. SEO Value (SEOV) shows the total value of traffic that a #1 ranked site gets for a particular keyword in Google SERP. It’s up to you how many parameters you want to check with the tool. These 7 are the most important in my opinion. You can see a full breakdown of the different metrics here or by holding your mouse over them. Once you have your list of golden keywords you can move each of them into the SEO Competition module to take a closer look at the current top 10. Here you can input your URL and compare it to the current top 10 results for a range of both on site and off site related metrics. 2 More Ways To Find Profitable Keywords The main problem with using a tool is that if lots of people are using the tool, then you can end up with a similar set of keyword ideas. So to help differentiate yourself from the competiton here are 2 other methods you can use to generate keywords to import for analysis in Market Samurai. Merchant Words MerchantWords is a relatively unknown service but it allows you to find out exactly what people are searching for on Amazon. Not only that but it tells you other things like search volume as well. If you’re using Amazon’s associate program then this monthly service is a true gem. A subscription gives you access to explore &amp;#8203;the top 20 million Amazon searches. If you think about it, you have buyers keywords at your finger tips. Don’t get it wrong! These are real Amazon searches that Amazon visitors use everyday as they shop. These are keywords with very high commercial intent. In other words… You get unique keyword data with search volume – so you’ll know which searches are the most popular, and which are the least popular. This lets you focus on the best phrases or do long tail research for your money pages and product reviews. SEMRush The SEMRush service needs no introduction. They’ve been around for several years now. I suggest you read this guide first: How To Discover Thousands of Profitable Keywords in Minutes Using SEMrush Then this blog post right here: SEMrush Review: 22 Stealth Competitor Research Tactics These two articles alone will give you enough insights to be able to use the tool like a pro. Source : matthewwoodward.co.uk</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h2>Two word keywords vs. Long tail keywords vs. Money keywords</h2><br />It is important that you understand the differnece between the types of keywords you can target and why that can make a difference between profit or failure.<br /><h3>Two word keywords</h3><br />While some may think these are bringing the most traffic, they’re the worst to target for reasons you’ll find in a minute.<br /><br />Examples:<br /><ul><li> v***** pills<br /></li><li> Credit cards<br /></li><li> Cheap shoes<br /></li><li> Birthday cards<br /></li></ul><br />You get the idea.<br /><br />Two word keyterms used to be (very) profitable keywords and easy to rank back in 2000.<br /><br />Today, competition is fierce, and you’ll probably have to spend thousands of dollars every month to rank on page #1 for these terms – yet, attract less targeted visitors and buyers.<br /><br />It won’t make sense to go after such keywords anymore. Specific, long tail key phrases and money words is where the gold is.<br /><h3>Long tail keywords</h3><br />80% of most peoples’ organic traffic is generated by visitors typing in a combination of four, five or more words in Google.<br /><br />Long tail keywords are the rage in today’s competitive world. Yet, not all long-tail keywords are profitable.<br /><br />Often, long-tail keywords have little or no search volume according to Google’s Keyword Tool. Or they attract the wrong crowd of people.<br /><br />That’s why we have to aim only for certain long tail keywords and key phrases.<br /><h4>Top 10 Long Tail Keywords to Target</h4><br />Best long tail keywords to target are the ones including:<br /><ul><li> reviews<br /></li><li> review<br /></li><li> tutorials<br /></li><li> tutorial<br /></li><li> best ___<br /></li><li> top ___<br /></li><li> latest ___<br /></li><li> script(s)<br /></li><li> template(s)<br /></li><li> download(s)<br /></li></ul><br />Yet, they are not the best money makers.<br /><h3>Money Keywords</h3><br />These are buying intent keywords. Best to target. What happens when you use them is simple: you start attracting buyers.<br /><br />People with credit cards in hand.<br /><br />Paypal accounts holders.<br /><br />Men and women actively looking for a solution to their problems.<br /><h4>Top 20 Money Keywords To Focus On</h4><br />These keywords are usually made up of your main niche keyterm or product name followed by money words like..<br /><ul><li> discount<br /></li><li> buy<br /></li><li> order<br /></li><li> purchase<br /></li><li> trial<br /></li><li> coupon<br /></li><li> deal<br /></li><li> bargain<br /></li><li> bonus<br /></li><li> cheap<br /></li><li> delivery<br /></li><li> price<br /></li><li> promotion<br /></li><li> rent<br /></li><li> save<br /></li><li> shop<br /></li><li> sale<br /></li><li> shipping<br /></li><li> voucher<br /></li><li> wholesale<br /></li></ul><br />Examples:<br /><ul><li> Buy Thesis<br /></li><li> Market Samurai Trial<br /></li><li> Rent Toyota Highlander Hybrid<br /></li><li> Clothes Shop With Free Delivery<br /></li><li> The Body Shop Free Delivery Discount Code<br /></li></ul><br /><h2>Niche sites vs. Affiliate Blogs</h2><br />Most people confuse affiliate blogs and niche sites, but they are actually 2 very different things.<br /><br />Niche sites are relevant to a particular category of people or related to a specific problem.<br /><br />Example:<br /><ul><li> Weight loss after pregnancy<br /></li><li> Dating for seniors<br /></li><li> Blogging for dummies<br /></li></ul><br />Niche sites can promote affiliate products and one’s own info products, services and programs. It’s like a boutique.<br /><br />Affiliate blogs are usually product review sites where the owner does not promote his own stuff but other people’s products.<br /><br />An affiliate blog can also be a niche site if it’s tailored to a specific market or problem.<br /><br />Any niche site can be easily turned into an affiliate blog, just like any affiliate blog can be upgraded to a niche site.<br /><br />Before starting your keyword research, ensure you know the type of site or blog you want to build.<br /><br />It can be a mix – niche affiliate blogs are everywhere these days and this very blog is a great example of that.<br /><h2>Keyword Research Made Easy Free</h2><br />One of Matthew’s favourite IM tactics, especially if you are just starting out or have a limited budget is to take advantage of the world of free trials available.<br /><br />You see companies are deseperate to acquire new paying users and more often then not, you can get full access to their toolset free of charge for x amount of days.<br /><br />Even to this day Matthew takes advantage of this to string together with campaigns while keeping costs as close to zero as possible.<br /><br /><a href="http://www.tgmember.com/902-market-samurai.html" >Market Samurai</a> does exactly that &amp; will gives you instant access to a truck load of golden money terms that help build your niche sites and money pages.<br /><br /><a href="http://www.tgmember.com/902-market-samurai.html" ><img class="aligncenter size-medium wp-image-38710" src="http://cdn.matthewwoodward.co.uk/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/samurai-features.jpg-618x393.jpg" alt="samurai-features.jpg" width="618" height="393" /></a><br /><br />In short Market Samurai, is more than a keyword research tool because it also..<br /><ol type="1"><li> Monitors your page ranking in Google, Yahoo and Bing<br /></li><li> Uncovers less competitive markets in the SERPs<br /></li><li> Discovers easy link building opportunities<br /></li><li> Finds the most profitable affiliate offers<br /></li><li> Saves you time and money, by allowing you to automate all the manual tasks<br /></li></ol><br /><h3>How To Find Those Golden Keywords</h3><br />So lets’ take a look at how to take full advantage of the trial to squeeze as many golden keywords out of it as we can!<br /><h4>Step #1 – Google Integration</h4><br />Market Samurai integrates with Google Keyword Planner to help pull additional data.<br /><br />All you need is a free Google Adwords account which you can then link into Market Samurai. If you don’t have an account there is a link to create one in the software.<br /><br />Just head over to settings and input your account details!<br /><h4>Step #2 – Creating Your Project</h4><br />Now you need to create your first project.<br /><br />This is where you enter the keyword you’d like to inspect. Never worry about keyword competition at this point. We’re just testing the waters.<br /><br />For this example, I’m going to be using the keyword phrase “portrait photography” to show you how this works. (Image credit – <a href="http://www.kylejlarson.com/blog/2015/market-samurai-review-increase-traffic/"  target="_blank">Kyle Larson</a>)<br /><br /><img class="aligncenter size-medium wp-image-38719" src="http://cdn.matthewwoodward.co.uk/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/market-samurai-keyword-generation-618x392.jpg" alt="market-samurai-keyword-generation" width="618" height="392" /><br /><h5>Starting The Keyword Gold Rush</h5><br />Click “Generate Keywords” and you’ll get your list of keywords for inspection or removal.<br /><br />Remember: you need to be signed in to your Google account in order for this tool to “fetch the keywords” along with their search counts.<br /><br />If you already have a list of keywords from another source, you can manually input your keyword(s) or import a list directly from your computer.<br /><h4>Step #3 – Keyword Analysis</h4><br />Once you click on the ‘<strong>Keyword Analysis</strong>’ button, you will be taken to a new screen and all your keywords will be ready to be analysed.<br /><br />This is where Market Samurai reveals it’s true magic. A mega time saver.<br /><br />It generates all this info for the top 10 search results in Google for your targeted keyword at the click of a button. Best part — <strong>it takes less than a minute</strong>.<br /><br />If you had to access this data manually, you’d expect to spend at least 30 minutes per keyword and know how to do it. The software does everything on your behalf, and in the background – while you can do something else.<br /><br />Here’s an example of the type of data for “movie review” keyword (image credit – <a href="http://imtips.co/seo-keyword-research.html"  target="_blank">IMTips.in</a>)<br /><br /><img class="aligncenter size-medium wp-image-38720" src="http://cdn.matthewwoodward.co.uk/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/keywords-seo-movie-review-618x417.png" alt="keywords-seo-movie-review" width="618" height="417" /><br /><br />Don’t be scared with the plethora of parameters Market Samurai gives you. We’ll just focus on the key ones-<br /><ol type="1"><li> <strong>SEOT</strong> represents the maximum daily clicks that a #1 ranked site for your chosen keyword could potentially achieve.<br /></li><li> <strong>PBR</strong> indicateds the percentage of phrase-match searches out of broad-match searches per keyword.<br /></li><li> <strong>SEO Comp (SEOC)</strong> gives the total number of web pages globally that mention a specific keyword term, in the same (phrase) word order, in Google’s index. (as written by Kristoffer Sandven @ <a href="http://www.joomlablogger.com/seo/joomla-seo/how-to-do-keyword-research-with-market-samurai"  target="_blank">JoomlaBlogger</a>)<br /></li><li> <strong>Trends</strong> shows monthly traffic trends for a particular keyword.<br /></li></ol><br />Other important parameters to check:<br /><ul><li> <strong>Total Searches</strong> gives the average number of daily searches for your keyword.<br /></li><li> <strong>OCI</strong> points the posibility that someone searching for a keyword is looking to buy as opposed to just looking for information.<br /></li><li> <strong>SEO Value (SEOV)</strong> shows the total value of traffic that a #1 ranked site gets for a particular keyword in Google SERP.<br /></li></ul><br />It’s up to you how many parameters you want to check with the tool. These 7 are the most important in my opinion.<br /><br />You can see a full breakdown of the different metrics <a href="http://www.noblesamurai.com/dojo/marketsamurai/8457-glossary-of-market-samurai-acronyms"  target="_blank">here</a> or by holding your mouse over them.<br /><br />Once you have your list of golden keywords you can move each of them into the SEO Competition module to take a closer look at the current top 10.<br /><br />Here you can input your URL and compare it to the current top 10 results for a range of both on site and off site related metrics.<br /><h2>2 More Ways To Find Profitable Keywords</h2><br />The main problem with using a tool is that if lots of people are using the tool, then you can end up with a similar set of keyword ideas.<br /><br />So to help differentiate yourself from the competiton here are 2 other methods you can use to generate keywords to import for analysis in Market Samurai.<br /><h3>Merchant Words</h3><br /><a href="http://merchantwords.com/"  target="_blank">MerchantWords</a> is a relatively unknown service but it allows you to find out exactly what people are searching for on Amazon.<br /><br />Not only that but it tells you other things like search volume as well. If you’re using Amazon’s associate program then this monthly service is a true gem.<br /><br />A subscription gives you access to explore &#8203;the top 20 million Amazon searches. If you think about it, you have buyers keywords at your finger tips.<br /><br />Don’t get it wrong! These are real Amazon searches that Amazon visitors use everyday as they shop. These are keywords with very high commercial intent.<br /><br />In other words…<br /><br />You get unique keyword data with search volume – so you’ll know which searches are the most popular, and which are the least popular.<br /><br />This lets you focus on the best phrases or do long tail research for your money pages and product reviews.<br /><h3>SEMRush</h3><br />The <a href="http://www.matthewwoodward.co.uk/get/semrush/"  target="_blank">SEMRush</a> service needs no introduction. They’ve been around for several years now.<br /><br /><a href="http://www.matthewwoodward.co.uk/get/semrush/"  target="_blank"><img class="aligncenter size-medium wp-image-38997" src="http://cdn.matthewwoodward.co.uk/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/semrush-keywords-618x224.jpg" alt="semrush-keywords" width="618" height="224" /></a><br /><br />I suggest you read this guide first:<br /><br /><a href="http://www.cloudliving.com/discover-profitable-keywords/"  target="_blank">How To Discover Thousands of Profitable Keywords in Minutes Using SEMrush</a><br /><br />Then this blog post right here:<br /><br /><a href="http://www.robbierichards.com/review/competitor-research/"  target="_blank">SEMrush Review: 22 Stealth Competitor Research Tactics</a><br /><br />These two articles alone will give you enough insights to be able to use the tool like a pro.<br /><strong>Source :</strong> matthewwoodward.co.uk]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>1.15 TB Lynda.com Video Tutorials</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1048-115-tb-lyndacom-video-tutorials.html</link>
<description>Name : 1.15 TB Lynda.com Video Tutorials Price : $3000 Homepage : SalePage There are 12 parts in the rar and a list of what they contain, totaling 1.15 Terabyte of video tutorials from Lynda.com. List of tutorials 2010 SBIFF Directors&#039; Panel: On Directing 2010 SBIFF Producers&#039; Panel: Movers and Shakers 2010 SBIFF Women&#039;s Panel: Creative Women in the Business 2010 SBIFF Writers&#039; Panel: It Starts with the Script 2011 SBIFF Directors&#039; Panel: Directors On Directing 2011 SBIFF Producers&#039; Panel: Movers and Shakers 2011 SBIFF Women&#039;s Panel: Creative Forces: Women in the Business 2011 SBIFF Writers&#039; Panel: It Starts with the Script 2012 SBIFF Directors&#039; Panel: Directors on Directing 2012 SBIFF Producers&#039; Panel: Movers and Shakers 2012 SBIFF Screenwriters&#039; Panel: It Starts with the Script 2012 SBIFF Women&#039;s Panel: Women in the Biz 2D Character Animation 3ds Max 2009 Beyond the Basics 3ds Max 2009 Essential Training 3ds Max 2010 Essential Training 3ds Max 2010: Lighting and Rendering with mental ray 3ds Max 2010 New Features 3ds Max 2010 Textures and Materials 3ds Max 2011 Essential Training 3ds Max 2011: Getting Started with Reactor 3ds Max 2011 New Features 3ds Max 2011: Particle Effects 3ds Max 2013 Essential Training 3ds Max 9 Essential Training 3ds Max 9 Modeling Ableton Live 8 Essential Training Access 2003 Essential Training Access 2007 Essential Training Access 2007: Forms and Reports in Depth Access 2007 Power Shortcuts Access 2007: Queries in Depth Access 2010 Essential Training Access 2010: Forms and Reports in Depth Access 2010 New Features Access 2010 Power Shortcuts Access 2010: Queries in Depth Access 2010: Real-World Projects Account Manager for FileMaker 8 Achieving Your Goals Acing Your Interview Acrobat 3D Version 8 Essential Training Acrobat 7 Essential Training Acrobat 7 New Features Acrobat 8 Professional Beyond the Basics Acrobat 8 Professional Essential Training Acrobat 9 Pro: Creating Forms Acrobat 9 Pro: Creating Multimedia Projects Acrobat 9 Pro Essential Training Acrobat 9 Pro Getting Started Acrobat 9 Pro Tips and Tricks Acrobat X: Creating Forms Acrobat X Essential Training Acrobat X Tips and Tricks ACT! 2010 Essential Training After Effects 5.0 Overview.zip After Effects 6 Essential Training.zip After Effects 7 and Flash 8 Integration.zip After Effects 7 and Photoshop CS2 Integration.zip After Effects 7 Animation Techniques.zip After Effects 7 Essential Training.zip After Effects 7 New Features.zip After Effects 7 Title Design Techniques.zip After Effects Apprentice 01: Pre-Roll.zip After Effects Apprentice 02: Basic Animation.zip After Effects Apprentice 03: Advanced Animation.zip After Effects Apprentice 04: Layer Control.zip After Effects Apprentice 05: Creating Transparency.zip After Effects Apprentice 06: Type and Music.zip After Effects Apprentice 07: Parenting.zip After Effects Apprentice 08: Nesting and Precomposing.zip After Effects Apprentice 09: Expressions.zip After Effects Apprentice 10: Time Games.zip After Effects Apprentice 11: 3D Space.zip After Effects Apprentice 12: Tracking and Keying.zip After Effects Apprentice 13: Paint and Puppet.zip After Effects Apprentice 14: Shape Layers.zip After Effects Apprentice 15: Final Project.zip After Effects CS3 Effects.zip After Effects CS3 Professional Beyond the Basics.zip After Effects CS3 Professional Essential Training.zip After Effects CS3 Professional New Features.zip After Effects CS4: Apprentice&#039;s Guide to Key Features.zip After Effects CS4 Beyond the Basics.zip After Effects CS4 Essential Training.zip After Effects CS4 Getting Started.zip After Effects CS4 New Creative Techniques.zip After Effects CS4 New Features.zip After Effects CS4: Wiggle Transform Tips.zip After Effects CS5.5 New Creative Techniques.zip After Effects CS5.5 New Features.zip After Effects CS5 Essential Training.zip After Effects CS5 New Creative Techniques.zip After Effects CS5 New Features.zip After Effects CS6 Essential Training.zip After Effects CS6 New Features.zip After Effects: Extended Vi.comte Techniques.zip After Effects: Insight into Effects.zip After Effects: Lighting Effects in Post.zip After Effects: Light Transmission.zip After Effects: Natural Light Effects.zip After Effects: Principles of Motion Graphics.zip After Effects Project Workflow.zip After Effects: Rigging a Character Arm for Animation.zip ActionScript 2.0 Beyond the Basics.zip ActionScript 2.0 Essential Training.zip ActionScript 3.0: Building Particle Systems.zip ActionScript 3.0 in Flash CS3 Professional Beyond the Basics.zip ActionScript 3.0 in Flash CS3 Professional Essential Training.zip ActionScript 3.0 in Flash CS4 Professional for Designers.zip ActionScript 3.0 in Flash Professional CS5 Essential Training.zip ActionScript 3.0 in Flex Builder 2.0 Essential Training.zip ActionScript 3.0 Projects: Game Development.zip ActionScript 3.0: Working with XML.zip Add a Video to an iBook for iPad.zip Add a Wraparound Effect for a Marquee with jQuery and Dreamweaver.zip Add a Wraparound Effect for a Marquee with jQuery.zip Adding a Filmic Glow to Your Footage Using After Effects.zip Adding a Filmic Glow to Your Footage Using Final Cut Pro.zip Adding a Filmic Glow to Your Footage Using Motion.zip Add Your jQuery Project to a Digital Magazine.zip Adobe Connect Essential Training.zip Advanced Flash 5.zip Advanced Modeling in Revit Architecture.zip Advanced Photoshop 6.zip AIR 1.5 for Dreamweaver and AJAX Developers.zip AIR 2 with Flash and Flex Essential Training.zip AIR Essential Training (200.zip AIR for Flash Developers (200.zip AIR for Flex Developers (200.zip AJAX Crash Course by SitePoint.zip AJAX Essential Training.zip Analyzing Your Website to Improve SEO.zip Android App Development with Java Essential Training.zip Animation Principles.zip Animation Tips and Tricks with Flash Professional.zip Aperture 1.1 Essential Training.zip Aperture 1.5 Beyond the Basics.zip Aperture 2 Essential Training.zip Aperture 2 New Features.zip Aperture 3 Essential Training (2012).zip Apple Color Essential Training.zip Artistic Video with Photoshop.zip Artist Series with Hillman Curtis.zip ASP.COM Essential Training.zip Audio for Film and Video with Pro Tools.zip Audio Post Workflow with Final Cut Pro X and Pro Tools.zip Audio Recording Techniques.zip Audition 2.0 Essential Training.zip Audition 3 Essential Training.zip Audition CS6 Essential Training.zip AutoCAD 2008 Essential Training.zip AutoCAD 2009: 2D Drafting Techniques.zip AutoCAD 2009: Annotation.zip AutoCAD 2009 Essential Training.zip AutoCAD 2009: Mastering References.zip AutoCAD 2009 New Features.zip AutoCAD 2010 Essential Training.zip AutoCAD 2010 New Features.zip AutoCAD 2011 Essential Training.zip AutoCAD 2011: Migrating from Windows to Mac.zip AutoCAD 2011 New Features.zip AutoCAD 2011: Tips, Tricks, and Industry Secrets.zip AutoCAD Essentials 1: Interface and Drawing Management.zip AutoCAD Essentials 2: Drawing Fundamentals.zip AutoCAD Essentials 3: Editing and Organizing Drawings.zip AutoCAD Essentials 4: Annotating a Drawing.zip AutoCAD Essentials 5: Working with References.zip AutoCAD Essentials 6: Sharing Drawings with Others.zip Avid Media Composer 5 Essential Training.zip Avid Media Composer 5 Getting Started.zip Avid Media Composer 6 Essential Training.zip Avid Xpress Pro 5.5 Essential Editing.zip Bento 2 Essential Training.zip Bento 2 New Features.zip Bento Essential Training.zip Bert Monroy, Digital Painter and Illustrator.zip Bert Monroy: Dreamscapes.zip Bert Monroy: The Making of Times Square, The People.zip Bert Monroy: The Making of Times Square, The Techniques.zip Bert Monroy: The Making of Times Square, The Tools.zip Best Practices for Flash-based Banner Ads.zip Beyond Skin: Going Deeper with Photoshop CS3.zip Big Spaceship Animated Logo: Start to Finish.zip Big Spaceship, Digital Creative Agency.zip Blackboard 9.x Essential Training for Instructors.zip Blackboard 9.x Essential Training for Students.zip Blender 2.6 Essential Training.zip Blender Essential Training.zip Blogger Essential Training (2004).zip Blue + Green Screen Production Principles.zip Brand Building Basics.zip Branden Hall: Interactive Architect and Digital Maker.zip Bridge CS4: 10 Things Designers Need to Know.zip Budgeting Video Projects.zip Building and M.comizing Game Apps for iOS.zip Building Android and iOS Applications with Flex.zip Building Android and iOS Apps with Dreamweaver CS5.5.zip Building an Ecommerce Web Site Using Dreamweaver with PHP.zip Building an Online Shopping Cart (2006).zip Building Blocks and Macros in Word.zip Building Facebook Applications with HTML and j&amp;#097;vascript.zip Building Flash Games with Starling.zip Building Mobile Apps for Multiple Devices with Flash Professional.zip Building Templates in Word.zip Camtasia Studio 8 Essential Training.zip Captivate 2 Essential Training.zip Captivate 4 Essential Training.zip Captivate 5 Essential Training.zip Capture NX 2 Essential Training.zip Carrara 5 Essential Training.zip C_C++ Essential Training.zip C# Essential Training.zip CGI Essential Training.zip Digital Anarchy Demonstration.zip Digital Asset Management for Photographers.zip Digital Audio Principles.zip Digital Creature Creation in ZBrush, Photoshop, and Maya.zip Digital Matte Painting: Changing a Scene From Summer to Winter.zip Digital Photography Principles: The Camera.zip Digital Photography Principles.zip Digital Publishing Fundamentals.zip Digital Video Principles.zip Director MX Essential Training.zip Distributing iOS Applications Through the App Store.zip Distributing Mac OS X Applications Through the App Store.zip Divvy-Up for FileMaker 8.zip Documentary Editing with Avid Media Composer.zip Documentary Editing with Final Cut Pro X.zip Documentary Editing with Premiere Pro.zip Documentary Photo Techniques with Photoshop and After Effects.zip Douglas Kirkland on Photography: A Conversation with Gerd Ludwig.zip Douglas Kirkland on Photography: A Photographer&#039;s Eye.zip Douglas Kirkland on Photography: Editorial Assignment.zip Douglas Kirkland on Photography: Natural Light Portraiture.zip Douglas Kirkland on Photography: Photographing Kids and Families.zip Douglas Kirkland on Photography: Shooting with a Medium-Format Camera.zip Douglas Kirkland on Photography: Shooting with an 8x10 Camera.zip Douglas Kirkland on Photography: Studio Portraiture.zip Douglas Kirkland, Photographer.zip Doyald Young, Logotype Designer.zip Dragon Web Surveys for FileMaker 8.5.zip Character Animation Fundamentals in 3ds Max.zip Character Animation Fundamentals with Maya.zip Character Animation in Discreet 3ds max 6.zip Character Rigging in Discreet 3ds max 6.zip Character Rigging in Maya.zip Choosing and Using Web Fonts.zip CINEMA 4D and After Effects Integration.zip CINEMA 4D: Designing a Promo.zip CINEMA 4D Essentials 1: Interface, Objects, and Hierarchies.zip CINEMA 4D Essentials 2: Polygon and Spline Modeling.zip CINEMA 4D Essentials 3: Cameras, Animation, and Deformers.zip CINEMA 4D Essentials 4: Materials, Texturing, and Lights.zip CINEMA 4D Essentials 5: Rendering and Compositing.zip CINEMA 4D Essentials 6: HyperNURB Modeling and Sculpting.zip CINEMA 4D Essentials 7: MoGraph Modeling and Animation.zip CINEMA 4D Essentials 8: Character Rigging and Xpresso.zip CINEMA 4D Essentials 9: Particles and Dynamics.zip CINEMA 4D R10 Essential Training.zip CINEMA 4D R11.5 Essential Training.zip CINEMA 4D R12 Essential Training.zip CINEMA 4D R13 New Features.zip CINEMA 4D R9.5 Essential Training.zip CINEMA 4D: Rendering Motion Graphics for After Effects.zip Cleaning Up Your Excel Data.zip Cloud Computing First Look.zip CMS Fundamentals.zip Cocoa Essential Training.zip ColdFusion 8 Beyond the Basics.zip ColdFusion 8 Essential Training.zip ColdFusion 8 New Features.zip ColdFusion 9: AJAX Controls and Techniques.zip ColdFusion 9 Essential Training.zip ColdFusion 9 New Features.zip ColdFusion Builder Essential Training.zip ColdFusion MX Essential Training.zip Color 1.5 Essential Training.zip Color 1.5 New Features.zip Color Correction: Creating a Polished Look in Avid Media Composer.zip Color Correction in Final Cut Pro X.zip Color Management Essential Training.zip Compressor 2.1 Essential Training.zip Compressor 3.5 Essential Training.zip Compressor 3 Essential Training.zip Compressor 4 Essential Training.zip Compressor Essential Training.zip Computer Literacy for the Mac.zip Computer Literacy for Windows.zip Computer Privacy and Security Essential Training (2006).zip Contribute 3 Essential Training.zip Contribute CS3 Essential Training.zip Contribute CS4 Essential Training.zip Core Data for iOS and OS X.zip CorelDRAW 12 Beyond the Basics.zip CorelDRAW Essential Training.zip CorelDRAW Graphics Suite X3 Essential Training.zip CorelDRAW X4 Essential Training.zip Corel Painter 11: Mastering Brushes.zip Create an Animated Bar Chart with jQuery and Dreamweaver.zip Create an Animated Bar Chart with jQuery.zip Create and Embed a Photo Gallery in a PDF.zip Create an Expandable FAQ Listing with jQuery and Dreamweaver.zip Create an Expandable FAQ Listing with jQuery.zip Create an HTML5 Video Gallery with jQuery and Dreamweaver.zip Create an HTML5 Video Gallery with jQuery.zip Create Animated Rollovers with jQuery and Dreamweaver.zip Create Animated Rollovers with jQuery.zip Create an Interactive Homepage Marquee with jQuery and Dreamweaver.zip Create an Interactive Homepage Marquee with jQuery.zip Create an Interactive Map with jQuery and Dreamweaver.zip Create an Interactive Map with jQuery.zip Create an Interactive Photo Gallery with jQuery and Dreamweaver.zip Create an iPad Web App.zip Create an Online Portfolio with WordPress.zip Create a Rotating Carousel with jQuery and Dreamweaver.zip Create a Rotating Carousel with jQuery.zip Create a Sliding Tabbed Panel with jQuery and Dreamweaver.zip Create a Sliding Tabbed Panel with jQuery.zip Create a Tooltip with jQuery and Dreamweaver.zip Create a Tooltip with jQuery.zip Create Navigation Menus with jQuery and Dreamweaver.zip Create Navigation Menus with jQuery.zip Create Your First Online Store with Drupal Commerce.zip Create Your First Online Store with Magento Go.zip Creating a CSS Style Guide: Hands-On Training.zip Creating a First Web Site with Dreamweaver CS4.zip Creating a First Web Site with Dreamweaver CS5.zip Creating a First Web Site with Dreamweaver CS6.zip Creating a First Web Site with Flash CS4 Professional.zip Creating a First Web Site with Flash Professional CS5.zip Creating a Fixed-Layout EPUB.zip Creating a Mini Documentary with Premiere Elements.zip Creating an Adaptive Web Site for Multiple Screens.zip Creating and Managing a Blog Network with WordPress.zip Creating an Effective Resume.zip Creating an HTML Email Newsletter.zip Creating Animated Characters in After Effects.zip Creating an Online Resume: Hands-On Training.zip Creating a Portfolio Web Site Using Flash CS4 Professional.zip Creating a Responsive Web Design.zip Creating a Sports Highlight Reel with iMovie.zip Creating a Vacation Video with iMovie.zip Creating Dynamic Menus.zip Creating Flash Web Sites in Encore CS4.zip Creating Game Environments in Maya and Photoshop.zip Creating Long Documents with InDesign.zip Creating Particle and Fire Effects with Maya.zip Creating Photo Books with Blurb.zip Creating Urban Game Environments in 3ds Max.zip Creative Slideshows with Aperture.zip Crystal Reports 2011 Essential Training.zip CSS2 Essential Training (2003).zip CSS3 First Look.zip CSS: Core Concepts.zip CSS Crash Course by SitePoint.zip CSS for Designers.zip CSS for Developers.zip CSS Fundamentals.zip CSS: Page Layouts.zip CSS Positioning Best Practices.zip CSS: Styling Forms.zip CSS: Transitions and Transforms.zip CSS Web Site Design.zip CSS with LESS and Sass.zip Dale Herigstad and Schematic, Interactive Design Agency.zip Deke&#039;s Techniques: The Challenge.zip Deke&#039;s Techniques.zip Designing a Book Cover.zip Designing a Brochure.zip Designing a Business Card.zip Designing a CD Cover.zip Designing a House in Revit Architecture.zip Designing a Logo.zip Designing a Magazine Cover.zip Designing a Magazine Layout.zip Designing a Newsletter.zip Designing a Portfolio Website with Muse.zip Designing a Poster.zip Designing a Restaurant Menu.zip Designing Web Sites from Photoshop to Dreamweaver.zip Design in Motion.zip Developing a Style Guide.zip Device Central CS4 Essential Training.zip Dreamweaver 8 Beyond the Basics.zip Dreamweaver 8 Dynamic Development.zip Dreamweaver 8 Essential Training.zip Dreamweaver 8 New Features.zip Dreamweaver and WordPress: Building Mobile Sites.zip Dreamweaver and WordPress: Building Sites.zip Dreamweaver and WordPress: Building Themes.zip Dreamweaver and WordPress: Core Concepts.zip Dreamweaver CS3 Beyond the Basics.zip Dreamweaver CS3 Dynamic Development.zip Dreamweaver CS3 Essential Training.zip Dreamweaver CS3 Projects: Creating Custom Spry Widgets.zip Dreamweaver CS3 with CSS Essential Training.zip Dreamweaver CS4 Dynamic Development.zip Dreamweaver CS4 Essential Training.zip Dreamweaver CS4 Getting Started.zip Dreamweaver CS4: Introduction to Spry.zip Dreamweaver CS4 New Features.zip Dreamweaver CS4 with CSS Essential Training.zip Dreamweaver CS5.5 New Features.zip Dreamweaver CS5 Essential Training.zip Dreamweaver CS5: Getting Started with HTML5.zip Dreamweaver CS5 New Features.zip Dreamweaver CS6 Essential Training.zip Dreamweaver CS6 New Features.zip Dreamweaver MX 2004 Beyond the Basics.zip Dreamweaver MX 2004 Dynamic Development with ASP.zip Dreamweaver MX 2004 Essential Training.zip Dreamweaver with PHP and MySQL.zip Drupal 6: Creating and Editing Custom Themes.zip Drupal 6 Essential Training.zip Drupal 6: Online Presentation of Data.zip Drupal 7 Advanced Training.zip Drupal 7: Creating and Editing Custom Themes.zip Drupal 7 Custom Module Development.zip Drupal 7 Essential Training.zip Drupal 7 New Features.zip Drupal 7: Reporting and Visualizing Data.zip Drupal Gardens Essential Training.zip DSLR Video Tips.zip Duarte Design, Presentation Design Studio.zip DVD Studio Pro 3 Essential Training.zip DVD Studio Pro 4 + Compressor 2 New Features.zip DVD Studio Pro 4 Essential Training.zip EaselJS First Look.zip eBay for Buyers Essential Training.zip eBay for Sellers Essential Training.zip Ed Emberley, Children&#039;s Book Illustrator.zip Edge First Look Preview 6.zip Editing Video in Photoshop CS6.zip Editing with Composites and Effects in Avid Media Composer.zip Effective Email (2006).zip Effective Email Marketing Strategies.zip Effective HTML Email and Newsletters.zip Effective Meetings.zip Effective Presentations (2006).zip Effective Public Speaking.zip Effective Storytelling with Final Cut Pro X.zip Encore CS3 Essential Training.zip Encore CS4 Essential Training.zip Encore CS4 Getting Started.zip Encore CS4 New Features.zip Encore CS5 Essential Training.zip Encore CS5 New Features.zip Encore DVD 2.0 Essential Training.zip Enhancing an Environmental Portrait with Photoshop.zip Enhancing Digital Photography with Photoshop CS2.zip Enhancing Digital Photography with Photoshop CS.zip Entourage 2008 for Mac Essential Training.zip Excel 2003 Essential Training.zip Excel 2007: Advanced Formatting Techniques.zip Excel 2007: Advanced Formulas and Functions.zip Excel 2007: Business Statistics.zip Excel 2007: Charts in Depth.zip Excel 2007: Creating and Managing Invoices.zip Excel 2007: Creating Business Budgets.zip Excel 2007: Creating Charts with Dynamic Data.zip Excel 2007: Data Validation in Depth.zip Excel 2007 Essential Training.zip Excel 2007: Financial Analysis.zip Excel 2007: Introduction to Formulas and Functions.zip Excel 2007: Macros in Depth.zip Excel 2007: Managing Multiple Worksheets and Workbooks.zip Excel 2007: Pivot Tables for Data Analysis.zip Excel 2007 Power Shortcuts.zip Excel 2007: Working with Dates and Times.zip Excel 2008 for Mac Essential Training.zip Excel 2008 for Mac: Pivot Tables for Data Analysis.zip Excel 2010: Advanced Formatting Techniques.zip Excel 2010: Advanced Formulas and Functions.zip Excel 2010: Charts in Depth.zip Excel 2010: Data Validation in Depth.zip Excel 2010 Essential Training.zip Excel 2010: Financial Functions in Depth.zip Excel 2010: Macros in Depth.zip Excel 2010: Managing Multiple Worksheets and Workbooks.zip Excel 2010 New Features.zip Excel 2010: Pivot Tables in Depth.zip Excel 2010 Power Shortcuts.zip Excel 2010: Real-World Projects.zip Excel 2010: Working with Dates and Times.zip Excel for Mac 2011 Essential Training.zip Expression Blend Beta Preview.zip Expression Web: CSS Workflow.zip Expression Web Essential Training.zip Facebook Essential Training (2012).zip Family and Group Portraiture.zip Family Photography: Taking and Sharing Great Photographs.zip FileMaker 8.5 Web Publishing.zip FileMaker Pro 10 Essential Training.zip FileMaker Pro 11 Essential Training.zip FileMaker Pro 11 New Features.zip FileMaker Pro 12 Essential Training.zip FileMaker Pro 7 Essential Training.zip FileMaker Pro 8.5 Beyond the Basics.zip FileMaker Pro 8.5 Essential Training.zip FileMaker Pro 8.5 New Features.zip FileMaker Pro 9 Beyond the Basics.zip FileMaker Pro 9 Essential Training.zip Film Scoring with Pro Tools.zip Final Cut Express 4 Essential Training.zip Final Cut Express HD 3.5 Essential Training.zip Final Cut Pro 5 Beyond the Basics.zip Final Cut Pro 5 Color Correction.zip Final Cut Pro 5 Essential Editing.zip Final Cut Pro 5 Essential Effects.zip Final Cut Pro 6 Essential Editing.zip Final Cut Pro 6 Essential Effects.zip Final Cut Pro 6 New Features.zip Final Cut Pro 6 with Photoshop CS3 Integration.zip Final Cut Pro 6 Workflow.zip Final Cut Pro 7 Essential Training.zip Final Cut Pro: Lighting Effects in Post.zip Final Cut Pro Optimization and Troubleshooting.zip Final Cut Pro X Essential Training.zip Final Cut Server 1.5 Getting Started.zip Final Cut Studio 2: Chroma Keying.zip Final Cut Studio 2: Moving on Stills.zip Final Cut Studio Integration.zip Final Cut Studio Overview.zip Final Cut Studio: Round-Tripping.zip Finale 2012 Essential Training.zip Fireworks 8 Essential Training.zip Fireworks CS3 Essential Training.zip Fireworks CS4 Essential Training.zip Fireworks CS4 Getting Started.zip Fireworks CS4 New Features.zip Fireworks CS4: Rapid Prototyping.zip Fireworks CS5 Essential Training.zip Fireworks CS5 New Features.zip Fireworks CS5: Rapid Prototyping.zip Fireworks CS6 Essential Training.zip Fireworks CS6 New Features.zip Fireworks MX 2004 Essential Training.zip Fixing Video Exposure Problems in Premiere Pro.zip Flash 8 and FileMaker 8.5 Integration.zip Flash Builder 4.5 and Flex 4.5 New Features.zip Flash Builder 4 and Flex 4 Essential Training.zip Flash Builder 4 and Flex 4 New Features.zip Flash Catalyst CS5.5 Essential Training.zip Flash Catalyst CS5 Essential Training.zip Flash CS3 Animation Secrets.zip Flash CS3 for Designers.zip Flash CS3 Interactive Video Techniques.zip Flash CS3 Professional Beyond the Basics.zip Flash CS3 Professional: Creating Games for the Wii.zip Flash CS3 Professional Essential Training.zip Flash CS3 Professional Fundamentals.zip Flash CS3 Projects: Delivering Flash to Mobile Devices.zip Flash CS4 Professional Audio Techniques.zip Flash CS4 Professional: Building Search Engine Friendly Sites.zip Flash CS4 Professional: Building UI Elements.zip Flash CS4 Professional Essential Training.zip Flash CS4 Professional Getting Started.zip Flash CS4 Professional New Features.zip Flash CS4 Professional: Object-Oriented Programming.zip Flash CS4 Professional Tools for Character Animation.zip Flash MX 2004 Audio and Video Integration.zip Flash MX 2004 Beyond the Basics.zip Flash MX 2004 Essential Training.zip Flash Player 10 New Features.zip Flash Professional 8 Beyond the Basics.zip Flash Professional 8 Building Data-Driven Applications.zip Flash Professional 8 Essential Training.zip Flash Professional 8 New Features.zip Flash Professional 8 Video Integration.zip Flash Professional CS5.5 New Features.zip Flash Professional CS5: Animation Projects.zip Flash Professional CS5: Character Animation.zip Flash Professional CS5: Code Snippets and Templates in Depth.zip Flash Professional CS5: Creating a Simple Game for Android Devices.zip Flash Professional CS5: Creating a Simple Game for iOS Devices.zip Flash Professional CS5 Essential Training.zip Flash Professional CS5 New Features.zip Flash Professional CS6 Essential Training.zip Flash Professional CS6 New Features.zip Flash Professional Power Shortcuts.zip Flash User Experience Best Practices.zip Flex 2 Advanced: Using Data Services.zip Flex 2 Beyond the Basics.zip Flex 2 Essential Training.zip Flex 3 Beyond the Basics.zip Flex 3 Essential Training.zip Flex 3 New Features.zip Flex 4.5 and PHP: Creating Data-Driven Applications.zip Flex 4.6 and AIR 3.0 New Features for Mobile Apps.zip Flickr Essential Training.zip Font Management.zip Food and Drink Photography.zip Foundations of Audio: Compression and Dynamic Processing.zip Foundations of Audio: Delay and Modulation.zip Foundations of Audio: EQ and Filters.zip Foundations of Photography: Black and White.zip Foundations of Photography: Composition.zip Foundations of Photography: Exposure.zip Foundations of Photography: Lenses.zip Foundations of Photography: Night and Low Light.zip Foundations of Programming: Fundamentals.zip Foundations of Programming: Object-Oriented Design.zip FrameMaker 10 Essential Training.zip FrontPage 2003 Essential Training.zip Fundamentals of Software Version Control.zip Fundamentals of Video: Cameras and Shooting.zip Game Character Creation in Maya.zip Game Prop Creation in 3ds Max.zip Game Prop Creation in Maya.zip GarageBand &#039;08 Essential Training.zip GarageBand &#039;09 Essential Training.zip GarageBand &#039;11 Essential Training.zip GarageBand 2 Essential Training.zip Getting Pro Results from a Compact Camera.zip Getting Started with Acrobat 8 Professional.zip Getting Started with Apple Color.zip Getting Started with CAT Rigging Tools in 3ds Max.zip Getting Started with CorelDRAW 11.zip Getting Started with CorelDRAW Graphics Suite 12.zip Getting Started with CorelDRAW Graphics Suite X3.zip Getting Started with Corel Painter 8.zip Getting Started with Corel Painter Essentials 3.zip Getting Started with Corel Painter IX.zip Getting Started with Corel Paint Shop Pro Photo X2.zip Getting Started with Corel Paint Shop Pro Photo XI.zip Getting Started with Dreamweaver CS5 and Business Catalyst.zip Getting Started with Expression Blend.zip Getting Started with Expression Design.zip Getting Started with Paint Shop Pro X.zip Getting Started with Quark Interactive Designer.zip Getting Started With WordPerfect Office X3.zip Getting Started with WordPerfect Office X4.zip Git Essential Training.zip Gmail Essential Training.zip Gmail for Power Users.zip GoLive 9 New Features.zip GoLive CS2 Essential Training.zip Google AdWords Essential Training.zip Google Analytics Essential Training.zip Google Calendar Essential Training.zip Google Docs Essential Training.zip Google Drive Essential Training.zip Google+ First Look.zip Google+ for Business.zip Google SketchUp 6 Essential Training.zip Google SketchUp 7 New Features.zip Google SketchUp 8 Essential Training.zip Google SketchUp Pro: Tools and Techniques.zip Graphic Secrets for Business Professionals.zip Groove 2007 Essential Training.zip Harry Marks, Broadcast Designer.zip HD Workflows with Final Cut Studio 2.zip Hello Design, Interactive Design Studio.zip Hot Looks Using Floating Point in After Effects.zip Hot Studio, Experience Design.zip Hot Studio&#039;s Open Architecture Network: Start to Finish.zip How to use lynda.com.zip HTML5: Background Processes with Web Workers.zip HTML5: Document Editing in Depth.zip HTML5: Drag and Drop in Depth.zip HTML5: File API in Depth.zip HTML5 First Look.zip HTML5 for Flash Developers.zip HTML5: Geolocation in Depth.zip HTML5: Graphics and Animation with Canvas.zip HTML5: Local Storage and Offline Applications in Depth.zip HTML5: Managing Browser History.zip HTML5: Messaging and Communications in Depth.zip HTML5: Structure, Syntax, and Semantics.zip HTML5 + UX: Advanced To-Do List.zip HTML5 + UX: Customized Photo Cards.zip HTML5 + UX: Engaging Ecommerce.zip HTML5: Video and Audio in Depth.zip HTML5: Web Forms in Depth.zip HTML Essential Training (2012).zip iBooks Author Essential Training.zip iDVD &#039;08 Essential Training.zip iDVD &#039;09 Essential Training.zip iLife &#039;09 New Features.zip Illustrator CS2 and Flash 8 Integration.zip Illustrator CS2 Creative Techniques.zip Illustrator CS2 Essential Training.zip Illustrator CS2 FAQs.zip Illustrator CS2 Power Shortcuts.zip Illustrator CS3 and Flash CS3 Professional Integration.zip Illustrator CS3 Essential Training.zip Illustrator CS3 for the Web.zip Illustrator CS3 One-on-One: Advanced Techniques.zip Illustrator CS3 One-on-One: Beyond the Basics.zip Illustrator CS3 One-on-One: The Essentials.zip Illustrator CS4 Beyond the Basics.zip Illustrator CS4 Essential Training.zip Illustrator CS4 for the Web.zip Illustrator CS4 Getting Started.zip Illustrator CS4 New Features.zip Illustrator CS4 One-on-One: Advanced.zip Illustrator CS4 One-on-One: Fundamentals.zip Illustrator CS4 One-on-One: Mastery.zip Illustrator CS5 Essential Training.zip Illustrator CS5 for Web and Interactive Design.zip Illustrator CS5 New Features.zip Illustrator CS5 One-on-One: Advanced.zip Illustrator CS5 One-on-One: Fundamentals.zip Illustrator CS5 One-on-One: Mastery.zip Illustrator CS6 Essential Training.zip Illustrator CS6 New Features.zip Illustrator CS6 One-on-One: Fundamentals.zip Illustrator CS Essential Training.zip Illustrator for Web Design.zip Illustrator Insider Training: Coloring Artwork.zip Illustrator Insider Training: Drawing without the Pen Tool.zip Illustrator Insider Training: Rethinking the Essentials.zip Illustrator Insider Training: Seeing Through Transparency.zip Illustrator Insider Training: Type and Text.zip iMovie &#039;08 Essential Training.zip iMovie &#039;09 Essential Training.zip iMovie &#039;11 Essential Training.zip iMovie for iPad Essential Training.zip iMovie HD 6 + iDVD 6 Essential Training.zip iMovie HD + iDVD 5 Essential Training.zip Improving SEO Using Accessibility Techniques.zip InCopy CS2 Essential Training.zip InCopy CS3 + InDesign CS3 Integration.zip InCopy CS4 and InDesign CS4 Workflow Essential Training.zip InDesign: 10 Essential Tips.zip InDesign: 10 Things to Know About GREP.zip InDesign CS2 Beyond the Basics.zip InDesign CS2 Essential Training.zip InDesign CS2 Power Shortcuts.zip InDesign CS2 Print Project Workflow.zip InDesign CS2 Professional Typography.zip InDesign CS3 Beyond the Basics.zip InDesign CS3 Essential Training.zip InDesign CS3 Long Documents.zip InDesign CS3 One-on-One: Style Sheets.zip InDesign CS3 Prepress Essentials.zip InDesign CS3 Professional Typography.zip InDesign CS4: 10 Free Must-Have Plug-ins.zip InDesign CS4: 10 Free Must-Have Scripts.zip InDesign CS4: 10 Habits of Highly Effective Pros.zip InDesign CS4: 10 Things to Know About Interactive PDFs.zip InDesign CS4: 10 Tips for Troubleshooting Files.zip InDesign CS4 Beyond the Basics.zip InDesign CS4 Essential Training.zip InDesign CS4 Getting Started.zip InDesign CS4: Interactive Documents and Presentations.zip InDesign CS4 New Features.zip InDesign CS4 Power Shortcuts.zip InDesign CS4 to EPUB, Kindle, and iPad.zip InDesign CS4: Typography.zip InDesign CS5.5 New Features.zip InDesign CS5.5 to EPUB, Kindle, and iPad.zip InDesign CS5: Collaborative Workflows with InCopy CS5.zip InDesign CS5: Dynamic Publishing Workflows in XML.zip InDesign CS5 Essential Training.zip InDesign CS5: Interactive Documents and Presentations.zip InDesign CS5 New Features.zip InDesign CS5: Print Production Guidelines.zip InDesign CS5 to EPUB, Kindle, and iPad.zip InDesign CS6 Essential Training.zip InDesign CS6: Interactive Documents.zip InDesign CS6 New Features.zip InDesign CS6 to EPUB, Kindle, and iPad.zip InDesign CS Essential Training.zip InDesign for Web Design.zip InDesign FX.zip InDesign Secrets.zip InDesign Styles in Depth.zip InDesign Tables In Depth.zip InDesign Typography.zip Infographics: Area Bubbles.zip Infographics: Planning and Wireframing.zip Infographics: Visualizing Relationships.zip InfoPath 2007 Essential Training.zip InfoPath 2010 Essential Training.zip Inkjet Printing for Photographers.zip Insights from a Business Coach.zip Insights from a Career Coach.zip Insights from a Content Marketer.zip Insights from an Online Marketer.zip Inspector for FileMaker Pro 8.5 Advanced.zip Installing Apache, MySQL, and PHP.zip Interaction Design Fundamentals.zip Interaction Design: Process and Inspiration.zip Interactive Data Visualization with Processing.zip Intermediate Dreamweaver 4.zip Intermediate Dreamweaver MX.zip Intermediate Flash 5.zip Intermediate Flash MX.zip Introduction to Inte.com Searching (2004).zip Invaluable: Becoming a Leading Authority.zip Invaluable: Building Professional Connections.zip Invaluable: Developing Your Business Savvy.zip Invaluable: Making Yourself Irreplaceable.zip Invaluable: Unlocking Your Abilities.zip iOS 4 App Development New Features.zip iOS 4: Building Data-Driven Applications.zip iOS 4 Web Applications with HTML5 and CSS3.zip iOS 5 SDK New Features.zip iOS SDK: Building Apps with MapKit and Core Location.zip iOS SDK Essential Training (2012).zip iPad Music Production: GarageBand.zip iPad Music Production: Inputs, Mics, and MIDI.zip iPad Tips and Tricks.zip iPhone and iPod Touch iOS 4 Essential Training.zip iPhone and iPod touch iOS 5 Essential Training.zip iPhone Photography, from Shooting to Storytelling.zip iPhone SDK: Developing iPad Applications.zip iPhone SDK Essential Training (2009).zip iPhoto &#039;08 Essential Training.zip iPhoto &#039;09: 10 Things to Know About Facebook.zip iPhoto &#039;09: 10 Things to Know About Faces.zip iPhoto &#039;09: 10 Things to Know About Flickr.zip iPhoto &#039;09: 10 Things to Know About Places.zip iPhoto &#039;09 Essential Training.zip iPhoto &#039;11 Essential Training.zip iPhoto 5 Essential Training.zip iPhoto 6 Essential Training.zip iTunes 10 Essential Training.zip iTunes 5 and 6 + iPod Essential Training.zip iTunes 7 New Features.zip iTunes 9 Essential Training.zip iWeb &#039;08 Essential Training.zip iWeb &#039;09 Essential Training.zip iWeb Essential Training.zip iWork &#039;09 New Features.zip Jason Bentley, Radio DJ and Musician.zip Jason Bentley&#039;s Twilight Remix: Start to Finish.zip Java Advanced Training.zip Java Essential Training.zip j&amp;#097;vascript Essential Training (2007).zip j&amp;#097;vascript Essential Training (2011).zip Jerry Uelsmann and Maggie Taylor: This is not photography.zip Job Search Strategies.zip Joomla! 1.5: Creating and Editing Custom Templates.zip Joomla! 1.5: Developing Secure Sites.zip Joomla! 1.5 Essential Training.zip Joomla! 1.5: Styling with CSS.zip Joomla! 1.6 and 1.7 Essential Training.zip Joomla! 1.7 and Joomla! 2.5: Access Control Lists in Depth.zip Joomla! 1.7: Programming and Packaging Extensions.zip Joomla! 2.5 Essential Training.zip Joomla!: Creating and Editing Custom Templates.zip jQuery Essential Training.zip jQuery Mobile Essential Training.zip jQuery Mobile Web Applications.zip Keynote &#039;08 Essential Training.zip Keynote &#039;09 Essential Training.zip Keynote 2 Essential Training.zip Keynote 3 Essential Training.zip Kit Hinrichs, Graphic Designer.zip Kuler Essential Training.zip Layouts with CSS in Dreamweaver.zip Learning Acrobat 5.zip Learning Acrobat 6.zip Learning ActionScript in Flash MX.zip Learning Adobe CS Integration and Version Cue.zip Learning After Effects 5.zip Learning Amorphium Pro.zip Learning Director 8.5.zip Learning Discreet 3ds max 6.zip Learning Dreamweaver 3.zip Learning Dreamweaver 4.zip Learning Dreamweaver MX.zip Learning Final Cut Pro 4.zip Learning Fireworks 3.zip Learning Fireworks 4.zip Learning Fireworks MX.zip Learning Flash 5.zip Learning Flash MX.zip Learning GarageBand.zip Learning GoLive 6.zip Learning GoLive CS.zip Learning GREP with InDesign.zip Learning iLife: iTunes 4, iPhoto 2, iMovie 3 and iDVD 3.zip Learning Illustrator 10.zip Learning Illustrator 9.zip Learning InDesign 2.zip Learning Inte.com Explorer 6.zip Learning Jasc Paint Shop Power Suite Photo Edition.zip Learning Keynote.zip Learning LiveType.zip Learning Mac OS X 10.2 Jaguar.zip Learning Mac OS X 10.3 Panther.zip Learning Motion.zip Learning Photoshop 6 and ImageReady 3 for the Web.zip Learning Photoshop 6.zip Learning Photoshop 7.zip Learning Photoshop CS for the Web.zip Learning Photoshop Elements 2.zip Learning Photoshop Elements.zip Learning QuarkXPress 5.zip Learning the After Effects Glow Plug-In.zip Learning UltraDev 4.zip Learning Windows Movie Maker 2.zip Lighting for Photographers: Portraiture.zip Lighting Tricks in After Effects.zip LightWave 10 Essential Training.zip LinkedIn Essential Training.zip LiveType 2 Essential Training.zip Logic Pro 8 Essential Training.zip Logic Pro 9 Essential Training.zip Logic Pro 9 New Features.zip lynda.com Presents: AIGA.zip</description>
<category>SEO Training</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2015 23:07:19 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Mac OS X 10.4 Tiger Beyond the Basics.zip Mac OS X 10.4 Tiger Essential Training.zip Mac OS X 10.5 Leopard Beyond the Basics.zip Mac OS X 10.5 Leopard Essential Training.zip Mac OS X 10.5 Leopard New Features.zip Mac OS X 10.6 Snow Leopard New Features.zip Mac OS X Lion Essential Training.zip Mac OS X Lion Server Essential Training.zip Mac OS X Mountain Lion New Features.zip Mac OS X Server 10.4 Tiger Essential Training.zip Mac OS X Server 10.5 Leopard Essential Training.zip Mac OS X Server 10.6 Snow Leopard: DNS and Network Services.zip Mac OS X Server 10.6 Snow Leopard Essential Training.zip Mac OS X Server 10.6 Snow Leopard New Features.zip Managing a Hosted Web Site.zip Managing and Analyzing Data in Excel.zip Managing CSS in Dreamweaver.zip Managing Documents with SharePoint 2010.zip Managing Spam Essential Training.zip Managing Your Career.zip Margo Chase, Graphic Designer.zip Margo Chase&#039;s Hand-Lettered Poster: Start to Finish.zip Marian Bantjes, Graphic Artist.zip Mark Mothersbaugh, Music Composer.zip Matting, Framing, and Hanging Your Photographs.zip Maximizing Your Web Video and Podcast Audience with Hypersyndication.zip Maya 2008 Essential Training.zip Maya 2009 Essential Training.zip Maya 2009 New Features.zip Maya 2010: Getting Started with MatchMover, Toxik, and Backburner.zip Maya 2011: Creating Natural Environments.zip Maya 2011: Creating Textures and Shaders.zip Maya 2011 Essential Training.zip Maya 2011 Lighting and Rendering in mental ray.zip Maya 2011: Modeling a Character.zip Maya 2011 New Features.zip Maya 6.5 Essential Training.zip Maya 8.5 Character Rigging.zip Maya 8 Essential Training.zip Maya Essentials 1: Interface and Organization.zip Maya Essentials 2: Polygonal Modeling Techniques.zip Maya Essentials 3: NURBS Modeling Techniques.zip Maya Essentials 4: Creating Textures and Materials.zip Maya Essentials 5: Animation Tools.zip Maya Essentials 6: Lights and Rendering.zip Maya Particle Effects.zip Maya Rendering for After Effects Composites.zip Melodyne Advanced Techniques.zip Melodyne Studio Essential Training.zip Mexopolis, Animation Studio.zip Migrating from Access 2003 to Access 2007.zip Migrating from Access 2003 to Access 2010.zip Migrating from Entourage 2008 for Mac to Outlook 2011.zip Migrating from Excel 2003 to Excel 2007.zip Migrating from Excel 2003 to Excel 2010.zip Migrating from Excel 2008 for Mac to Excel 2011.zip Migrating from Final Cut Pro 7 to Avid Media Composer 5.5.zip Migrating from Final Cut Pro 7 to Final Cut Pro X.zip Migrating from Final Cut Pro 7 to Premiere Pro.zip Migrating from FreeHand to Illustrator CS2.zip Migrating from FreeHand to Illustrator CS3.zip Migrating from FrontPage to Expression Web.zip Migrating from GoLive to Dreamweaver CS3.zip Migrating from Joomla! 1.5 to Joomla! 2.5.zip Migrating from Outlook 2003 to Outlook 2007.zip Migrating from Outlook 2003 to Outlook 2010.zip Migrating from PowerPoint 2003 to PowerPoint 2007.zip Migrating from PowerPoint 2003 to PowerPoint 2010.zip Migrating from PowerPoint 2008 for Mac to PowerPoint 2011.zip Migrating from Windows XP to Windows 7.zip Migrating from Word 2003 to Word 2007.zip Migrating from Word 2003 to Word 2010.zip Migrating from Word 2008 for Mac to Word 2011.zip Mixing and Mastering with Pro Tools.zip Mixing a Rock Song in Pro Tools.zip Mobile Web Design and Development Fundamentals.zip mocha Essential Training.zip Modeling a Character in 3ds Max.zip Modeling in Discreet 3ds max 6.zip modo 501 Essential Training.zip Moodle 1.9 Essential Training for Students.zip Moodle 1.9 Essential Training for Teachers.zip Moodle 2 Essential Training for Students.zip Moodle 2 Essential Training for Teachers.zip Motion 2 Essential Training.zip Motion 3 Essential Training.zip Motion 4 Essential Training.zip Motion 5 Essential Training.zip Motion Control 3D: Bringing Your Photos to Life in Three Dimensions.zip Motion: Lighting Effects in Post.zip Motion: Natural Light Effects.zip Motion: Principles of Motion Graphics.zip Mudbox 2013 Essential Training.zip Muse Beta Preview.zip Muse Essential Training.zip Music Editing for TV and Film in Pro Tools.zip MVC Frameworks for Building PHP Web Applications.zip MySQL Essential Training.zip Narrative Portraiture: Foundations of Portraiture.zip Narrative Portraiture: On Location in New York City.zip Narrative Portraiture: On Location in New York with Rodney Smith.zip Narrative Portraiture: On Location in Texas with Keith Carter.zip Narrative Portraiture: Portraits of Two Texas Artists.zip Natalie Fobes, Photographer.zip Negotiation Fundamentals.zip New Deal Studios, Visual Effects.zip New in Director MX 2004.zip New in Photoshop 7.zip New in Photoshop CS.zip Node.js First Look.zip Nondestructive Exposure and Color Correction with Photoshop.zip No Pixels Harmed!.zip Nuke 5 Essential Training.zip Nuke 6.3 New Features.zip Nuke 6 New Features.zip Numbers &#039;08 Essential Training.zip Numbers &#039;09 Essential Training.zip Objective-C Essential Training.zip Object-Oriented Programming with PHP.zip Office 2008 for Mac: Small Business Projects.zip Office 2013 First Look.zip Office for Mac 2008 New Features.zip OmniFocus Essential Training.zip OmniGraffle 5: Creating Web Sitemaps and Wireframes.zip OmniGraffle Professional 5 Essential Training.zip OneNote 2007 Essential Training.zip OneNote 2010 Essential Training.zip OneNote 2010 New Features.zip On Getting Published.zip Online Marketing Fundamentals.zip OpenOffice.org 2 Base Getting Started.zip OpenOffice.org 2 Calc Getting Started.zip OpenOffice.org 2 Draw Getting Started.zip OpenOffice.org 2 Impress Getting Started.zip OpenOffice.org 2 Writer Getting Started.zip Optimizing Flash 5 Content.zip Organizing and Archiving Digital Photos.zip Outlook 2003 Essential Training.zip Outlook 2007: Effective Email Management.zip Outlook 2007 Essential Training.zip Outlook 2007 Power Shortcuts.zip Outlook 2007: Time Management with Calendar and Tasks.zip Outlook 2010: Effective Email Management.zip Outlook 2010 Essential Training.zip Outlook 2010 New Features.zip Outlook 2010 Power Shortcuts.zip Outlook 2010: Real-World Projects.zip Outlook 2010: Time Management with Calendar and Tasks.zip Outlook for Mac 2011 Essential Training.zip Outlook for Mac 2011 Power Shortcuts.zip Pages &#039;08 Essential Training.zip Pages &#039;09 Essential Training.zip Pages 2 Essential Training.zip Pages Essential Training.zip Painter 11 Essential Training.zip Painter 12 Essential Training.zip Painter X Essential Training.zip Paint Shop Pro X Essential Training.zip Papervision3D 2 Essential Training.zip PayPal Essential Training.zip Perl 5 Essential Training.zip Photo Assignment: Backlit Portraits.zip Photo Assignment: Fill Flash Portraits.zip Photo Assignment: Group Shots.zip Photo Assignment: Natural Light Portraits.zip Photo Assignment: Off-Camera Flash.zip Photography Video Workflow: Final Cut Pro + Canon 5D Mark II.zip Photorealism with Bert Monroy: Volume 1.zip Photorealism with Bert Monroy: Volume 2.zip Photo Restoration with Photoshop.zip Photoshop 7 Slices, Rollovers and Animation.zip Photoshop and Bridge CS5 for Photographers New Features.zip Photoshop Blend Mode Magic.zip Photoshop Brushes.zip Photoshop Companion Apps First Look.zip Photo Workshop: Car Photography Tips.zip Unity 3D Tutorial.zip Photoshop CS2 Actions and Automation.zip Photoshop CS2 and Flash 8 Integration.zip Photoshop CS2 Channels and Masks.zip Photoshop CS2 Essential Training.zip Photoshop CS2 FAQs.zip Photoshop CS2 for the Web Essential Training.zip Photoshop CS2 Mastering Camera Raw.zip Photoshop CS3 Channels and Masks: Advanced Techniques.zip Photoshop CS3 Channels and Masks: The Essentials.zip Photoshop CS3 Color Correction.zip Photoshop CS3 Creative Photographic Techniques.zip Photoshop CS3 Extended for 3D + Video.zip Photoshop CS3 Extended for BioMedical Research.zip Photoshop CS3 Extended: Research Methods and Workflows.zip Photoshop CS3 for Designers.zip Photoshop CS3 for Photographers.zip Photoshop CS3 for the Web Essential Training.zip Photoshop CS3 Mastering Lab Color.zip Photoshop CS3 New Features.zip Photoshop CS3 One-on-One: Advanced Techniques.zip Photoshop CS3 One-on-One: Beyond the Basics.zip Photoshop CS3 One-on-One: The Essentials.zip Photoshop CS3 Portrait Retouching Essentials.zip Photoshop CS3 Portrait Retouching Techniques.zip Photoshop CS3 Prepress Essentials.zip Photoshop CS3 Sharpening Images.zip Photoshop CS4: Color Correction.zip Photoshop CS4 Essential Training.zip Photoshop CS4 Extended for 3D.zip Photoshop CS4 Extended for Video.zip Photoshop CS4 for Photographers: Camera Raw.zip Photoshop CS4 for Photographers: Creative Color.zip Photoshop CS4 for Photographers: Creative Effects.zip Photoshop CS4 for Photographers: Desktop Printing Techniques.zip Photoshop CS4 for Photographers.zip Photoshop CS4 for the Web.zip Photoshop CS4 Getting Started.zip Photoshop CS4: Image Adjustments in Depth.zip Photoshop CS4: Image Compositing for Photographers.zip Photoshop CS4: Layer Masks in Depth.zip Photoshop CS4: Layers in Depth.zip Photoshop CS4 New Features.zip Photoshop CS4 One-on-One: Advanced.zip Photoshop CS4 One-on-One: Fundamentals.zip Photoshop CS4 One-on-One: Mastery.zip Photoshop CS4 Portrait Retouching Essential Training.zip Photoshop CS4 Power Shortcuts.zip Photoshop CS4 Retouching: Fashion Photography Projects.zip Photoshop CS4: Selections in Depth.zip Photoshop CS4: Sharpening Images New Features.zip Photoshop CS5: Athletic Retouching Projects.zip Photoshop CS5: Creative Compositing.zip Photoshop CS5: Creative Effects.zip Photoshop CS5 Essential Training.zip Photoshop CS5 Extended One-on-One: 3D Fundamentals.zip Photoshop CS5 Extended One-on-One: 3D Objects.zip Photoshop CS5 Extended One-on-One: 3D Scenes.zip Photoshop CS5 Extended One-on-One: 3D Type Effects.zip Photoshop CS5: Fashion Retouching Projects.zip Photoshop CS5 for Photographers: Camera Raw 6.zip Photoshop CS5 for Photographers.zip Photoshop CS5 for the Web.zip Photoshop CS5: Landscape Photography.zip Photoshop CS5 New Features.zip Photoshop CS5 One-on-One: Advanced.zip Photoshop CS5 One-on-One: Fundamentals.zip Photoshop CS5 One-on-One: Mastery.zip Photoshop CS5: Painting with the Mixer Brush.zip Photoshop CS5: Portrait Retouching.zip Photoshop CS5: Prepress and Printing.zip Photoshop CS5: Selections in Depth.zip Photoshop CS5 Top 5.zip Photoshop CS6 Essential Training.zip Photoshop CS6 for Photographers: Camera Raw 7.zip Photoshop CS6 for Photographers New Features.zip Photoshop CS6 for Photographers.zip Photoshop CS6 New Features: Brushes.zip Photoshop CS6 New Features.zip Photoshop CS6 One-on-One: Advanced.zip Photoshop CS6 One-on-One: Fundamentals.zip Photoshop CS6 One-on-One: Intermediate.zip Photoshop CS and Flash MX 2004 Integration.zip Photoshop CS Essential Training.zip Photoshop CS Power Shortcuts.zip Photoshop CS Prepress Essentials.zip Photoshop Elements 10 Essential Training.zip Photoshop Elements 11 Essentials: Editing and Retouching Photos.zip Photoshop Elements 3 Essential Training.zip Photoshop Elements 5 Essential Training.zip Photoshop Elements 6 for Mac Essential Training.zip Photoshop Elements 7 for Windows Essential Training.zip Photoshop Elements 8 for Mac Essential Training.zip Photoshop Elements 8 for Windows Essential Training.zip Photoshop Elements 9 Essential Training.zip Photoshop Elements 9: Scanning and Restoring Photos.zip Photoshop Express Beta Essential Training.zip Photoshop Filters.zip Photoshop for Designers: Color.zip Photoshop for Designers: Layer Effects.zip Photoshop for Designers: Shape Layers.zip Photoshop for Designers: Textures.zip Photoshop for Designers: Type Effects.zip Photoshop for Designers: Type Essentials.zip Photoshop for Photographers: Compositing.zip Photoshop for Photographers: Creative Effects.zip Photoshop for Photographers: Portrait Retouching.zip Photoshop for Web Design.zip Photoshop Insider Training: Enhancing Photos.zip Photoshop Lightroom 1.1 New Features.zip Photoshop Lightroom 1.3 for Digital Photographers.zip Photoshop Lightroom 2 Essential Training.zip Photoshop Lightroom 2 New Features.zip Photoshop Lightroom 3 Advanced Techniques.zip Photoshop Lightroom 3 Essential Training.zip Photoshop Lightroom 3 New Features.zip Photoshop Lightroom 4 Catalogs in Depth.zip Photoshop Lightroom 4 Essentials 1: Organizing and Sharing with the Library Module.zip Photoshop Lightroom 4 Essentials 2: Enhancing Photos with the Develop Module.zip Photoshop Lightroom 4 Essentials 3: Creating Prints and Books.zip Photoshop Lightroom 4 Essentials 4: Creating Slideshows and Web Galleries.zip Photoshop Lightroom 4 New Features.zip Photoshop Lightroom 4 Power Shortcuts.zip Photoshop Lightroom Essential Training.zip Photoshop Lightroom Workflow Strategies.zip Photoshop Masking and Compositing: Advanced Blending.zip Photoshop Masking and Compositing: Fundamentals.zip Photoshop Masking and Compositing: Hair.zip Photoshop Smart Objects.zip Photoshop Top 40.zip</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<br><ol type="1"><li> Mac OS X 10.4 Tiger Beyond the Basics.zip<br></li><li> Mac OS X 10.4 Tiger Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Mac OS X 10.5 Leopard Beyond the Basics.zip<br></li><li> Mac OS X 10.5 Leopard Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Mac OS X 10.5 Leopard New Features.zip<br></li><li> Mac OS X 10.6 Snow Leopard New Features.zip<br></li><li> Mac OS X Lion Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Mac OS X Lion Server Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Mac OS X Mountain Lion New Features.zip<br></li><li> Mac OS X Server 10.4 Tiger Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Mac OS X Server 10.5 Leopard Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Mac OS X Server 10.6 Snow Leopard: DNS and Network Services.zip<br></li><li> Mac OS X Server 10.6 Snow Leopard Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Mac OS X Server 10.6 Snow Leopard New Features.zip<br></li><li> Managing a Hosted Web Site.zip<br></li><li> Managing and Analyzing Data in Excel.zip<br></li><li> Managing CSS in Dreamweaver.zip<br></li><li> Managing Documents with SharePoint 2010.zip<br></li><li> Managing Spam Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Managing Your Career.zip<br></li><li> Margo Chase, Graphic Designer.zip<br></li><li> Margo Chase's Hand-Lettered Poster: Start to Finish.zip<br></li><li> Marian Bantjes, Graphic Artist.zip<br></li><li> Mark Mothersbaugh, Music Composer.zip<br></li><li> Matting, Framing, and Hanging Your Photographs.zip<br></li><li> Maximizing Your Web Video and Podcast Audience with Hypersyndication.zip<br></li><li> Maya 2008 Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Maya 2009 Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Maya 2009 New Features.zip<br></li><li> Maya 2010: Getting Started with MatchMover, Toxik, and Backburner.zip<br></li><li> Maya 2011: Creating Natural Environments.zip<br></li><li> Maya 2011: Creating Textures and Shaders.zip<br></li><li> Maya 2011 Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Maya 2011 Lighting and Rendering in mental ray.zip<br></li><li> Maya 2011: Modeling a Character.zip<br></li><li> Maya 2011 New Features.zip<br></li><li> Maya 6.5 Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Maya 8.5 Character Rigging.zip<br></li><li> Maya 8 Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Maya Essentials 1: Interface and Organization.zip<br></li><li> Maya Essentials 2: Polygonal Modeling Techniques.zip<br></li><li> Maya Essentials 3: NURBS Modeling Techniques.zip<br></li><li> Maya Essentials 4: Creating Textures and Materials.zip<br></li><li> Maya Essentials 5: Animation Tools.zip<br></li><li> Maya Essentials 6: Lights and Rendering.zip<br></li><li> Maya Particle Effects.zip<br></li><li> Maya Rendering for After Effects Composites.zip<br></li><li> Melodyne Advanced Techniques.zip<br></li><li> Melodyne Studio Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Mexopolis, Animation Studio.zip<br></li><li> Migrating from Access 2003 to Access 2007.zip<br></li><li> Migrating from Access 2003 to Access 2010.zip<br></li><li> Migrating from Entourage 2008 for Mac to Outlook 2011.zip<br></li><li> Migrating from Excel 2003 to Excel 2007.zip<br></li><li> Migrating from Excel 2003 to Excel 2010.zip<br></li><li> Migrating from Excel 2008 for Mac to Excel 2011.zip<br></li><li> Migrating from Final Cut Pro 7 to Avid Media Composer 5.5.zip<br></li><li> Migrating from Final Cut Pro 7 to Final Cut Pro X.zip<br></li><li> Migrating from Final Cut Pro 7 to Premiere Pro.zip<br></li><li> Migrating from FreeHand to Illustrator CS2.zip<br></li><li> Migrating from FreeHand to Illustrator CS3.zip<br></li><li> Migrating from FrontPage to Expression Web.zip<br></li><li> Migrating from GoLive to Dreamweaver CS3.zip<br></li><li> Migrating from Joomla! 1.5 to Joomla! 2.5.zip<br></li><li> Migrating from Outlook 2003 to Outlook 2007.zip<br></li><li> Migrating from Outlook 2003 to Outlook 2010.zip<br></li><li> Migrating from PowerPoint 2003 to PowerPoint 2007.zip<br></li><li> Migrating from PowerPoint 2003 to PowerPoint 2010.zip<br></li><li> Migrating from PowerPoint 2008 for Mac to PowerPoint 2011.zip<br></li><li> Migrating from Windows XP to Windows 7.zip<br></li><li> Migrating from Word 2003 to Word 2007.zip<br></li><li> Migrating from Word 2003 to Word 2010.zip<br></li><li> Migrating from Word 2008 for Mac to Word 2011.zip<br></li><li> Mixing and Mastering with Pro Tools.zip<br></li><li> Mixing a Rock Song in Pro Tools.zip<br></li><li> Mobile Web Design and Development Fundamentals.zip<br></li><li> mocha Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Modeling a Character in 3ds Max.zip<br></li><li> Modeling in Discreet 3ds max 6.zip<br></li><li> modo 501 Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Moodle 1.9 Essential Training for Students.zip<br></li><li> Moodle 1.9 Essential Training for Teachers.zip<br></li><li> Moodle 2 Essential Training for Students.zip<br></li><li> Moodle 2 Essential Training for Teachers.zip<br></li><li> Motion 2 Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Motion 3 Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Motion 4 Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Motion 5 Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Motion Control 3D: Bringing Your Photos to Life in Three Dimensions.zip<br></li><li> Motion: Lighting Effects in Post.zip<br></li><li> Motion: Natural Light Effects.zip<br></li><li> Motion: Principles of Motion Graphics.zip<br></li><li> Mudbox 2013 Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Muse Beta Preview.zip<br></li><li> Muse Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Music Editing for TV and Film in Pro Tools.zip<br></li><li> MVC Frameworks for Building PHP Web Applications.zip<br></li><li> MySQL Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Narrative Portraiture: Foundations of Portraiture.zip<br></li><li> Narrative Portraiture: On Location in New York City.zip<br></li><li> Narrative Portraiture: On Location in New York with Rodney Smith.zip<br></li><li> Narrative Portraiture: On Location in Texas with Keith Carter.zip<br></li><li> Narrative Portraiture: Portraits of Two Texas Artists.zip<br></li><li> Natalie Fobes, Photographer.zip<br></li><li> Negotiation Fundamentals.zip<br></li><li> New Deal Studios, Visual Effects.zip<br></li><li> New in Director MX 2004.zip<br></li><li> New in Photoshop 7.zip<br></li><li> New in Photoshop CS.zip<br></li><li> Node.js First Look.zip<br></li><li> Nondestructive Exposure and Color Correction with Photoshop.zip<br></li><li> No Pixels Harmed!.zip<br></li><li> Nuke 5 Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Nuke 6.3 New Features.zip<br></li><li> Nuke 6 New Features.zip<br></li><li> Numbers '08 Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Numbers '09 Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Objective-C Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Object-Oriented Programming with PHP.zip<br></li><li> Office 2008 for Mac: Small Business Projects.zip<br></li><li> Office 2013 First Look.zip<br></li><li> Office for Mac 2008 New Features.zip<br></li><li> OmniFocus Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> OmniGraffle 5: Creating Web Sitemaps and Wireframes.zip<br></li><li> OmniGraffle Professional 5 Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> OneNote 2007 Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> OneNote 2010 Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> OneNote 2010 New Features.zip<br></li><li> On Getting Published.zip<br></li><li> Online Marketing Fundamentals.zip<br></li><li> OpenOffice.org 2 Base Getting Started.zip<br></li><li> OpenOffice.org 2 Calc Getting Started.zip<br></li><li> OpenOffice.org 2 Draw Getting Started.zip<br></li><li> OpenOffice.org 2 Impress Getting Started.zip<br></li><li> OpenOffice.org 2 Writer Getting Started.zip<br></li><li> Optimizing Flash 5 Content.zip<br></li><li> Organizing and Archiving Digital Photos.zip<br></li><li> Outlook 2003 Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Outlook 2007: Effective Email Management.zip<br></li><li> Outlook 2007 Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Outlook 2007 Power Shortcuts.zip<br></li><li> Outlook 2007: Time Management with Calendar and Tasks.zip<br></li><li> Outlook 2010: Effective Email Management.zip<br></li><li> Outlook 2010 Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Outlook 2010 New Features.zip<br></li><li> Outlook 2010 Power Shortcuts.zip<br></li><li> Outlook 2010: Real-World Projects.zip<br></li><li> Outlook 2010: Time Management with Calendar and Tasks.zip<br></li><li> Outlook for Mac 2011 Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Outlook for Mac 2011 Power Shortcuts.zip<br></li><li> Pages '08 Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Pages '09 Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Pages 2 Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Pages Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Painter 11 Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Painter 12 Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Painter X Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Paint Shop Pro X Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Papervision3D 2 Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> PayPal Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Perl 5 Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Photo Assignment: Backlit Portraits.zip<br></li><li> Photo Assignment: Fill Flash Portraits.zip<br></li><li> Photo Assignment: Group Shots.zip<br></li><li> Photo Assignment: Natural Light Portraits.zip<br></li><li> Photo Assignment: Off-Camera Flash.zip<br></li><li> Photography Video Workflow: Final Cut Pro + Canon 5D Mark II.zip<br></li><li> Photorealism with Bert Monroy: Volume 1.zip<br></li><li> Photorealism with Bert Monroy: Volume 2.zip<br></li><li> Photo Restoration with Photoshop.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop 7 Slices, Rollovers and Animation.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop and Bridge CS5 for Photographers New Features.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop Blend Mode Magic.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop Brushes.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop Companion Apps First Look.zip<br></li><li> Photo Workshop: Car Photography Tips.zip<br></li><li> Unity 3D Tutorial.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS2 Actions and Automation.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS2 and Flash 8 Integration.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS2 Channels and Masks.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS2 Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS2 FAQs.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS2 for the Web Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS2 Mastering Camera Raw.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS3 Channels and Masks: Advanced Techniques.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS3 Channels and Masks: The Essentials.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS3 Color Correction.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS3 Creative Photographic Techniques.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS3 Extended for 3D + Video.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS3 Extended for BioMedical Research.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS3 Extended: Research Methods and Workflows.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS3 for Designers.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS3 for Photographers.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS3 for the Web Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS3 Mastering Lab Color.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS3 New Features.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS3 One-on-One: Advanced Techniques.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS3 One-on-One: Beyond the Basics.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS3 One-on-One: The Essentials.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS3 Portrait Retouching Essentials.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS3 Portrait Retouching Techniques.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS3 Prepress Essentials.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS3 Sharpening Images.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS4: Color Correction.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS4 Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS4 Extended for 3D.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS4 Extended for Video.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS4 for Photographers: Camera Raw.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS4 for Photographers: Creative Color.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS4 for Photographers: Creative Effects.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS4 for Photographers: Desktop Printing Techniques.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS4 for Photographers.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS4 for the Web.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS4 Getting Started.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS4: Image Adjustments in Depth.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS4: Image Compositing for Photographers.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS4: Layer Masks in Depth.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS4: Layers in Depth.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS4 New Features.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS4 One-on-One: Advanced.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS4 One-on-One: Fundamentals.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS4 One-on-One: Mastery.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS4 Portrait Retouching Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS4 Power Shortcuts.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS4 Retouching: Fashion Photography Projects.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS4: Selections in Depth.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS4: Sharpening Images New Features.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS5: Athletic Retouching Projects.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS5: Creative Compositing.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS5: Creative Effects.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS5 Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS5 Extended One-on-One: 3D Fundamentals.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS5 Extended One-on-One: 3D Objects.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS5 Extended One-on-One: 3D Scenes.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS5 Extended One-on-One: 3D Type Effects.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS5: Fashion Retouching Projects.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS5 for Photographers: Camera Raw 6.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS5 for Photographers.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS5 for the Web.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS5: Landscape Photography.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS5 New Features.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS5 One-on-One: Advanced.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS5 One-on-One: Fundamentals.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS5 One-on-One: Mastery.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS5: Painting with the Mixer Brush.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS5: Portrait Retouching.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS5: Prepress and Printing.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS5: Selections in Depth.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS5 Top 5.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS6 Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS6 for Photographers: Camera Raw 7.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS6 for Photographers New Features.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS6 for Photographers.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS6 New Features: Brushes.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS6 New Features.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS6 One-on-One: Advanced.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS6 One-on-One: Fundamentals.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS6 One-on-One: Intermediate.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS and Flash MX 2004 Integration.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS Power Shortcuts.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop CS Prepress Essentials.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop Elements 10 Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop Elements 11 Essentials: Editing and Retouching Photos.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop Elements 3 Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop Elements 5 Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop Elements 6 for Mac Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop Elements 7 for Windows Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop Elements 8 for Mac Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop Elements 8 for Windows Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop Elements 9 Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop Elements 9: Scanning and Restoring Photos.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop Express Beta Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop Filters.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop for Designers: Color.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop for Designers: Layer Effects.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop for Designers: Shape Layers.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop for Designers: Textures.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop for Designers: Type Effects.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop for Designers: Type Essentials.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop for Photographers: Compositing.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop for Photographers: Creative Effects.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop for Photographers: Portrait Retouching.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop for Web Design.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop Insider Training: Enhancing Photos.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop Lightroom 1.1 New Features.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop Lightroom 1.3 for Digital Photographers.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop Lightroom 2 Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop Lightroom 2 New Features.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop Lightroom 3 Advanced Techniques.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop Lightroom 3 Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop Lightroom 3 New Features.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop Lightroom 4 Catalogs in Depth.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop Lightroom 4 Essentials 1: Organizing and Sharing with the Library Module.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop Lightroom 4 Essentials 2: Enhancing Photos with the Develop Module.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop Lightroom 4 Essentials 3: Creating Prints and Books.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop Lightroom 4 Essentials 4: Creating Slideshows and Web Galleries.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop Lightroom 4 New Features.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop Lightroom 4 Power Shortcuts.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop Lightroom Essential Training.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop Lightroom Workflow Strategies.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop Masking and Compositing: Advanced Blending.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop Masking and Compositing: Fundamentals.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop Masking and Compositing: Hair.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop Smart Objects.zip<br></li><li> Photoshop Top 40.zip<br></li></ol><br><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="1.15 TB Lynda.com Video Tutorials"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Ubot Studio Video Tutorials</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1041-ubot-studio-video-tutorials.html</link>
<description>Name : Ubot Studio Video Tutorials Price : $0 Homepage : SalePage Ubot Studio Completes Video Series For New babies</description>
<category>SEO Training</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2015 12:59:48 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Your First Steps Into UBot Studio - Part 1 Your First Steps Into UBot Studio - Part 2 Your First Steps Into UBot Studio - Part 3 Your First Steps Into UBot Studio - Part 4 Your First Steps Into UBot Studio - Part 5 Your First Steps Into UBot Studio - Part 6 Your First Steps Into UBot Studio - Part 7 Intermediate Tutorials - 1 - Bot Design With Defines UBot Studio Basic Tutorials – Windows Automation Advanced Tutorial - Regex and UBot Studio - Part 1 Advanced Tutorial - Regex and UBot Studio - Part 2 Advanced Tutorial - Regex and UBot Studio - Part 3 Quick Tutorial - Automate Your Accounts Quick Tutorial - Know How and When to Push Buttons Quick Tutorial - Use UBot&#039;s Built-in Functions Quick Tutorial - Make Bots to Make Decisions For You Quick Tutorial - Repeat Tasks So You Don&#039;t Have To Quick Tutorial - Save Info You Want Later Quick Tutorial - Use Lists to Make Your Life Easier Quick Tutorial - Grab Info to Get More Done Quick Tutorial - Build Tables to Simplify Things Quick Tutorial - Go Full-Auto with Captcha Solving Quick Tutorial - Use the Email Verification Wizard Quick Tutorial - Using Shared Scripts Inside the Bot Bank [list]</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/a2AGRYwyUqU?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Your First Steps Into UBot Studio - Part 1<br /></li><li> Your First Steps Into UBot Studio - Part 2<br /></li><li> Your First Steps Into UBot Studio - Part 3<br /></li><li> Your First Steps Into UBot Studio - Part 4<br /></li><li> Your First Steps Into UBot Studio - Part 5<br /></li><li> Your First Steps Into UBot Studio - Part 6<br /></li><li> Your First Steps Into UBot Studio - Part 7<br /></li><li> Intermediate Tutorials - 1 - Bot Design With Defines<br /></li><li> UBot Studio Basic Tutorials – Windows Automation<br /></li><li> Advanced Tutorial - Regex and UBot Studio - Part 1<br /></li><li> Advanced Tutorial - Regex and UBot Studio - Part 2<br /></li><li> Advanced Tutorial - Regex and UBot Studio - Part 3<br /></li><li> Quick Tutorial - Automate Your Accounts<br /></li><li> Quick Tutorial - Know How and When to Push Buttons<br /></li><li> Quick Tutorial - Use UBot's Built-in Functions<br /></li><li> Quick Tutorial - Make Bots to Make Decisions For You<br /></li><li> Quick Tutorial - Repeat Tasks So You Don't Have To<br /></li><li> Quick Tutorial - Save Info You Want Later<br /></li><li> Quick Tutorial - Use Lists to Make Your Life Easier<br /></li><li> Quick Tutorial - Grab Info to Get More Done<br /></li><li> Quick Tutorial - Build Tables to Simplify Things<br /></li><li> Quick Tutorial - Go Full-Auto with Captcha Solving<br /></li><li> Quick Tutorial - Use the Email Verification Wizard<br /></li><li> Quick Tutorial - Using Shared Scripts Inside the Bot Bank<br />[list]<br /><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Ubot Studio Video Tutorials" title="Ubot Studio Video Tutorials"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>