<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Content Creator - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Content Creator - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>SEO Content Machine 4.18.4.30</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1476-seo-content-machine.html</link>
<description>Name : SEO Content Machine Version : 4.18.4.30 OS : Windows Type : Content Marketing Tools Price : $237$/yearly Homepage : SalePage Change The Way You Create Content The first multi-language content creator program. You can also generate content specific to your local region. Trouble Creating Content?SEO Content Machine takes the pain out of creating SEO Content.</description>
<category>Content Creator</category>
<enclosure url="http://seocontentmachine.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/SCM-Monitor-Copy-e1408635573145.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2018 09:04:12 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Accelerate Your Link Building Manage Your PBNs : Draft &amp;amp; post to WordPress/Blogger or any site that supports post by email. Schedule drip feed content and keep your blog.comwork fresh indefinitely. Content Toolbag : Get your content tools. Scrape Google Suggest, create Tier 1 Content, create About Me’s. Roll your own content with an Article Downloader, Translator &amp;amp; Content Combiner. Content In Any Language : This program is a multi-language content scraper &amp;amp; generator. Supports all western languages. Create SEO content in Spanish, French, German and more. You can also generate content specific to your local region. Custom Content Sources : Find and download 100s of pages of content on any topic on any site. Customizable content sources means you don’t get caught scraping the same over-used sites as everyone else. Linkbuilding Content Generation : Make the most of your link building programs. Generate keyword targeted articles for unlimited content submissions. Supports popular programs directly such as GSA SER, Senuke &amp;amp; Ultimate Demon. Creates Readable + Keyword Relevant Articles : Special filtering algorithms remove spammy and irrelevant content automatically. This program will individually rank content against your keyword for relevancy before it is used to generate articles. Simple Content Generation : You don’t need proxies, VPS installs or other special tools. A Content Wizard mode for beginners lets you create content in less than 10 clicks. Online help + video tutorials at your finger tips. 100% Automated Content Generation : Create articles with images, videos and links. Translate or re-write articles using spinners to generate 100% unique content. 100% task automation with the option of scheduling it to repeat for as long as you like. http://direct.seocontentmachine.com/download/changelog.txt</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/f1bx-q2dudk?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Accelerate Your Link Building<br></li><li> Manage Your PBNs : Draft &amp; post to WordPress/Blogger or any site that supports post by email.  Schedule drip feed content and keep your blog.comwork fresh indefinitely.<br></li><li> Content Toolbag : Get your content tools. Scrape Google Suggest, create Tier 1 Content, create About Me’s.  Roll your own content with an Article Downloader, Translator &amp; Content Combiner. <br></li><li> Content In Any Language : This program is a multi-language content scraper &amp; generator.  Supports all western languages. Create SEO content in Spanish, French, German and more.  You can also generate content specific to your local region. <br></li><li> Custom Content Sources : Find and download 100s of pages of content on any topic on any site.  Customizable content sources means you don’t get caught scraping the same over-used sites as everyone else.  <br></li><li> Linkbuilding Content Generation : Make the most of your link building programs. Generate keyword targeted articles for  unlimited content submissions.  Supports popular programs directly such as GSA SER, Senuke &amp; Ultimate Demon.  <br></li><li> Creates Readable + Keyword Relevant Articles : Special filtering algorithms remove spammy and irrelevant content automatically.  This program will individually rank content against your keyword for relevancy before it is used to generate articles. <br></li><li> Simple Content Generation : You don’t need proxies, VPS installs or other special tools.  A Content Wizard mode for beginners lets you create content in less than 10 clicks.  Online help + video tutorials at your finger tips.<br></li><li> 100% Automated Content Generation : Create articles with images, videos and links.  Translate or re-write articles using spinners to generate 100% unique content.  100% task automation with the option of scheduling it to repeat for as long as you like.<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://seocontentmachine.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/SCM-Monitor-Copy-e1408635573145.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="SEO Content Machine 4.18.4.30"><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><a href="http://direct.seocontentmachine.com/download/changelog.txt"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">http://direct.seocontentmachine.com/download/changelog.txt</a><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>ContentBomb Elite 1.1.1</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1069-content-bomb.html</link>
<description>Name : ContentBomb Version : Elite 1.1.1 OS : Windows Type : Content Marketing Tools Price : $297 Homepage : SalePage Scrape, Convert, Output and Submit - All in One! ContentBomb is designed to be very smart, allowing you to scrape anything and convert it into any format of new content, then you can save the new content in any custom format or submit it to your blog or website. Get Started Now !</description>
<category>Content Creator</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.contentbomb.com/img/mobile.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 07:44:55 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Scrape Content From Any Source Manage Unlimited Blog/Site Accounts And Run Unlimited AutoBlog Tasks! Plenty of Content Sources Content Mix Rule and Templates Create New Content, Download Articles, Images and Videos etc.... Submit Content to Blog/Site and Ping</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/OB7DlPrkqiA?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Scrape Content From Any Source<br></li><li> Manage Unlimited Blog/Site Accounts And Run Unlimited AutoBlog Tasks!<br></li><li> Plenty of Content Sources<br></li><li> Content Mix Rule and Templates<br></li><li> Create New Content, Download Articles, Images and Videos etc....<br></li><li> Submit Content to Blog/Site and Ping<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://www.contentbomb.com/img/mobile.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="ContentBomb Elite 1.1.1"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Content Creator 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3992-content-creator.html</link>
<description>Name : Content Creator Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Creator Content Tool Price : $59 Homepage : SalePage Content Creator is a software tool that will search Google for your keyword and download all related content from Google&#039;s results for that keyword. You can then use this content in a Blackhat or Whitehat way. The Blackhat way will spin the content and shuffles all sentances allowing you to use this unique spun content in your links to your money website. The Whitehat way is an option to bring back all the h1 and h2 tags, the results of this is a list of all the topics that the top 100 articles for that keyword have covered.</description>
<category>Content Creator</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2018 21:53:30 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Content Creator scrapes the top 100 results from Google for your keyword then extracts all p tag contents and h2/h2 tags. Content and topic headings are then generated from this.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/hyalcLjL0uE?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Content Creator scrapes the top 100 results from Google for your keyword then extracts all p tag contents and h2/h2 tags. Content and topic headings are then generated from this.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Content Creator 1.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Elite Content Creator 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4101-elite-content-creator.html</link>
<description>Name : Elite Content Creator Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Content Creator Price : $200 Homepage : SalePage Elite Content Creator is a windows desktop application that is capable of generating an unlimited amount of niche related high quality content for your website. You simply give it your keyword then sit back and let the unique high quality content be generated.</description>
<category>Content Creator</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 06:16:27 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features When you enter your keyword into Elite Content Creator it simply scrapes YouTube for videos related to your keyword (there are several filters so you can find just what you are looking for) for every video it finds it will rip/scrape the subtitles from. This content is not indexed by Google so you can use it freely without worry of duplicate content issues. This tool even has a built in uniqueness checker just to be sure no one else has used this tool on the same video and uploaded the content to their website or the YouTube uploader has a transcript of the video on their website. This tool will even punctuate the content for you, producing excellent high quality articles for your website. This tool is perfect for people who either want a high quaility content and articles for their white hat websites or people who want quality keyword and LSI rich content for the web 2.0s or PBNs. The quality of the content it produces is so good its also Adsense and Amazon safe. Writing quality content takes time and with this tool you can make use of the inte.coms largest gold mine of unindexed high quality content...YouTube.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/bdxaQ9WMMCA?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> When you enter your keyword into Elite Content Creator it simply scrapes YouTube for videos related to your keyword (there are several filters so you can find just what you are looking for) for every video it finds it will rip/scrape the subtitles from. This content is not indexed by Google so you can use it freely without worry of duplicate content issues. This tool even has a built in uniqueness checker just to be sure no one else has used this tool on the same video and uploaded the content to their website or the YouTube uploader has a transcript of the video on their website. This tool will even punctuate the content for you, producing excellent high quality articles for your website.<br></li><li> This tool is perfect for people who either want a high quaility content and articles for their white hat websites or people who want quality keyword and LSI rich content for the web 2.0s or PBNs. The quality of the content it produces is so good its also Adsense and Amazon safe. Writing quality content takes time and with this tool you can make use of the inte.coms largest gold mine of unindexed high quality content...YouTube.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Elite Content Creator 1.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>The Journal 7.0.0.1099</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3932-the-journal.html</link>
<description>Name : The Journal Version : 7.0.0.1099 OS : Windows Type : Diary Software Price : $995 Homepage : SalePage You want to keep a diary. You want to write every day. With The Journal, you can! Whatever your journaling or writing needs, The Journal gives you unmatched convenience, flexibility, security, and reliability. The Journal is always available when you need it, and lets you make entries with text, photos, images, and just about anything else. Plus, The Journal’s optional password-protection and encryption ensure that your secrets remain secret. The Journal runs on any PC, laptop, notebook or tablet with Windows 10, Windows 8, Windows 7, Windows Vista, or Windows XP. Plus, with The Journal’s “Household License” you can use The Journal on any computer you own.</description>
<category>Content Creator</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 00:05:41 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features The Journal is Incredibly Easy to Use! - Make new entries easily! - Make entries on any date, at any time! - Review past entries with just a click on the calendar! - Runs on nearly all versions of Windows! - Search for anything, anywhere in your journal! The Journal is Both Powerful and Flexible! - Store anything! (text, digital photographs, videos, files…) - Doodle in your entries, or even edit photographs! - Print your entries for binding or sharing! - Set reminders for appointments, events, tasks &amp;amp; special days! - Be as organized as you want to be! The Journal is Secure! - Keep your secrets secret! - Be as secure as you want to be! - Full password protection! (But only if you want it.) - Want more than the default level of security? The Journals’ Extended Security features are also available to lock your journal up as tight as possible. The Journal is Reliable! - Your entries are automatically saved as you make them! - Built-in backup and restore! - Easily move The Journal to a new computer!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> The Journal is Incredibly Easy to Use!<br></li><li>  - Make new entries easily!<br></li><li>  - Make entries on any date, at any time!<br></li><li>  - Review past entries with just a click on the calendar!<br></li><li>  - Runs on nearly all versions of Windows!<br></li><li>  - Search for anything, anywhere in your journal!<br></li><li> The Journal is Both Powerful and Flexible!<br></li><li>  - Store anything! (text, digital photographs, videos, files…)<br></li><li>  - Doodle in your entries, or even edit photographs!<br></li><li>  - Print your entries for binding or sharing!<br></li><li>  - Set reminders for appointments, events, tasks &amp; special days!<br></li><li>  - Be as organized as you want to be!<br></li><li> The Journal is Secure!<br></li><li>  - Keep your secrets secret!<br></li><li>  - Be as secure as you want to be!<br></li><li>  - Full password protection! (But only if you want it.)<br></li><li>  - Want more than the default level of security? The Journals’ Extended Security features are also available to lock your journal up as tight as possible.<br></li><li> The Journal is Reliable!<br></li><li>  - Your entries are automatically saved as you make them!<br></li><li>  - Built-in backup and restore!<br></li><li>  - Easily move The Journal to a new computer!<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="The Journal 7.0.0.1099"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Dom Recovery 1.0.34.0 Pro</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1651-domrecovery.html</link>
<description>Name : Dom Recovery Version : 1.0.34.0 Pro OS : Windows Type : Keyword Research, Price : $97 Homepage : SalePage Ideal for PBN Domains Quickly and Easily build out PBN Domains for next level SEO In 2016 there is no alternative for a niche related PBN built with expired domains. With DomRecovery you can build out your PBN domains with relevant content within minutes instead of spending lots of time and money on new content and designs for each domain. Get aged unique content with minimal effort and time. DomRecovery is simple to use yet incredibly powerful software that can recover any website from the Wayback Machine making filling out your PBN websites quicker than it ever could be before. DomRecovery is an innovative new software that can be used to recover any website from the Inte.com Archive’s Wayback Machine* so that it can be re-uploaded and used again. The Wayback Machine* contains perfect copies of most websites online today and in the past so it is a great resource for checking what a website used to look like. This makes it perfect for recovering old versions of a website or for recovering past instances of a website. DomRecovery is the only tool capable of downloading websites from the Wayback Machine* in their entirety including layout, styles, content and images and any other media that has been archived with it.</description>
<category>Content Creator</category>
<enclosure url="http://domrecovery.com/assets/img/carousel-screeny.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 07:50:18 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Easy yet Customisable : Can recover a website by entering the domain but also offers lots of optional controls if required Very Fast : DomRecovery uses thread and sockets which means it is very fast to recover websites Unlimited Recoveries : Recover as many of your old websites as you need with no limits. Regular Upgrades : DomRecovery is regularly updated to add features and ensure smooth running. Professional Website Recovery : Download any website from Wayback Machine - Downloads all content from the wayback machine - Get all images, JS and stylesheets - Works for any website in the Wayback Machine - Fastest known method to save you time - Works for any website in the Wayback Machine Very Easy to Use Wizard Driven for Simplicity - Wizard makes everything as simple as possible - Optional controls for extra power - Can edit content for use on other domains - Maintains look and feel of original website</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ZbEuYqrp3FY?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><p><br></p><br><h3>Features</h3><br><p><br><ul><li> Easy yet Customisable : Can recover a website by entering the domain but also offers lots of optional controls if required<br></li><li> Very Fast : DomRecovery uses thread and sockets which means it is very fast to recover websites<br></li><li> Unlimited Recoveries : Recover as many of your old websites as you need with no limits.<br></li><li> Regular Upgrades : DomRecovery is regularly updated to add features and ensure smooth running.<br></li><li> Professional Website Recovery : Download any website from Wayback Machine<br></li><li> - Downloads all content from the wayback machine<br></li><li> - Get all images, JS and stylesheets<br></li><li> - Works for any website in the Wayback Machine<br></li><li> - Fastest known method to save you time<br></li><li> - Works for any website in the Wayback Machine<br></li><li> Very Easy to Use<br></li><li> Wizard Driven for Simplicity<br></li><li> - Wizard makes everything as simple as possible<br></li><li> - Optional controls for extra power<br></li><li> - Can edit content for use on other domains<br></li><li> - Maintains look and feel of original website<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://domrecovery.com/assets/img/carousel-screeny.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Dom Recovery 1.0.34.0 Pro"></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>ICC Express Pro 2.2.13</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1103-iccexpress.html</link>
<description>Name : Instant Content Curator Express Version : Pro 2.2.13 OS : Windows Type : Content Building Tools Price : $97 Homepage : SalePage &quot;How do you draw thousands of visitors to your promotions and money-pages without breaking the bank on expensive ads?&quot; You Use The World&#039;s Most Powerful Traffic Strategy</description>
<category>Content Creator</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.hotdealsoftware.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/02/iccexpress1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 22:57:55 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Effortlessly rank for long tail phrases that pin point potential buyers and suck them ino your funnel NEVER have to worry about creating original content... and all the headaches that come from THAT process ALWAYS have the hottest, freshest, highest converting stuff on your site... to ensure a loyal fanbase and RAPID growth in a short amount of time Generate TONS of traffic... without spending a DIME! Quickly demonstrate &quot;Authority By Association&quot; which lets you charge MORE for whatever it is you are trying to sell Immediately tap into trending topics for MAX viral exposure And much more... Manage multiple blogs in one location (depending on the license you choose) Quickly find targeted articles through multiple “Feeds” Insert the curated articles with one click Format your post for SEO with the click of your mouse (h1 tags and all that stuff are normally so confusing - not here!) Quickly search for images which are legal to use (that&#039;s important -- The ability to make sure the images you get have rights for you to use them saves your ass legally!) Quickly search for and review targeted YouTube videos -- Insert media you find into your post with one click (NO embed code - now that&#039;s what I like!) Create crazy looking memes in the meme editor with a royalty free image that you obtain using the image browser – post directly to your blog, Facebook timeline or schedule to fan pages.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/lx2EPSzvPp8?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Effortlessly rank for long tail phrases that pin point potential buyers and suck them ino your funnel<br></li><li> NEVER have to worry about creating original content... and all the headaches that come from THAT process<br></li><li> ALWAYS have the hottest, freshest, highest converting stuff on your site... to ensure a loyal fanbase and RAPID growth in a short amount of time<br></li><li> Generate TONS of traffic... without spending a DIME!<br></li><li> Quickly demonstrate "Authority By Association" which lets you charge MORE for whatever it is you are trying to sell<br></li><li> Immediately tap into trending topics for MAX viral exposure<br></li><li> And much more...<br></li><li> Manage multiple blogs in one location (depending on the license you choose)<br></li><li> Quickly find targeted articles through multiple “Feeds”<br></li><li> Insert the curated articles with one click<br></li><li> Format your post for SEO with the click of your mouse (h1 tags and all that stuff are normally so confusing - not here!)<br></li><li> Quickly search for images which are legal to use (that's important -- The ability to make sure the images you get have rights for you to use them saves your ass legally!)<br></li><li> Quickly search for and review targeted YouTube videos -- Insert media you find into your post with one click (NO embed code - now that's what I like!)<br></li><li> Create crazy looking memes in the meme editor with a royalty free image that you obtain using the image browser – post directly to your blog, Facebook timeline or schedule to fan pages.<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://www.hotdealsoftware.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/02/iccexpress1.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt="ICC Express Pro 2.2.13"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Expired Article Hunter 2.0.7.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1415-expired-article-hunter.html</link>
<description>Name : Expired Article Hunter Version : 2.0.7.0 OS : Windows Type : Article Scrape Price : $47 Homepage : SalePage Quickly find hundreds of unique articles. Expired Article Hunter tracks down content from expired websites, quickly generating tons of unique content for use on your money site or SEO campaign!</description>
<category>Content Creator</category>
<enclosure url="http://expiredarticlehunter.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/Expired.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2017 23:33:01 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Extremely easy to install and use Multi-threaded for quick article searching Find hundreds of unique articles ready to be used for your SEO needs! Expired Domain Scraper : Expired Article Hunter has an expired domain scraper built in. Built in Copyscape Checking : Check Copyscape to ensure articles are one of a kind! (Requires Copyscape account)</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/m96b1T1WIFM?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" gesture="media" allow="encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Extremely easy to install and use<br></li><li> Multi-threaded for quick article searching<br></li><li> Find hundreds of unique articles ready to be used for your SEO needs!<br></li><li> Expired Domain Scraper : Expired Article Hunter has an expired domain scraper built in.<br></li><li> Built in Copyscape Checking : Check Copyscape to ensure articles are one of a kind! (Requires Copyscape account)<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://expiredarticlehunter.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/Expired.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Expired Article Hunter 2.0.7.0"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Auto blogging 2.0 Build 578</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1812-auto-blogging-software.html</link>
<description>Name : Auto blogging Version : 2.0 Build 578 OS : Windows Type : Content Creator Price : $199 Homepage : SalePage The Most Powerful Auto Blogging Software</description>
<category>Content Creator</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2016-07/thumbs/1467318484_header.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2016-07/thumbs/1467318419_wso-features.gif" type="image/gif" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2016 01:51:12 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features &quot;This Software Grabs Content From Other Websites, Just Like Google Does and Posts To Your Own Blog!&quot; You won&#039;t believe until you see it in action! The software uses a highly complicated algorithms to grab content from websites just like the way Google and other major web players read your website for content after filtering out the unwanted fluff. Actually when a feed is downloaded, the software will visit each of the article item&#039; original website and grabs the full-text content for posting in your own Blog. &quot;It Will Also Post Unique Content By Translating It More Than Once, Automatically&quot; It is well known that Google hates duplicated content but did you know that simply by translating the content from one language to another and then back to the same language using online translator services will result in unique content? Yes, it works! Translating the content multiple times may result in slight grammatical errors but translating once should be fine. Using Google&#039; Translated search feature, it is very easy to find feeds in foreign language which you can add to the software and it will translate the content to your desired language before posting to your blog. &quot;It Makes The Posts Look Natural and Hand Made By Posting Images On Your Own Website&quot; The software can grab the image associated with the article and uploads to your own server before posting to your Blog so there is no reference made to the original websites. In case of free Blogger.com blogs, the software can upload the images to any FTP server you specify. (Completely optional!)</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/xWMnxqISU68?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /> "This Software Grabs Content From Other Websites, Just Like Google Does and Posts To Your Own Blog!"<br /><br />You won't believe until you see it in action! The software uses a highly complicated algorithms to grab content from websites just like the way Google and other major web players read your website for content after filtering out the unwanted fluff.<br /><br />Actually when a feed is downloaded, the software will visit each of the article item' original website and grabs the full-text content for posting in your own Blog.<br /><br />"It Will Also Post Unique Content By Translating It More Than Once, Automatically"<br /><br />It is well known that Google hates duplicated content but did you know that simply by translating the content from one language to another and then back to the same language using online translator services will result in unique content? Yes, it works!<br /><br />Translating the content multiple times may result in slight grammatical errors but translating once should be fine. Using Google' Translated search feature, it is very easy to find feeds in foreign language which you can add to the software and it will translate the content to your desired language before posting to your blog.<br /><br />"It Makes The Posts Look Natural and Hand Made By Posting Images On Your Own Website"<br /><br />The software can grab the image associated with the article and uploads to your own server before posting to your Blog so there is no reference made to the original websites.<br /><br />In case of free Blogger.com blogs, the software can upload the images to any FTP server you specify. (Completely optional!)<br /><a href="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2016-07/1467318484_header.jpg" rel="highslide" class="highslide"><img src="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2016-07/thumbs/1467318484_header.jpg" alt='Auto blogging 2.0 Build 578' title='Auto blogging 2.0 Build 578'  /></a><br /><a href="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2016-07/1467318419_wso-features.gif" rel="highslide" class="highslide"><img src="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2016-07/thumbs/1467318419_wso-features.gif" alt='Auto blogging 2.0 Build 578' title='Auto blogging 2.0 Build 578'  /></a><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Auto blogging 2.0 Build 578" title="Auto blogging 2.0 Build 578"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Content Spiffer 1.42</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1832-content-spiffer.html</link>
<description>Name : Proxy Gather Bot Version : 1.0 Premium OS : Windows Type : Content Creator Price : $67 Homepage : SalePage Content Spiffer takes a different approach by blending content that you&#039;ve already acquired and adding your own links, images, videos, keywords and customized text. This enables you to turn your old, over-scraped, over-used articles into fresh unique content! Need Unique Content? Content Spiffer is the ultimate tool for producing huge volumes of Unique Content! It&#039;s not a scraper, and it&#039;s not a spinner... Content Spiffer raises the bar by mixing related content and adding HTML, BBCode or Wiki Markup for links, images, videos, keywords and your own custom content to text articles in bulk. This enables you to produce THOUSANDS of Unique Articles with just a few mouse clicks! It&#039;s simple enough that setting up a project only takes minutes, and yet versatile enough to make content just the way you want.</description>
<category>Content Creator</category>
<enclosure url="http://contentspiffer.com/images/ss-kw-ruleset.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2016 21:26:08 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Randomly insert links, images, videos and plain text from lists into articles. Blend articles together at the paragraph or sentence level. Pattern controls let you determine how and where elements are inserted. Pattern rule sets are saved for use in future projects. Random URL &amp; keyword selection is balanced to avoid redundancy. Supports HTML, BBCode and Wiki Markup. Can insert single elements, or multiple elements in spintax format. Content Spiffer gives you an ideal balance of control and randomness, allowing you to create fresh content with relevant links, images and URLs from even the most used and abused articles! Four different methods for blending articles at the paragraph or sentence level. Spintax Friendly! You can blend articles and insert links, images, videos and text even if your articles have already been spun. Blender&#039;s Single File Output lets you compile a bunch of separate articles into a single content file, and can output it in spintax format as well! Spintax Validator makes it easy to make sure there is no broken spintax in your articles prior to validating. Option to preserve articles titles when blending or inserting links, images, videos and text.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/L2LH34ssGlw?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Randomly insert links, images, videos and plain text from lists into articles.<br /></li><li> Blend articles together at the paragraph or sentence level.<br /></li><li> Pattern controls let you determine how and where elements are inserted.<br /></li><li> Pattern rule sets are saved for use in future projects.<br /></li><li> Random URL & keyword selection is balanced to avoid redundancy.<br /></li><li> Supports HTML, BBCode and Wiki Markup.<br /></li><li> Can insert single elements, or multiple elements in spintax format.<br /></li><li> Content Spiffer gives you an ideal balance of control and randomness, allowing you to create fresh content with relevant links, images and URLs from even the most used and abused articles!<br /></li><li> Four different methods for blending articles at the paragraph or sentence level.<br /></li><li> Spintax Friendly! You can blend articles and insert links, images, videos and text even if your articles have already been spun.<br /></li><li> Blender's Single File Output lets you compile a bunch of separate articles into a single content file, and can output it in spintax format as well!<br /></li><li> Spintax Validator makes it easy to make sure there is no broken spintax in your articles prior to validating.<br /></li><li> Option to preserve articles titles when blending or inserting links, images, videos and text.<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://contentspiffer.com/images/ss-kw-ruleset.jpg" alt="Content Spiffer 1.42" title="Content Spiffer 1.42"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Content Spiffer 1.42" title="Content Spiffer 1.42"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>