<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Web 2.0 Posters - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Web 2.0 Posters - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>TurboWeb 2.0 v2.65 DB 274</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/952-turboweb-20.html</link>
<description>Name : TurboWeb 2.0 Version : 2.65 DB 274 OS : Windows Type : Link Building Tools,Web 2.0 Posters Price : $149 Homepage : SalePage The Ultimate Web 2.0 Blogs Network Builder TurboWeb 2.0 Submitter is offering the flexibility and quality of manual link building, but it automated mode.Just setup your campaign and let the application do the work for you. When it comes to link building and SEO technique syncing the latest Google updates, marketers should never ignore the power by quality web 2.0 blog.comwork. Building a premium private blog.comwork is not an easy thing that it requires much time and energy on it. However, TurboWeb 2.0 Submitter transforms the hard work into an easy stuff that everyone can handle it with simple set up and clicks. All you have to do is to place your campaign and let the application do the work for you automatically along with quality of manual link building.</description>
<category>Web 2.0 Posters</category>
<enclosure url="http://devmd.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/07/TWS20-11.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="https://www.turboware.com/wp-content/uploads/Turboweb-3.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2017 02:11:13 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Speed : By using our custom coded engine, the application will be vey light on system usage (low CPU and memory usage), allowing it to run fast even on low performance computers. Easy to Use : Simple and easy to understand interface. Wizard task creation step by step process. Detailed video tutorials to help you get started. Visual Script Builder : Create your own templates by using our point and dick visual script builder. Create backlinks where your competitors can&#039;t master any niche by using your own secret websites. Captcha Support : Built in support for the most important captcha services (8 captcha services + custom service). Smart captha retires based on the solving order set by the user Regular Updates : We are constantly adding new features and follow users requests. We are weekly checking the included list and fixing the templates if required. Database website list is constantly increasing. Accuracy : We know that the success rate is very important for you. Our templates are made to offer the best accuracy possible. Even if you wrongly configure a task, on the run step, the application will modify some data on the fly, in order for the submission to comply with every website request. Ongoing Support : We are dedicated to offer the best support you can rely on. You have a question? You need support for any type of issue? We are glad to help! Blogs Management : Register one time and submit as many times as you desire. There is no need to register everytime you need to submit You can export account (usemame, passwords,. emails, backlinks, etc) to .td tiles Of to excel. Import Articles : Ready made articles can be imported from articles generator applications. Option to import/export articles from other tasks. Proxy Support : Public and private proxies are supported. The proxy management interface comes with the options to test proxies, check response time, import/export list, delete bad proxies, etc. Integrated Email Account Creator Automatic retries if a step fails Automatic Captcha Retries Automatic account generation settings Spintax support for every possible field Advanced Scheduler Automatic Updates Nice and easy to use Interface Detailed video tutorials Extensive support by tickets, community forum or IM New features adding and new websites by request :::Free Members ::: Download Now Password : www.tgmember.com :::ViP Only:::</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/GZ37TvJ8TGs?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><p></p><br><h3>Features</h3><br><p><br><ul><li> Speed : By using our custom coded engine, the application will be vey light on system usage (low CPU and memory usage), allowing it to run fast even on low performance computers.<br></li><li> Easy to Use : Simple and easy to understand interface. Wizard task creation step by step process. Detailed video tutorials to help you get started. <br></li><li> Visual Script Builder : Create your own templates by using our point and dick visual script builder. Create backlinks where your competitors can't master any niche by using your own secret websites. <br></li><li> Captcha Support : Built in support for the most important captcha services (8 captcha services + custom service). Smart captha retires based on the solving order set by the user <br></li><li> Regular Updates : We are constantly adding new features and follow users requests. We are weekly checking the included list and fixing the templates if required. Database website list is constantly increasing. <br></li><li> Accuracy : We know that the success rate is very important for you. Our templates are made to offer the best accuracy possible. Even if you wrongly configure a task, on the run step, the application will modify some data on the fly, in order for the submission to comply with every website request. <br></li><li> Ongoing Support : We are dedicated to offer the best support you can rely on. You have a question? You need support for any type of issue? We are glad to help! <br></li><li> Blogs Management : Register one time and submit as many times as you desire. There is no need to register everytime you need to submit You can export account (usemame, passwords,. emails, backlinks, etc) to .td tiles Of to excel. <br></li><li> Import Articles : Ready made articles can be imported from articles generator applications. Option to import/export articles from other tasks. <br></li><li> Proxy Support : Public and private proxies are supported. The proxy management interface comes with the options to test proxies, check response time, import/export list, delete bad proxies, etc.<br></li><li> Integrated Email Account Creator<br></li><li> Automatic retries if a step fails<br></li><li> Automatic Captcha Retries<br></li><li> Automatic account generation settings<br></li><li> Spintax support for every possible field<br></li><li> Advanced Scheduler<br></li><li> Automatic Updates<br></li><li> Nice and easy to use Interface<br></li><li> Detailed video tutorials Extensive support by tickets, community forum or IM<br></li><li> New features adding and new websites by request<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://devmd.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/07/TWS20-11.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt="TurboWeb 2.0 v2.65 DB 274"><br><img src="https://www.turboware.com/wp-content/uploads/Turboweb-3.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><span style="font-size:12pt;"><b><span style="color:#006600;">:::Free Members :::</span></b></span><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><a href="http://31.220.48.156/engine/go.php?url=aHR0cHM6Ly9tZWdhLmNvLm56LyMhTzFBU2lMYWEhcFpsanRnNXRsRkxqQnJaVzY4alBobFZOR3dJbVFiY3VIMDNVbTZfOEJnMA%3D%3D"  target="_blank">Download Now</a><br>Password : www.tgmember.com<br></div></div><br><p><br><br></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><span style="font-size:12pt;"><b><span style="color:#ff0000;">:::ViP Only:::</span></b></span><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Tpost Bloger 3.1</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2124-tpost-bloger.html</link>
<description>Name : Tpost Bloger Version : 3.1 OS : Windows Type : Blogger Creator and Poster Price : $67 Homepage : SalePage TPOST Automatic Blogger Posts How to Create Blogs - Techniques to Manipulate Google, SEO This is one of the techniques of creating thousands of blogs To manipulate google results</description>
<category>Web 2.0 Posters</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 14:27:06 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features This Tools can create tons of Blogger Blog Then Create Post Also</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><div class="dlevideoplayer" style="width:100%;max-width:425px;"><ul data-theme="default" data-preload="metadata"><li data-title="" data-type="youtube" data-url="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7ijI765b02s"></li></ul></div></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br />This Tools can create tons of Blogger Blog Then Create Post Also<br /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Tpost Bloger 3.1" title="Tpost Bloger 3.1"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>IFTTT Backlink Alpha 2.0.1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/891-ifttt-backlink-commando.html</link>
<description>Name : IFTTT Backlink Alpha (IFTTT Backlink Commando) Version : 2.0.1.0 OS : Windows Type : Link Building, Social Media Tools, Web 2.0 Tools Price : $147 Homepage : SalePage What If You Could Create Unlimited IFTTT Accounts &amp;amp; Have Mass Social Content Syndication With In Built SEO Strategies? Taking Hands Free, Set &amp;amp; Forget Social SEO Syndication &amp;amp; Social Content Marketing To A Whole New Level! There are some accounts such as YouTube, Blogger and Facebook that we cannot automate the account creation for. I always have and always will recommend that you use your own YouTube channel and these channels should always have a well optimized blogger account associated with the same Google account. Facebook you should add your own account anyway and if you want to do tiered blogger linking then you can buy Facebook PVA accounts on fiverr. Watch out for the email offering WordPress Backlink Commando to get it at it lowest price. This really is hands free social seo syndication and we will be adding more strategies each month for a period of 6 months or 6 strategies, whichever comes first!</description>
<category>Web 2.0 Posters</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.iftttbacklinkcommando.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/12/ifttt-backlink-commando-full.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2016 22:42:14 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features 4 Social SEO Syndication Strategies built in SEO strategies for plain clean syndication using WordPress or Youtube SEO strategies for Using Blogger as a 1st Tier With Other links pointing To Blogger which links back to YouTube or WordPress Make a WordPress Post and IFTTT will syndicate it hands free for you! Upload or Favorite a video in YouTube and IFTTT will syndicate it hands Free for You Account creation can be done using schedular over 30 days Additional Onlywire Poster RSS masher &amp;amp; Poster Tool Additional bookmarking &amp;amp; Youtube Favoriting tool 6 more Social &amp;amp; Web 2.0 SEO strategies to be added over the next 6 months All Future Upgrades For WordPress Backlink Commando Access to all bonuses from my SEO product creator friends at launch Use this for every YouTube channel and WordPress site, PBN site you ever create. Unlimited IFTTT account creation saving you time and money from using fiverr gigs :::Free Members ::: http://mir.cr/DHYRSECM Password : www.tgmember.com :::ViP Only:::</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ryg7sapma8E?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><br><ul><li> 4 Social SEO Syndication Strategies built in<br></li><li> SEO strategies for plain clean syndication using WordPress or Youtube<br></li><li> SEO strategies for Using Blogger as a 1st Tier With Other links pointing To Blogger which links back to YouTube or WordPress<br></li><li> Make a WordPress Post and IFTTT will syndicate it hands free for you!<br></li><li> Upload or Favorite a video in YouTube and IFTTT will syndicate it hands Free for You<br></li><li> Account creation can be done using schedular over 30 days<br></li><li> Additional Onlywire Poster<br></li><li> RSS masher &amp; Poster Tool<br></li><li> Additional bookmarking &amp; Youtube Favoriting tool<br></li><li> 6 more Social &amp; Web 2.0 SEO strategies to be added over the next 6 months<br></li><li> All Future Upgrades For WordPress Backlink Commando<br></li><li> Access to all bonuses from my SEO product creator friends at launch<br></li><li> Use this for every YouTube channel and WordPress site, PBN site you ever create.<br></li><li> Unlimited IFTTT account creation saving you time and money from using fiverr gigs<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://www.iftttbacklinkcommando.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/12/ifttt-backlink-commando-full.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="IFTTT Backlink Alpha 2.0.1.0"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><span style="font-size:12pt;"><b><span style="color:#006600;">:::Free Members :::</span></b></span><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><a href="http://mir.cr/DHYRSECM"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer"><a href="http://mir.cr/DHYRSECM" target="_blank"><a href="http://mir.cr/DHYRSECM"  target="_blank">http://mir.cr/DHYRSECM</a></a></a><br>Password : www.tgmember.com<br></div></div><br><br><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><span style="font-size:12pt;"><b><span style="color:#ff0000;">:::ViP Only:::</span></b></span><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Spetsnaz Link Tool 4.6.1.0 Premium</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1515-spetsnaz-link-tool.html</link>
<description>Name : Spetsnaz Link Tool Version : 4.6.1.0 Premium OS : Windows Type : Backlink Addiontal Price : $47 Homepage : SalePage SenukeXcr Spetsnaz Link Tool add 1000&#039;s Extra Sites to Your Senuke Spetsnaz Link Tool is tool that Adding new sites to your copy of SEnuke is now as simple as pressing a button . You will need to either be a Defcon 3 subscriber or use our free SEnuke Bonus offer to use this tool. The additional sites are updated with additional new sites at least every 2 weeks and a full retest is done at least once each month on all existing sites in the list. We test using 3 different machines and a success on any one machine is enough for it to be included in our list. We see a variation of about 15% between machines, as each one runs a different configuration of AV and OS, so do not expect to get 100% of all sites every time.</description>
<category>Web 2.0 Posters</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.zontseo.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/07/spetsnaz-links-2015.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://www.zontseo.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/07/Open-File-Location.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2016 21:48:24 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Firstly you need to install this software in to your “SEnuke/config” folder, this varies from PC to PC but the easiest way to find this is to ‘right click’ on your SEnuke icon and selection ‘Open File Location&#039;” This will open the SEnuke directory, then navigate to the ‘Config’ directory and copy all files from the download above. To make your life easier in the future you may then like to create a shortcut from the ‘SpetsnaZ Links.exe’ on your desktop. Please be aware that during testing 90% of all problems we have encountered were down to Anti Virus programs or Windows 8 blocking the file. As such you may have to whitelist the program within your AV package, Norton for instance will auto delete the file ‘SharpCompress.dll’. In addition the file requires inte.com access in order to download the latest lists from our servers, so it will need access through any firewall you have. The other 10% of problems are when the file is not copied to the correct folder, it will only work when inside the SEnuke Config folder. Once the two main files are installed, ‘SharpCompress.dll’ &amp; ‘SpetsnaZ Links.exe’ simply run the program, read and accept the disclaimer and login using your ZontSEO username and password (do not try to use your SEnuke username and password here). If there are any updates to the software these will be auto installed at this point. You will now have the application open, enter your Zont SEO username and password and click connect: Make sure your SEnuke proxies are off and any close all copies of SEnuke, make sure they are fully closed not just minimised to the taskbar. Now firstly create a backup of your existing files, select ‘Backup’ and press the backup button (1). Any time you need to restore this original configuration select ‘Restore’ and press the backup button again. Then choose which list you want (2), all sites or only those sites PR1 or higher. The PR1+ option will always offer a smaller selection of sites than the ‘All Sites’, typically 20-40%. Next select your mode (3): - Reset &amp; Update: all existing user defined sites will be removed and our latest working list downloaded and installed to your copy of SEnuke. This option clears out any other sites you have installed yourself and also resets all the site ID numbers. If you use this option any existing campaigns you have running will probably not work properly anymore. We suggest using this option the first time you run the tool, and any time in the future where you need to effectively ‘start again’ - Update Only: our latest list of sites will be downloaded and merged with your current site list. Any sites you already have will not be included again, however broken sites removed from our master list will also not be removed from your lists (unless you use ‘Delete Dead Sites option’) and it will be up to you to remove broken sites. If you remove a site and later on we find it working again it will automatically be added again to your site list. Lastly choose if you want to ‘Delete dead sites’ (4), this feature will look at your list and remove any sites which have failed our tests. It only deletes sites based on failures from the last 2 updates, so if you have not updated your list for a couple of months it will not delete all the dead sites and you will need to use the ‘Reset &amp; Update’ option instead to clear out dead sites. However if you run this at least once a month, preferably every update though, your list will automatically stay quite clean. Then press update (5), wait for the ‘Complete’ message and open SEnuke again to see your new user defined site lists. If you want to alter your SEnuke so the built in list only has sites of PR2+ in then use button (6). Please note however this option is making changes to SEnuke files, not just the custom site files that our regular list changes, so it is for advanced users only! Be aware that when creating accounts SEnuke first creates for all built in sites and then goes back and does the custom sites, so do not be concerned if you see SEnuke move on from a site type without completing your custom sites yet.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/AZL8sLDvjxY?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><br />Firstly you need to install this software in to your “SEnuke/config” folder, this varies from PC to PC but the easiest way to find this is to ‘right click’ on your SEnuke icon and selection ‘Open File Location'”<br />This will open the SEnuke directory, then navigate to the ‘Config’ directory and copy all files from the download above. To make your life easier in the future you may then like to create a shortcut from the ‘SpetsnaZ Links.exe’ on your desktop.<br /><br />Please be aware that during testing 90% of all problems we have encountered were down to Anti Virus programs or Windows 8 blocking the file. As such you may have to whitelist the program within your AV package, Norton for instance will auto delete the file ‘SharpCompress.dll’. In addition the file requires inte.com access in order to download the latest lists from our servers, so it will need access through any firewall you have. The other 10% of problems are when the file is not copied to the correct folder, it will only work when inside the SEnuke Config folder.<br /><br />Once the two main files are installed, ‘SharpCompress.dll’ & ‘SpetsnaZ Links.exe’ simply run the program, read and accept the disclaimer and login using your ZontSEO username and password (do not try to use your SEnuke username and password here). If there are any updates to the software these will be auto installed at this point.<br /><br />You will now have the application open, enter your Zont SEO username and password and click connect:<br /><img src="http://www.zontseo.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/07/spetsnaz-links-2015.png" alt="Spetsnaz Link Tool 4.6.1.0 Premium" title="Spetsnaz Link Tool 4.6.1.0 Premium"  /><br />Make sure your SEnuke proxies are off and any close all copies of SEnuke, make sure they are fully closed not just minimised to the taskbar.<br /><br />Now firstly create a backup of your existing files, select ‘Backup’ and press the backup button (1). Any time you need to restore this original configuration select ‘Restore’ and press the backup button again.<br /><br />Then choose which list you want (2), all sites or only those sites PR1 or higher. The PR1+ option will always offer a smaller selection of sites than the ‘All Sites’, typically 20-40%.<br /><br /><b>Next select your mode (3):</b><br />- Reset & Update: all existing user defined sites will be removed and our latest working list downloaded and installed to your copy of SEnuke. This option clears out any other sites you have installed yourself and also resets all the site ID numbers. If you use this option any existing campaigns you have running will probably not work properly anymore. We suggest using this option the first time you run the tool, and any time in the future where you need to effectively ‘start again’<br />- Update Only: our latest list of sites will be downloaded and merged with your current site list. Any sites you already have will not be included again, however broken sites removed from our master list will also not be removed from your lists (unless you use  ‘Delete Dead Sites option’) and it will be up to you to remove broken sites. If you remove a site and later on we find it working again it will automatically be added again to your site list.<br /><br />Lastly choose if you want to ‘Delete dead sites’ (4), this feature will look at your list and remove any sites which have failed our tests. It only deletes sites based on failures from the last 2 updates, so if you have not updated your list for a couple of months it will not delete all the dead sites and you will need to use the ‘Reset & Update’ option instead to clear out dead sites. However if you run this at least once a month, preferably every update though, your list will automatically stay quite clean.<br /><br />Then press update (5), wait for the ‘Complete’ message and open SEnuke again to see your new user defined site lists.<br /><br />If you want to alter your SEnuke so the built in list only has sites of PR2+ in then use button (6). Please note however this option is making changes to SEnuke files, not just the custom site files that our regular list changes, so it is for advanced users only!<br /><br />Be aware that when creating accounts SEnuke first creates for all built in sites and then goes back and does the custom sites, so do not be concerned if you see SEnuke move on from a site type without completing your custom sites yet.<br /><img src="http://www.zontseo.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/07/Open-File-Location.png" alt="Spetsnaz Link Tool 4.6.1.0 Premium" title="Spetsnaz Link Tool 4.6.1.0 Premium"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Spetsnaz Link Tool 4.6.1.0 Premium" title="Spetsnaz Link Tool 4.6.1.0 Premium"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Rank Leap Pro 1.0.20</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1237-rank-leap.html</link>
<description>Name : Rank Leap Version : Pro 1.0.20 OS : Windows Type : Web 2.0 Poster Price : $397 Homepage : SalePage Rank Leap - the most powerful web 2.0 backlink software ever released. Now you can automatically create HUNDREDS of High PR Web 2.0 backlinks within a few minutes</description>
<category>Web 2.0 Posters</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2015 20:54:38 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Web 2.0 Article Sites Web 2.0 Profile Links</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/dqeX4uOxo0I?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Web 2.0 Article Sites<br /></li><li> Web 2.0 Profile Links<br /></li></ul><br /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Rank Leap Pro 1.0.20" title="Rank Leap Pro 1.0.20"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>ZSubmitter Enterprise v3.0.4</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/973-zsubmitter-enterprise.html</link>
<description>Name : ZSubmitter Version : 3.0.4 Enterprise OS : Windows Type : Web 2.0 Poster Price : $359 Homepage : SalePage Super Fast Create &amp; Maintain Unlimited Authority Tiered Web. 2.0 Blog.comworks Quality Web2.0 Blog Networks Create and maintain easily Scheduler, Fast, 100% socket, Automatic, Multi-Platform, Update Daily</description>
<category>Web 2.0 Posters</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.zsubmitter.com/wp-content/themes/new_template/images/engine0919.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2015 22:12:12 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Third party captcha support Option to Auto change ip by proxy &amp; HMA Authority Blogs, Constant Sites Updates Email verification Unlimited Account Creation and Posting Account &amp; Post veri&amp;#64257;cation and Re veri&amp;#64257;cation Auto compensate when account or posts deleted Multi-way to input content Random everything to look nature put keyword in subdomain or path Unlimited Projects Tiered link building Super Fast, Relialbe, Regular Updates Easily check accounts and verified posts Detail Reporting and Log to know what happen under hood Minimal human intervention, Auto pilot Create and Update Blog Network Automatically : With schedule feature, you can control how fast and how many accounts/post made every day,week or month, so you will get a growing web2.0.comwork without babysitting. Image how profitable to own high quality private.comworks with just clicks to get it started and leave it. Tier creation and link-building Link-wheel creation Proxy scraper and verifier Content generation: using the article image and video scraper and mixer(stop support) Account registration and posting using the in-built scheduler, so you can control how many posts per day per account and how many accounts per site per day and much more. Post verification and re-verification, so you can check if your links are stick, dofollow or changed. Activation of Web 2.0 email(s) Alerts for low captcha balance or no working proxy so there&#039;s no need to keep check everything repeatedly Import email from global email pool so there &#039;s no need to add email to every project manually Check and track your web site&#039;s ranking(not support yet) Index and/or ping after verification of your post(s)(not support yet) Create a full statistical report and email on schedule And much, much more 100 Blog Supported, New Engines Added Daily : Clean and powerful engine/mod system allowing you to easily add nearly any site/platform into the software.Currently, it support only 100 web2.0, range from PR4 to PR8. Most are context links. New web2.0 sites will be added weekly even daily so that you have 100+ Web2.0. Success Rate : Because web2.0 natural, you will not get 100% success rate. For the best result, the Web 2.0 engines are updated daily. It is also important to better success rate how you register and post. Here is some tips. 100% Socket, Speedy and Reliable : Robustly designed software architecture means we can easily support many new sites. It can even reboot itself on schedule or auto boot itself in the event of a crash. It even can reboot PC on schedule and resume automatically. There&#039;s no need for you to babysit the software. :::Free Members ::: Download Now Password : www.tgmember.com :::ViP Only:::</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/71PDtKf8OdA?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><br /><ul><li> Third party captcha support<br /></li><li> Option to Auto change ip by proxy & HMA<br /></li><li> Authority Blogs, Constant Sites Updates<br /></li><li> Email verification<br /></li><li> Unlimited Account Creation and Posting<br /></li><li> Account & Post veri&#64257;cation and Re veri&#64257;cation<br /></li><li> Auto compensate when account or posts deleted<br /></li><li> Multi-way to input content<br /></li><li> Random everything to look nature<br /></li><li> put keyword in subdomain or path<br /></li><li> Unlimited Projects<br /></li><li> Tiered link building<br /></li><li> Super Fast, Relialbe, Regular Updates<br /></li><li> Easily check accounts and verified posts<br /></li><li> Detail Reporting and Log to know what happen under hood<br /></li><li> Minimal human intervention, Auto pilot<br /></li><li> Create and Update Blog Network Automatically : With schedule feature, you can control how fast and how many accounts/post made every day,week or month, so you will get a growing web2.0.comwork without babysitting. Image how profitable to own high quality private.comworks with just clicks to get it started and leave it.<br /></li><li> Tier creation and link-building<br /></li><li> Link-wheel creation<br /></li><li> Proxy scraper and verifier<br /></li><li> Content generation: using the article image and video scraper and mixer(stop support)<br /></li><li> Account registration and posting using the in-built scheduler, so you can control how many posts per day per account and how many accounts per site per day and much more.<br /></li><li> Post verification and re-verification, so you can check if your links are stick, dofollow or changed.<br /></li><li> Activation of Web 2.0 email(s)<br /></li><li> Alerts for low captcha balance or no working proxy so there's no need to keep check everything repeatedly<br /></li><li> Import email from global email pool so there 's no need to add email to every project manually<br /></li><li> Check and track your web site's ranking(not support yet)<br /></li><li> Index and/or ping after verification of your post(s)(not support yet)<br /></li><li> Create a full statistical report and email on schedule<br /></li><li> And much, much more<br /></li><li> 100 Blog Supported, New Engines Added Daily : Clean and powerful engine/mod system allowing you to easily add nearly any site/platform into the software.Currently, it support only 100 web2.0, range from PR4 to PR8. Most are context links. New web2.0 sites will be added weekly even daily so that you have 100+ Web2.0.<br /></li><li> Success Rate : Because web2.0 natural, you will not get 100% success rate. For the best result, the Web 2.0 engines are updated daily. It is also important to better success rate how you register and post. Here is some tips.<br /></li><li> 100% Socket, Speedy and Reliable : Robustly designed software architecture means we can easily support many new sites. It can even reboot itself on schedule or auto boot itself in the event of a crash. It even can reboot PC on schedule and resume automatically. There's no need for you to babysit the software.<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://www.zsubmitter.com/wp-content/themes/new_template/images/engine0919.jpg" alt="ZSubmitter Enterprise v3.0.4" title="ZSubmitter Enterprise v3.0.4"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><span style="font-size:12pt;"><b><span style="color:#006600">:::Free Members :::</span></b></span><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" alt="ZSubmitter Enterprise v3.0.4" title="ZSubmitter Enterprise v3.0.4"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><a href="http://www.tgmember.com/engine/go.php?url=aHR0cHM6Ly9tZWdhLm56LyMhSG9KWHhLWlEhTHVkdzI2NUp4MVFpZnF3SU54Qi1XbHd0LURmQi1yamxHS2lJNzZJc2tsOA%3D%3D"  target="_blank">Download Now</a><br />Password : www.tgmember.com<br /></div><br /></div><br /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><span style="font-size:12pt;"><b><span style="color:#FF0000">:::ViP Only:::</span></b></span><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="ZSubmitter Enterprise v3.0.4" title="ZSubmitter Enterprise v3.0.4"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>FA Creator 2.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1185-facreator.html</link>
<description>Name :FA Creator Version : 2.0 OS : Windows Type : Web 2.0 Poster, LinkBuilding Tools Price : $12/m Homepage : SalePage FACreator - Fast Web 2.0 Account Creator (100+ Supported Websites).</description>
<category>Web 2.0 Posters</category>
<enclosure url="http://facreator.com/images/slide/auto_captcha_solving.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://facreator.com/images/slide/spin_details.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2015 03:55:40 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features 100% Socket , Amazing speed : FACreator has multi-threading feature which makes it several times faster and no crash like Web-Browser bots. 100+ Web 2.0 supported : Currently, FACreator support over 100 web2.0, range from PR4 to PR8. New web 2.0 sites will be added weekly even daily. 800+ High PR Web Profile : FACreator allow you post link to lot of High PR websites, range from PR3 to PR9. New websites will be added daily. Bypass Security Questions : FACreator has built-in “questions and answers” database. Allow you bypass security questions when register forum accounts. Bulk Hotmail/AOL Account Creator : FACreator has hotmail and AOL email account creator. You can create unlimited email accounts. Bookmarking Submitter : FACreator allow you post link to Pligg, PHPDug, Scuttle. New websites will be added weekly Wiki Submitter : FACreator allow you post article to MediaWiki, WikaWiki, DokuWiki, MoinMoin. Article Submitter : FACreator allow you post article to WordPress Article, ARB Article, Article MS, Article Friendly, Article Dashboard, Phpld Articles. Forum Profile Poster : FACreator support vbulletin 3/4, Xenforo, phpBB, IPB, Smf, myBB. New websites will be added weekly CAPTCHA solving : FACreator is integrated to work with Captcha Solving services, such as de-captcher.com, deathbycaptcha.com, and bypasscaptcha.com Proxy Support : Hide your footprints and protect your IP from getting banned by webmasters. FACreator supports both public and private proxies.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/AHeoR2v-5HE?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> 100% Socket , Amazing speed : FACreator has multi-threading feature which makes it several times faster and no crash like Web-Browser bots. <br /></li><li> 100+ Web 2.0 supported : Currently, FACreator support over 100 web2.0, range from PR4 to PR8. New web 2.0 sites will be added weekly even daily.<br /></li><li> 800+ High PR Web Profile : FACreator allow you post link to lot of High PR websites, range from PR3 to PR9. New websites will be added daily.<br /></li><li> Bypass Security Questions : FACreator has built-in “questions and answers” database. Allow you bypass security questions when register forum accounts.<br /></li><li> Bulk Hotmail/AOL Account Creator : FACreator has hotmail and AOL email account creator. You can create unlimited email accounts.<br /></li><li> Bookmarking Submitter : FACreator allow you post link to Pligg, PHPDug, Scuttle. New websites will be added weekly<br /></li><li> Wiki Submitter : FACreator allow you post article to MediaWiki, WikaWiki, DokuWiki, MoinMoin.<br /></li><li> Article Submitter : FACreator allow you post article to WordPress Article, ARB Article, Article MS, Article Friendly, Article Dashboard, Phpld Articles.<br /></li><li> Forum Profile Poster : FACreator support vbulletin 3/4, Xenforo, phpBB, IPB, Smf, myBB. New websites will be added weekly<br /></li><li> CAPTCHA solving : FACreator is integrated to work with Captcha Solving services, such as de-captcher.com, deathbycaptcha.com, and bypasscaptcha.com<br /></li><li> Proxy Support : Hide your footprints and protect your IP from getting banned by webmasters. FACreator supports both public and private proxies. <br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://facreator.com/images/slide/auto_captcha_solving.png" alt="FA Creator 2.0" title="FA Creator 2.0"  /><br /><img src="http://facreator.com/images/slide/spin_details.png" alt="FA Creator 2.0" title="FA Creator 2.0"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="FA Creator 2.0" title="FA Creator 2.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Web 2.0 Commando 1.0.0.42</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/965-web-20-commando.html</link>
<description>Name : Web 2.0 Commando Version : 1.0.0.42 OS : Windows Type : Web 2.0 Posters Price : $495 Homepage : SalePage Introducing The Next Generation Mass Optimized Posting &amp; Backlinking Tool Local Traffic Commando Is Back From The Dead! But So Much Different, So Much Better, So Much Power! So what are we doing now? Well, in short.It is still a WordPress plugin but it doesn&#039;t post to WordPress.say what!? Now this is where things start to get really cool! It has been built into a new tool called web 2.0 commando which will post on unlimited web 2.0 accounts on different sites, so you could in theory created 500 accounts in each and Web2commando can post to them but using random accounts every time, drip feeding, varying anchor text, fully optimized with H tags, alt tags automatically inserted into images and randomizing the videos and images on every page. This makes every page unique even if creating 1000&#039;s of posts at one time.</description>
<category>Web 2.0 Posters</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2015 00:30:12 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Create Unlimited Accounts Make Unlimited Posts Nothing To Install Except The Web 2.0 Account Creator ONE Click Bulk Account Creation ONE Click web 2.0 Account Uploads To Web 2.0 Commando Create 100&#039;s of Long Tail Posts in Competitive Niches Automated On Page SEO Every Post Unique! YOU Control The Quality Of The Posts YOU Control The Quantity of Posts Use For Local Marketing Use For CPA or Affiliate Offers Nothing Like This In Web 2.0 Syndication :::Free Members ::: Download Now Password : www.tgmember.com :::ViP Only:::</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/qDl_8g_YwYM?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Create Unlimited Accounts<br /></li><li> Make Unlimited Posts<br /></li><li> Nothing To Install Except The Web 2.0 Account Creator<br /></li><li> ONE Click Bulk Account Creation<br /></li><li> ONE Click web 2.0 Account Uploads To Web 2.0 Commando<br /></li><li> Create 100's of Long Tail Posts in Competitive Niches<br /></li><li> Automated On Page SEO<br /></li><li> Every Post Unique!<br /></li><li> YOU Control The Quality Of The Posts<br /></li><li> YOU Control The Quantity of Posts<br /></li><li> Use For Local Marketing<br /></li><li> Use For CPA or Affiliate Offers<br /></li><li> Nothing Like This In Web 2.0 Syndication <br /></li></ul><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><span style="font-size:12pt;"><b><span style="color:#006600">:::Free Members :::</span></b></span><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" alt="Web 2.0 Commando 1.0.0.42" title="Web 2.0 Commando 1.0.0.42"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><a href="http://www.tgmember.com/engine/go.php?url=aHR0cHM6Ly9tZWdhLmNvLm56LyMhbjFnd2xKaEshUVlBdGpiMWlUcmV0ZWNMZE5LU0pIbTgzeVU3ZlBhRUdXS2Z6U3NCYUNIQQ%3D%3D"  target="_blank">Download Now</a><br />Password : www.tgmember.com<br /></div><br /></div><br /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><span style="font-size:12pt;"><b><span style="color:#FF0000">:::ViP Only:::</span></b></span><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Web 2.0 Commando 1.0.0.42" title="Web 2.0 Commando 1.0.0.42"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Softnoia Blog Creator 2.1.35</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/927-softnoia-blog-creator.html</link>
<description>Name : Softnoia Blog Creator Version : 2.1.35 OS : Windows Type : Web 2.0 Creator, PBN Price : $15 /month Homepage : SalePage Softnoia BLog Creator is an extremely powerful blog creator and poster.it&#039;s the perect tool to create and manage your own blog.comwork.You can literally create thousands of high quality contextual backlinks to any site you want.</description>
<category>Web 2.0 Posters</category>
<enclosure url="http://i.imgur.com/9YucIKa.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2015 00:57:42 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br /><img src="http://i.imgur.com/9YucIKa.png" alt="Softnoia Blog Creator 2.1.35" title="Softnoia Blog Creator 2.1.35"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Softnoia Blog Creator 2.1.35" title="Softnoia Blog Creator 2.1.35"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Ant Aladdin 2.1.5.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/865-ant-aladdin.html</link>
<description>Name : Ant Aladdin Version : 2.1.5.0 Enterprise Premium OS : Windows Type : Link Building, Web 2.0 Price : $99 Homepage : SalePage It&#039;s a Highly Effective Drag and Drop Backlink Building Software Tool to Achieve Higher Rankings. Instantly Build Complete &quot;Drag and Drop&quot; Style Link Building Campaigns Using The Brand NEW Aladdin SEO Software The great part about automated link building is that it saves you having to carry out a tedious task that can suck up all of your time. Time that you could spend on other, more productive tasks. However, when marketers use automated link building tools there can be a fine line between &quot;Overkill&quot; and getting it &quot;just right&quot;. With Oz&#039;s brand new Aladdin SEO software you not only get &quot;drag and drop&quot; access to the best, most authoritive platforms... You also get the features and functionality to create these links in a natural, layered, drip fed pattern. With Aladdin you are able to quickly design &quot;drag and drop&quot; SEO campaigns using the built-in drag and drop campaign builder. With this you are able to create multiple, strategically layered backlinks from a number of top authority platforms. What makes this really great is that you are also able to add in your OWN PBN&#039;s and Wordpress sites.</description>
<category>Web 2.0 Posters</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2015 00:55:36 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Create Media-Rich (Videos &amp; Images) Content that Google Loves Captivate your audience by randomly embedding a variety of engaging and highly relevant videos and images into the content that you syndicate. Mix and match videos and images with articles. You can use the same video or image with different articles and also use the same article with different videos and images. Google loves rich content and will reward you with even higher rankings. Do ALL this just by specifying a target keyword and without having to create any videos or images yourself. No more spending hours on the tedious legwork! You can even add your Youzign designs to your content with just a few clicks. Leverage the Power of PBNs and Authority of Web 2.0s: Use the same easy to use drag-n-drop interface to leverage PBN backlinks, Web 2.0 backlinks and bookmarks. You won&#039;t have to juggle different tools and spreadsheets any longer to manage complex campaigns. Get the backlinks you need to rank your sites on Page 1 of Google with just one click — a massive time saver over manual backlink building. And since Aladdin is so simple and fun to use, you&#039;ll be increasing the amount of syndicated content you have out... and with your brand coming up again and again... you&#039;ll start to be recognized as an authority. Enjoy the Advantage of Drag-n-drop Backlinking Strategies: Design your strategies (and add content) much more quickly than before with our simple Drag-n-drop interface – I promise you&#039;ll never have to figure out the best syndication strategy again by staring at long lists of URLs! Your results show that some of your strategies are working better than others? Quickly and easily make changes to your campaigns by dragging and dropping a few icons. Syndicate Your Videos Without Any Extra Work (***New in Version 2.0): In Aladdin 1.0 you could add relevant videos to your articles. Now with Aladdin 2.0 – in addition to adding relevant videos to your articles, you can also syndicate your videos to the most popular video aggregation sites such as Youtube. And you know what that means... Get lots more visitors from these highly trafficked video sites! Make It Even Faster &amp; Easier To Syndicate Your Content (***New in Version 2.0): With Aladdin 2.0 – you can just click one button and watch Aladdin do all the heavy lifting for you. Avoid Expensive Mistakes When Planning a Backlinking Campaign: Keep your money sites safer from Google slaps because you’ll avoid accidentally creating two-way links. No more wondering if you’ve covered all the bases planning your campaigns—have visual proof you did it right before the links are created No more copying and pasting URLs to platform interfaces until your eyes cross and your mind goes numb and you start to make mistakes.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/90QcrUWbpjw?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><br /><h3>Features</h3><br />Create Media-Rich (Videos & Images) Content that Google Loves<br /><ul><li> Captivate your audience by randomly embedding a variety of engaging and highly relevant videos and images into the content that you syndicate.<br /></li><li> Mix and match videos and images with articles. You can use the same video or image with different articles and also use the same article with different videos and images. Google loves rich content and will reward you with even higher rankings.<br /></li><li> Do ALL this just by specifying a target keyword and without having to create any videos or images yourself. No more spending hours on the tedious legwork!<br /></li><li> You can even add your Youzign designs to your content with just a few clicks.<br /></li></ul> <br />Leverage the Power of PBNs and Authority of Web 2.0s:<br /><br /><ul><li> Use the same easy to use drag-n-drop interface to leverage PBN backlinks, Web 2.0 backlinks and bookmarks. You won't have to juggle different tools and spreadsheets any longer to manage complex campaigns.<br /></li><li> Get the backlinks you need to rank your sites on Page 1 of Google with just one click — a massive time saver over manual backlink building.<br /></li><li> And since Aladdin is so simple and fun to use, you'll be increasing the amount of syndicated content you have out... and with your brand coming up again and again... you'll start to be recognized as an authority.<br /></li></ul> <br />Enjoy the Advantage of Drag-n-drop Backlinking Strategies:<br /><br /><ul><li> Design your strategies (and add content) much more quickly than before with our simple Drag-n-drop interface – I promise you'll never have to figure out the best syndication strategy again by staring at long lists of URLs!<br /></li><li> Your results show that some of your strategies are working better than others? Quickly and easily make changes to your campaigns by dragging and dropping a few icons.<br /></li></ul> <br />Syndicate Your Videos Without Any Extra Work (***New in Version 2.0):<br /><ul><li> In Aladdin 1.0 you could add relevant videos to your articles. Now with Aladdin 2.0 – in addition to adding relevant videos to your articles, you can also syndicate your videos to the most popular video aggregation sites such as Youtube. And you know what that means... Get lots more visitors from these highly trafficked video sites!<br /></li></ul> <br /><br />Make It Even Faster & Easier To Syndicate Your Content (***New in Version 2.0):<br /><ul><li> With Aladdin 2.0 – you can just click one button and watch Aladdin do all the heavy lifting for you. <br /></li></ul> <br />Avoid Expensive Mistakes When Planning a Backlinking Campaign:<br /><ul><li> Keep your money sites safer from Google slaps because you’ll avoid accidentally creating two-way links.<br /></li><li> No more wondering if you’ve covered all the bases planning your campaigns—have visual proof you did it right before the links are created<br /></li><li> No more copying and pasting URLs to platform interfaces until your eyes cross and your mind goes numb and you start to make mistakes.<br /></li></ul> <br /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Ant Aladdin 2.1.5.0" title="Ant Aladdin 2.1.5.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>