<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Guest Posting - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Guest Posting - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>Contact Form Submitter 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4221-contact-form-submitter.html</link>
<description>Name : Contact Form Submitter Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Contact Form Submit Tool Price : $59 Homepage : SalePage Contact Form Submitter is a software tool that allows users to generate traffic by automatically submitting a websites contact form with any given message and contact details. T his is one of the most powerful tools available for automatic contact form submission. Enter the required details such as your message, email, telephone number and website then click start and let this contact form bot do all the hard work for you.</description>
<category>Guest Posting</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 03:26:48 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Contact Form Submitter has three different modes of operation. - Submit to a list of websites - The software will work its way through a given list of websites attempting to find the contact form on each one then populate it with your message and contact details then automatically submit the contact form. - Submit to all websites results from a Google search query - The software will search Google for your given search querie(s) then search for a contact form on each website returned from Google. It will then populate it with your message and contact details then automatically submit the contact form. This is a great method for just entering your niche keywords and generating traffic for your website quickly and easily. - Endless posting on all websites it can find on the inte.com - Simply enter your seed websites and the tool will crawl these seed websites extracting all external domains and submitting their contact forms. It will then crawl these external domains repeating the process endlessly. True set and forget, generating traffic for your website.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/_Oml5Fof85c?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Contact Form Submitter has three different modes of operation.<br></li><li> - Submit to a list of websites - The software will work its way through a given list of websites attempting to find the contact form on each one then populate it with your message and contact details then automatically submit the contact form.<br></li><li> - Submit to all websites results from a Google search query - The software will search Google for your given search querie(s) then search for a contact form on each website returned from Google. It will then populate it with your message and contact details then automatically submit the contact form. This is a great method for just entering your niche keywords and generating traffic for your website quickly and easily.<br></li><li> - Endless posting on all websites it can find on the inte.com - Simply enter your seed websites and the tool will crawl these seed websites extracting all external domains and submitting their contact forms. It will then crawl these external domains repeating the process endlessly. True set and forget, generating traffic for your website.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Contact Form Submitter 1.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Guest Post Finder 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3730-guest-post-finder.html</link>
<description>Name : Guest Post Finder Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Guest Post Finder Price : $0 Homepage : SalePage Guest Post Finder is a 100% free and full desktop application that will search (scrape) Google for guest posting opportunities in your niche so you don&#039;t have to spend hours manually doing the same. It will even check Moz DA for each website so you can assess how powerful each link will be.</description>
<category>Guest Posting</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 05:28:20 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>[media=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9uDAVMRFox8] Features How does Guest Post Finder work? Guest Post Finder simply fires HTTP requests to Google to perform searches with your niche keywords and typical guest posting keywords words such as &quot;guest posters wanted&quot;. There is currently a total of 40 and you are free to add and remove your own. The conditions for finding guest posts are highly customisable for example the guest post keyword match must be in the body, or title or meta data. Guest Post Finder also support proxies for blazingly fast results. List of guest posting keywords we use accepting guest posters accepting guest posts articles wanted become a contributor become a guest blogger become an author become guest writer blog for us contribute to our site contributing writer contributor guidelines guest article guest author guest blogger guest column guest post courtesy of guest post opportunities guest poster wanted guest posters wanted guest posting guidelines guest posts guest posts wanted looking for guest posts submit an article submit article submit blog post submit content submit guest post submit post submit your content suggest a post this is a guest post by this post was written by want to contribute to our website want to write a post want to write an article want to write for write for us writers wanted Why should I use Guest Post Finder? Finding niche related guest posts can take hours, even days sometimes. Why spend all that time when you can simply enter your niche keywords and let Guest Post Finder do all the searching and metric checking for you. Simply enter your niche keywords and come back to every guest posting opportunity there is for you.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;">[media=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9uDAVMRFox8]</div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br>How does Guest Post Finder work?<br>Guest Post Finder simply fires HTTP requests to Google to perform searches with your niche keywords and typical guest posting keywords words such as "guest posters wanted". There is currently a total of 40 and you are free to add and remove your own. The conditions for finding guest posts are highly customisable for example the guest post keyword match must be in the body, or title or meta data. Guest Post Finder also support proxies for blazingly fast results.<br><br>List of guest posting keywords we use<br>accepting guest posters<br>accepting guest posts<br>articles wanted<br>become a contributor<br>become a guest blogger<br>become an author<br>become guest writer<br>blog for us<br>contribute to our site<br>contributing writer<br>contributor guidelines<br>guest article<br>guest author<br>guest blogger<br>guest column<br>guest post courtesy of<br>guest post opportunities<br>guest poster wanted<br>guest posters wanted<br>guest posting guidelines<br>guest posts<br>guest posts wanted<br>looking for guest posts<br>submit an article<br>submit article<br>submit blog post<br>submit content<br>submit guest post<br>submit post<br>submit your content<br>suggest a post<br>this is a guest post by<br>this post was written by<br>want to contribute to our website<br>want to write a post<br>want to write an article<br>want to write for<br>write for us<br>writers wanted<br>Why should I use Guest Post Finder?<br>Finding niche related guest posts can take hours, even days sometimes. Why spend all that time when you can simply enter your niche keywords and let Guest Post Finder do all the searching and metric checking for you. Simply enter your niche keywords and come back to every guest posting opportunity there is for you.<br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Guest Post Finder 1.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>WordPhire 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3721-wordphire.html</link>
<description>Name : WordPhire Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : WordPress Comment Bot Price : $0 Homepage : SalePage WordPhire is an experiment I&#039;ve written to see if we can automatically add comments to wordpress websites that actually add value to the website and will genuinely help out the website owner.</description>
<category>Guest Posting</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 07:11:52 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>[media=https://youtu.be/lwSmukaQi5o] Features WordPhire works by using the Twitter streaming API to listen out for people/accounts that are tweeting about your niche. Once it finds a tweet about your niche it will check the users profile bio to see if there is a link to their website. If there is a link in the bio it will follow it to the website where it it will get their latest wordpress post and analyze the page to extract a whole range of different information about the website so you can automatically construct a commenting that actually offers value. See the comment below for an example. Hi Jamie, I saw you tweeting about funny cats and I&#039;d thought I&#039;d come back out your website. Its cool I like it, the &quot;Digital Blue&quot; theme you&#039;ve got is really nice, Roboto is one of my favourite Google fonts. Nice job on the social buttons people would love to share your stuff. I see you&#039;re not building a mailing list, you should do this, people would love to know when you publish more stuff! Another little hint, get Google analytics installed its great! :-) Anyways keep aming great stuff Jamie! Thats just a quick little sample of the power of WordPhire, you wouldn&#039;t think thats auto generated would you? Also because you can search for custom HTML you&#039;re not restrcited in the value of the comment you can post either. If you know of a bad plugin that is getting everyone hacked you can add a check for it and warn the website owner. Why should I use WordPhire? Because these comments will stick and you can post thousands per day, just imagine what that will do for your website traffic and brand awareness.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;">[media=https://youtu.be/lwSmukaQi5o]</div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br>WordPhire works by using the Twitter streaming API to listen out for people/accounts that are tweeting about your niche. Once it finds a tweet about your niche it will check the users profile bio to see if there is a link to their website. If there is a link in the bio it will follow it to the website where it it will get their latest wordpress post and analyze the page to extract a whole range of different information about the website so you can automatically construct a commenting that actually offers value. See the comment below for an example.<br><br>Hi Jamie,<br>I saw you tweeting about funny cats and I'd thought I'd come back out your website. Its cool I like it, the "Digital Blue" theme you've got is really nice, Roboto is one of my favourite Google fonts.<br>Nice job on the social buttons people would love to share your stuff.<br>I see you're not building a mailing list, you should do this, people would love to know when you publish more stuff! <br>Another little hint, get Google analytics installed its great! :-) Anyways keep aming great stuff Jamie!<br><br>Thats just a quick little sample of the power of WordPhire, you wouldn't think thats auto generated would you? Also because you can search for custom HTML you're not restrcited in the value of the comment you can post either. If you know of a bad plugin that is getting everyone hacked you can add a check for it and warn the website owner.<br><br>Why should I use WordPhire?<br>Because these comments will stick and you can post thousands per day, just imagine what that will do for your website traffic and brand awareness.<br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="WordPhire 1.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>TrafficPhire 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3722-trafficphire.html</link>
<description>Name : TrafficPhire Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : GuestBlog Post Price : $0 Homepage : SalePage TrafficPhire allows you to automate a large part of your outreach. If you want to promote your website or new content to other webmasters/businsess it can be very time consuming filling out contact forms. TrafficPhire listens for users on twitter (based on what they tweet) and fills out their website contact form with your custom message if its thinks they&#039;ll be interested in your product or service. As SEO is shifting more towards content marketing than just manually building links having the ability to automatically market your content with laser targeted precision while on autopilot can change your business. TrafficPhire uses the Twitter API to for people in your niche then populates and submits thir websites contact form.</description>
<category>Guest Posting</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 07:10:13 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>[media=https://youtu.be/4abrHyanq2I] Features How does TrafficPhire? TrafficPhire works by using the Twitter Streaming API and listening for a set of keyords you specify to decide if the user making a tweet is interested in your product or service. For example if you offer a Wordpress service you would set Wordpress as your keyword (you can have many) then when anyone who tweets about wordpress is found by PhireTraffic it will check their bio for a link to their website then follow the link and populate their websites contact form with your message regarding your service. Why use TrafficPhire? TrafficPhire can find you lazer targetted niche related websites and contact them on auto pilot 24/7. TrafficPhire is capable of sending thousands of messages per day and generating you massive amounts of traffic. Oh yeah, also...its 100% FULL and FREE.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;">[media=https://youtu.be/4abrHyanq2I]</div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br>How does TrafficPhire?<br>TrafficPhire works by using the Twitter Streaming API and listening for a set of keyords you specify to decide if the user making a tweet is interested in your product or service. For example if you offer a Wordpress service you would set Wordpress as your keyword (you can have many) then when anyone who tweets about wordpress is found by PhireTraffic it will check their bio for a link to their website then follow the link and populate their websites contact form with your message regarding your service.<br><br>Why use TrafficPhire?<br>TrafficPhire can find you lazer targetted niche related websites and contact them on auto pilot 24/7. TrafficPhire is capable of sending thousands of messages per day and generating you massive amounts of traffic. Oh yeah, also...its 100% FULL and FREE.<br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="TrafficPhire 1.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Backlink Refresh 1.4 SEO Edition</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1859-backlink-refresh.html</link>
<description>Name : Backlink Refresh Version : 1.4 SEO Edition OS : Windows Type : Blog Comment Tools, Guest Blog Post, EDU/GOV Posting Price : $75 Homepage : SalePage Harvest fresh and relevant backlinks, Collect high-quality keyword backlinks,Search, save, comment, and rank! BacklinkRefresh is a powerful tool for automatically collecting fresh and relevant high-quality backlinks for your web site. BacklinkRefresh is very easy to use. Simply enter your target keyword and choose your options for backlinks from .COM, .COM, .ORG, .EDU, and .GOV web sites. Save the search results, visit the sites, and leave a comment. This simple process can help gradually increase your backlinks and ranking over time! Backlinks generated with BacklinkRefresh come from recent, well-maintained blogs. Results can come from blog posts as recent as 1 hour old or span across the entire year. These types of fresh posts are often well-moderated, contain few existing comments, and result in quicker comment approval and backlink generation.</description>
<category>Guest Posting</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.dummysoftware.com/backlinkrefresh-cap1.gif" type="image/gif" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2016 00:12:00 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Unlimited time usage of software. Unlimited generation of backlinks for any number of web sites. Generation of backlinks for commercial purposes. Generation of backlinks for other businesses and clients.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/m8boF-zDRb8?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Unlimited time usage of software.<br /></li><li> Unlimited generation of backlinks for any number of web sites.<br /></li><li> Generation of backlinks for commercial purposes.<br /></li><li> Generation of backlinks for other businesses and clients.<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://www.dummysoftware.com/backlinkrefresh-cap1.gif" alt="Backlink Refresh 1.4 SEO Edition" title="Backlink Refresh 1.4 SEO Edition"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Backlink Refresh 1.4 SEO Edition" title="Backlink Refresh 1.4 SEO Edition"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Guest Post Pro 1.0.3</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1101-guest-post-pro.html</link>
<description>Name : Guest Post Pro Version : 1.0.3 OS : Windows Type : Backlink Building Tools Price : $50 Homepage : SalePage Guest Posting Just Got Easier GuestPosterPRO lets you find high traffic sites in any niche that accept guest posts quickly and easily. It&#039;s Simple, Fast and Effective. Guest Poster PRO is the amazing software lets you find high traffic sites in any niche that accept guest post quickly and easily.. We know that you will be extremely happy with your purchase, but want you to have full peace of mind. Therefore, we offer a complete 30 day money back guarantee with no questions asked. Get Guest Poster PRO now!</description>
<category>Guest Posting</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2016 09:24:40 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Find Guest Posting Opportunities : Type in any keyword and find guest posting opportunities quickly and easily. Contact Site Owners : Just click the contact button to contact your list of site owners from within the software. You can literally contact 100&#039;s of sites within minutes. Saves Time : Automating this time consuming task saves countless hours that can be used on other activities. Search Specific Niches : The keyword search lets you quickly and easily search for any niche regardless of size. Create A Blogging Network : Save all of your search contact and create a blogging.comwork that you can access over and over again for guest posting. Export Contact List : Once you have saved your contact list it can be easily exported to a csv file. Search Multiple Google Datacenters : You can search several Google datacenters around the world. Simply selection your desired location from the drop down menu. Check the Authority : Check Authority via Pagerank and other traffic statistics to ensure sites are worth contacting. Cross Platform Functionality : GuestPosterPRO is an Adobe AIR software that runs on both Mac and Windows platforms. 100% Free Support : Support is available online through our help desk, which is staffed by US and UK employees. We are here to help you deal with any issue you may have.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><video width="640" height="480" preload="metadata" poster="rss.xml" controls="controls">
						<source type="video/mp4" src="http://embed.wistia.com/deliveries/580f3b2662fdb55ec406c57875ce0ef082f2998c/file.mp4"></source>
						</video></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Find Guest Posting Opportunities : Type in any keyword and find guest posting opportunities quickly and easily. <br /></li><li> Contact Site Owners : Just click the contact button to contact your list of site owners from within the software. You can literally contact 100's of sites within minutes. <br /></li><li> Saves Time : Automating this time consuming task saves countless hours that can be used on other activities. <br /></li><li> Search Specific Niches : The keyword search lets you quickly and easily search for any niche regardless of size. <br /></li><li> Create A Blogging Network : Save all of your search contact and create a blogging.comwork that you can access over and over again for guest posting. <br /></li><li> Export Contact List : Once you have saved your contact list it can be easily exported to a csv file.<br /></li><li> Search Multiple Google Datacenters : You can search several Google datacenters around the world. Simply selection your desired location from the drop down menu. <br /></li><li> Check the Authority : Check Authority via Pagerank and other traffic statistics to ensure sites are worth contacting. <br /></li><li> Cross Platform Functionality : GuestPosterPRO is an Adobe AIR software that runs on both Mac and Windows platforms. <br /></li><li> 100% Free Support : Support is available online through our help desk, which is staffed by US and UK employees. We are here to help you deal with any issue you may have.<br /></li></ul><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Guest Post Pro 1.0.3" title="Guest Post Pro 1.0.3"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>TrafficAid Pro 1.53 Build 17</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1212-trafficaid.html</link>
<description>Name : TrafficAid Version : Pro 1.53 Build 17 OS : Windows/MAC Type : Guest Blog Post Price : $47 Homepage : SalePage Can Traffic Aid REALLY Help You Build A Steady Steam Of &#039;Google Traffic&#039; By Using Their &#039;Secret&#039; White-Hat System? Is TrafficAid Truly a Fast Profit-Generating System? This is the power of commenting, but there is one problem: it takes a lot of time to find blogs, and you may never find some with the most social power. That’s where TrafficAid Software comes in handy. This software was designed specifically for white-hat commenters trying to increase their social presence online. It allows you to put in any keyword of your choice and then select a variety of customized search features to quickly identify blogs that meet the following criteria:</description>
<category>Guest Posting</category>
<enclosure url="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/trafficaid/fe-sales-page-graphics/traffic-aid-logo.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://mecanto.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/screenshot-01.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 01:37:00 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features High search engine ranking Type of website (.com, .edu, .gov, etc.) Comments enabled Preferred plaform Guest post opportunities Last date updated Minimum number of posts Leave unique comments every time, never dropping the same prewritten comment on multiple blog posts. Read all comments previously left on a post so that you don’t repeat what others have said. Leave longer comments to draw attention to your posts. Take advantage of side conversations to leave multiple comments on a single blog post. Take the time to get to know each individual blogger so that your comments impress rather than aggravate them. Some blogs manually approve comments, so you may have to contact the blogger if they don’t approve your message in a reasonable time frame, but do so with respect and courtesy Commenting on multiple blogs on a consistent basis does take time, but TrafficAid Software is designed to cut some corners so that you find more blogs in less time. You can spend more time commenting and less time searching and analyzing blogs.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/CJifIbplAa8?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> High search engine ranking<br /></li><li> Type of website (.com, .edu, .gov, etc.)<br /></li><li> Comments enabled<br /></li><li> Preferred plaform<br /></li><li> Guest post opportunities<br /></li><li> Last date updated<br /></li><li> Minimum number of posts<br /></li><li> Leave unique comments every time, never dropping the same prewritten comment on multiple blog posts.<br /></li><li> Read all comments previously left on a post so that you don’t repeat what others have said.<br /></li><li> Leave longer comments to draw attention to your posts.<br /></li><li> Take advantage of side conversations to leave multiple comments on a single blog post.<br /></li><li> Take the time to get to know each individual blogger so that your comments impress rather than aggravate them.<br /></li><li> Some blogs manually approve comments, so you may have to contact the blogger if they don’t approve your message in a reasonable time frame, but do so with respect and courtesy<br /></li><li> Commenting on multiple blogs on a consistent basis does take time, but TrafficAid Software is designed to cut some corners so that you find more blogs in less time. You can spend more time commenting and less time searching and analyzing blogs.<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/trafficaid/fe-sales-page-graphics/traffic-aid-logo.png" alt="TrafficAid Pro 1.53 Build 17" title="TrafficAid Pro 1.53 Build 17"  /><br /><img src="http://mecanto.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/screenshot-01.jpg" alt="TrafficAid Pro 1.53 Build 17" title="TrafficAid Pro 1.53 Build 17"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="TrafficAid Pro 1.53 Build 17" title="TrafficAid Pro 1.53 Build 17"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>GuestPost Supremacy Pro v3.5</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1149-guestpost-supremacy.html</link>
<description>Name : GuestPost Supremacy Version : Pro v3.5 OS : Windows Type : GuestPost Tool Price : $25 Homepage : SalePage Relevancy and quality are probably the two most important words in today’s SEO world. The best type of backlinks is the one coming from relevant, similar websites to yours, which are in the same niche or closely related niches. That’s what’s so beautiful about guest posts. The simplicity of the system allows you to get the most relevant type of backlink possible WHILE still getting direct traffic from the guest post itself. There’s no doubt that guest posts work and they work incredibly well (we have tons of proof for that) but it’s really hard to identify guest posts that are worthy of your efforts, with so many outdated low quality blogs out there. GuestPost Supremacy will change that. This amazing little software harvests hundreds of guest post opportunities within minutes, for any keyword you can think of. Not only it does that, you can also see the Page Rank and Alexa Rank right within the app. You can even save the URLs that you like and email the webmasters straight from the software.</description>
<category>Guest Posting</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2015 15:41:41 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features GuestPost Supremacy uncovers hundreds of guest post opportunities within minutes! Gets you an instant surge of ultra-targeted, pre-sold traffic ets you SEO juice that actually counts and is slap-proof</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/pqOl5RFAuZo?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> GuestPost Supremacy uncovers hundreds of guest post opportunities within minutes!<br></li><li> Gets you an instant surge of ultra-targeted, pre-sold traffic<br></li><li> ets you SEO juice that actually counts and is slap-proof<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="GuestPost Supremacy Pro v3.5"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Guest Post Hunter 1.0.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1100-guest-post-hunter.html</link>
<description>Name : Guest Post Hunter Version : 1.0.0 OS : Windows Type : Backlink Building Tools Price : $47 Homepage : SalePage Guest Post Hunter is the Free Tool Which Helps You To Find Those Blog Which Are Accepting Blogs Post. You Can Search Blogs &amp;amp; Send Direct Emails From This Software. its amazing software for Backlinks. ask for guest posting to other webmasters and increase Backlinks for your site.</description>
<category>Guest Posting</category>
<enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/wfsalespages/guest1.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/hostedsalespages/guest_04.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2015 02:27:38 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><div class="dlevideoplayer" style="width:100%;max-width:425px;">
			<ul data-theme="default" data-preload="metadata">
				<li data-title="guestpostdemo" data-type="m4v" data-url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/hostedsalespages/guestpostdemo.mp4" ></li>
			</ul>
		</div></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><img src="https://s3.amazonaws.com/wfsalespages/guest1.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Guest Post Hunter 1.0.0"><br><img src="https://s3.amazonaws.com/hostedsalespages/guest_04.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>