<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Social Media - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Social Media - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>Twt Dominator 5.5.0.21</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/955-twtdominator.html</link>
<description>Name :Twt Dominator Version : 5.5.0.21 OS : Windows Type : Twitter Marketing Price : $499 Homepage : SalePage TwtDominator lets you target with precision, connect directly with your audience, spread your message throughout the day, manage campaigns and do much more to make sure you achieve your marketing goal. There&#039;s no doubt that Twitter, with its more than 600 million users, has become a great marketing tool for business today. With growing targeting, analytics, promotional tactics and marketing tools provided by Twitter, it&#039;s definitely a great arsenal in your digital marketing tool kit. Now Brands have been opening Twitter accounts thick and fast like you, but how confident are you of obtaining real results, and are you able to measure the impact of their messaging on the microblogging.comwork? So the difficulty remains: Who will you reach on Twitter? How will you reach them? How effectively are you using this tool? How can you tell if you&#039;ve done a good job? etc.</description>
<category>Twitter Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 27 May 2018 11:22:36 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Follower : Follow multiple accounts from your accounts uploaded. Tweet : Keep your accounts active. Easily Retweet or Reply using trending keywords. Unfollower : Get rid of users who are not following you back easily with a click Account Actions : Allows you to always use the best accounts for your process and campaigns. Wait &amp;amp; Reply : Upload a list of Messages and Keywords let the software tweet and reply. Scrape Users : Scrape users from keywords, names and also get a list of trending hash tags easily. Tweet Creator : Tweet using keywords to the targeted users. Retweet &amp;amp; Favorite : Resell or increase RTs &amp;amp; FAVs of specific tweets in no time. Campaign Manager : Easily create different campaigns for different process and run them all together.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/haf09BOHCzw?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Follower : Follow multiple accounts from your accounts uploaded. <br></li><li> Tweet : Keep your accounts active. Easily Retweet or Reply using trending keywords. <br></li><li> Unfollower : Get rid of users who are not following you back easily with a click <br></li><li> Account Actions : Allows you to always use the best accounts for your process and campaigns. <br></li><li> Wait &amp; Reply : Upload a list of Messages and Keywords let the software tweet and reply. <br></li><li> Scrape Users : Scrape users from keywords, names and also get a list of trending hash tags easily. <br></li><li> Tweet Creator : Tweet using keywords to the targeted users. <br></li><li> Retweet &amp; Favorite : Resell or increase RTs &amp; FAVs of specific tweets in no time. <br></li><li> Campaign Manager : Easily create different campaigns for different process and run them all together. <br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Twt Dominator 5.5.0.21"><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>FaceDominator 3.5.0.39</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/879-facedominator.html</link>
<description>Name :FaceDominator Agency Version : 3.5.0.39 OS : Windows Type : Facebook Marketing Price : $499 Homepage : SalePage FaceDominator is a tool which is very useful for managing and automating your facebook advertising campaign. Learn more about FaceDominator Features with our Case Studies to help your business. Facebook marketing of your products through Facedominator To Promote Your Product through Wall Using Wall Poster,Manage Group,Photo Tagging,Manage Pages &amp;amp; Fan Page Poster</description>
<category>Facebook Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 27 May 2018 11:22:20 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FB Event Manager : Complete management of Events on facebook, Scrape users, Ask users to join it, etc. Customize Your Account : You can upload accounts,Check active and deactive accounts of facebook to upload a huge text file of accounts easily change the accout profile name and language of the accounts. Fanpage Manager : It can create Fanpage automatically or with your custom data. You can also use your keywords and categories to create pages Friend Adder :You can add targeted friends in your account. Targeting can be done based on Geo-Location or from fanpages. Wall Poster : You can post your message on the wall of friends or walls of fanpages with your targated keywords. Group Manager : you can invite your friends to join the groups,send request to groups,Post photo,url and messages on groups easily. Supports IP Proxies : It support both private and public proxies for all its features. You can also use Hide my Ass VPN to use with this tool. Automatic Captcha : It support Decaptcher.com and Deathbycaptcha.com for decoding captcha Auto Group Joiner Group Scraper Fans Scraper Multithreaded &amp;amp; Proxy Support Group Campaign Manager Group Request Manager Free For All http://mir.cr/AWYD8MSI</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/o592U_gke4I?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> FB Event Manager : Complete management of Events on facebook, Scrape users, Ask users to join it, etc.<br></li><li> Customize Your Account : You can upload accounts,Check active and deactive accounts of facebook to upload a huge text file of accounts easily change the accout profile name and language of the accounts.<br></li><li> Fanpage Manager : It can create Fanpage automatically or with your custom data. You can also use your keywords and categories to create pages<br></li><li> Friend Adder :You can add targeted friends in your account. Targeting can be done based on Geo-Location or from fanpages.<br></li><li> Wall Poster : You can post your message on the wall of friends or walls of fanpages with your targated keywords.<br></li><li> Group Manager : you can invite your friends to join the groups,send request to groups,Post photo,url and messages on groups easily.<br></li><li> Supports IP Proxies : It support both private and public proxies for all its features. You can also use Hide my Ass VPN to use with this tool.<br></li><li> Automatic Captcha : It support Decaptcher.com and Deathbycaptcha.com for decoding captcha<br></li><li> Auto Group Joiner<br></li><li> Group Scraper<br></li><li> Fans Scraper<br></li><li> Multithreaded &amp; Proxy Support<br></li><li> Group Campaign Manager<br></li><li> Group Request Manager<br></li></ul><br><div class="quote">Free For All<br><a href="http://mir.cr/AWYD8MSI"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">http://mir.cr/AWYD8MSI</a><br></div><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="FaceDominator 3.5.0.39"><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Social Page Analyzer 1.0.12</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/941-social-page-analyzer.html</link>
<description>Name : Social Page Analyzer Version : 1.0.12 OS : Windows Type : FB Fanpage Tool Price : $354.95 Homepage : SalePage The NEW Social Page Analyzer, an extremely powerful Mac/PC software that analyzes facebook pages, posts, and comments helping you uncover the top marketing content and strategies for your own social marketing campaigns! A new powerful tool for analyzing Facebook fanpages, fanpage posts and post comments with 5 built-in tools for uncovering the secrets behind any successful fanpage in just seconds!</description>
<category>Social Ads Tools</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2018 13:31:47 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Search thousands of fanpages by keyword or paste in as many facebook page you links want to analyze Check fanpage names for Facebook ad interest keywords for your ad campaigns Generate VERY detailed page score reports for optimizing your fanpages for high natural organic traffic! Get 27 different data metrics for every fanpage Extract emails &amp;amp; websites for fanpages! Contact page owners to build valuable marketing relationships to skyrocket your Facebook marketing success! Works on both Mac and PC computers Get 1000&#039;s of fanpages using sophisticated search features that no other software has! Generate sophisticated page scores for all pages to get the &quot;REAL&quot; sense of the true page value! Extract 1000&#039;s of posts from ANY fanpage in just seconds! Sort by shares, comments, likes, or any other data metric to uncover the content with the best engagement! Preview the top posts in a beautiful post layout preview window! Extract thousands of comments from ANY fanpage post in just seconds! Reveal powerful information using the cutting-edge &quot;Word Analyzer&quot; tool to instantly uncover all the most common word-combinations across thousands of user comments or page posts! Uncover product ideas that are hiding inside your competitors user comments! Use built-in blazing fast filters and custom filters to get the data you really need!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/245289125?app_id=122963" width="425" height="239" frameborder="0" title="Social Page Analyzer - Facebook Fanpage Research Software" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Search thousands of fanpages by keyword or paste in as many facebook page you links want to analyze<br></li><li> Check fanpage names for Facebook ad interest keywords for your ad campaigns<br></li><li> Generate VERY detailed page score reports for optimizing your fanpages for high natural organic traffic!<br></li><li> Get 27 different data metrics for every fanpage<br></li><li> Extract emails &amp; websites for fanpages! Contact page owners to build valuable marketing relationships to skyrocket your Facebook marketing success!<br></li><li> Works on both Mac and PC computers<br></li><li> Get 1000's of fanpages using sophisticated search features that no other software has!<br></li><li> Generate sophisticated page scores for all pages to get the "REAL" sense of the true page value!<br></li><li> Extract 1000's of posts from ANY fanpage in just seconds! Sort by shares, comments, likes, or any other data metric to uncover the content with the best engagement!<br></li><li> Preview the top posts in a beautiful post layout preview window!<br></li><li> Extract thousands of comments from ANY fanpage post in just seconds!<br></li><li> Reveal powerful information using the cutting-edge "Word Analyzer" tool to instantly uncover all the most common word-combinations across thousands of user comments or page posts!<br></li><li> Uncover product ideas that are hiding inside your competitors user comments!<br></li><li> Use built-in blazing fast filters and custom filters to get the data you really need!<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Social Page Analyzer 1.0.12"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Instabot PW 1.0.62 Pro</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1177-instabot-pw.html</link>
<description>Name : Instabot PW Version : 1.0.62 Pro OS : Windows Type : Instagram Marketing Bot Price : $45 Homepage : SalePage Use our instagram bot to get your target audience! Instabot.pw will promote your profile, your product or service 24 hours a day. You only need to specify the desirable settings. Follows, likes, comments - dozens of settings according to different criteria.</description>
<category>Instagram Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2018 13:31:27 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features unlimit likes per hour unlimit follow per hour unlimit unfollow per hour unlimit comments per hour proxy support multiply accounts</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/110780293?app_id=122963" width="425" height="239" frameborder="0" title="Carbongram Bot short overview - The best Instagram bot ever made" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> unlimit likes per hour<br></li><li> unlimit follow per hour<br></li><li> unlimit unfollow per hour<br></li><li> unlimit comments per hour<br></li><li> proxy support<br></li><li> multiply accounts<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Instabot PW 1.0.62 Pro"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Socinator 1.2</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3634-socinator.html</link>
<description>Name : Socinator Version : 1.2 OS : Windows Type : Instagram, Facebook, Twitter, Quora, LinkedIn, YouTube, Pinterest, Google+, Reddit, Tumblr Automation Price : $145 Homepage : SalePage Easy Automation For Busy Marketers - Manage and Grow All Your Social Accounts - dfccd d y and Organically Socinator gives you more control over your social accounts and helps you publish regular content over social media. It helps you drive greater level of ENGAGEMENT, reply in REAL TIME and mainly with content in response to specific actions. It makes EASIER to communicate with the audience and make the brand more relatable. Nevertheless, its a terrific Time saver driving more TRAFFIC to your site. Socinator lets you auto publish and schedule your posts on multiple.comworks at once, including Instagram, Twitter, Facebook, Google+, LinkedIn etc. Its also having an ability of content curation by importing content via RSS feeds, monitoring folder etc. making it the smart auto post scheduler.</description>
<category>Social Media</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 13:28:45 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Instagram Automation Features Grow your Instagram accounts 10x faster: Auto Follow, Follow Back, Auto Like, Auto Comment, Auto Repost, Auto Messages, Live Chat and Many More Facebook Automation Features Increase Engagement and Precised Audience Reach: Auto Friend Requests, Auto Accept Friends, Auto Like, Auto Comment, Auto Join Groups, Auto Unjoin, Live Chat and Many More Twitter Automation Features Boost your activities on Twitter for better engagement and ROI Auto Follow, Follow Back, Auto Like, Auto Comment, Auto Retweet, Auto Messages, Live Chat and Many More YouTube Automation Features Schedule your YouTube accounts on Auto-pilot, and watch them growing. Auto Follow, Auto Subscribe, Auto Unfollow, , Auto Like, Auto Comment and Many More Quora Automation Features Everything you need to succeed on Quora: Auto Friend Requests, Auto Downvote Answers, Auto Upvote Answers, Auto Report User, Auto Upvote Questions, Find And Extract Answers, Find And Extract Users and Many More gPlus Automation Features Be 24/7 Engaged with your Audience on gPlus. Auto Follow, Auto Post/Share Content In Your Communities, Auto Unfollow, Auto Unfollow, Join/Unjoin Communities In Your Niche and Many More Pinterest Automation Features Give boost to your Pinterest account for faster growth and 20x more revenue. Auto Follow, Auto Follow Back, Auto Try, Auto Comment, Auto Repin, Auto Create Boards, Auto Unfollow and Many More LinkedIn Automation Features Make your Professional Network more bigger and connect with potential partners and customers on the go. Auto Accept/Cancel Connection Requests, Auto Endorse Connections, Auto Engage with Likes and Comments, Auto Post/Share Content In Your Groups, Auto Reply to new messages, Find And Extract Answers, Find And Extract Users and Many More Reddit Automation Features Boost your activities on Twitter for better engagement and ROI Auto Follow, Follow Back, Auto Like, Auto Comment, Auto Retweet, Auto Messages, Live Chat and Many More Tumblr Automation Features Schedule your YouTube accounts on Auto-pilot, and watch them growing. Auto Follow, Auto Subscribe, Auto Unfollow, , Auto Like, Auto Comment and Many More Auto publish posts from RSS, Auto shorten URLs, Auto Submit captcha verification, Detailed report for each and every activity, Embedded browser for each.comwork, Analytics and Growth Metrics. ScreenShot</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Z-qsfVy-HYQ?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Instagram Automation Features Grow your Instagram accounts 10x faster: Auto Follow, Follow Back, Auto Like, Auto Comment, Auto Repost, Auto Messages, Live Chat and Many More<br></li><li> Facebook Automation Features Increase Engagement and Precised Audience Reach: Auto Friend Requests, Auto Accept Friends, Auto Like, Auto Comment, Auto Join Groups, Auto Unjoin, Live Chat and Many More <br></li><li> Twitter Automation Features Boost your activities on Twitter for better engagement and ROI  Auto Follow, Follow Back, Auto Like, Auto Comment, Auto Retweet, Auto Messages, Live Chat and Many More<br></li><li> YouTube Automation Features  Schedule your YouTube accounts on Auto-pilot, and watch them growing.  Auto Follow, Auto Subscribe, Auto Unfollow, , Auto Like, Auto Comment and Many More <br></li><li> Quora Automation Features  Everything you need to succeed on Quora:  Auto Friend Requests, Auto Downvote Answers, Auto Upvote Answers, Auto Report User, Auto Upvote Questions, Find And Extract Answers, Find And Extract Users and Many More <br></li><li> gPlus Automation Features  Be 24/7 Engaged with your Audience on gPlus.  Auto Follow, Auto Post/Share Content In Your Communities, Auto Unfollow, Auto Unfollow, Join/Unjoin Communities In Your Niche and Many More <br></li><li> Pinterest Automation Features  Give boost to your Pinterest account for faster growth and 20x more revenue.  Auto Follow, Auto Follow Back, Auto Try, Auto Comment, Auto Repin, Auto Create Boards, Auto Unfollow and Many More <br></li><li> LinkedIn Automation Features  Make your Professional Network more bigger and connect with potential partners and customers on the go.  Auto Accept/Cancel Connection Requests, Auto Endorse Connections, Auto Engage with Likes and Comments, Auto Post/Share Content In Your Groups, Auto Reply to new messages, Find And Extract Answers, Find And Extract Users and Many More <br></li><li> Reddit Automation Features  Boost your activities on Twitter for better engagement and ROI  Auto Follow, Follow Back, Auto Like, Auto Comment, Auto Retweet, Auto Messages, Live Chat and Many More <br></li><li> Tumblr Automation Features  Schedule your YouTube accounts on Auto-pilot, and watch them growing.  Auto Follow, Auto Subscribe, Auto Unfollow, , Auto Like, Auto Comment and Many More <br></li><li> Auto publish posts from RSS, Auto shorten URLs, Auto Submit captcha verification, Detailed report for each and every activity, Embedded browser for each.comwork, Analytics and Growth Metrics.<br><br></li></ul><br><h3>ScreenShot</h3><br><img src="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/nV7xWSbxcSvn_Cyf-DKt5ApOtvhp0IjnmGBbdNUlr-1NXWpZoYe4J0eL4HiR6ldXC-CnhATVSTnU96VIUM3GU1YcEXnApecojKfnUDIkMR_8RzGJVckiL5CvUNz9BTZDs5n0_vpA" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Socinator 1.2"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>TumblingJazz 1.912</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/947-tumblingjazz.html</link>
<description>Name : TumblingJazz Version : 1.912 OS : Windows Type : Social Marketing, Tumblr Marketing Price : $77 Homepage : SalePage Tumbling Jazz - The Ultimate Tumblr Bot Tumblr is one of the most popular social media blogging websites around at the moment. Millions of users with millions of blogs use the site EVERY DAY. With the use of TumblingJazz, the world&#039;s leading Tumblr automation bot, you can harness this power for your own needs. The TumblingJazz tumblr bot can fully automate all actions and interactions of the Tumblr.com site, hands free!. Harness The Huge Amount Of Users And Traffic On Tumblr Using TumblingJazz it is a walk in the park to generate tonnes of traffic to your Tumblr blog and then onto your money sites. Due to the multi capacity, multi-threaded, raw socket implementation you can really let the bot rip, doing what it does best. All hands free. Set it up, schedule it, repeat it. Site back and watch the traffic FLOOD in. Be The Master Of Puppets (Pulling Strings) Everything you can do on the Tumblr website has been automated. This means you have full control over your accounts. Let the bots run on repeat and your accounts will grow rapidly destroying all before them, but most importantly they will grow naturally and organically. The TumblingJazz automation bot gives you the full command at your fingertips, nothing is restricted, we are here to help your realise your Tumblr domination dreams.</description>
<category>Tumblr Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 13:08:51 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Automatic Following Automatic Liking Automatic Reblogging Automatic Reblogging Articles Automatic Reblogging Images Automatic Reblogging Quotes Automatic Reblogging Converstations Automatic Reblogging Links Automatic Posting Articles Post Articles from RSS feed automatically - fully customisable to work with ANY RSS feed Automatic Posting Images with watermark options Post Images from RSS feed automatically - fully customisable to work with ANY RSS feed Post Images as a photoshoot, up to 10 images per post Automatic Posting YouTube Videos Post Videos from RSS feed automatically - fully customisable to work with ANY RSS feed Pinterest Image Scraper Tumblr Blog Image Scraper Tumblr Tagged Search Image scraper FULL Tumblr search functionality, tags / blogs / recent / popular Tumblr search filters (audio / links / text / video etc) Full Secondary blog support Watch folder automatic image uploader - Automatically upload images that are put into a specific folder Syndicate posted content to Wordpress and Blogger - Before posting your content to Tumblr, post it to any wordpress / blogger blog then insert the syndicated link to your Tumblr post! Account creation and automatic email verification Manage an unlimited amount of accounts, unlike other softwares we do not charge you a monthly fee nor limit the amount of accounts you can use. Account Verification Update account names / titles / description / avatar / theme easily Fully socket implemented. No webbrowser / WYSIWYG bot here. TumblingJazz is a lean, mean fighting machine *Create accounts uses a browser rendered to memory for high success rate Get your accounts / content trending by utilizing our MASS features, Mass Like, Mass Reblog, Mass Follow. Better yet, how about MASS INCEST TRENDING. Use your accounts to create a social web of likes / reblogs / follows. Proxy scraper Proxy verification Auto content spinning control Content creation tool with custom synonum files for ease of content creation Full Spintax support Supports Tokens in content posting Control all aspects of the application via Settings Schedule all actions for Drip Feeding potential. Time delay between actions when posting Repeat all actions for constant blog updates Post all content immediately or to your Tumblr queue Run SEO improvements to your blog theme with one click Frequent updates High quality support via multiple systems Full Captcha API support All processes are stored so can be restarted in case of power failure Detailed logs of all processes Import/Export features for profiles, proxies. It is your data to take and do what you want with Redo / retry / pause / cancel any action</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/B9G_F6-8Br0?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><br><ul><li> Automatic Following<br></li><li> Automatic Liking<br></li><li> Automatic Reblogging<br></li><li> Automatic Reblogging Articles<br></li><li> Automatic Reblogging Images<br></li><li> Automatic Reblogging Quotes<br></li><li> Automatic Reblogging Converstations<br></li><li> Automatic Reblogging Links<br></li><li> Automatic Posting Articles<br></li><li> Post Articles from RSS feed automatically - fully customisable to work with ANY RSS feed<br></li><li> Automatic Posting Images with watermark options<br></li><li> Post Images from RSS feed automatically - fully customisable to work with ANY RSS feed<br></li><li> Post Images as a photoshoot, up to 10 images per post<br></li><li> Automatic Posting YouTube Videos<br></li><li> Post Videos from RSS feed automatically - fully customisable to work with ANY RSS feed<br></li><li> Pinterest Image Scraper<br></li><li> Tumblr Blog Image Scraper<br></li><li> Tumblr Tagged Search Image scraper<br></li><li> FULL Tumblr search functionality, tags / blogs / recent / popular<br></li><li> Tumblr search filters (audio / links / text / video etc)<br></li><li> Full Secondary blog support<br></li><li> Watch folder automatic image uploader - Automatically upload images that are put into a specific folder<br></li><li> Syndicate posted content to Wordpress and Blogger - Before posting your content to Tumblr, post it to any wordpress / blogger blog then insert the syndicated link to your Tumblr post!<br></li><li> Account creation and automatic email verification<br></li><li> Manage an unlimited amount of accounts, unlike other softwares we do not charge you a monthly fee nor limit the amount of accounts you can use.<br></li><li> Account Verification<br></li><li> Update account names / titles / description / avatar / theme easily<br></li><li> Fully socket implemented. No webbrowser / WYSIWYG bot here. TumblingJazz is a lean, mean fighting machine *Create accounts uses a browser rendered to memory for high success rate<br></li><li> Get your accounts / content trending by utilizing our MASS features, Mass Like, Mass Reblog, Mass Follow. Better yet, how about MASS INCEST TRENDING. Use your accounts to create a social web of likes / reblogs / follows.<br></li><li> Proxy scraper<br></li><li> Proxy verification<br></li><li> Auto content spinning control<br></li><li> Content creation tool with custom synonum files for ease of content creation<br></li><li> Full Spintax support<br></li><li> Supports Tokens in content posting<br></li><li> Control all aspects of the application via Settings<br></li><li> Schedule all actions for Drip Feeding potential.<br></li><li> Time delay between actions when posting<br></li><li> Repeat all actions for constant blog updates<br></li><li> Post all content immediately or to your Tumblr queue<br></li><li> Run SEO improvements to your blog theme with one click<br></li><li> Frequent updates<br></li><li> High quality support via multiple systems<br></li><li> Full Captcha API support<br></li><li> All processes are stored so can be restarted in case of power failure<br></li><li> Detailed logs of all processes<br></li><li> Import/Export features for profiles, proxies. It is your data to take and do what you want with<br></li><li> Redo / retry / pause / cancel any action<br><br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="TumblingJazz 1.912"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>GPlusDominator 2.0.11</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/885-gplusdominator.html</link>
<description>Name :GPlus Dominator Agency Version : 2.0.11 OS : Windows Type : Google Plus Marketing Price : $499 Homepage : SalePage GPlusDominator offers you features to simplify any task on Google+. From managing circles and connections to posting content, from tracking a post&#039;s performance to comparing with others; from knowing your follower growth to tracking the activity of popular users GPlusDominator is your one-stop solution to trust. No doubt Google+ has emerged as a relatively new social.comworking player. It has, however, evolved continually to offer business communities an amazing platform with unique features and important SEO capabilities that no marketer can afford to overlook. A research shows that if your business has 100 followers with active engagement, your Google search engine results position can improve by at least 14 spots. With instant Indexing, SEO and an array of amazing services from videos, maps, books, analytics etc. to hangouts and apps unlike Facebook, Twitter or any other social.comworking site, Google+ can make or break a brand&#039;s presence online along with impacting traffic, leads and sales incredibly. But as both bouquet and range of Google+ services continue to grow by the day, both individuals and brands are looking for comprehensive yet easy tools to make the most of their digital marketing move on Google+.</description>
<category>GPlus Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 13:06:18 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Account Like Increaser Text Community People Photos Pages Circles Profile</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/YdmOj73BDVs?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Account<br></li><li> Like Increaser<br></li><li> Text<br></li><li> Community<br></li><li> People<br></li><li> Photos<br></li><li> Pages<br></li><li> Circles<br></li><li> Profile<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="GPlusDominator 2.0.11"><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Autland Suite 8.9</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1541-autland-suite.html</link>
<description>Name : Autland Suite Version : 8.9 OS : Windows Type : 12 in 1 Marketing Tools Price : $1999 Homepage : SalePage The Easiest way to marketing Online with + SMS Online, Whats, Email, Olx, Skype, SEO, Facebook, Wifi with Check-In on Facebook and Extractors</description>
<category>Social Media</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 13:04:03 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Facebook Tools Facebook Data Miner : Search Emails and Phones from within Facebook Facebook Multi Messenger : Bulk Messaging using Facebook Messenger Facebook Hunter Posts : Extract Emails and Phones from Posts Facebook Post Groups : Group Mass Posts Facebook Extractor : Extractor User IDs with multiple customizations (ID only) Facebook Add Users : Add bulk users as Friends to your profile Facebook Add Groups : Participate in Groups in Mass, choosing by keyword Facebook Add Members : Add friends in Mass to your Group or who you Manage Facebook Auto Reply : Respond to bulk comments on posts Facebook Tanned Puller : Extracts all users who enjoyed any post Facebook Post Profiles : Mass Posting in Friends Profiles Facebook Auto Post : Sharing Page Posts Facebook Post Coments : Comment on posts in Mass Facebook Management Profile : Enjoy, Comment, and Share Timeline posts WhatsApp Tools Whatsapp Sender : Send individual bulk message Whatsapp Groups Sender : Send individual message using groups Whatsapp Lists Separator : Separate your lists by dividing the ones you have and the ones you do not have Whatsapp SMS Tools SMS ONLINE SUBMISSIONS WITHOUT MODEM : Send individual message NO LIMITS USING LIVE CHIP SIMPLE MULTI OPERATOR SMS : Sends SMS in Mass separating the 4 main operators SIMPLE SMS WITH TWO MODENS : Sending Turbo SMS Mass using 2 Modens Instagram Tools Instagram Followers : Follows and Discontinues users (includes extractor) Instagram Messenger : Mass message sending to users Instagram Tanned : Enjoy user posts in bulk OLX Tools Mass OLX Chat : Submit your bulk marketing on OLX chat OLX Unlocking Cell Phones : Do your search and remove the bulk ads phones Linkedin Tools LinkedIn Message Boards : Submit your bulk marketing using Linkedin messages Email Tools Mass Email With MS Outlook : Your email in the inbox with Powerful Microsoft Outlook Mass Email With Free Email : Send thousands of emails in your inbox using free accounts Skype Tools Mass Skype Message : Send bulk messages in Skype Chat Skype Add Contacts by Keyword : Add bulk contacts using keywords Youtube Tools Mass YouTube Comments : Mass comment on multiple channels, or all channel videos YouTube Search emails from Channels : Search email from search channels by keyword YouTube Increase Subscribers : Create multiple channels, and use ones to subscribe to others Twitter Tools Mass Twitters Message : Bulk Dash for hashtags on countless Twitters Wifi Tools Wifi with Check-in on Facebook : Check-In + Posting Sharing at check-in time Wifi with data of who accesses : Put your Wifi, and have the data of who accesses your inte.com SEO Tools UNLIMITED GMAPS Submit : Make your signup in bulk on Google Maps TSR LINK GENERATOR : Increase your referral links and appear at the top of Google</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/uUSy-Vf-4dU?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><b>Facebook Tools</b><br><ul><li> Facebook Data Miner : Search Emails and Phones from within Facebook<br></li><li> Facebook Multi Messenger : Bulk Messaging using Facebook Messenger<br></li><li> Facebook Hunter Posts : Extract Emails and Phones from Posts<br></li><li> Facebook Post Groups : Group Mass Posts<br></li><li> Facebook Extractor : Extractor User IDs with multiple customizations (ID only)<br></li><li> Facebook Add Users : Add bulk users as Friends to your profile<br></li><li> Facebook Add Groups : Participate in Groups in Mass, choosing by keyword<br></li><li> Facebook Add Members : Add friends in Mass to your Group or who you Manage	<br></li><li> Facebook Auto Reply : Respond to bulk comments on posts<br></li><li> Facebook Tanned Puller : Extracts all users who enjoyed any post<br></li><li> Facebook Post Profiles : Mass Posting in Friends Profiles<br></li><li> Facebook Auto Post : Sharing Page Posts<br></li><li> Facebook Post Coments : Comment on posts in Mass<br></li><li> Facebook Management Profile : Enjoy, Comment, and Share Timeline posts<br></li></ul><br><b>WhatsApp Tools</b><br><ul><li> Whatsapp Sender : Send individual bulk message<br></li><li> Whatsapp Groups Sender : Send individual message using groups<br></li><li> Whatsapp Lists Separator : Separate your lists by dividing the ones you have and the ones you do not have Whatsapp<br></li></ul><br><b>SMS Tools</b><br><ul><li> SMS ONLINE SUBMISSIONS WITHOUT MODEM : Send individual message NO LIMITS USING LIVE CHIP<br></li><li> SIMPLE MULTI OPERATOR SMS : Sends SMS in Mass separating the 4 main operators<br></li><li> SIMPLE SMS  WITH TWO MODENS : Sending Turbo SMS Mass using 2 Modens<br></li></ul><br><b>Instagram Tools</b><br><ul><li> Instagram Followers : Follows and Discontinues users (includes extractor)<br></li><li> Instagram Messenger : Mass message sending to users<br></li><li> Instagram Tanned : Enjoy user posts in bulk<br></li></ul><br><b>OLX Tools</b><br><ul><li> Mass OLX Chat : Submit your bulk marketing on OLX chat<br></li><li> OLX  Unlocking Cell Phones : Do your search and remove the bulk ads phones<br></li></ul><br><b>Linkedin Tools</b><br><ul><li> LinkedIn Message Boards : Submit your bulk marketing using Linkedin messages<br></li></ul><br><b>Email Tools</b><br><ul><li> Mass Email With MS Outlook : Your email in the inbox with Powerful Microsoft Outlook<br></li><li> Mass Email With Free Email : Send thousands of emails in your inbox using free accounts<br></li></ul><br><b>Skype Tools</b><br><ul><li> Mass Skype Message : Send bulk messages in Skype Chat <br></li><li> Skype Add Contacts by Keyword : Add bulk contacts using keywords<br></li></ul><br><b>Youtube Tools</b><br><ul><li> Mass YouTube Comments : Mass comment on multiple channels, or all channel videos<br></li><li> YouTube Search emails from Channels : Search email from search channels by keyword<br></li><li> YouTube Increase Subscribers : Create multiple channels, and use ones to subscribe to others<br></li></ul><br><b>Twitter Tools</b><br><ul><li> Mass Twitters Message : Bulk Dash for hashtags on countless Twitters<br></li></ul><br><b>Wifi Tools</b><br><ul><li> Wifi with Check-in on Facebook : Check-In + Posting Sharing at check-in time<br></li><li> Wifi with data of who accesses : Put your Wifi, and have the data of who accesses your inte.com<br></li></ul><br><b>SEO Tools</b><br><ul><li> UNLIMITED GMAPS Submit : Make your signup in bulk on Google Maps<br></li><li> TSR LINK GENERATOR : Increase your referral links and appear at the top of Google<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Autland Suite 8.9"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Instadub 3.412</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1025-insta-dub.html</link>
<description>Name : Instadub - ISG Bot Version : 3.412 OS : Windows Type : Instagram Marketing Bot Price : $67 Homepage : SalePage The Ultimate Instagram Automation bot. Increase your followers, auto follow, auto like, auto comment and more! Increase your followers and profile popularity using Instadub...</description>
<category>Instagram Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 12:58:05 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Search And Follow Users / Unfollow : Search for users, community members, community contributors, authors of posts returned by search and follow them automatically. Following users is a great way to get followers as most users will follow you back. But better than this is getting users to follow you back who are interested in the same niche as yourself, so the Instagram bot from rootjazz allows you to find users to follow by searching keywords / hashtags and numerous scrape functionality Search And Post Comments : Search for images and add comments automatically. Posting messages to a post is a great way to engage the user and to get them to check your profile / pages Search And Like Images : Search for images, process all images for a user, search by hashtag, geolocation, images of followers, images of users who liked or commented and more. Instagram bot allows you to find images to Like by searching keywords / hashtags with the option to use advanced filters so you can find targeted images to like. Liking an images adds your profile URL to the post and is another way for users browsing Instagram to stumble across your profile Full Accounts Support : Run an unlimited number of accounts in instadub. No limits or hidden charges for extra accounts! Instagram Scraper : Scrape lists of images / users to file Import / Export : All your data belongs to you. You can import / export everything for your promotions Database Storage : Instadub stores your data in a database structure. If you want to shut down the application, it can restart all processes currently queued up for processing. All processes can be redone, retried if failed, paused or cancelled. Captcha API Support : Death by Captcha, By Pass Captcha, Human Coder, Decaptcher</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/125337741?app_id=122963" width="425" height="270" frameborder="0" title="instagram like bot instadub" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Search And Follow Users / Unfollow : Search for users, community members, community contributors, authors of posts returned by search and follow them automatically. Following users is a great way to get followers as most users will follow you back. But better than this is getting users to follow you back who are interested in the same niche as yourself, so the Instagram bot from rootjazz allows you to find users to follow by searching keywords / hashtags and numerous scrape functionality<br></li><li> Search And Post Comments : Search for images and add comments automatically. Posting messages to a post is a great way to engage the user and to get them to check your profile / pages<br></li><li> Search And Like Images : Search for images, process all images for a user, search by hashtag, geolocation, images of followers, images of users who liked or commented and more. Instagram bot allows you to find images to Like by searching keywords / hashtags with the option to use advanced filters so you can find targeted images to like. Liking an images adds your profile URL to the post and is another way for users browsing Instagram to stumble across your profile<br></li><li> Full Accounts Support : Run an unlimited number of accounts in instadub. No limits or hidden charges for extra accounts!<br></li><li> Instagram Scraper : Scrape lists of images / users to file<br></li><li> Import / Export : All your data belongs to you. You can import / export everything for your promotions<br></li><li> Database Storage : Instadub stores your data in a database structure. If you want to shut down the application, it can restart all processes currently queued up for processing. All processes can be redone, retried if failed, paused or cancelled.<br></li><li> Captcha API Support : Death by Captcha, By Pass Captcha, Human Coder, Decaptcher<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Instadub 3.412"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Twitterdub 1.435</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1223-twitterdub.html</link>
<description>Name : Twitterdub by RootJazz Version : 1.435 OS : Windows Type : Twitter Marketing Bot Price : $77 Homepage : SalePage Twitterdub - The Ultimate in Twitter Automation The Ultimate Twitter Automation bot. Increase your followers, auto follow, auto like, auto comment and more! Increase your followers and profile popularity using Twitterdub...</description>
<category>Twitter Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 12:55:26 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Easy to use Promo module, click click jobs done Automatic Following Automatic unfollowing Automatic Liking Automatic Commenting Post Tweets / videos / audio / images RSS Post Tweets / videos / audio / images Schedule Tweets / videos / audio / images Instantly react to new followers / tweets / mentions Full account support, multi account support Full account support, update account details Full search support Build custom searches Advanced compound searches Action via search via media or authors Filter support of media / user properties Twitter List Scraper Email List Scraper Scrape profile details include location, language, ids, profile and more Manage an unlimited amount of accounts. Account Verification Account safeguards for safe usage Daily stats Full Spintax support Schedule all actions for Drip Feeding potential. Time delay between actions to appear realistic Multi actions at once to appear realistic Repeat all actions for constant promotions hands free! Frequent updates Good quality support via multiple systems Full Captcha API support All processes are stored so can be restarted in case of power failure Save / load actions for future use Detailed logs of all processes Import / Export features for profiles, proxies. It is your data to take and do what you want with Redo / retry / pause / cancel any action Money back Guarantee</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/TL80pg6IB0o?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Easy to use Promo module, click click jobs done<br></li><li> Automatic Following<br></li><li> Automatic unfollowing<br></li><li> Automatic Liking<br></li><li> Automatic Commenting<br></li><li> Post Tweets / videos / audio / images<br></li><li> RSS Post Tweets / videos / audio / images<br></li><li> Schedule Tweets / videos / audio / images<br></li><li> Instantly react to new followers / tweets / mentions<br></li><li> Full account support, multi account support<br></li><li> Full account support, update account details<br></li><li> Full search support<br></li><li> Build custom searches<br></li><li> Advanced compound searches<br></li><li> Action via search via media or authors<br></li><li> Filter support of media / user properties<br></li><li> Twitter List Scraper<br></li><li> Email List Scraper<br></li><li> Scrape profile details include location, language, ids, profile and more<br></li><li> Manage an unlimited amount of accounts.<br></li><li> Account Verification<br></li><li> Account safeguards for safe usage<br></li><li> Daily stats<br></li><li> Full Spintax support<br></li><li> Schedule all actions for Drip Feeding potential.<br></li><li> Time delay between actions to appear realistic<br></li><li> Multi actions at once to appear realistic<br></li><li> Repeat all actions for constant promotions hands free!<br></li><li> Frequent updates<br></li><li> Good quality support via multiple systems<br></li><li> Full Captcha API support<br></li><li> All processes are stored so can be restarted in case of power failure<br></li><li> Save / load actions for future use<br></li><li> Detailed logs of all processes<br></li><li> Import / Export features for profiles, proxies. It is your data to take and do what you want with<br></li><li> Redo / retry / pause / cancel any action<br></li><li> Money back Guarantee<br><br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Twitterdub 1.435"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>