<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PPC keyword Tools - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>PPC keyword Tools - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>Keyword Feast 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3727-keyword-feast.html</link>
<description>Name : Keyword Feast (Google Keyword Finder) Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Keyword suggested Scraper Price : $0 Homepage : SalePage Keyword Feast will generate near unlimited amounts of new keywords for you to tune your SEO efforts around. You&#039;ll have more long tails than you&#039;ll know what to do with, and a much greater understanding of what your website visitors are actually searching for. It will also alert you of any new trends that people are searching for in your niche by comparing different sets of suggestion results from Google. Keyword Feast uses the Google suggestion API to generate thousands of long tail keywords for your niche, some of which will have zero competition. It can even alert you of new search trends in your niche so you can be the first to dominate a search term.</description>
<category>PPC keyword Tools</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 13:59:01 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>[media=https://youtu.be/SR39F2UB8NM] Features How Keyword Feast works Keyword Feast workds by taking your seed list of keywords and pulling all the suggested autocompletion results from the Google suggest feature. You know the one where you type in &quot;funny videos of a&quot; and you&#039;ll get a list like the below appear. apes apples africans attacks And so on. You can set many features such as the suggestion depth. 1-3 resulting in all a-z or aaa-zzz being used to generate keywords from suggestions and if you really want a keyword overdose you can set keyword feast to generate keywords from the suggestions Google brings back. This is explained in the video below but it will basically get you thousands for most niches. Why should I use Keyword Feast? Sometimes when you&#039;re breaking into a niche its best to go for the long tail search queries and this tool can generate thousands of them for you. Also if you&#039;re already in the SERPs for a good keyword but you want more traffic then sprinkle some of these long tails into your content and watch your traffic shoot up! Also the trend alert feature will allow you to find brand new keywords that have JUST entered your niche, where there is literally no competition for yet :-) Known issues If you&#039;re planning on bringing back over 5000 keywords please bump up the delay between calls to Google to 1000 in the settings, so they don&#039;t block your IP address for making to many API queries to quickly.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;">[media=https://youtu.be/SR39F2UB8NM]</div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br>How Keyword Feast works<br>Keyword Feast workds by taking your seed list of keywords and pulling all the suggested autocompletion results from the Google suggest feature. You know the one where you type in "funny videos of a" and you'll get a list like the below appear.<br><br>apes<br>apples<br>africans<br>attacks<br>And so on. You can set many features such as the suggestion depth. 1-3 resulting in all a-z or aaa-zzz being used to generate keywords from suggestions and if you really want a keyword overdose you can set keyword feast to generate keywords from the suggestions Google brings back. This is explained in the video below but it will basically get you thousands for most niches.<br>Why should I use Keyword Feast?<br>Sometimes when you're breaking into a niche its best to go for the long tail search queries and this tool can generate thousands of them for you. Also if you're already in the SERPs for a good keyword but you want more traffic then sprinkle some of these long tails into your content and watch your traffic shoot up! Also the trend alert feature will allow you to find brand new keywords that have JUST entered your niche, where there is literally no competition for yet :-)<br><br>Known issues<br>If you're planning on bringing back over 5000 keywords please bump up the delay between calls to Google to 1000 in the settings, so they don't block your IP address for making to many API queries to quickly.<br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Keyword Feast 1.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Google Advertiser Search 2.1</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3921-google-advertiser-search.html</link>
<description>Name : Google Advertiser Search Version : 2.1 OS : Windows Type : PPC Tools Price : $67 Homepage : SalePage FINDING COMPETITORS &amp;amp; PROSPECTS ADWORDS CAMPAIGNS HAS NEVER BEEN EASIER! Auto Collects Google Adwords Pay Per Call, Click Campaigns From The Entire Google Network And More. That’s Not All! Learn How To Manage And Close Campaigns For Businesses In Any Market Step By Step Live.</description>
<category>PPC keyword Tools</category>
<enclosure url="https://i.imgur.com/3aQGA85.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 08:03:09 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Google Advertiser Search (Adobe Air/PC - Computers) -Compile, Export Google Advertiser Leads in many different levels. -Works on both platforms mac and pc computers. Basics Video &amp;amp; Quick Guide - Included! (Recording) -In the members area you’ll find detailed training from start to finish. 100% over the the shoulder. Pause, Play or rewind it’s completely up to you. LIVE - Step By Step Training! -ZERO Experience required! I’m going to show you exactly how you can start closing and managing google campaigns with absolutely ZERO experience.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/x2XyQkhTjhU?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Google Advertiser Search (Adobe Air/PC - Computers)<br></li><li> -Compile, Export Google Advertiser Leads in many different levels.<br></li><li> -Works on both platforms mac and pc computers.<br></li><li> Basics Video &amp; Quick Guide - Included! (Recording)<br></li><li> -In the members area you’ll find detailed training from start to finish. 100% over the the shoulder. Pause, Play or rewind it’s completely up to you.<br></li><li> LIVE - Step By Step Training!<br></li><li> -ZERO Experience required! I’m going to show you exactly how you can start closing and managing google campaigns with absolutely ZERO experience.<br></li></ul><br><img src="https://i.imgur.com/3aQGA85.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Google Advertiser Search 2.1"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>PPC Prospector 1.71</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1161-ppc-prospector.html</link>
<description>Name : PPC Prospector Version : 1.71 OS : Windows/MAC Type : PPC Tools Price : $47 Homepage : SalePage Find and collect businesses advertising with Google and instantly see which ones are spending the most money and need the most help!</description>
<category>PPC keyword Tools</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-08/1440284091_feature-prospector.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 04:20:31 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Easily search by keyword and location Adobe Air Application (Mac and PC compatible) Detects which Ad Extensions are being used Multi country support Mini-Audit Report Generation Customizable Templates Integrated with Analytic Call Tracking</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><div class="dlevideoplayer" style="width:100%;max-width:425px;">
			<ul data-theme="default" data-preload="metadata">
				<li data-title="file" data-type="m4v" data-url="http://embed.wistia.com/deliveries/72c0c84091a84dd5035a74aa72c6c7e8aa853b49/file.mp4" ></li>
			</ul>
		</div></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Easily search by keyword and location<br></li><li> Adobe Air Application (Mac and PC compatible)<br></li><li> Detects which Ad Extensions are being used<br></li><li> Multi country support<br></li><li> Mini-Audit Report Generation<br></li><li> Customizable Templates<br></li><li> Integrated with Analytic Call Tracking<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-08/1440284091_feature-prospector.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="PPC Prospector 1.71"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Ant Rapunzel 8.1.1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2145-ant-rapunzel.html</link>
<description>Name : Ant Rapunzel Version : 8.1.1.2 OS : Windows Type : PPC Keyword Tools Price : $497 Homepage : SalePage Intelligent Analytics tool for Inte.com Business owners that want to increase market awareness for their products and services. Filled with features that are not available anywhere else.</description>
<category>PPC keyword Tools</category>
<enclosure url="http://antdownloads.com/rapunzel/img/aed-combo.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2017 03:36:54 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Rapunzel is a premium Niche Analytics tool that will enable you to: Retrieve Keywords, Data &amp;amp; Metrics With One Click Find Lucrative Niches Easily Discover Sub-Niches within Niches Eliminate Hundreds of Dud Niches Access ALL the HIDDEN DATA Guarantee P1 Rankings With One Click Access the vital Search Volume data that Google is hiding from me. Exploit powerful metrics that are NOT available anywhere else. Eliminate HUNDREDS of DUD, TIME-SUCKING niches in just seconds. Spot ZERO-COMPETITION niches with just a few clicks. Dominate Lucrative Niches that the IGNORANT Inte.com Marketers ignore. Multiply Search Volume by a factor of 5X or even more. Leverage thousands of keywords that are INVISIBLE to everyone else. Validate Niches before I waste my time and money on them. [center]</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><div class="dlevideoplayer" style="width:100%;max-width:425px;"><ul data-theme="default" data-preload="metadata"><li data-title="" data-type="youtube" data-url="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MoIritCh-Ew"></li></ul></div></div><br><b>Features</b><br>Rapunzel is a premium Niche Analytics tool that will enable you to:<br><ul><li> Retrieve Keywords, Data &amp; Metrics With One Click<br></li><li> Find Lucrative Niches Easily<br></li><li> Discover Sub-Niches within Niches<br></li><li> Eliminate Hundreds of Dud Niches<br></li><li> Access ALL the HIDDEN DATA<br></li><li> Guarantee P1 Rankings With One Click<br></li></ul><br><ul><li> Access the vital Search Volume data that Google is hiding from me.<br></li><li> Exploit powerful metrics that are NOT available anywhere else.<br></li><li> Eliminate HUNDREDS of DUD, TIME-SUCKING niches in just seconds.<br></li><li> Spot ZERO-COMPETITION niches with just a few clicks.<br></li><li> Dominate Lucrative Niches that the IGNORANT Inte.com Marketers ignore.<br></li><li> Multiply Search Volume by a factor of 5X or even more.<br></li><li> Leverage thousands of keywords that are INVISIBLE to everyone else.<br></li><li> Validate Niches before I waste my time and money on them.<br></li></ul><br><br><img src="http://antdownloads.com/rapunzel/img/aed-combo.png" alt="Ant Rapunzel 8.1.1.0"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><br>[center]<br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>TrendMiner Pro 2.11.4</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2062-trendminer-pro.html</link>
<description>Name : TrendMiner Pro Version : 2.11.4 OS : Windows Type : Bot Creator Price : $27 Homepage : SalePage FIND HOT TRENDS Watch this video and you&#039;ll actually know how to discover 3 HOT TRENDS in seconds with TrendMiner Pro... TrendMiner Pro could have alerted you to the huge spike in the &quot;quinoa food trend&quot; back in 2008...</description>
<category>PPC keyword Tools</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2016 19:59:23 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features 14 Million Terabytes : Trend analysis from 3.5 Billion searches per day at Google.com Statistically Significant : Statistically significant data is based on 70% of all searches worldwide. Dig Deeper : Dig deeper than any other tool. Locate hidden trends quickly. Uncover Everything : Spot top trends in just minutes instead of weeks. Ready in 60 seconds... Hidden Trends : Imagine getting &quot;tipped off&quot; just before a market becomes hyper competitive. Boost Traffic : Get more traffic, faster, by tapping into HOT trends that are targeted and non-competitive...</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/S7Rp_ioAsbk?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> 14 Million Terabytes : Trend analysis from 3.5 Billion searches per day at Google.com <br /></li><li> Statistically Significant : Statistically significant data is based on 70% of all searches worldwide.<br /></li><li> Dig Deeper : Dig deeper than any other tool. Locate hidden trends quickly.  <br /></li><li> Uncover Everything : Spot top trends in just minutes instead of weeks. Ready in 60 seconds...  <br /></li><li> Hidden Trends : Imagine getting "tipped off" just before a market becomes hyper competitive. <br /></li><li> Boost Traffic : Get more traffic, faster, by tapping into HOT trends that are targeted and non-competitive...<br /></li></ul><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="TrendMiner Pro 2.11.4" title="TrendMiner Pro 2.11.4"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Redfly Keyword Management Tool 1.1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2050-redfly-keyword-management-tool.html</link>
<description>Name : Redfly Keyword Management Tool Version : 1.1.0 OS : Windows Type : Bot Creator Price : $0 Homepage : SalePage TheRedFly Keyword Manager Tool enables you to quickly and easily create keyword lists for Google AdWords, allowing you to batch modify and manipulate your keywords efficiently and easily. This tool reduces formatting errors and can endlessly expand your keyword lists by giving you the tools to batch add and remove terms, including misspellings. Designed to work with Google AdWords keyword matching options, however this tool can also be used to create keyword lists for other search based advertising programs.</description>
<category>PPC keyword Tools</category>
<enclosure url="https://www.redflymarketing.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/12/8.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2016 14:05:16 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Delete duplicate keywords. Delete keywords that contain a specific term, in a specific location within said keyword. Delete keywords with a certain number of words. Remove repeated spaces or repeated characters. Remove unwanted characters, such as line feed, carriage returns and tabs. Remove character sets such as punctuations or all non alpha-numeric characters. Remove terms from the start of keywords. Add words to the start or end of keywords. Search and replace terms in a keyword list. Convert to lowercase or uppercase. Create misspellings – choose from duplicate characters, swapped characters, missing characters and qwerty keyword errors. Replace words and retain original keywords using the Replace Words and Duplicate option. Assign Google AdWords keyword matching options to keywords. Highlight keywords containing specific keywords or with a certain number of words. Import and export keyword lists to text files. Export with commas separating each keyword. Who is this for? Any PPC manager who needs to batch modify keyword lists. Any Google AdWords user that wants to make better use of the keywords suggested to them by Google. Any search based advertising user that wants more control when editing or creating keyword lists. Any SEO who wants to create lists of keyword tags. Any digital marketing agency who uses programmatic tools for their Google AdWords management.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/UXGJZiXroA0?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Delete duplicate keywords.<br /></li><li> Delete keywords that contain a specific term, in a specific location within said keyword.<br /></li><li> Delete keywords with a certain number of words.<br /></li><li> Remove repeated spaces or repeated characters.<br /></li><li> Remove unwanted characters, such as line feed, carriage returns and tabs.<br /></li><li> Remove character sets such as punctuations or all non alpha-numeric characters.<br /></li><li> Remove terms from the start of keywords.<br /></li><li> Add words to the start or end of keywords.<br /></li><li> Search and replace terms in a keyword list.<br /></li><li> Convert to lowercase or uppercase.<br /></li><li> Create misspellings – choose from duplicate characters, swapped characters, missing characters and qwerty keyword errors.<br /></li><li> Replace words and retain original keywords using the Replace Words and Duplicate option.<br /></li><li> Assign Google AdWords keyword matching options to keywords.<br /></li><li> Highlight keywords containing specific keywords or with a certain number of words.<br /></li><li> Import and export keyword lists to text files.<br /></li><li> Export with commas separating each keyword.<br /></li></ul><br /><br /><b>Who is this for?</b><br /><ul><li> Any PPC manager who needs to batch modify keyword lists.<br /></li><li> Any Google AdWords user that wants to make better use of the keywords suggested to them by Google.<br /></li><li> Any search based advertising user that wants more control when editing or creating keyword lists.<br /></li><li> Any SEO who wants to create lists of keyword tags.<br /></li><li> Any digital marketing agency who uses programmatic tools for their Google AdWords management.<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="https://www.redflymarketing.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/12/8.jpg" alt="Redfly Keyword Management Tool 1.1.0" title="Redfly Keyword Management Tool 1.1.0"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Redfly Keyword Management Tool 1.1.0" title="Redfly Keyword Management Tool 1.1.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>AdvantageBot 3.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2065-advantagebot.html</link>
<description>Name : AdvantageBot Version : 3.0 OS : Windows Type : Google Ads Tool, Social Ads Tool Price : $197 Homepage : SalePage AdvantageBot is perfect tool for testing &amp; improving your salepages, ads, banners, links and more.Prime everything for maximum response. AdvantageBot contains a built-in database of over two hundred and seventy thousand profitable and unprofitable ads. It allows you to score your own text against this database for profitability.</description>
<category>PPC keyword Tools</category>
<enclosure url="http://advantagebot.com/x/wp-content/uploads/AdvantageBot-Benefits.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="http://advantagebot.com/x/wp-content/uploads/AdvantageBot-Bonus.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2016 13:20:59 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features When you use AdvantageBot to score your text you are effectively eliminating guesswork and prolonged, expensive testing. This affords you faster results and minimizes ‘bad ad’ spend. You can optimize any copy, across multiple niches, market sectors and regions quickly for yourself and/or your clients. Perfect for marketers, business owners, copywriters and ad/marketing agencies. Built-in database of hundreds of thousands of ads – We’d argue the most powerful advertising and marketing tool ever created. Instant results from Scientific Proven Methods – AdvantageBot has taken over 7 years to become fully realized and presented as it is today with tens of thousands of dollars spent in testing and data analysis.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/jNN8m7eUCFQ?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> When you use AdvantageBot to score your text you are effectively eliminating guesswork and prolonged, expensive testing.  This affords you faster results and minimizes ‘bad ad’ spend.<br /></li><li> You can optimize any copy, across multiple niches, market sectors and regions quickly for yourself and/or your clients.  Perfect for marketers, business owners, copywriters and ad/marketing agencies.<br /></li><li> Built-in database of hundreds of thousands of ads – We’d argue the most powerful advertising and marketing tool ever created.<br /></li><li> Instant results from Scientific Proven Methods – AdvantageBot has taken over 7 years to become fully realized and presented as it is today with tens of thousands of dollars spent in testing and data analysis.<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://advantagebot.com/x/wp-content/uploads/AdvantageBot-Benefits.jpg" alt="AdvantageBot 3.0" title="AdvantageBot 3.0"  /><br /><img src="http://advantagebot.com/x/wp-content/uploads/AdvantageBot-Bonus.jpg" alt="AdvantageBot 3.0" title="AdvantageBot 3.0"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="AdvantageBot 3.0" title="AdvantageBot 3.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>PPC Keyword Toolz 5.1.1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1598-ppc-keyword-toolz.html</link>
<description>Name : PPC Keyword Toolz Version : 5.1.1.0 OS : Windows Type : PPC Marketing Tools, Google Adword Tools Price : $67 Homepage : SalePage &quot;Generate Google AdWords and Bing AdCenter Campaigns with 1000s of AdGroups, Text Ads and Image Banner Ads and Dynamic Landing Pages in seconds! Your AdWords Campaigns are Razor Targeted, 100% Accurate Pay Per Click Adwords Campaigns&quot;. Most people new to PPC Adwords and Pay Per Click Advertising create their campaigns incorrectly! This Pay Per Click Management Tool Will generate razor targeted Google Adwords campaigns! SpeedPPC and Keyword RoskStar are great tools ... BUT! They are very expensive AND charge a monthly fee! Most of my customers want to create high quality Google Adwords Campaigns with 1000s of keywords, 1000s of AdGroups and Ads with 1000s of auto generated image text banner ads quickly and that&#039;s what PPC Keyword Toolz does extremely well! Don&#039;t just take my word for it read what my customers are saying below! But watch all 6 videos to see the software in action! There are many more expensive tools like SpeedPPC or AdGrenade. You&#039;ll see that PPC Keyword Toolz is all you really need for a very affordable price. Besides you get a lifetime of updates for FREE! Plus my 100% - no questions asked - money back gaurantee! It&#039;s a no brainer!</description>
<category>PPC keyword Tools</category>
<enclosure url="http://ppckeywordtoolz.com/images/header3a.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2016 16:00:08 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Keyword List Cleaner:Remove duplicate keywords, white spaces, sorting, upper case, lower case, find and replace text, prefix text, postfix text and much more. No need for Microsoft Excel! Group Keywords:Group your list of keywords into specific lists or groups by various filter options. Keyword Mixer - Keyword Content Multiplier:Create hundreds of combinations of keywords! Keyword Match Type Generator:Easily build Google &quot;match type&quot; keyword lists including negative keyword lists. The effective use match types will increase Click Through Rate (CTR) which inturn means a better Quality Score (QS), which leads to cheaper cost-per-click (CPC) and more targeted traffic. Geographical Target Keywords:The Geographical Keywords tool allows you to rapidly expand any of your keyword lists based upon geographical location. Target any Country / State / Province / City / Towns of the world and more. Plus create your own custom lists. This tool allows you to start doing what the super affiliates do everyday. Long Tail Keywords:This tool allows you to generate very large long tail keywords list of unique keyword phrases. Keyword Typos:You would be surprised how many people type in the wrong spellings for words. Super affiliates exploite this to their advantage and build huge lists of typo keywords. Now you can too! Use the Typo Generator Tool to manipulate your keyword list by generating all possible combinations of typographical errors for each word. PPC ROI Calculator:Use this Return On Investment (ROI) Calculator to estimate your potential Return On Investment of any of your campaigns. Keyword Scraper:This tool allows you to enter multiple website URLs and steal their complete keywords list in a single click! This is a very powerful way to build a huge targeted keywords list that your competitors are using on thier web sites! Watch Video : Dynamic Image Ad Banner Support Watch Video : Image Ad Banner Template Designer Watch Video 6: Dynamic Keyword Insertion Expalined (DKI) Watch Video : Professional Quality Keyword Tools to Clean, Group, Multiply, GEO Target and much more ...</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><object classid="clsid:D27CDB6E-AE6D-11cf-96B8-444553540000" codebase="http://download.macromedia.com/pub/shockwave/cabs/flash/swflash.cab#version=9,0,0,0" width="640" height="480" id="Player-626e1b2e66f67b031a540e9cc5fc901e">
							<param name="movie" value="http://www.tgmember.com/engine/classes/flashplayer/media_player_v3.swf?stageW=640&amp;stageH=480&amp;contentType=video&amp;videoUrl=http://ppckeywordtoolz.com/promo/camp2.flv&amp;videoHDUrl=&amp;showWatermark=true&amp;watermarkPosition=right&amp;watermarkMargin=0&amp;watermarkAlpha=1&amp;watermarkImageUrl=http://31.220.48.156/templates/mmo3513/dleimages/flv_watermark.png&amp;showPreviewImage=false&amp;isYouTube=false&amp;rollOverAlpha=0.5&amp;contentBgAlpha=0.8&amp;progressBarColor=0xFFFFFF&amp;defaultVolume=1&amp;fullSizeView=1&amp;showRewind=false&amp;showInfo=false&amp;showFullscreen=true&amp;showScale=true&amp;showSound=true&amp;showTime=true&amp;showCenterPlay=true&amp;autoHideNav=true&amp;autoHideNavTime=3&amp;videoLoop=false&amp;defaultBuffer=3" />
							<param name="allowFullScreen" value="true" />
							<param name="scale" value="noscale" />
							<param name="quality" value="high" />
							<param name="bgcolor" value="#000000" />
							<param name="wmode" value="opaque" />
							<embed src="http://www.tgmember.com/engine/classes/flashplayer/media_player_v3.swf?stageW=640&amp;stageH=480&amp;contentType=video&amp;videoUrl=http://ppckeywordtoolz.com/promo/camp2.flv&amp;videoHDUrl=&amp;showWatermark=true&amp;watermarkPosition=right&amp;watermarkMargin=0&amp;watermarkAlpha=1&amp;watermarkImageUrl=http://31.220.48.156/templates/mmo3513/dleimages/flv_watermark.png&amp;showPreviewImage=false&amp;isYouTube=false&amp;rollOverAlpha=0.5&amp;contentBgAlpha=0.8&amp;progressBarColor=0xFFFFFF&amp;defaultVolume=1&amp;fullSizeView=1&amp;showRewind=false&amp;showInfo=false&amp;showFullscreen=true&amp;showScale=true&amp;showSound=true&amp;showTime=true&amp;showCenterPlay=true&amp;autoHideNav=true&amp;autoHideNavTime=3&amp;videoLoop=false&amp;defaultBuffer=3" quality="high" bgcolor="#000000" wmode="opaque" allowFullScreen="true" width="640" height="480" align="middle" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" pluginspage="http://www.macromedia.com/go/getflashplayer"></embed>
							</object></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Keyword List Cleaner:Remove duplicate keywords, white spaces, sorting, upper case, lower case, find and replace text, prefix text, postfix text and much more. No need for Microsoft Excel!<br /></li><li> Group Keywords:Group your list of keywords into specific lists or groups by various filter options.<br /></li><li> Keyword Mixer - Keyword Content Multiplier:Create hundreds of combinations of keywords!<br /></li><li> Keyword Match Type Generator:Easily build Google "match type" keyword lists including negative keyword lists. The effective use match types will increase Click Through Rate (CTR) which inturn means a better Quality Score (QS), which leads to cheaper cost-per-click (CPC) and more targeted traffic.<br /></li><li> Geographical Target Keywords:The Geographical Keywords tool allows you to rapidly expand any of your keyword lists based upon geographical location. Target any Country / State / Province / City / Towns of the world and more. Plus create your own custom lists. This tool allows you to start doing what the super affiliates do everyday.<br /></li><li> Long Tail Keywords:This tool allows you to generate very large long tail keywords list of unique keyword phrases.<br /></li><li> Keyword Typos:You would be surprised how many people type in the wrong spellings for words. Super affiliates exploite this to their advantage and build huge lists of typo keywords. Now you can too! Use the Typo Generator Tool to manipulate your keyword list by generating all possible combinations of typographical errors for each word.<br /></li><li> PPC ROI Calculator:Use this Return On Investment (ROI) Calculator to estimate your potential Return On Investment of any of your campaigns.<br /></li><li> Keyword Scraper:This tool allows you to enter multiple website URLs and steal their complete keywords list in a single click! This is a very powerful way to build a huge targeted keywords list that your competitors are using on thier web sites!<br /></li></ul><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><video width="640" height="480" preload="metadata" poster="rss.xml" controls="controls">
						<source type="video/mp4" src="http://ppckeywordtoolz.com/promo/part1.mp4"></source>
						</video><br /><video width="640" height="480" preload="metadata" poster="rss.xml" controls="controls">
						<source type="video/mp4" src="http://ppckeywordtoolz.com/promo/part2.mp4"></source>
						</video><br />Watch Video : Dynamic Image Ad Banner Support<br /></div><br /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><video width="640" height="480" preload="metadata" poster="rss.xml" controls="controls">
						<source type="video/mp4" src="http://ppckeywordtoolz.com/promo/part3.mp4"></source>
						</video><br /><video width="640" height="480" preload="metadata" poster="rss.xml" controls="controls">
						<source type="video/mp4" src="http://ppckeywordtoolz.com/promo/part4.mp4"></source>
						</video><br />Watch Video : Image Ad Banner Template Designer<br /></div><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><object classid="clsid:D27CDB6E-AE6D-11cf-96B8-444553540000" codebase="http://download.macromedia.com/pub/shockwave/cabs/flash/swflash.cab#version=9,0,0,0" width="640" height="480" id="Player-2d450a682a3696ffef04823092de94e6">
							<param name="movie" value="http://www.tgmember.com/engine/classes/flashplayer/media_player_v3.swf?stageW=640&amp;stageH=480&amp;contentType=video&amp;videoUrl=http://ppckeywordtoolz.com/promo/dki.flv&amp;videoHDUrl=&amp;showWatermark=true&amp;watermarkPosition=right&amp;watermarkMargin=0&amp;watermarkAlpha=1&amp;watermarkImageUrl=http://31.220.48.156/templates/mmo3513/dleimages/flv_watermark.png&amp;showPreviewImage=false&amp;isYouTube=false&amp;rollOverAlpha=0.5&amp;contentBgAlpha=0.8&amp;progressBarColor=0xFFFFFF&amp;defaultVolume=1&amp;fullSizeView=1&amp;showRewind=false&amp;showInfo=false&amp;showFullscreen=true&amp;showScale=true&amp;showSound=true&amp;showTime=true&amp;showCenterPlay=true&amp;autoHideNav=true&amp;autoHideNavTime=3&amp;videoLoop=false&amp;defaultBuffer=3" />
							<param name="allowFullScreen" value="true" />
							<param name="scale" value="noscale" />
							<param name="quality" value="high" />
							<param name="bgcolor" value="#000000" />
							<param name="wmode" value="opaque" />
							<embed src="http://www.tgmember.com/engine/classes/flashplayer/media_player_v3.swf?stageW=640&amp;stageH=480&amp;contentType=video&amp;videoUrl=http://ppckeywordtoolz.com/promo/dki.flv&amp;videoHDUrl=&amp;showWatermark=true&amp;watermarkPosition=right&amp;watermarkMargin=0&amp;watermarkAlpha=1&amp;watermarkImageUrl=http://31.220.48.156/templates/mmo3513/dleimages/flv_watermark.png&amp;showPreviewImage=false&amp;isYouTube=false&amp;rollOverAlpha=0.5&amp;contentBgAlpha=0.8&amp;progressBarColor=0xFFFFFF&amp;defaultVolume=1&amp;fullSizeView=1&amp;showRewind=false&amp;showInfo=false&amp;showFullscreen=true&amp;showScale=true&amp;showSound=true&amp;showTime=true&amp;showCenterPlay=true&amp;autoHideNav=true&amp;autoHideNavTime=3&amp;videoLoop=false&amp;defaultBuffer=3" quality="high" bgcolor="#000000" wmode="opaque" allowFullScreen="true" width="640" height="480" align="middle" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" pluginspage="http://www.macromedia.com/go/getflashplayer"></embed>
							</object><br />Watch Video 6: Dynamic Keyword Insertion Expalined (DKI)<br /></div><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><object classid="clsid:D27CDB6E-AE6D-11cf-96B8-444553540000" codebase="http://download.macromedia.com/pub/shockwave/cabs/flash/swflash.cab#version=9,0,0,0" width="640" height="480" id="Player-71582758f2560b08a9dae50f8d66c757">
							<param name="movie" value="http://www.tgmember.com/engine/classes/flashplayer/media_player_v3.swf?stageW=640&amp;stageH=480&amp;contentType=video&amp;videoUrl=http://ppckeywordtoolz.com/promo/toolz2.flv&amp;videoHDUrl=&amp;showWatermark=true&amp;watermarkPosition=right&amp;watermarkMargin=0&amp;watermarkAlpha=1&amp;watermarkImageUrl=http://31.220.48.156/templates/mmo3513/dleimages/flv_watermark.png&amp;showPreviewImage=false&amp;isYouTube=false&amp;rollOverAlpha=0.5&amp;contentBgAlpha=0.8&amp;progressBarColor=0xFFFFFF&amp;defaultVolume=1&amp;fullSizeView=1&amp;showRewind=false&amp;showInfo=false&amp;showFullscreen=true&amp;showScale=true&amp;showSound=true&amp;showTime=true&amp;showCenterPlay=true&amp;autoHideNav=true&amp;autoHideNavTime=3&amp;videoLoop=false&amp;defaultBuffer=3" />
							<param name="allowFullScreen" value="true" />
							<param name="scale" value="noscale" />
							<param name="quality" value="high" />
							<param name="bgcolor" value="#000000" />
							<param name="wmode" value="opaque" />
							<embed src="http://www.tgmember.com/engine/classes/flashplayer/media_player_v3.swf?stageW=640&amp;stageH=480&amp;contentType=video&amp;videoUrl=http://ppckeywordtoolz.com/promo/toolz2.flv&amp;videoHDUrl=&amp;showWatermark=true&amp;watermarkPosition=right&amp;watermarkMargin=0&amp;watermarkAlpha=1&amp;watermarkImageUrl=http://31.220.48.156/templates/mmo3513/dleimages/flv_watermark.png&amp;showPreviewImage=false&amp;isYouTube=false&amp;rollOverAlpha=0.5&amp;contentBgAlpha=0.8&amp;progressBarColor=0xFFFFFF&amp;defaultVolume=1&amp;fullSizeView=1&amp;showRewind=false&amp;showInfo=false&amp;showFullscreen=true&amp;showScale=true&amp;showSound=true&amp;showTime=true&amp;showCenterPlay=true&amp;autoHideNav=true&amp;autoHideNavTime=3&amp;videoLoop=false&amp;defaultBuffer=3" quality="high" bgcolor="#000000" wmode="opaque" allowFullScreen="true" width="640" height="480" align="middle" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" pluginspage="http://www.macromedia.com/go/getflashplayer"></embed>
							</object><br />Watch Video : Professional Quality Keyword Tools to Clean, Group, Multiply, GEO Target and much more ...<br /></div><br /><br /><img src="http://ppckeywordtoolz.com/images/header3a.jpg" alt="PPC Keyword Toolz 5.1.1.0" title="PPC Keyword Toolz 5.1.1.0"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="PPC Keyword Toolz 5.1.1.0" title="PPC Keyword Toolz 5.1.1.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>PPC Keyword Generator 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1214-ppc-keyword-generator.html</link>
<description>Name : PPC Keyword Generator Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Keyword Research Tools Price : $29 Homepage : SalePage PPC Keyword Generator is keyword combination generation tool created by OverZone Software. The tool allows you to swap lists of keywords from side-to-side to generate as many keyword combinations as you wish. The program can output keywords with quotes and brackets for generating phrase and exact-match types. At one point, OverZone Software was into developing SEO and paid search software. They have since switched their focus to develop a Source Code Library product. As a result, their discontinued PPC Keyword Generator tool has been floating around on free download sites since 2006.</description>
<category>PPC keyword Tools</category>
<enclosure url="http://keywordclassifier.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/05/PPC-Keyword-Generator-Beta.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 01:29:16 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Step 1: Copy the following list of keywords and paste them into the first column of PPC Keyword Generator. Step 2: Hit the “Generate Keywords” button (next to the awesome lightning bolt!). This will generate 144 keyphrases: You can then click the little blue swap arrows in between columns to transport keyword lists from side-to-side and generate more keyword combinations.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/wf4MtTJFRo4?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Step 1: Copy the following list of keywords and paste them into the first column of PPC Keyword Generator.<br /></li><li> Step 2: Hit the “Generate Keywords” button (next to the awesome lightning bolt!).  This will generate 144 keyphrases:<br /></li></ul><br />You can then click the little blue swap arrows in between columns to transport keyword lists from side-to-side and generate more keyword combinations.<br /><img src="http://keywordclassifier.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/05/PPC-Keyword-Generator-Beta.png" alt="PPC Keyword Generator 1.0" title="PPC Keyword Generator 1.0"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="PPC Keyword Generator 1.0" title="PPC Keyword Generator 1.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>