<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Link List - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Link List - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>Top High PR Classified Submission Sites List 2017</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1902-top-high-pr-classified-submission-sites-list-2016.html</link>
<description>Classified Sites are one of the best source to promote your company service or products. There are two types classified sites available, free and premium. If you are an affiliate marketer, then classified sites will definitely help you to sales more affiliate product and get more commission. Some classified sites also provides backlinks, so this is also great source to build quality backlinks also. You will find lot of Free Classified Submission Sites List when you search on Google or Bing. But most of the list are not updated with current Page Rank, Domain Authority and Page Authority. So you need to find an updated list that will help you to promote your personal or business site.</description>
<category>Link List</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2016 03:15:37 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Download Now</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Top High PR Classified Submission Sites List 2017"><br><div class="quote"><br><a href="https://vip16.tgmember.com/LinkList/Classic.List.2016.xlsx"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Download Now</a><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Top High PR Guest Blogging Sites List 2017</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1901-top-high-pr-guest-blogging-sites-list-2016.html</link>
<description>Now-a-days, Guest Blogging is one of the most popular link building technique that is used by millions of bloggers and webmasters. This is also most effective to build strong community and build email list. As, different link building techniques currently not working due to Google Penguin updates, so most of the popular blogger and inte.com marketer use Guest Blogging to build high quality backlinks. With the help of guest blogging, you can also drive huge referral traffic to your blog easily and quickly. So today, I’m going to share Top 100 High PR Guest Blogging Sites List. This list will help you to find some popular blogs that accept guest post. These blogs are run and maintain by some popular blogger and inte.com marketer. Almost all blogs in this list accept guest post, just read their guest post accepting policy carefully before submit a post. In this list, you will find guest posting blog with different niche such as blogging tips, SEO and SMM, health and relationship, family and living, entertainment and celebrity gossip, sports, marketing blog and much more.</description>
<category>Link List</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2016 03:12:31 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Download Now</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Top High PR Guest Blogging Sites List 2017"><br><div class="quote"><br><a href="https://vip16.tgmember.com/LinkList/Guest.Blog.List.2016.xlsx"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Download Now</a><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Top High PR Infographic Submission Sites List 2017</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1900-top-high-pr-infographic-submission-sites-list-2016.html</link>
<description>Best free infographic submission sites List: Started creating infographics? Then you might want to submit your infographic in the high PR inforgraphic submission websites. If you have just started a blog, then this is a step you must consider to give your site some strong SEO benefits. Infographics are a great way to teach and learn any news concept easily. So usage of free infographic submission sites is increasing day by day and this surely is an advanced content marketing strategy.</description>
<category>Link List</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2016 03:07:45 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>What is infographic submission in SEO? Some may think that submitting infographics does not have much SEO value. SEO is no doubt the building block of your site. And to a large extent, it depends on building the number of inbound links that direct to your website. Sharing infographics can support that cause by earning backlinks from high authority sites. For submitting infographics to directories, you must check their terms and conditions properly. Does it provide dofollow or nofollow, whether it requires registration or only a contact email etc. Try to make a good infographic with some quality information in it. Share it in the right platforms to drive huge traffic on your website while getting backlinks from high authority sites. Infographics are viral by nature and can reach a wider audience if you submit them to the right places. So once you start creating your own infographics, consider to share them to the top infographic directories. Download Now</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[What is infographic submission in SEO?<br><br>Some may think that submitting infographics does not have much SEO value. SEO is no doubt the building block of your site. And to a large extent, it depends on building the number of inbound links that direct to your website. Sharing infographics can support that cause by earning backlinks from high authority sites.<br><br>For submitting infographics to directories, you must check their terms and conditions properly. Does it provide dofollow or nofollow, whether it requires registration or only a contact email etc. Try to make a good infographic with some quality information in it. Share it in the right platforms to drive huge traffic on your website while getting backlinks from high authority sites.<br><br>Infographics are viral by nature and can reach a wider audience if you submit them to the right places. So once you start creating your own infographics, consider to share them to the top infographic directories.<br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Top High PR Infographic Submission Sites List 2017"><br><div class="quote"><br><a href="https://vip16.tgmember.com/LinkList/InfoGraphic.Site.List.2016.xlsx"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Download Now</a><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Ping Submission Sites List 2017</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1898-ping-submission-sites-list-2016.html</link>
<description>Ping submission sites help you in faster indexing of your blog posts and reach them to the major search engines. At times you may find that few of the URLs of your blog are not getting indexed or taking too much time for that. Free ping tools or auto ping websites help you to overcome such issues. Pinging submission sites are known for indexing any blog into the major search engines or RSS directories in no time. Pinging is a process through which you can notify the Search Engines and web directories that you have updated content in your website/ blog. This helps you to increase your SEO ranking very fast and increase your traffic to a large extent.</description>
<category>Link List</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2016 03:01:37 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>What is Ping submission in SEO? Does Ping submission has any correlation with SEO? Offcourse it has. There are many benefits of using these free Ping Submission sites. Some of these are: Faster indexing of your web pages or blog post URLs. List your website in multiple search engines. Increase search engine visibility. Multiply your organic search traffic. The non-indexed web pages can be easily indexed. Ping submission is indeed very easy. You just have to provide some necessary details like your blog URL, blog title and/ or some other information and press the Ping button. Ping service sites will then automatically submit your URL to the major search engines and web directories. Download Now</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[What is Ping submission in SEO?<br><br>Does Ping submission has any correlation with SEO? Offcourse it has. There are many benefits of using these free Ping Submission sites. Some of these are:<br><br>Faster indexing of your web pages or blog post URLs.<br>List your website in multiple search engines.<br>Increase search engine visibility.<br>Multiply your organic search traffic.<br>The non-indexed web pages can be easily indexed.<br>Ping submission is indeed very easy. You just have to provide some necessary details like your blog URL, blog title and/ or some other information and press the Ping button. Ping service sites will then automatically submit your URL to the major search engines and web directories.<br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Ping Submission Sites List 2017"><br><div class="quote"><br><a href="https://vip16.tgmember.com/LinkList/Ping.SiteList.2016.xlsx"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Download Now</a><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Press Release Submission Sites List 2017</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1895-press-release-submission-sites-list-2016.html</link>
<description>Press Release Submission is one of the oldest techniques of SEO that help to get good result in Search Engine Result Pages. After latest Panda and Penguin update, most of the bloggers, webmasters and SEO’s think that, Press Release is dead and it have no effect in SEO. And most of the SEO’s don’t consider press release as SEO task. But still now, press release submission one of the best way to get good keywords rank in SREP as well as page rank. It also helps to drive huge traffic to your site/blog. You need to submit press release in proper way and in proper place. Relevancy is one of the important facts in press release submission, you need to submit press release in a proper category according to your niche. It is also important to submit in High PR and dofollow press releases sites.High PR Dofollow Press Release Submission Site List</description>
<category>Link List</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2016 02:49:32 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>What Is Press Release Site? Press Release Sites are basically platforms for news distribution, where organizations can publish their news. These press distribution services then distribute that news to Search Engines, News Blogs etc. and spread about the new startup more than the basic announcement. Top Press Release Submission sites help you to know the public about your new steps. Importance of Press Release Submission in SEO Before you start exploring the list of sites for free submission of press release, you must first know if there is any benefits of press release submission in SEO. Press Releases get crawled by almost all the major search engines and can boost the search engine rank of your site in no time. Also it is a great way of converting common queries into sales. However, you must make sure that you provide informative content including all the related keywords that your potential clients may look for. Press Release can bring huge amount of natural and referral traffic. A strongly written Press Release can build a huge buzz and establish you as an industry expert. Also make sure that it reaches to the targeted readers to attract more customers for your business. Download Now</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[What Is Press Release Site?<br><br>Press Release Sites are basically platforms for news distribution, where organizations can publish their news. These press distribution services then distribute that news to Search Engines, News Blogs etc. and spread about the new startup more than the basic announcement. Top Press Release Submission sites help you to know the public about your new steps.<br><br>Importance of Press Release Submission in SEO<br><br>Before you start exploring the list of sites for free submission of press release, you must first know if there is any benefits of press release submission in SEO. Press Releases get crawled by almost all the major search engines and can boost the search engine rank of your site in no time. Also it is a great way of converting common queries into sales.<br><br>However, you must make sure that you provide informative content including all the related keywords that your potential clients may look for. Press Release can bring huge amount of natural and referral traffic. A strongly written Press Release can build a huge buzz and establish you as an industry expert. Also make sure that it reaches to the targeted readers to attract more customers for your business.<br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Press Release Submission Sites List 2017"><br><div class="quote"><br><a href="https://vip16.tgmember.com/LinkList/Press.Release.Site.List.2016.xlsx"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Download Now</a><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Video Sharing Sites List 2017</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1894-video-sharing-sites-list-2016.html</link>
<description>Now-a-days, Video Sharing or Video Submission is one of the most helpful and latest ways to create high quality backlinks. This is another important part of today’s Search Engine Optimization process. You can also drive massive high quality and targeted traffic through video marketing. As this is really not easy for newbies but also not too hard. You need to create some high quality and helpful videos related to your blog/site niche and submit them to video sharing sites with High PR, DA, PA and Alexa Rank.</description>
<category>Link List</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2016 02:46:51 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>You may look for an effective free video sharing sites list to submit your videos, but failed to find effective one. So in this post, I’m going to share some top and best video sharing sites. Almost all video submission sites in this list come with high page rank, good Alexa rank, domain and page authority. So let’s check the list and submit your video now. Download Now</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[You may look for an effective free video sharing sites list to submit your videos, but failed to find effective one. So in this post, I’m going to share some top and best video sharing sites. Almost all video submission sites in this list come with high page rank, good Alexa rank, domain and page authority. So let’s check the list and submit your video now.<br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Video Sharing Sites List 2017"><br><div class="quote"><br><a href="https://vip16.tgmember.com/LinkList/Video.Sharing.Site.List.2017.xlsx"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Download Now</a><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Search Engine Submission Sites List 2017</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1893-search-engine-submission-sites-list-2016.html</link>
<description>Best free search engine submission sites list: Free website submission to the top search engines is one of the most important step for SEO. It is indeed very helpful for the website owners. We know that most of the inte.com users in the world use Google for indexing their web pages. But do you know that you can multiply your search traffic by submitting your website to other search engines? There are many alternatives where you can submit your web URLs to get them indexed. Also, some of these are used only in specific countries. So you can get a good amount of free organic traffic from different part of the world. Now which is the best search engine alternative to Google? There are actually many which can fetch you a decent amount of users other than Google</description>
<category>Link List</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2016 02:43:34 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>What is search engine submission in SEO? To make your website more searchable and get it found on the search engine result pages (SERPs), your website pages/ URLs must be indexed by the Search Engines. Most of the time, the search engine bots of the major search engines like Google, Yahoo and Bing crawl through your web pages and index them. But to be sure that your pages are indexed, you can submit them to those search engines. Crawling and Indexing are the most essential terms for Web search results. I am sure that, most of you know the above terms. But in case you may not, let me share the basics. Crawling: Crawling is main factor in Search Engine. Search engines use search spider or web crawler to crawl through the different webpages. They reach to every possible page on web to display them in the search results. Indexing: After crawling, search engine bots includes the web page in its database and index it according to the search queries/ keywords. Once the Search Engine index the web page, people are able to find it through searches. So, submitting a site to the high PR search engine submission list is the first step towards search engine optimization. Also some search engines are localised or area specific. For that reason, it is better to free submt your websites to the different search engines. Download Now</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[What is search engine submission in SEO?<br><br>To make your website more searchable and get it found on the search engine result pages (SERPs), your website pages/ URLs must be indexed by the Search Engines. Most of the time, the search engine bots of the major search engines like Google, Yahoo and Bing crawl through your web pages and index them. But to be sure that your pages are indexed, you can submit them to those search engines.<br><br>Crawling and Indexing are the most essential terms for Web search results. I am sure that, most of you know the above terms. But in case you may not, let me share the basics.<br><br>Crawling: Crawling is main factor in Search Engine. Search engines use search spider or web crawler to crawl through the different webpages. They reach to every possible page on web to display them in the search results.<br><br>Indexing: After crawling, search engine bots includes the web page in its database and index it according to the search queries/ keywords. Once the Search Engine index the web page, people are able to find it through searches.<br><br>So, submitting a site to the high PR search engine submission list is the first step towards search engine optimization. Also some search engines are localised or area specific. For that reason, it is better to free submt your websites to the different search engines.<br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Search Engine Submission Sites List 2017"><br><div class="quote"><br><a href="https://vip16.tgmember.com/LinkList/SES.SiteList.2016.xlsx"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Download Now</a><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>High PR Article Directory List 2017</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1892-high-pr-article-directory-list-2016.html</link>
<description>Article Directory Submission is one of the most popular ways to get huge traffic as well as high quality one way backlink to your site/blog. You need to find some most popular Article Directory Sites with high page rank, good Alexa Rank. If you find some high PR article directories with dofollow attributions, then you can build high quality backlinks to your blog/site easily and effectively. You must consider your blog/site niche when you search Article Directory sites which are most important for quality backlinks.</description>
<category>Link List</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2016 02:15:48 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Download Now</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="High PR Article Directory List 2017"><br><div class="quote"><br><a href="https://vip16.tgmember.com/LinkList/Article.Directory.List.2016.tgMember.xlsx"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Download Now</a><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>High PR Web 2.0 Sites List 2017</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1891-high-pr-web-20-sites-list-2016.html</link>
<description>200+ Most Popular High PR Web 2.0 Sites List 2016– Web 2.0 sites are commonly used to create back links and gets an advantage in SEO rankings.These High PR web 2.0 sites 2016 are the most important websites, where you can get back links and direct traffic to your valuable content.After writing the useful content in your blog, publish your article link in these web 2.0 sites and gets the benefit of back link, SEO, traffic and more important rankings on search engines. There are number of different types of web 2.0 applications including wikis, blogs, social bookmarking, social.comworking, social media, pod casting and content hosting services. Many of the most popular websites are Web 2.0 sites such as such as social media sites and applications include forums, micro blogging, social.comworking, social bookmarking, and wikis. Here&#039;s the list of most popular and the best web 2.0 sites list for SEO and link building (back links).</description>
<category>Link List</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2016 01:28:03 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Download Now</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="High PR Web 2.0 Sites List 2017"><br><div class="quote"><br><a href="https://vip16.tgmember.com/LinkList/HighPR.Web.20.List.2016.tgMember.xlsx"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Download Now</a><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>High PR Social Bookmarking Sites List 2017</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1890-high-pr-social-bookmarking-sites-list-2016.html</link>
<description>High PR social bookmarking sites like Delicious, Digg and StumbleUpon help search engines in different ways by indexing published articles in a quicker way, measuring quality of post, getting top in search engines for specific targeted keywords and categorized.There are many free social bookmarking sites are available on the web but all social bookmarking sites are not do follow. Some social bookmarking sites use the no follow attributes, do not use such kind of websites,which are really worthless.Google likes only qualify back links with do follow attributes.Getting back links from high page rank social bookmarking sites is incredibly valued by the search engines.Here&#039;s the list of the 100+ high PR social bookmarking sites list 2016 (updated).</description>
<category>Link List</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2016 01:25:34 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Download Now</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="High PR Social Bookmarking Sites List 2017"><br><div class="quote"><br><a href="https://vip16.tgmember.com/LinkList/HighPR%20SocialBookmarking.List.2016.xlsx"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Download Now</a><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>