<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Social Networking Plugins - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Social Networking Plugins - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>WP SociXplode 1.9.0.2 Enterprise</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2147-wp-socixplode.html</link>
<description>Name : WP SociXplode Enterprise Version : 1.9.0.2 OS : Linux Type : Social Network Plugin Price : $199 Homepage : Salepage WP SociXplode – A Brand New 1-Click Idiot Proof Software That Sesure 100% Real Unlimited Traffic From FB, Twitter &amp;amp; Instagram Hands Free… Best suited for JVs having MMO, WP, Traffic, Social &amp;amp; Software Lists Gets Free viral traffic from FB, Twitter &amp;amp; Instagram Hands Free 100% Newbie Friendly – Very Simple to use High conversions And Mind Blowing EPCs New system – Absolutely NO Rehashes Traffic: Red-hot topic always in demand WP SociXplode is a unique and never-revealed before system for creating a tidal wave of targeted traffic and scale your business to new heights. WPSociXplode is a set and forget 100% newbie friendly software that drives 100% REAL server crushing FREE targeted traffic to any website on complete autopilot. You can Easily make huge profits by driving unlimited supply of laser targeted traffic hands down in any niche.</description>
<category>Social Networking Plugins</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2017 03:22:27 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Promote unlimited pages or posts to get targeted traffic 100% Real traffic from FB without investing into ads Use Traffic Finder to find high potential FB groups &amp;amp; pages Instant FB preview of your posts Boost engagement &amp;amp; viewership for your FB posts in one click Generate an avalanche of FREE targeted customers in any niche Make campaign scheduling easy with our scheduler Get unlimited visitors, leads &amp;amp; sales on complete autopilot 100% automated easy to profits system Very Easy &amp;amp; Intuitive Dashboard to Manage Everything Much much more is waiting inside…You need to feel it for yourself.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/jmrWC78Hmjk?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><p><br><b>Features</b><br><ul><li> Promote unlimited pages or posts to get targeted traffic<br></li><li> 100% Real traffic from FB without investing into ads<br></li><li> Use Traffic Finder to find high potential FB groups &amp; pages<br></li><li> Instant FB preview of your posts<br></li><li> Boost engagement &amp; viewership for your FB posts in one click<br></li><li> Generate an avalanche of FREE targeted customers in any niche<br></li><li> Make campaign scheduling easy with our scheduler<br></li><li> Get unlimited visitors, leads &amp; sales on complete autopilot<br></li><li> 100% automated easy to profits system<br></li><li> Very Easy &amp; Intuitive Dashboard to Manage Everything<br></li><li> Much much more is waiting inside…You need to feel it for yourself.<br></li></ul><br><br></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="WP SociXplode 1.9.0.2 Enterprise"> <br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Social Networks Auto Poster Pro 3.8.2</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/848-snap-for-wordpress.html</link>
<description>Name : WP Social Networks Auto Poster Version : 3.8.2 - Pro Multi Account WPMU Type : Social Plugin Price : $50 Homepage : SalePage SNAP can publish nicely formatted messages to your Facebook, Twitter, Google+(Google Plus), Blogger, LiveJournal, Delicious, Diigo, Stumbleupon, LinkedIn, Pinterest, Plurk, VKontakte(VK.com), WordPress, and Tumblr accounts. You can reach the most audience and let all your friends, readers and followers about your new post automatically. Plugin works with profiles, business pages, community pages, groups, etc.</description>
<category>Social Networking Plugins</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.nextscripts.com/images/sc/0004-223-m.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://www.nextscripts.com/imgs/sc-mu-edit.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2017 12:58:27 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Scheduled and Delayed postings Auto-repost existing random posts from from specific dates or &quot;older then N days and younger then X days&quot;. Limit random or one-by-one auto-reposting for specific days of the week and times. (like Monday-Friday from 8AM to 7PM Only) Advanced Autoposting to Blogger [Limited Time Only - included for free] ($49/year value) SNAP Universal API (Run-time Only). This adds autoposting to Google+, Pinterest, LinkedIn Company Pages, Reddit, Flipboard, YouTube App.com - Autopost to your account. Blogger/Blogspot - Autopost to your Blog. HTML is supported. Delicious - Auto-submit bookmark to your account. Deviantart.com -Autopost to your blog. HTML is supported. Diigo - Auto-submit bookmark to your account. Evernote/postach.io [New] - Auto-post to your Evernote account or postach.io Blog. Facebook - Autopost to your profile, business page, community page, or Facebook group page. Ability to attach your blogpost to Facebook post. Ability to make &quot;Image&quot; posts. Flickr [New] - Autopost to your photostream and/or sets. Tags are supported. FriendFeed - Autopost to your account. Ability to attach Image to posts. Instapaper - Auto-submit bookmark to your account. Google+ (with third party API library) - Autopost to your profile or business page. Ability to attach your blogpost to Google+ post. Ability to make &quot;Image&quot; posts. LinkedIn - Autopost to your account. Ability to attach your blogpost to LinkedIn post. Autopost to LinkedIn Company pages and/or Groups (with third party API library) LiveJournal - Auto-submit your blogpost to LiveJournal. Pinterest (with third party API library) - Pin your blogpost&#039;s featured image to your Pinterest board. Reddit (with third party API library) - Post to your subreddits. Scoop.It [New] - Autopost to your &quot;Topics&quot;. Ability to attach your blogpost to scoop. Ability to make &quot;Image&quot; posts.. SETT [New] - Auto-post to your Sett.com Blog. Stumbleupon - Auto-submit bookmark to your account. Tumblr - Autopost to your account. Ability to attach your blogpost to Tumblr post. HTML is supported. Twitter - Autopost to your account. Ability to attach Image to tweets. Plurk - Autopost to your account. Ability to attach Image to messages. vBulletin - Auto-submit your blogpost to vBulletin forums. Could create new threads or new posts. vKontakte(ВКонтакте)(VK.com) - Autopost to your profile or group page. Ability to attach your blogpost to vKontaktepost. Ability to make &quot;Image&quot; posts. WordPress - Auto-submit your blogpost to another blog based on WordPress. This options includes WordPress.com, Blog.com, etc.. YouTube - (with third party API library) - Post messages to your YouTube channel feed. If blogpost has youtube reference it will be attached.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/E9grZPDaKLQ?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Scheduled and Delayed postings<br></li><li> Auto-repost existing random posts from from specific dates or "older then N days and younger then X days".<br></li><li> Limit random or one-by-one auto-reposting for specific days of the week and times. (like Monday-Friday from 8AM to 7PM Only)<br></li><li> Advanced Autoposting to Blogger<br></li><li> [Limited Time Only - included for free] (/year value) SNAP Universal API (Run-time Only). This adds autoposting to Google+, Pinterest, LinkedIn Company Pages, Reddit, Flipboard, YouTube<br></li><li> App.com - Autopost to your account.<br></li><li> Blogger/Blogspot - Autopost to your Blog. HTML is supported.<br></li><li> Delicious - Auto-submit bookmark to your account.<br></li><li> Deviantart.com -Autopost to your blog. HTML is supported.<br></li><li> Diigo - Auto-submit bookmark to your account.<br></li><li> Evernote/postach.io [New] - Auto-post to your Evernote account or postach.io Blog.<br></li><li> Facebook - Autopost to your profile, business page, community page, or Facebook group page. Ability to attach your blogpost to Facebook post. Ability to make "Image" posts.<br></li><li> Flickr [New] - Autopost to your photostream and/or sets. Tags are supported.<br></li><li> FriendFeed - Autopost to your account. Ability to attach Image to posts.<br></li><li> Instapaper - Auto-submit bookmark to your account.<br></li><li> Google+ (with third party API library) - Autopost to your profile or business page. Ability to attach your blogpost to Google+ post. Ability to make "Image" posts.<br></li><li> LinkedIn - Autopost to your account. Ability to attach your blogpost to LinkedIn post. Autopost to LinkedIn Company pages and/or Groups (with third party API library)<br></li><li> LiveJournal - Auto-submit your blogpost to LiveJournal.<br></li><li> Pinterest (with third party API library) - Pin your blogpost's featured image to your Pinterest board.<br></li><li> Reddit (with third party API library) - Post to your subreddits.<br></li><li> Scoop.It [New] - Autopost to your "Topics". Ability to attach your blogpost to scoop. Ability to make "Image" posts..<br></li><li> SETT [New] - Auto-post to your Sett.com Blog.<br></li><li> Stumbleupon - Auto-submit bookmark to your account.<br></li><li> Tumblr - Autopost to your account. Ability to attach your blogpost to Tumblr post. HTML is supported.<br></li><li> Twitter - Autopost to your account. Ability to attach Image to tweets.<br></li><li> Plurk - Autopost to your account. Ability to attach Image to messages.<br></li><li> vBulletin - Auto-submit your blogpost to vBulletin forums. Could create new threads or new posts.<br></li><li> vKontakte(ВКонтакте)(VK.com) - Autopost to your profile or group page. Ability to attach your blogpost to vKontaktepost. Ability to make "Image" posts.<br></li><li> WordPress - Auto-submit your blogpost to another blog based on WordPress. This options includes WordPress.com, Blog.com, etc..<br></li><li> YouTube - (with third party API library) - Post messages to your YouTube channel feed. If blogpost has youtube reference it will be attached.<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://www.nextscripts.com/images/sc/0004-223-m.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Social Networks Auto Poster Pro 3.8.2"><br><img src="http://www.nextscripts.com/imgs/sc-mu-edit.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>WP Social Traffic Pro 1.2.4</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3477-wp-social-traffic.html</link>
<description>Name : WP Social Traffic Pro Version : 1.2.4 Type : Facebook Fanpage Poster/Comment Plugins Price : $97 Homepage : SalePage This Brand New Wordpress Plugin That Gets 100% REAL - Unlimited Social Traffic from Facebook on Complete AUTOPILOT... A Complete Set &amp;amp; Forget Wordpress Plugin for Inte.com Marketers Every website &amp;amp; blog on this pl.com needs more traffic. What if you could just log into your wordpress site, press just ONE BUTTON and 100s &amp;amp; 1000s of visitors would start visiting your site AUTOMATICALLY. Yes - 100% REAL People - that&#039;s what WP Social Traffic does. It connects with niche communities and fanpages on facebook and shares your content with them automatically &amp;amp; engages with them to DRIVE them back to your site. This is a software that everyone with a website needs. You&#039;ll never have to pay for traffic ever again. Works in ANY Niche you want. 100% NEWBIE Friendly - Push Button software. Getting more traffic is now just ONE Click away!</description>
<category>Social Networking Plugins</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2017 19:45:40 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Front End - Features One-Click Software Gets REAL Traffic to Any WP Site! Get Targeted Traffic from Facebook - without any ads. 100% AUTOPILOT - Set &amp;amp; Forget software, just press one button &amp;amp; get real traffic. Fully Newbie Friendly - click a button &amp;amp; you get traffic. Full Control over how your posts look on Facebook - Preview &amp;amp; Customize. Get Traffic from the most popular &amp;amp; active fanpages &amp;amp; communities on Facebook. Use Custom Spintax for your posts and comments - make your posts look more natural. OTO 1 - PRO Version Features Create Unlimited Traffic Campaigns to run in parallel. Promote the same post across multiple campaigns at the same time. Get Ultra Targeted traffic to your site, posts &amp;amp; pages. Promote your content to Unlimited Pages, reach 100,000+ people at the same time. Get 10x MORE reach for your posts - 10x more traffic. Find &amp;amp; Target more niches - use upto 10 keywords to create your campaigns. Target 10x more fanpages in the PRO version. You can also add custom fanpages for driving traffic. Use Nested Spintax for comments and posts. Get a complete LOG of posts - shows all successful promotions and any errors. Live Scheduler lets you see exactly what promotions you have queued up</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/olG2IgnbpRk?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br>Front End - Features<br><ul><li> One-Click Software Gets REAL Traffic to Any WP Site!<br></li><li> Get Targeted Traffic from Facebook - without any ads.<br></li><li> 100% AUTOPILOT - Set &amp; Forget software, just press one button &amp; get real traffic.<br></li><li> Fully Newbie Friendly - click a button &amp; you get traffic.<br></li><li> Full Control over how your posts look on Facebook - Preview &amp; Customize.<br></li><li> Get Traffic from the most popular &amp; active fanpages &amp; communities on Facebook.<br></li><li> Use Custom Spintax for your posts and comments - make your posts look more natural.<br></li></ul><br>OTO 1 - PRO Version Features<br><ul><li> Create Unlimited Traffic Campaigns to run in parallel.<br></li><li> Promote the same post across multiple campaigns at the same time.<br></li><li> Get Ultra Targeted traffic to your site, posts &amp; pages.<br></li><li> Promote your content to Unlimited Pages, reach 100,000+ people at the same time.<br></li><li> Get 10x MORE reach for your posts - 10x more traffic.<br></li><li> Find &amp; Target more niches - use upto 10 keywords to create your campaigns.<br></li><li> Target 10x more fanpages in the PRO version.<br></li><li> You can also add custom fanpages for driving traffic.<br></li><li> Use Nested Spintax for comments and posts.<br></li><li> Get a complete LOG of posts - shows all successful promotions and any errors.<br></li><li> Live Scheduler lets you see exactly what promotions you have queued up<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="WP Social Traffic Pro 1.2.4"><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>WP Tweet Machine Pro 2.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1421-wp-tweet-machine.html</link>
<description>Name : WP Tweet Machine Version : Pro 2.0 OS : LInux Type : Twitter Marketing Bot Price : $27 Homepage : SalePage Starts Adding an Unlimited Number of 100% REAL, Targeted FOLLOWERS to Any Twitter Account in under 2 mins...</description>
<category>Social Networking Plugins</category>
<enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/wptweetmachine/images/wptweetmachine.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 21:29:13 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features 100% Autopilot Software Setup to go in 2 minutes Newbie Friendly - Tested Guaranteed 100% Real Twitter Followers Works for Twitter Accounts in ANY NICHE Auto Content Posting to Twitter Massive Time Saver + Beta Tester Approved</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/JOT-yppbGaw?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> 100% Autopilot Software<br /></li><li> Setup to go in 2 minutes<br /></li><li> Newbie Friendly - Tested<br /></li><li> Guaranteed 100% Real Twitter Followers<br /></li><li> Works for Twitter Accounts in ANY NICHE<br /></li><li> Auto Content Posting to Twitter<br /></li><li> Massive Time Saver + Beta Tester Approved<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="https://s3.amazonaws.com/wptweetmachine/images/wptweetmachine.png" alt="WP Tweet Machine Pro 2.0" title="WP Tweet Machine Pro 2.0"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="WP Tweet Machine Pro 2.0" title="WP Tweet Machine Pro 2.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Easy Social Share Buttons 4.1</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2085-easy-social-share-buttons-for-wordpress.html</link>
<description>Name : Easy Social Share Buttons for WordPress Version : 4.1 OS : Linux Type : Social Networking plugin Price : $19 Homepage : SalePage Easy Social Share Buttons for WordPress is the best social sharing plugin on the market, and the most complete and optimized social share buttons package. With a single plugin, the whole world of social media sharing is opened up to you: increase your shares, grow your profile, build your following and drive more traffic.</description>
<category>Social Networking Plugins</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 15:39:03 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Easy Social Share Buttons for WordPress Features 40+ popular social.comworks 21 display positions automatic buttons triggers unique visual experience no coding knowledge is required! easy mode powerful followers counter detailed analytics after share actions 12 native social buttons easy social metrics lite visual composer integrated social profiles 1 click ready made styles apply</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<br /><b>Easy Social Share Buttons for WordPress Features</b><br /><ul><li>40+ popular social.comworks<br /></li><li>21 display positions<br /></li><li>automatic buttons triggers<br /></li><li>unique visual experience<br /></li><li>no coding knowledge is required!<br /></li><li>easy mode<br /></li><li>powerful followers counter<br /></li><li>detailed analytics<br /></li><li>after share actions<br /></li><li>12 native social buttons<br /></li><li>easy social metrics lite<br /></li><li>visual composer integrated<br /></li><li>social profiles<br /></li><li>1 click ready made styles apply<br /></li></ul><br /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Easy Social Share Buttons 4.1" title="Easy Social Share Buttons 4.1"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Social Share &amp; Locker Pro 6.9</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2089-social-share-locker-pro.html</link>
<description>Name : Social Share &amp;amp; Locker Pro Wordpress Plugin Version : 6.9 OS : Linux Type : Social Networking plugin Price : $19 Homepage : SalePage Social Share&amp;amp;Locker Pro is far away the best Social sharing plugin for WordPress. Was built to cover all the necessities and to gets more Shares into your website. With a WordPress Social Locker module integrated, brings over the Social Network a bigger exposure and viral visitors.</description>
<category>Social Networking Plugins</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 13:21:15 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Social Share &amp;amp; Locker Pro WordPress Plugin Features Fast Social Buttons Loading Responsive Social Themes CSS3 Hover Effects Custom Box Position Display based on page&#039;s type 2 Social Buttons Align type (horizontal/vertical) Social Share ShortCode generator Social Locker ShortCode generator Realistic Share Counts Visual Composer integration Passion and Soul</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<br><b>Social Share &amp; Locker Pro WordPress Plugin Features</b><br><ul><li>Fast Social Buttons Loading<br></li><li>Responsive Social Themes<br></li><li>CSS3 Hover Effects<br></li><li>Custom Box Position<br></li><li>Display based on page's type<br></li><li>2 Social Buttons Align type (horizontal/vertical)<br></li><li>Social Share ShortCode generator<br></li><li>Social Locker ShortCode generator<br></li><li>Realistic Share Counts<br></li><li>Visual Composer integration<br></li><li>Passion and Soul<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Social Share &amp; Locker Pro 6.9"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Copy Traffic 1.2 Pro</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2096-copy-traffic.html</link>
<description>Name : Copy Traffic Pro Version : 1.2 Type : Onpage Plugin, Social Optimize Plugin Price : $37 Homepage : SalePage Need Traffic? This Final Offer Gives You The Technology NBC, National Geographic &amp; The New York Post Are Using... How To Double Your Social Traffic In 7 Seconds ... Copy Traffic lets you take advantage of this massive untapped copy/paste traffic source by letting you add attributions that automatically get added as the visitor copies and pastes your content.</description>
<category>Social Networking Plugins</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.ultimatebannerplugin.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/paste.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://www.ultimatebannerplugin.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/cct-settings.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://www.ultimatebannerplugin.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/fbshare.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://www.ultimatebannerplugin.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/amessage.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://www.ultimatebannerplugin.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/gmail.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://www.ultimatebannerplugin.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/syndication.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2016 21:51:30 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Attribution Message Builder : Create Stunning Ads &amp; Bio Boxes That Will Generate More Clicks For Your Links! Powerful Macros : Use These In Your Attribution Messages To Automatically Include Links, Time, Titles Etc. Add Attribution To Feeds : Automatically Include Your Attribution Message &amp; Link To Your RSS Feed &amp; Get Backlinks Whenever Your Blog Is Scraped! Use Keyword Rich Anchor Text : Automatically Add Anchor Text To Your Feed Attribution Links For Increased SEO Benefit! Use Copy Traffic On Any Website : Use The 1-Click Script Generator To Easily Unleash The Power Of Copy Traffic On Any Website (Not Just On Your WordPress Blogs). As we now know up to 70% of the people of the people wanting to share that content will ignore those buttons - and instead mark and copy the text like I did here: Then they would paste the copied text into email or some other source - and I would get nothing from it, but because I have the Copy Traffic plugin installed - some clever &quot;magic&quot; happens behind the scenes... And when they go to paste the content into their email this happens... Copy Traffic Example When Posting YOUR Blog Content Via Email : See, the Copy Traffic plugin automatically inserted my text and the link to the post the content was copied from! And this is what the plugin does automatically, right out of the box without the need to change any settings! But of course we gave you options to completely customize your links and text - as you see in the screenshot below... You can customise your added message too... - Change the text appearing before your link. You have unlimited space here - and you can even leave it blank if you only want to show a link. - You get full control over what link you want included when people copy and paste from your site. - You can link to the individual sites the content was copied from (great for deep links and targeted traffic). - You can choose to link your blog&#039;s home page (great if you are trying to rank the front page or get traffic there). - You can link to any website - this could for example be an affiliate link (a great way to profit from social sharing). - You can even choose not to use any links, if you just want the text to appear. - You decide if you want your attribution (text and link) to show above or below the copy-pasted content. - And finally you can set a minimum number of copied words required before the plugin activates your magic (if you set it to zero it will kick in if they copy as much as a blank space from your site!) Social Sharing Get&#039;s An Upgrade Too: See what happens when your content is copy/pasted on Facebook... As you can see, the link back to your site is automatically included here too! Using technology like this is so powerful in generating links and traffic that would otherwise have been lost... But we haven&#039;t stopped there because we&#039;ve included some extra features at no extra cost! Instead of just being able to enter a single line of text before your link... You can use a full message area to construct a bio box or any kind of advert you like. You can use macro&#039;s to automatically add in different content AND simply check one box - and your attribution messages and links will be automatically added to your RSS feed. And that means that every time someone scrapes our autoblogs from our blog - our message and backlink will be included on their blog! This is so powerful you&#039;re actually now hoping that people will scrape your blog!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<br /><div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/JcKXVjgqCCg?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Attribution Message Builder : Create Stunning Ads & Bio Boxes That Will Generate More Clicks For Your Links!<br /></li><li> Powerful Macros : Use These In Your Attribution Messages To Automatically Include Links, Time, Titles Etc.<br /></li><li> Add Attribution To Feeds : Automatically Include Your Attribution Message & Link To Your RSS Feed & Get Backlinks Whenever Your Blog Is Scraped!<br /></li><li> Use Keyword Rich Anchor Text : Automatically Add Anchor Text To Your Feed Attribution Links For Increased SEO Benefit!<br /></li><li> Use Copy Traffic On Any Website : Use The 1-Click Script Generator To Easily Unleash The Power Of Copy Traffic On Any Website (Not Just On Your WordPress Blogs).<br /></li></ul><br />As we now know up to 70% of the people of the people wanting to share that content will ignore those buttons - and instead mark and copy the text like I did here:<br />Then they would paste the copied text into email or some other source - and I would get nothing from it, but because I have the Copy Traffic plugin installed - some clever "magic" happens behind the scenes...<br />And when they go to paste the content into their email this happens...<br />Copy Traffic Example When Posting YOUR Blog Content Via Email : <br /><img src="http://www.ultimatebannerplugin.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/paste.png" alt="Copy Traffic 1.2 Pro" title="Copy Traffic 1.2 Pro"  /><br />See, the Copy Traffic plugin automatically inserted my text and the link to the post the content was copied from!<br /><br />And this is what the plugin does automatically, right out of the box without the need to change any settings!<br /><br />But of course we gave you options to completely customize your links and text - as you see in the screenshot below...<br /><img src="http://www.ultimatebannerplugin.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/cct-settings.png" alt="Copy Traffic 1.2 Pro" title="Copy Traffic 1.2 Pro"  /><br />You can customise your added message too...<br /> - Change the text appearing before your link. You have unlimited space here - and you can even leave it blank if you only want to show a link.<br /> - You get full control over what link you want included when people copy and paste from your site.<br /> - You can link to the individual sites the content was copied from (great for deep links and targeted traffic).<br /> - You can choose to link your blog's home page (great if you are trying to rank the front page or get traffic there).<br /> - You can link to any website - this could for example be an affiliate link (a great way to profit from social sharing).<br /> - You can even choose not to use any links, if you just want the text to appear.<br /> - You decide if you want your attribution (text and link) to show above or below the copy-pasted content.<br /> - And finally you can set a minimum number of copied words required before the plugin activates your magic (if you set it to zero it will kick in if they copy as much as a blank space from your site!)<br />Social Sharing Get's An Upgrade Too: See what happens when your content is copy/pasted on Facebook...<br /><img src="http://www.ultimatebannerplugin.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/fbshare.png" alt="Copy Traffic 1.2 Pro" title="Copy Traffic 1.2 Pro"  /><br /><br />As you can see, the link back to your site is automatically included here too!<br />Using technology like this is so powerful in generating links and traffic that would otherwise have been lost...<br />But we haven't stopped there because we've included some extra features at no extra cost! <br />Instead of just being able to enter a single line of text before your link...<br />You can use a full message area to construct a bio box or any kind of advert you like.<br /><img src="http://www.ultimatebannerplugin.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/amessage.png" alt="Copy Traffic 1.2 Pro" title="Copy Traffic 1.2 Pro"  /><br /><br />You can use macro's to automatically add in different content <br /><img src="http://www.ultimatebannerplugin.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/gmail.png" alt="Copy Traffic 1.2 Pro" title="Copy Traffic 1.2 Pro"  /><br /><br />AND simply check one box - and your attribution messages and links will be automatically added to your RSS feed.<br /><img src="http://www.ultimatebannerplugin.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/syndication.png" alt="Copy Traffic 1.2 Pro" title="Copy Traffic 1.2 Pro"  /><br />And that means that every time someone scrapes our autoblogs from our blog - our message and backlink will be included on their blog!<br /><br />This is so powerful you're actually now hoping that people will scrape your blog!<br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Copy Traffic 1.2 Pro" title="Copy Traffic 1.2 Pro"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Blog2Social 3.1.3 Premium Business</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2107-blog2social.html</link>
<description>Name : Blog2Social Version : 3.1.3 Premium BUSINESS OS : Linux Type : Social Network Plugin Price : $199/Year Homepage : SalePage Social Media Automation for WordPress-Blogs Automatically share and schedule your blog posts to social media customized for each.comwork and scheduled for the best times to post to profiles, pages and groups.</description>
<category>Social Networking Plugins</category>
<enclosure url="https://www.blog2social.com/en/page/features/assets/images/screenshot.comworks.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="https://www.blog2social.com/en/page/start/assets/images/scheduling.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2016 17:24:23 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features User per license : 10 Accounts per.comwork : 15 Pure Auto-Posting : with preformatted posts on profiles, pages and groups when you publish a blog post Cross-Promoting : on social media profiles Cross-promoting : on social media pages &amp;amp; groups Pre-formatted posts : for each.comworks specifications One-Page Editor One easy workflow: for tailoring your social media posts with individual comments, #hashtags or @handles for more engagement. Rich HTML-Editor : for re-publishing on Medium, Tumblr &amp;amp; Torial Multiple-Accounts per Network : Connect multiple each.comwork One click.comwork selection : Select your standard.comworks or check or uncheck your selected.comworks per click. Pre-selected Networks : Select pre-defined.comwork bundles for various sharing activities. Immediate Sharing : Select your post and share it on your selected.comworks. Individual Scheduling : Define your own time settings for different dates and times to share your posts on each.comwork. Best Time Manager : Use pre-defined time settings to share your posts at the best times to post on each.comwork. Recurrent Sharing : Auto-Share your postings recurrently on specific.comworks. Re-sharing old posts : Re-share older posts as evergreen content on your social.comworks. Reporting : Track the status of your social media posts. Re-Scheduling : View and change scheduled posts if needed. Social Media Networks Facebook profiles Facebook pages Twitter profiles Google+ profiles Google+ pages Google+ communities LinkedIn profiles LinkedIn pages XING profiles XING pages XING groups Pinterest Instagram Flickr Medium Tumblr Torial Diigo Delicious</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><div class="dlevideoplayer" style="width:100%;max-width:425px;"><ul data-theme="default" data-preload="metadata"><li data-title="" data-type="youtube" data-url="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ywugec7atNU"></li></ul></div></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> User per license : 10<br></li><li> Accounts per.comwork : 15<br></li><li> Pure Auto-Posting : with preformatted posts on profiles, pages and groups when you publish a blog post  <br></li><li> Cross-Promoting : on social media profiles    <br></li><li> Cross-promoting : on social media pages &amp; groups     <br></li><li> Pre-formatted posts : for each.comworks specifications    <br></li><li> One-Page Editor  One easy workflow: for tailoring your social media posts with individual comments, #hashtags or @handles for more engagement.  <br></li><li> Rich HTML-Editor : for re-publishing on Medium, Tumblr &amp; Torial   <br></li><li> Multiple-Accounts per Network : Connect multiple each.comwork   <br></li><li> One click.comwork selection : Select your standard.comworks or check or uncheck your selected.comworks per click.   <br></li><li> Pre-selected Networks : Select pre-defined.comwork bundles for various sharing activities.   <br></li><li> Immediate Sharing : Select your post and share it on your selected.comworks.   <br></li><li> Individual Scheduling : Define your own time settings for different dates and times to share your posts on each.comwork.  <br></li><li> Best Time Manager : Use pre-defined time settings to share your posts at the best times to post on each.comwork.   <br></li><li> Recurrent Sharing : Auto-Share your postings recurrently on specific.comworks.   <br></li><li> Re-sharing old posts : Re-share older posts as evergreen content on your social.comworks.     <br></li><li> Reporting : Track the status of your social media posts.   <br></li><li> Re-Scheduling : View and change scheduled posts if needed.<br></li></ul><br><b>Social Media Networks</b><br><ul><li> Facebook profiles<br></li><li> Facebook pages<br></li><li> Twitter profiles<br></li><li> Google+ profiles<br></li><li> Google+ pages<br></li><li> Google+ communities<br></li><li> LinkedIn profiles<br></li><li> LinkedIn pages<br></li><li> XING profiles<br></li><li> XING pages<br></li><li> XING groups<br></li><li> Pinterest<br></li><li> Instagram<br></li><li> Flickr<br></li><li> Medium<br></li><li> Tumblr<br></li><li> Torial<br></li><li> Diigo<br></li><li> Delicious<br></li></ul><br><img src="https://www.blog2social.com/en/page/features/assets/images/screenshot.comworks.png" alt="Blog2Social 3.1.3 Premium Business"><br><img src="https://www.blog2social.com/en/page/start/assets/images/scheduling.png" alt=""><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>FB Like Jacking Ninja 4.0.8</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2084-fb-like-jacking-ninja.html</link>
<description>Name : FB Like Jacking Ninja 2016 Edition Version : 4.0.8 OS : Linux Type : Social Plugin Price : $47 Homepage : SalePage &quot;How A Secret WP Plugin Gets Real Likes For Your FB Pages, Making Them Insanely Popular and Profitable, In 30 Days Or Less, Without Using FB Ads!!&quot; Explode Your FB Pages With 1,000&#039;s of Real Likes Even If You&#039;re A Complete Newbie To Facebook Marketing...Now, if you&#039;re wondering what the FB Like Jacking Ninja does...and...why it&#039;s able to help so many people, I&#039;m more than happy to tell you. The FB Like Jacking Ninja is a WordPress Plugin that&#039;s designed specifically to help you make money from your Facebook pages by getting them an unlimited number of likes from REAL Facebook users which makes your pages incredibly popular. When you have a popular FB page, making money from it becomes child&#039;s play. Imagine owning a number of Facebook pages that each have 10,000&#039;s of targeted fans who are interested in what you post on your pages. Imagine how easy it would be to, at the touch of a button, post updates to your page and have all of those fans liking and sharing your posts with their friends who will then come and check out your page as well.</description>
<category>Social Networking Plugins</category>
<enclosure url="http://imageshack.com/a/img921/3306/iY1EOO.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/a/img923/8018/w1ajVR.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/a/img923/5319/vQUxxY.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2016 12:16:13 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Works on mobile and desktop traffic... Advanced features to help keep you off the FB radar Have TOTAL control over all parts of the Like Jacking Only jack visitors from countries you choose Avoid jacking traffic from certain IP&#039;s Avoid jacking traffic from certain referring sites Deactivate the jacker automatically at set times of the day Only jack a certain percentage of your traffic Get Likes for and FB Page Safe to use with AdSense Your visitors will never know they were Like jacked</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/1GdvkY_wvbk?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Works on mobile and desktop traffic...<br /></li><li> Advanced features to help keep you off the FB radar<br /></li><li> Have TOTAL control over all parts of the Like Jacking<br /></li><li> Only jack visitors from countries you choose<br /></li><li> Avoid jacking traffic from certain IP's<br /></li><li> Avoid jacking traffic from certain referring sites<br /></li><li> Deactivate the jacker automatically at set times of the day<br /></li><li> Only jack a certain percentage of your traffic<br /></li><li> Get Likes for and FB Page<br /></li><li> Safe to use with AdSense<br /></li><li> Your visitors will never know they were Like jacked<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://imageshack.com/a/img921/3306/iY1EOO.png" alt="FB Like Jacking Ninja 4.0.8" title="FB Like Jacking Ninja 4.0.8"  /><br /><img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/a/img923/8018/w1ajVR.png" alt="FB Like Jacking Ninja 4.0.8" title="FB Like Jacking Ninja 4.0.8"  /><br /><img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/a/img923/5319/vQUxxY.png" alt="FB Like Jacking Ninja 4.0.8" title="FB Like Jacking Ninja 4.0.8"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="FB Like Jacking Ninja 4.0.8" title="FB Like Jacking Ninja 4.0.8"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Revive Old Post Pro 1.8.6</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1792-revive-old-post-pro.html</link>
<description>Name : Revive Old Post Pro Version : 1.8.6 Type : Social Plugin Price : $75 Homepage : SalePage Revive old post Pro Add-on This plugin helps you to keeps your old posts alive by sharing them and driving more traffic to them from social.comworks</description>
<category>Social Networking Plugins</category>
<enclosure url="https://i.imgur.com/aZlIaTw.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2016 21:48:33 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Clean &amp; Validated Code : We have to brag with our ability to provide a code that&#039;s easily editable by any person with just enough HTML/PHP knowledge 5 link shortener to choose from : With TOP you can easily choose a link shortener for your links in a really simple way, currently we support services like bit.ly or is.gd or tinyurl or 1click.at or su.pr . Custom Tweet Content : With TOP you don&#039;t tweet just the title+link of your posts, you can add custom hashtags based on categories or a custom text Support and Updates : No worries mate we have your back! Each product comes with 1 year of updates and support</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/yV7FcUr9HQg?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Clean & Validated Code : We have to brag with our ability to provide a code that's easily editable by any person with just enough HTML/PHP knowledge<br /></li><li> 5 link shortener to choose from : With TOP you can easily choose a link shortener for your links in a really simple way, currently we support services like bit.ly or is.gd or tinyurl or 1click.at or su.pr .<br /></li><li> Custom Tweet Content : With TOP you don't tweet just the title+link of your posts, you can add custom hashtags based on categories or a custom text<br /></li><li> Support and Updates : No worries mate we have your back! Each product comes with 1 year of updates and support<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="https://i.imgur.com/aZlIaTw.png" alt="Revive Old Post Pro 1.8.6" title="Revive Old Post Pro 1.8.6"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Revive Old Post Pro 1.8.6" title="Revive Old Post Pro 1.8.6"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>