<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Proxies Scraper - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Proxies Scraper - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>Gather Proxy 9.0 Premium</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1355-gather-proxy.html</link>
<description>Name : Gather Proxy Version : 9.0 Premium OS : Windows Type : Proxy Scraper Price : $19 Homepage : SalePage Gather Proxy is a lightweight Windows utility designed to help users gather information about proxy servers and socks. Since this is a portable program, it is important to mention that it doesn’t leave any traces in the Windows Registry. You can copy it on any USB flash drive or other devices, and take it with you whenever you to need to generate proxy and socks lists on the breeze. Although it comes bundled with many useful functions, it boasts a clean and straightforward layout.</description>
<category>Proxies Scraper</category>
<enclosure url="http://i1-win.softpedia-static.com/screenshots/GatherProxy_2.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 17:22:03 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features 1. GatherProxy scrapes thousands of fresh proxies from over 300 daily updated websites. Its include leading sites such as Hidemyass Proxy List. 2. HTTP proxy checker, Socks 4/5 checker, SSL checker, Black List checker, Google Passed proxies checker. 3. Recurring Scaper and Checker. The program repeat gathering and checking proxy. Automatic saving them to your hardware or FTP server. Simple open program and you will get newest proxies and socks 24/7. 4. Url Expression feature, this is allow harvest proxies from Google Search, Forum or any site with smart method. Read more ... 5. It is a portable program, the tool really compact and save memory resource for your PC. WHY SHOULD I USE GATHER PROXY INSTEAD OF COMPETITOR PRODUCTS? 1. Features. GatherProxy giving you some features which are not any program available. (Ex: Url Expression, Scraper proxy from protected source (hidemyass)) 2. Price. For example, the product Forum Proxy Leecher, which ONLY leeches from predefined websites and has no dynamic website discovering ability like GatherProxy, costs $99.95. That also only includes a single year of updates. GatherProxy include updates for lifetime. Another example, Proxy Goblin? $96.00. Also only a leecher and does not include GatherProxy&#039;s unique search ability. Proxy Multiply? Black list check is not available. You can get unsafe proxies. Only scape proxies from unsafe sources. Can not harvest proxies by smart method such as Google Search. 3. Trial. We are offering FREE and PREMIUM version. So you can trial forever on FREE version and upgade to PREMIUM if you like it.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/yQxPhhX_Drc?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> 1. GatherProxy scrapes thousands of fresh proxies from over 300 daily updated websites. Its include leading sites such as Hidemyass Proxy List.<br></li><li> 2. HTTP proxy checker, Socks 4/5 checker, SSL checker, Black List checker, Google Passed proxies checker.<br></li><li> 3. Recurring Scaper and Checker. The program repeat gathering and checking proxy. Automatic saving them to your hardware or FTP server. Simple open program and you will get newest proxies and socks 24/7.<br></li><li> 4. Url Expression feature, this is allow harvest proxies from Google Search, Forum or any site with smart method. Read more ...<br></li><li> 5. It is a portable program, the tool really compact and save memory resource for your PC.<br></li></ul><br>WHY SHOULD I USE GATHER PROXY INSTEAD OF COMPETITOR PRODUCTS?<ul><li> 1. Features. GatherProxy giving you some features which are not any program available. (Ex: Url Expression, Scraper proxy from protected source (hidemyass))<br></li><li> 2. Price. For example, the product Forum Proxy Leecher, which ONLY leeches from predefined websites and has no dynamic website discovering ability like GatherProxy, costs .95. That also only includes a single year of updates. GatherProxy include updates for lifetime. Another example, Proxy Goblin? .00. Also only a leecher and does not include GatherProxy's unique search ability. Proxy Multiply? Black list check is not available. You can get unsafe proxies. Only scape proxies from unsafe sources. Can not harvest proxies by smart method such as Google Search.<br></li><li> 3. Trial. We are offering FREE and PREMIUM version. So you can trial forever on FREE version and upgade to PREMIUM if you like it.<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://i1-win.softpedia-static.com/screenshots/GatherProxy_2.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Gather Proxy 9.0 Premium"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>GSA Proxy Scraper 2.45</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1032-gsa-proxy-scraper.html</link>
<description>Tired of wasting time and money searching for the proxies you need? Or maybe you&#039;re tired of websites spying on you and collecting your data without your consent? Look no further, we have a solution for you GSA Proxy Scraper is a powerful, easy to use, Windows based, proxy scraping software that can harvest and test thousands of proxies quickly and reliably with just a few simple clicks. No more headaches wasting time to find the right proxy GSA Proxy harvester makes harvesting proxies easy. Our powerful proxy harvester has the unique ability to find and harvest proxies from thousands of sources across the web and continues to seek out and find proxies until YOU tell it to stop. If that isn&#039;t enough, GSA Proxy Scraper goes above and beyond by adding in a powerful Port Scanner, which gives GSA Proxy Scraper the power to harvest proxies from places that other competing software on the market can&#039;t touch. Useful features like Smart-Tagging allow you to easily create your own custom proxy tags which automatically filter proxies based on the criteria you set. (E.G. proxy must work with Youtube, Facebook, Etsy, etc.). Easy to use exporting and filtering options will take care of all the organizing, filtering, and exporting without any intervention on your end. Need Google passed proxies sent to one location (E.G. email), but want Ebay passed proxies saved to your local machine? No problem! GSA Proxy Harvester can export proxies to email, FTP upload, local destination, or even web upload. Simply choose the export interval and location to export the proxies, and GSA proxy harvester will handle it all automatically, while you sit back and drink your cup of coffee. After months of research and development, we&#039;re confident that no other software on the market comes close to offering the features that GSA Proxy Harvester comes with right out of the box.</description>
<category>Proxies Scraper</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-05/1431542544_1zf7i83.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-05/1431542806_gsa-ser-extension.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-05/1431542756_gsa-trial-reset.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2018 02:16:00 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>- Powerful Harvester: Built in proxy harvester goes above and beyond the competition by having the unique ability to scrape proxies from almost any site! The proxy harvester is so powerful it can harvest proxies from sources other proxy tools can&#039;t touch - Test Proxies Against: Automatically test newly scraped proxies against websites such as web 2.0&#039;s, social accounts, email providers, search engines and even your own custom URL&#039;s - Smart Tags: Proxy tags allow you to easily tag/group specific types of proxies which can later be used for different tasks - Proxy Types: GSA Proxy Scraper currently has support for Web, Connect, and Socks4/5 proxy types - Port Scanner: Powerful, multi-threaded port scanner allows you to easily scan I.P. and port ranges to discover more proxies - Proxy Filtering: Automatically filter by country, speed, Google passed, anonymity level, dangerous I.P.&#039;s and more - Compatibility: Supports proxy formats from all the most popular SEO tools such as GSA SER, Scrapebox, Gscraper, NohandsSEO, Ultimate Demon and many more - Internal Proxy Server: Internal proxy server allows the software to act as a personal VPN, giving your browser a fresh new I.P. after every refresh. - Export Options: Automatic proxy export to FTP, email, local directory, and web upload (GET, POST) - Lifetime license and updates: Just like other GSA tools, GSA Proxy Scraper is a one-time fee and includes free updates and support for the lifetime of the software. - And much more!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[- Powerful Harvester: Built in proxy harvester goes above and beyond the competition by having the unique ability to scrape proxies from almost any site! The proxy harvester is so powerful it can harvest proxies from sources other proxy tools can't touch<br> - Test Proxies Against: Automatically test newly scraped proxies against websites such as web 2.0's, social accounts, email providers, search engines and even your own custom URL's<br> - Smart Tags: Proxy tags allow you to easily tag/group specific types of proxies which can later be used for different tasks<br> - Proxy Types: GSA Proxy Scraper currently has support for Web, Connect, and Socks4/5 proxy types<br> - Port Scanner: Powerful, multi-threaded port scanner allows you to easily scan I.P. and port ranges to discover more proxies<br> - Proxy Filtering: Automatically filter by country, speed, Google passed, anonymity level, dangerous I.P.'s and more<br> - Compatibility: Supports proxy formats from all the most popular SEO tools such as GSA SER, Scrapebox, Gscraper, NohandsSEO, Ultimate Demon and many more<br> - Internal Proxy Server: Internal proxy server allows the software to act as a personal VPN, giving your browser a fresh new I.P. after every refresh.<br> - Export Options: Automatic proxy export to FTP, email, local directory, and web upload (GET, POST)<br> - Lifetime license and updates: Just like other GSA tools, GSA Proxy Scraper is a one-time fee and includes free updates and support for the lifetime of the software.<br> - And much more!<br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="GSA Proxy Scraper 2.45"></div><br><div class="quote"><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Paigham Bot Proxy Scraper &amp; Checker Pro 1.01</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3946-paigham-bot-proxy-scraper-checker-pro.html</link>
<description>Name : Paigham Bot Proxy Scraper &amp;amp; Checker Pro Version : 1.01 OS : Windows Type : Proxy Service Price : $19.99 Homepage : SalePage Everyone in marketing needs fresh, working proxies! Harvest ten’s of thousands of proxies anytime you need them with Paigham Bot Proxy Scraper &amp;amp; Checker Pro.</description>
<category>Proxies Scraper</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 06:41:03 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Harvest ten’s of thousands of proxies anytime you need them with Paigham Bot Proxy Scraper &amp;amp; Checker Pro. One thing that makes this proxy scraper and checker different than others on the market, is our method for actually testing proxies. We believe our proxy check works better than other software to give you more accurate results with proxies that will last longer than other software using stale proxy sources and inaccurate proxy judges. This software is simple, yet very accurate and efficient. Recent Features added include new checks implemented for testing against Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, Pinterest, Google.com, Google w/ Footprint and also whether or not proxy is showing a captcha and a Port skip/blacklist.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/wfpdlNnfZEo?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Harvest ten’s of thousands of proxies anytime you need them with Paigham Bot Proxy Scraper &amp; Checker Pro.<br></li><li> One thing that makes this proxy scraper and checker different than others on the market, is our method for actually testing proxies. We believe our proxy check works better than other software to give you more accurate results with proxies that will last longer than other software using stale proxy sources and inaccurate proxy judges.<br></li><li> This software is simple, yet very accurate and efficient.<br></li><li> Recent Features added include new checks implemented for testing against Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, Pinterest, Google.com, Google w/ Footprint and also whether or not proxy is showing a captcha and a Port skip/blacklist.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Paigham Bot Proxy Scraper &amp; Checker Pro 1.01"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Free Proxy Finder 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4124-free-proxy-finder.html</link>
<description>Name : Free Proxy Finder Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Proxy Finder Tools Price : $0 Homepage : SalePage Free Proxy Finder is a software tool that allows users to scrape open public proxies off proxy listing websites. It not only does this automatically in the background but it does it at scale, scraping hundreds of websites and then even testing the results for you</description>
<category>Proxies Scraper</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 06:11:37 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features You simply click &quot;find proxies&quot; and the software will fire queries at Google to find websites that have huge lists, once it finds these it will scrape their lists and test each result it finds to make sure its working for you by connecting to test websites. This all happens in the background saving you hours of work. The tool has two main options. Firstly the depth to scrape website results from Google, this can be 10 results per query or it can be up to 100. 100 will be slow but give you more results. 10 will be quicker but give you less results. The second option is the timeout on each proxy test, by default this is 10 seconds so if a successful connection can&#039;t be made to the target website in under 10 seconds it will class that result as failed. This setting can be adjusted to any timeout value you desire.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/huDT_usYOvA?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> You simply click "find proxies" and the software will fire queries at Google to find websites that have huge lists, once it finds these it will scrape their lists and test each result it finds to make sure its working for you by connecting to test websites. This all happens in the background saving you hours of work. The tool has two main options. Firstly the depth to scrape website results from Google, this can be 10 results per query or it can be up to 100. 100 will be slow but give you more results. 10 will be quicker but give you less results. The second option is the timeout on each proxy test, by default this is 10 seconds so if a successful connection can't be made to the target website in under 10 seconds it will class that result as failed. This setting can be adjusted to any timeout value you desire.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Free Proxy Finder 1.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Proxy Checker 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4281-proxy-checker.html</link>
<description>Name : Proxy Checker Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Check Proxy Tools Price : $50 Homepage : SalePage This tool is used for checking if your proxies are functioning as expected. Simply download and enter your proxies then click &quot;Check&quot;. Reliable working proxies are key to successful inte.com marketing. Often you may try and save money by purchasing semi, or even scraping public instead buying dedicated only to find out most of them are not going to work for your project.</description>
<category>Proxies Scraper</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 06:10:24 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features This free tool has three methods of checking if your proxies are working or not. - Basic HTTP - This check takes each proxy and tries to connect to your configured website (example.com by default) if it can successfully connect then it is deemed as working, if it can&#039;t them its deemed to be not working. - HTTP code - This check will allow you to enter your target URL (example.com by default) and the tool will connect through each proxy checking the HTTP response code it receives against the rules you have entered. For example it can fail if a 403 (forbidden) is given by the remote web server, or it can only pass if a 200 (success) is given by the remote web server. - HTML - This check allows you to pass and fail proxies based on what HTML is returned by the remote web server. For example if you think some of your proxies may of been blocked by the web server you can configure this check to fail if the word &quot;blocked&quot; is detected in the HTML returned by the remote web server. Or you can congifure this check to pass if some of the expected HTML is returned in the response from the web server.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/zzlkLpkJ59g?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> This free tool has three methods of checking if your proxies are working or not. <br></li><li> - Basic HTTP - This check takes each proxy and tries to connect to your configured website (example.com by default) if it can successfully connect then it is deemed as working, if it can't them its deemed to be not working.<br></li><li> - HTTP code - This check will allow you to enter your target URL (example.com by default) and the tool will connect through each proxy checking the HTTP response code it receives against the rules you have entered. For example it can fail if a 403 (forbidden) is given by the remote web server, or it can only pass if a 200 (success) is given by the remote web server.<br></li><li> - HTML - This check allows you to pass and fail proxies based on what HTML is returned by the remote web server. For example if you think some of your proxies may of been blocked by the web server you can configure this check to fail if the word "blocked" is detected in the HTML returned by the remote web server. Or you can congifure this check to pass if some of the expected HTML is returned in the response from the web server.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Proxy Checker 1.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Avira Phantom VPN Pro 2.8.4.30090</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4366-avira-phantom-vpn-pro.html</link>
<description>Name : Avira Phantom VPN Pro Version : 2.8.4.30090 OS : Windows Type : Tools For Private and Hidden Price : $12 Homepage : SalePage Surf the web securely and anonymously with our free VPN. Ideal for keeping your activities private and hidden from your Inte.com Service Provider.</description>
<category>Proxies Scraper</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 08:29:11 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Unhackable - Your financial info, passwords, and other private files are secure: they cannot be intercepted nor read by third parties. - Encrypt your web traffic and secure your inte.com connection - Safely surf on public WiFi hotspots (airport, coffee shops, etc.) - Block hackers from gaining access to your computer Untraceable - Prevent advertisers and eavesdroppers from tracking you. As far as they can see, you’re an anonymous user from an ever-changing location. - Create a unique, private, and fast path for you to surf the web - Prevent your Inte.com Service Provider (ISP) from monitoring you - Browse the web anonymously by hiding your IP address Uncensored - Bypass geographical restrictions by setting your inte.com connection to appear as if you’re somewhere else. Your data volume Unlimited Encrypted traffic Unlimited Private surfing Unlimited Access to geo-restricted sites Unlimited DNS leak prevention Unlimited Multi-device Unlimited (PC, Mac, Android &amp;amp; iOS) Unlimited Auto-connect VPN for Wi-Fi.comworks Unlimited Fail-safe Unlimited Tech support Unlimited</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Unhackable<br></li><li> - Your financial info, passwords, and other private files are secure: they cannot be intercepted nor read by third parties.<br></li><li> - Encrypt your web traffic and secure your inte.com connection<br></li><li> - Safely surf on public WiFi hotspots (airport, coffee shops, etc.)<br></li><li> - Block hackers from gaining access to your computer<br></li><li> Untraceable<br></li><li> - Prevent advertisers and eavesdroppers from tracking you. As far as they can see, you’re an anonymous user from an ever-changing location.<br></li><li> - Create a unique, private, and fast path for you to surf the web<br></li><li> - Prevent your Inte.com Service Provider (ISP) from monitoring you<br></li><li> - Browse the web anonymously by hiding your IP address<br></li><li> Uncensored<br></li><li> - Bypass geographical restrictions by setting your inte.com connection to appear as if you’re somewhere else.<br></li><li> Your data volume                       Unlimited<br></li><li> Encrypted traffic                      Unlimited<br></li><li> Private surfing                        Unlimited<br></li><li> Access to geo-restricted sites         Unlimited<br></li><li> DNS leak prevention                    Unlimited<br></li><li> Multi-device                           Unlimited<br></li><li> (PC, Mac, Android &amp; iOS)               Unlimited<br></li><li> Auto-connect VPN for Wi-Fi.comworks    Unlimited<br></li><li> Fail-safe                              Unlimited<br></li><li> Tech support                           Unlimited<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Avira Phantom VPN Pro 2.8.4.30090"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>CyberGhost VPN 6.5.0.3180</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4365-cyberghost-vpn.html</link>
<description>Name : CyberGhost VPN Version : 6.5.0.3180 OS : Windows Type : Online Privacy App Price : $99 Homepage : SalePage CyberGhost VPN is the all-in-one online privacy app, with a predefined and dedicated profile for any online need you may have.</description>
<category>Proxies Scraper</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 08:28:29 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Hide Your IP Your original IP address will be replaced with one from the CyberGhost.comwork, making it impossible for third parties to track you online. Access Restricted Websites No more censored or geo-restricted content. By connecting to the secure CyberGhost servers, you gain access to content from all over the world. Safe Online Transactions With CyberGhost VPN, nobody will be able to pry into your personal conversations, browsing history or online transactions, even on public WiFis. Block Malicious Content When you try to access a website, CyberGhost will make sure it’s safe for you, by running a thorough check on that URL in a dedicated database. Fully Encrypted Inte.com Your online activity will be encrypted with the 256-AES bit technology. Thus, it may take someone thousands of years to hack into your data! Protect All Your Devices Get simultaneous top-class protection on up to 5 devices with a German-made software, available on Windows, Mac, iOS and Android platforms.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Hide Your IP<br></li><li> Your original IP address will be replaced with one from the CyberGhost.comwork, making it impossible for third parties to track you online.<br></li><li> Access Restricted Websites<br></li><li> No more censored or geo-restricted content. By connecting to the secure CyberGhost servers, you gain access to content from all over the world.<br></li><li> Safe Online Transactions<br></li><li> With CyberGhost VPN, nobody will be able to pry into your personal conversations, browsing history or online transactions, even on public WiFis.<br></li><li> Block Malicious Content<br></li><li> When you try to access a website, CyberGhost will make sure it’s safe for you, by running a thorough check on that URL in a dedicated database.<br></li><li> Fully Encrypted Inte.com<br></li><li> Your online activity will be encrypted with the 256-AES bit technology. Thus, it may take someone thousands of years to hack into your data!<br></li><li> Protect All Your Devices<br></li><li> Get simultaneous top-class protection on up to 5 devices with a German-made software, available on Windows, Mac, iOS and Android platforms.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="CyberGhost VPN 6.5.0.3180"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Hotspot Shield 7.20.8 Elite Edition</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1787-hotspot-shield-elite.html</link>
<description>Name : Hotspot Shield Version : 7.20.8 Elite Edition OS : Windows Type : VPN CLient Price : $30 Homepage : SalePage Hotspot Shield Elite is a useful tool for protecting your computer data when you are frequently using unsecured wireless connections. Since most of the public hotspots are not secured, it is a must-have application for your laptop. Though Hotspot Shield Elite lets you download and surf without a bandwidth cap, you are limited to seven days before you have to pay. There is a wholly free version, but it’s riddled with ads. Once you’ve registered with Hotspot Shield, protecting your surfing only requires one click and no complicated setup.Today At Fullstuff I Came With The Latest Version Crack For The Hotspot Shield.So Just Follow Me And Enjoy ?</description>
<category>Proxies Scraper</category>
<enclosure url="http://i1-win.softpedia-static.com/screenshots/Hotspot-Shield-Elite_1.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 21:21:12 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>[media=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pK63R_tEFqo] Features Browse Anonymously:Use Hotspot Shield to anonymize and mask your online activities and hide your IP address. Bypass Censorship &amp;amp; Firewalls:Our VPN solution allows you access to blocked content and websites. Watch Blocked Content:Watch online content as if you were in that country! Choose from up to 6 virtual locations* (US, UK, AU, JP, CA and DE). Safe, Secure, Public Wifi Access:Hotspot Shield encrypts your Wifi connections, detects and blocks malicious malware. Ad-Free Browsing Experience:Elite members get unlimited browsing from all 6 virtual locations without any ad-supported content! Dedicated Customer Support:Having Trouble? Elite members get answers from our trained customer support team so you can browse the web safely.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;">[media=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pK63R_tEFqo]</div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Browse Anonymously:Use Hotspot Shield to anonymize and mask your online activities and hide your IP address.<br></li><li> Bypass Censorship &amp; Firewalls:Our VPN solution allows you access to blocked content and websites.<br></li><li> Watch Blocked Content:Watch online content as if you were in that country! Choose from up to 6 virtual locations* (US, UK, AU, JP, CA and DE).<br></li><li> Safe, Secure, Public Wifi Access:Hotspot Shield encrypts your Wifi connections, detects and blocks malicious malware.<br></li><li> Ad-Free Browsing Experience:Elite members get unlimited browsing from all 6 virtual locations without any ad-supported content!<br></li><li> Dedicated Customer Support:Having Trouble? Elite members get answers from our trained customer support team so you can browse the web safely.<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://i1-win.softpedia-static.com/screenshots/Hotspot-Shield-Elite_1.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Hotspot Shield 7.20.8 Elite Edition"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Hide ALL IP 2017.07.09.170709</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2152-hide-all-ip.html</link>
<description>Name : Hide ALL IP Version : 2017.07.09.170709 OS : Windows Type : Hide IP Price : $29 Homepage : SalePage Hide ALL IP is the worlds best IP hide software, hide all your applications and games IP from snoopers &amp;amp; hackers, you can surf anonymously, prevent identity theft, and guard against hacker intrusions, it just takes one click to get started. Your IP address can link your inte.com activities directly to you, it can easy leak you by this IP address, Hide ALL IP protects your online identity by changing your IP address to our private server&#039;s IP and routes all your inte.com traffic through our encrypted inte.com servers so that all remote servers only get a fake IP address, you are very safely. Unlike your ISP, Hide ALL IP does not track and does not record anywhere you go !</description>
<category>Proxies Scraper</category>
<enclosure url="https://screenshots.en.sftcdn.com/en/scrn/69663000/69663209/scr_1370577213-700x480.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2017 03:40:10 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Best hide ip software featuresChange Your IP Address - Just click &quot;Connect&quot; and your IP is instantly hidden! The Inte.com will see your fake IP, which is not associated with your real IP. How It Works. Change Your Location - Our servers are located throughout the world, you can easily connect to the different servers in different countries. Each time you press the &#039;Connect&#039; button, you will fake as this country&#039;s IP. If you want to change the country, just press the &quot;Connect&quot; button again. Encrypt ALL Transfer Data - All inbound and outbound connections (include UDP data) are encrypted using the industry standard RSA 1024 and RC4 encryption, It&#039;s government level encryption and is very safe. Even if your ISP or some other third party is monitoring your communications, they will have no idea what you are connecting to and what data is being transferred. Remote DNS Lookups - Using our secure remote DNS lookup technology, you can avoid any DNS faking or tracking, there are no any DNS leaks, and resolving DNS lookups are all safe! Access Inte.com TV (Hulu,BBC iplayer, and more) - Inte.com TV providers such as the BBC and Hulu use location detection to deny users certain content. Hide ALL IP provides all the tools what you need, Just connect to a server IP in the country associated with the TV providers and point your browser to the correct website. How to view Hulu outside US video tutorial How to view BBC iplayer outside UK video tutorial Support Almost ALL Applications And Games - Not only does Hide ALL IP support browsers, it also supports instant messengers, video players, games, and more! Unique Support Prevent WebRTC IP Leaks - WebRTC is a great technology, it is designed for browsers with Real-Time Communications (RTC) capabilities. There is already direct WebRTC support in Firefox, Chrome, and Opera. Unfortunately, WebRTC can be used to detect your Inte.com IP even under the presence of a VPN. Hide ALL IP includes a safe WebRTC work mode. In this mode, WebRTC will still work, but all public Inte.com IPs are hidden and not leaked. What&#039;s WebRTC? How Hide ALL IP prevent WebRTC IP leak? Unique Support UDP Applications - Other Hide IP software only supports TCP, Hide ALL IP also supports UDP based applications and games. Now play DNF, League of Legends, Battle Field 3, StarCraft II and Tank Of Worlds using Hide ALL IP is possible! UDP video player applications are also supported! Unique Support HTTP Tunnel - Depening on our auto http tunnel technology (Which doesn&#039;t requrie any setup), you can bypass any firewall and proxy. Even if you in a limited.comwork, such as school.comwork, that uses only pure HTTP proxy, Hide ALL IP still works. Playing games and videos is still possible. What&#039;s HTTP tunnel?. Unique Has Portable Version - We also provide a portable version of Hide ALL IP, not need install, can be run from removable media such as a USB stick, floppy, etc... and not need admin rights and can be used with limited.comwork environment. Safely Browse Technology - You don&#039;t need to clear cookies or online history when using our safe browsing functionality. This means cookies, history, and cached browsing data is only in memory, when you close your browsers; it is cleared automatically. Unique Support Hide Win8/8.1/10 Metro Applications IP - Not only hide desktop applications IP, Hide ALL IP can also hide win8/8.1/10 metro applications IP and support IE in EPM (Enhanced Protected Mode) mode and Microsoft Edge Browser. Unique Support Fake Html5 GeoLocation By Selected Fake IP - Some websites use Html5 GeoLocation feature to locate your real location, default browsers use WIFI/GPS to detect your location, Hide ALL IP can force browsers to locate your location using our fake IP address. Reduce Your Game Ping - Specifically optimize for the game, if your game Lag, use Hide ALL IP will significantly improve speed and reduce the Lag. How to reduce TCP game lag How to reduce P2P UDP game (League of Legends) lag Unique Support Auto Find Best Server For Any Game - You can enter any game server host or IP, Hide ALL IP will notify all fake IP servers to automatically ping this game server, and calculate which server is the fastest server to connect to this game server.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/d8Q2_vszdSc?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Best hide ip software featuresChange Your IP Address - Just click "Connect" and your IP is instantly hidden! The Inte.com will see your fake IP, which is not associated with your real IP. How It Works.<br></li><li> Change Your Location - Our servers are located throughout the world, you can easily connect to the different servers in different countries. Each time you press the 'Connect' button, you will fake as this country's IP. If you want to change the country, just press the "Connect" button again.<br></li><li> Encrypt ALL Transfer Data - All inbound and outbound connections (include UDP data) are encrypted using the industry standard RSA 1024 and RC4 encryption, It's government level encryption and is very safe. Even if your ISP or some other third party is monitoring your communications, they will have no idea what you are connecting to and what data is being transferred.<br></li><li> Remote DNS Lookups - Using our secure remote DNS lookup technology, you can avoid any DNS faking or tracking, there are no any DNS leaks, and resolving DNS lookups are all safe!<br></li><li> Access Inte.com TV (Hulu,BBC iplayer, and more) - Inte.com TV providers such as the BBC and Hulu use location detection to deny users certain content. Hide ALL IP provides all the tools what you need, Just connect to a server IP in the country associated with the TV providers and point your browser to the correct website.   How to view Hulu outside US video tutorial    How to view BBC iplayer outside UK video tutorial<br></li><li> Support Almost ALL Applications And Games - Not only does Hide ALL IP support browsers, it also supports instant messengers, video players, games, and more!<br></li><li> Unique Support Prevent WebRTC IP Leaks - WebRTC is a great technology, it is designed for browsers with Real-Time Communications (RTC) capabilities. There is already direct WebRTC support in Firefox, Chrome, and Opera. Unfortunately, WebRTC can be used to detect your Inte.com IP even under the presence of a VPN. Hide ALL IP includes a safe WebRTC work mode. In this mode, WebRTC will still work, but all public Inte.com IPs are hidden and not leaked.  What's WebRTC?   How Hide ALL IP prevent WebRTC IP leak?<br></li><li> Unique Support UDP Applications - Other Hide IP software only supports TCP, Hide ALL IP also supports UDP based applications and games. Now play DNF, League of Legends, Battle Field 3, StarCraft II and Tank Of Worlds using Hide ALL IP is possible! UDP video player applications are also supported!<br></li><li> Unique Support HTTP Tunnel - Depening on our auto http tunnel technology (Which doesn't requrie any setup), you can bypass any firewall and proxy. Even if you in a limited.comwork, such as school.comwork, that uses only pure HTTP proxy, Hide ALL IP still works. Playing games and videos is still possible. What's HTTP tunnel?.<br></li><li> Unique Has Portable Version - We also provide a portable version of Hide ALL IP, not need install, can be run from removable media such as a USB stick, floppy, etc... and not need admin rights and can be used with limited.comwork environment.<br></li><li> Safely Browse Technology - You don't need to clear cookies or online history when using our safe browsing functionality. This means cookies, history, and cached browsing data is only in memory, when you close your browsers; it is cleared automatically.<br></li><li> Unique Support Hide Win8/8.1/10 Metro Applications IP - Not only hide desktop applications IP, Hide ALL IP can also hide win8/8.1/10 metro applications IP and support IE in EPM (Enhanced Protected Mode) mode and Microsoft Edge Browser.<br></li><li> Unique Support Fake Html5 GeoLocation By Selected Fake IP - Some websites use Html5 GeoLocation feature to locate your real location, default browsers use WIFI/GPS to detect your location, Hide ALL IP can force browsers to locate your location using our fake IP address.<br></li><li> Reduce Your Game Ping - Specifically optimize for the game, if your game Lag, use Hide ALL IP will significantly improve speed and reduce the Lag.  How to reduce TCP game lag   How to reduce P2P UDP game (League of Legends) lag<br></li><li> Unique Support Auto Find Best Server For Any Game - You can enter any game server host or IP, Hide ALL IP will notify all fake IP servers to automatically ping this game server, and calculate which server is the fastest server to connect to this game server.<br></li></ul><br><img src="https://screenshots.en.sftcdn.com/en/scrn/69663000/69663209/scr_1370577213-700x480.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Hide ALL IP 2017.07.09.170709"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>BrowSEO Proxy Scraper 2.6</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1537-browseo-proxy-scraper.html</link>
<description>Name : BrowSEO Proxy Scraper Version : 2.6 Elite OS : Windows Type : Proxy Tools Price : $67 Homepage : SalePage There are some fairly big claims going on with this launch, namely that this very low cost product can replace your existing private proxy service. That would mean one small up front cost for the software and then no more monthly recurring fees as you would get with every private proxy company around.</description>
<category>Proxies Scraper</category>
<enclosure url="http://garyschollmeier.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/07/only-elite-proxies.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2016 10:19:47 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features I&#039;m by no means a power house proxy user however I do spend out monthly on a private proxy plan with Instant Proxies and I&#039;m pretty happy with them to be quite honest. I use them for GSA SER, Social Robot and some other software. However, I&#039;m also open to cutting my monthly out goings so I decided to pick up a 3-PC license copy and put it to the test.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/EfGM-zGm_V0?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br />I'm by no means a power house proxy user however I do spend out monthly on a private proxy plan with Instant Proxies and I'm pretty happy with them to be quite honest. I use them for GSA SER, Social Robot and some other software. However, I'm also open to cutting my monthly out goings so I decided to pick up a 3-PC license copy and put it to the test.<br /><br /><br /><img src="http://garyschollmeier.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/07/only-elite-proxies.png" alt="BrowSEO Proxy Scraper 2.6" title="BrowSEO Proxy Scraper 2.6"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="BrowSEO Proxy Scraper 2.6" title="BrowSEO Proxy Scraper 2.6"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>