<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Footprints Checker - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Footprints Checker - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>Footprint Factory Pro 1.1.0.11</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1475-footprint-factory-pro.html</link>
<description>Name : Footprint Factory Version : Pro 1.1.0.11 OS : Windows Type : Link Building Tools Price : $67 Homepage : SalePage UnlimitedBacklinks FpF finds ALL patterns across URLs, giving you immense 100% complete footprint lists. No footprint will be left undiscovered. You can use these footprints to: Find new link targets no one has ever used before Build link lists to use or sell</description>
<category>Footprints Checker</category>
<enclosure url="http://fpfactory.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/11/upgrade1.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://fpfactory.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/11/upgrade2.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://fpfactory.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/11/upgrade3.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2016 23:29:35 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/Cj2K-ggJrW8?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><br /><img src="http://fpfactory.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/11/upgrade1.png" alt="Footprint Factory Pro 1.1.0.11" title="Footprint Factory Pro 1.1.0.11"  /><br /><img src="http://fpfactory.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/11/upgrade2.png" alt="Footprint Factory Pro 1.1.0.11" title="Footprint Factory Pro 1.1.0.11"  /><br /><img src="http://fpfactory.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/11/upgrade3.png" alt="Footprint Factory Pro 1.1.0.11" title="Footprint Factory Pro 1.1.0.11"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Footprint Factory Pro 1.1.0.11" title="Footprint Factory Pro 1.1.0.11"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>SER Footprint Editor 1.0.2.14</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1426-ser-footprint-editor.html</link>
<description>Name : SER Footprint Editor Version : P 1.0.2.14 OS : Windows Type : Viber Marketing Tools Price : $0 Homepage : SalePage The whole idea behind SER Footprint Editor is to make it easier for SER users to add footprints to existing engines in SER. By adding more targeted footprints to your engines, you can scrape more targets and drop more backlinks.</description>
<category>Footprints Checker</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.imdevin.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/12/SER-Footprint-Editor-Screenshot-580x459.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2015 19:46:14 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Automatic Updater! Proxy Support! Automatically fetches Google search count for every footprint! Allows you to easily modify engines footprints! Another generic feature to make it sound better than it really is! Other features that I&#039;m too tired to come up with right now!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/YAWKPD1sojI?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Automatic Updater!<br /></li><li> Proxy Support!<br /></li><li> Automatically fetches Google search count for every footprint!<br /></li><li> Allows you to easily modify engines footprints!<br /></li><li> Another generic feature to make it sound better than it really is!<br /></li><li> Other features that I'm too tired to come up with right now!<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://www.imdevin.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/12/SER-Footprint-Editor-Screenshot-580x459.png" alt="SER Footprint Editor 1.0.2.14" title="SER Footprint Editor 1.0.2.14"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="SER Footprint Editor 1.0.2.14" title="SER Footprint Editor 1.0.2.14"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>TurboWare Platforms Filter 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/949-turbo-ranker-platform-filter.html</link>
<description>Name : TurboWare Platforms Filter Version : 1.0 OS : Windows 7/8/Server/10 Type : Misc, Platform Filter Price : $0 Homepage : SalePage Turbo Ranker - Platform Filter is an free addon (part of TurboRanker Submitter) that can be used without any constraints as a standalone application. The Platform Filter application will parse (filter) the many available backlink lists into manageable lists. It will save the filtered links into separated .txt files (named by the found platform type). The filter (footprints.txt) is fully editable. You can change it (improving/adding new platforms, etc) as desired.</description>
<category>Footprints Checker</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2015 00:58:27 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>How to use it: - Paste your links to be checked in the the &quot;URL List&quot; box, or use the &quot;Open&quot; button to import a .txt file. - Select the number of threads (by default it is set to 50 threads). - Click &quot;START&quot;. - After the scan was finished, use the &quot;Save&quot; button. You will find your .txt files in the &quot;Results&quot; folder.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>How to use it:</h3><br />- Paste your links to be checked in the the "URL List" box, or use the "Open" button to import a .txt file.<br />- Select the number of threads (by default it is set to 50 threads).<br />- Click "START".<br />- After the scan was finished, use the "Save" button. You will find your .txt files in the "Results" folder. <br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="TurboWare Platforms Filter 1.0" title="TurboWare Platforms Filter 1.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>GSA Platform Identifier 1.30</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1033-gsa-platform-identifier.html</link>
<description>GSA Platform Identifier is an extremely powerful, multi-threaded, Windows based computer program that automatically recognizes and sorts imported URLS based upon their platform E.G. Wordpress, BlogEngine, Expression Engine and hundreds more. GSA PI is able to recognize tons of various platforms right out of the box and can sort and detect lots of website URLS very fast. Using GSA PI, you have the ability to effortlessly sort and identify all of your harvested website URL&#039;s by simply importing them into the software, setting up a project and clicking go! After classifying is finished, the URLS are ready to be imported into your preferred link building software of choice such as GSA Search Engine Ranker for more efficient automated link building.</description>
<category>Footprints Checker</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-05/1431542544_1zf7i83.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-05/1431542806_gsa-ser-extension.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-05/1431542756_gsa-trial-reset.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2015 02:19:24 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>GSA Platform Identifier can also identify links based on the keyword criteria you set to help bring in more &quot;niche relevant&quot; URLS to use for your higher quality link-building campaigns. For example, if you are searching for URLS that include a specific keyword in the tags, Meta data, URL, domain, or visible text on the page, GSA PI can automatically identify and save them for you. And we all know that using niche relevant backlinks are generally more valuable than non-relevant backlinks which means higher search engine positions. GSA PI also has the ability to monitor live folders so as you&#039;re scraping URLS with your preferred scraping software, GSA Platform Identifier will automatically monitor the output directory and categorize the URLS based upon the requirements you specify. This means no need to babysit your search engine scraper and import website URLs by hand, GSA Platform Identifier will handle the importing, analyzing, classifying and categorizing for you automatically. There is no other application on the market that comes close to the performance and efficiency of GSA Platform Identifier when it comes to quickly sorting and identifying website URLs. Download your copy right away! Features for Platform Identification - Adjustable Multi-threading - Extremely fast and efficient. - One-time Charge and Free Product Updates for Life. - Multi Project Support - Run several campaigns simultaneously. - Keyword Filter- Powerful filter enables you to save only &quot;niche relevant&quot; urls by removing URL&#039;s that don&#039;t include your keyword phrase. - Engine Filter- Filter URLS for a specific type of platform. E.G. BlogEngine, Pligg, and so on. Only selected platforms will be saved. - Monitor Files and Folders - Automatically monitor files and directories, as new URLS are added to the file/folder, the application will automatically identify and sort them in. This is tremendously powerful when used with Scrapebox or Gscraper + GSA Search Engine Ranker. - Custom Engines - Want to identify and sort a platform that isn&#039;t added? Simply add your own via the custom engines option. - Live Graphs and Statistics - Live Charts and Statistics provide you a breakdown of how your project is doing. Watch your platform count rise in real time as links get categorized!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/k5l8OW2SCc0?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><br />GSA Platform Identifier can also identify links based on the keyword criteria you set to help bring in more "niche relevant" URLS to use for your higher quality link-building campaigns. For example, if you are searching for URLS that include a specific keyword in the  tags, Meta data, URL, domain, or visible text on the page, GSA PI can automatically identify and save them for you.<br />And we all know that using niche relevant backlinks are generally more valuable than non-relevant backlinks which means higher search engine positions.<br /><br />GSA PI also has the ability to monitor live folders so as you're scraping URLS with your preferred scraping software, GSA Platform Identifier will automatically monitor the output directory and categorize the URLS based upon the requirements you specify. This means no need to babysit your search engine scraper and import website URLs by hand, GSA Platform Identifier will handle the importing, analyzing, classifying and categorizing for you automatically. There is no other application on the market that comes close to the performance and efficiency of GSA Platform Identifier when it comes to quickly sorting and identifying website URLs. Download your copy right away!<br /><br /><b>Features for Platform Identification</b><br /> - Adjustable Multi-threading - Extremely fast and efficient.<br /> - One-time Charge and Free Product Updates for Life.<br /> - Multi Project Support - Run several campaigns simultaneously.<br /> - Keyword Filter- Powerful filter enables you to save only "niche relevant" urls by removing URL's that don't include your keyword phrase.<br /> - Engine Filter- Filter URLS for a specific type of platform. E.G. BlogEngine, Pligg, and so on. Only selected platforms will be saved.<br /> - Monitor Files and Folders - Automatically monitor files and directories, as new URLS are added to the file/folder, the application will automatically identify and sort them in. This is tremendously powerful when used with Scrapebox or Gscraper + GSA Search Engine Ranker.<br /> - Custom Engines - Want to identify and sort a platform that isn't added? Simply add your own via the custom engines option.<br /> - Live Graphs and Statistics - Live Charts and Statistics provide you a breakdown of how your project is doing. Watch your platform count rise in real time as links get categorized!<br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="GSA Platform Identifier 1.30" title="GSA Platform Identifier 1.30"  /></div><br /><div class="quote"><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>