<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Kindle Marketing - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Kindle Marketing - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>KDSpy 4.3.49</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1202-kdspy.html</link>
<description>Name : KDSpy Version : 4.3.49 OS : Windows/MAC Type : Kindle Research Marketing Price : $47 Homepage : SalePage The Ultimate Amazon Kindle Spy Tool &quot;New Unique Software Application &#039;Reverse Engineers&#039; The Kindle Marketplace &amp;amp; Reveals Lucrative Kindle Niches - In Seconds!&quot;</description>
<category>Kindle Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.kdspy.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/3.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://www.kdspy.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/2.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 14:44:21 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Reverse Engineer The &#039;Best-Selling&#039; Categories With A Single Click Another Click Tells You &#039;Exactly&#039; What Your Next Book Topic Should Be Analyse &quot;Niche Potential&quot; With The Kindle Search Results Analysis Feature Spy On Self Published Authors &amp;amp; Swipe Their &#039;Best-Selling&#039; Topics Track Your Competitors Book(s) Performance Daily Over 30 Days KDSPY v4 Now Supports Amazon Data From:USA,UK,CA,DE,IT,SP,FR</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/TdNZDF00YcY?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><p><br></p><br><h3>Features</h3><br><p><br><ul><li> Reverse Engineer The 'Best-Selling' Categories With A Single Click<br></li><li> Another Click Tells You 'Exactly' What Your Next Book Topic Should Be<br></li><li> Analyse "Niche Potential" With The Kindle Search Results Analysis Feature<br></li><li> Spy On Self Published Authors &amp; Swipe Their 'Best-Selling' Topics<br></li><li> Track Your Competitors Book(s) Performance Daily Over 30 Days<br></li><li> KDSPY v4 Now Supports Amazon Data From:USA,UK,CA,DE,IT,SP,FR<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://www.kdspy.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/3.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="KDSpy 4.3.49"><br><img src="http://www.kdspy.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/2.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>KDROI 1.5.25</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1766-kdroi.html</link>
<description>Name : KDROI Version : 1.5.25 OS : Windows/Linux/MAC Type : Kindle Marketing Tools Price : $47 Homepage : SalePage The Ultimate Kindle eBook Promotion Tool &quot;Forget outsourcing or paying a &quot;per submission&quot; fee to submit your Kindle eBooks to the book promotional sites. KDROI does it in 15 seconds with a handful of clicks...&quot; KDROI is the tool I’ve been waiting for. Leave it to Wes Atkins, the forward thinker who developed KDSpy, to come up with this incredible way to save time and money when submitting your Kindle book’s free days to promotional sites. In minutes after getting access to the program, I had it loaded and had submitted one of my books free promotional days to 22 sites. Minutes instead of what in the past would have taken hours! And, in the past, when I haven’t had the time to submit Kindle free days myself, I have paid (virtual assistant, Fiverr, etc.) to have the book submitted … KDROI will easily justify its price in a minimal number of submissions for book promotions that I would have paid for in the past. One of the best features of KDROI is that is comes from the force behind KDSpy. Based on my experience with KDSpy, the support is unparalleled: questions and concerns are addressed immediately, updates are frequent and free, and there is a hands-on understanding of self-publishers. Now that I have this fantastic tool, I am going to use it to schedule my next round of Kindle KDP free promotional days … and, do it quickly and efficiently. KDROI is a game changer.</description>
<category>Kindle Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.kdroi.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/11/4-kdroi1.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2017 16:25:27 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Step 1: Setup a Free Promo or Countdown Deal For Your Kindle eBook.Before using KDROI, just setup a Free book promotion or Kindle Countdown deal (OR just manually set your book price to 99c) for your Kindle eBook in your Amazon KDP account. Then revert back to your bookshelf and click on your books &#039;direct&#039; Amazon link to view your book on the Kindle store. Step 2: KDROI Pulls In The Essential Data For Your Chosen Kindle eBook : Once you&#039;re viewing your book on the Kindle store, KDROI will work on the background to grab all the essential information from your book listing page. A single click into KDROI on your browser and the only 2 things you need to do are, select whether you book is fiction OR non-fiction, then enter your email address. Step 3: Verify Your Book Description, Author BIO &amp;amp; Kindle Cover Image : After clicking next you will be presented with your book description, your author BIO and you cover image pulled from Amazon. If you want to make any changes to these details, you can amend them in the boxes provided. You can even upload a NEW image for your cover if you wish. Once you are happy with the details, click NEXT. Step 4: Choose The Start &amp;amp; End Date Of Your Book Promotion : On this screen you will be presented with a very simple calendar which corresponds to the dates of your promotion for your Kindle ebook. Just select the START and END data of your book promotion and click NEXT. Step 5: Choose The Type Of Promo &amp;amp; The Sites You Want To Submit To : You will then be presented with an &#039;ever-growing&#039; list of sites that will list your Kindle eBook on their website during your book promotion. Simply select the type of promo (FREE, 0.99c or Permafree) ... and the sites you want to submit to. Then, click &#039;submit promotion&#039;, and in less than 15 seconds, you&#039;re finished.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/bCOtzNZXpBM?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Step 1: Setup a Free Promo or Countdown Deal For Your Kindle eBook.Before using KDROI, just setup a Free book promotion or Kindle Countdown deal (OR just manually set your book price to 99c) for your Kindle eBook in your Amazon KDP account. Then revert back to your bookshelf and click on your books 'direct' Amazon link to view your book on the Kindle store.<br></li><li> Step 2: KDROI Pulls In The Essential Data For Your Chosen Kindle eBook : Once you're viewing your book on the Kindle store, KDROI will work on the background to grab all the essential information from your book listing page. A single click into KDROI on your browser and the only 2 things you need to do are, select whether you book is fiction OR non-fiction, then enter your email address.<br></li><li> Step 3: Verify Your Book Description, Author BIO &amp; Kindle Cover Image : After clicking next you will be presented with your book description, your author BIO and you cover image pulled from Amazon. If you want to make any changes to these details, you can amend them in the boxes provided. You can even upload a NEW image for your cover if you wish. Once you are happy with the details, click NEXT.<br></li><li> Step 4: Choose The Start &amp; End Date Of Your Book Promotion : On this screen you will be presented with a very simple calendar which corresponds to the dates of your promotion for your Kindle ebook. Just select the START and END data of your book promotion and click NEXT.<br></li><li> Step 5: Choose The Type Of Promo &amp; The Sites You Want To Submit To : You will then be presented with an 'ever-growing' list of sites that will list your Kindle eBook on their website during your book promotion. Simply select the type of promo (FREE, 0.99c or Permafree) ... and the sites you want to submit to. Then, click 'submit promotion', and in less than 15 seconds, you're finished.<br><br></li></ul><br><img src="http://www.kdroi.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/11/4-kdroi1.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="KDROI 1.5.25"><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>AK Booster Pro 1.2</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1986-ak-booster-pro-12.html</link>
<description>Name : AK Booster Pro Version : 1.2 OS : Windows/MAC Type : Kindle Tools Price : $197 Homepage : SalePage AK Booster Pro is a Kindle market research desktop software. This is a one-stop solution for Kindle market research that has been designed to cut users average research time by 95% and automatically list out all the popular and easy to rank niches in Kindle that can easily be dominated. AKbooster is designed in a KISS layout with only the tabs and information you really need. No complicated layout or campaign set up that confuses non-tech savvy individuals. All the data can easily be exported to excel file…</description>
<category>Kindle Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/akbooster/6.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/akbooster/4.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 20:34:53 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features There are 3 sections in the software: Niche Finder Section: Niche Finder finds amazons leading indicators (what users are searching for on just Amazon) and can organize them instantly by rank of most popular to least popular. Niche Finder can find a specific score for how competitive a niche keyword will be, how in demand it will be, and an overall score of how easy it will be to make money or rank your book with this keyword. This is calculated specifically on Amazon and for Amazon Kindle, not with the Google keyword tool or Google trends. The competition, demand, and overall scores are shown in red, yellow, and green letting you know instantly if this is a good niche keyword. A number from 1-100 is assigned for each score letting you know specifically how well this keyword will do. Submitter Section: The submitter section contains the largest collection of free and paid sites users can submit their books to get reviews and downloads including more than Author Marketing Club. These include not just Kindle freebie sites, but popular Facebook groups that allow you to advertise your book for free. By clicking on the tab, the submitter section opens the exact page you need to submit your book saving hours of time. The submitter section also contains the best paid-advertising sites to submit your books to, such as Kindle Nation Daily and BookBub. Reviewer: The reviewer section finds potential reviewers for your book in Amazon, GoodReads, and Facebook. The Amazon section finds the most recent and helpful reviewers in any specific niche and shows you their email, ID, and website. Goodreads section searches specific reading groups in your desired niche and pulls their ID, email, and website for you to contact them. Facebook section searches for other authors and readers for your specific niche in Facebook groups and gives your their link ID to contact.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/C9mqtT3d55A?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br />There are 3 sections in the software:<br /><b>Niche Finder Section:</b><br />Niche Finder finds amazons leading indicators (what users are searching for on just Amazon) and can organize them instantly by rank of most popular to least popular.<br />Niche Finder can find a specific score for how competitive a niche keyword will be, how in demand it will be, and an overall score of how easy it will be to make money or rank your book with this keyword. This is calculated specifically on Amazon and for Amazon Kindle, not with the Google keyword tool or Google trends.<br />The competition, demand, and overall scores are shown in red, yellow, and green letting you know instantly if this is a good niche keyword. A number from 1-100 is assigned for each score letting you know specifically how well this keyword will do.<br /><b>Submitter Section:</b><br />The submitter section contains the largest collection of free and paid sites users can submit their books to get reviews and downloads including more than Author Marketing Club. These include not just Kindle freebie sites, but popular Facebook groups that allow you to advertise your book for free.<br />By clicking on the tab, the submitter section opens the exact page you need to submit your book saving hours of time.<br />The submitter section also contains the best paid-advertising sites to submit your books to, such as Kindle Nation Daily and BookBub.<br /><b>Reviewer:</b><br />The reviewer section finds potential reviewers for your book in Amazon, GoodReads, and Facebook. The Amazon section finds the most recent and helpful reviewers in any specific niche and shows you their email, ID, and website.<br />Goodreads section searches specific reading groups in your desired niche and pulls their ID, email, and website for you to contact them.<br />Facebook section searches for other authors and readers for your specific niche in Facebook groups and gives your their link ID to contact.<br /><img src="https://s3.amazonaws.com/akbooster/6.jpg" alt="AK Booster Pro 1.2" title="AK Booster Pro 1.2"  /><br /><img src="https://s3.amazonaws.com/akbooster/4.jpg" alt="AK Booster Pro 1.2" title="AK Booster Pro 1.2"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="AK Booster Pro 1.2" title="AK Booster Pro 1.2"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>AK Elite 1.3</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1985-ak-elite.html</link>
<description>Name : AK Elite Version : 1.3 OS : Windows Type : Kindle Tools Price : $57 Homepage : SalePage The truth is, if you don&#039;t know how to use AK Elite to build a quick, long-term income, its pretty much a WORTHLESS software. So to help you get Benefit with AK Elite, FASTER, I wanna share some simple, underground strategies with you... On top of sharing my powerful strategies, I&#039;ll also guide you with 60 days of 1-on-1 consulting on your Kindle ebook projects (so you can avoid costly mistakes and fast-track your success). In a nutshell, AK Elite helps you research profitable topics to write about, identifies the hottest keywords, and then helps you get your ebook ranked for those keywords. Brad&#039;s salesletter and his demonstration video do a pretty good job explaining how the software works, so I won&#039;t really get into that here (you can watch it by clicking the links below)... But here&#039;s the thing, EVEN if you&#039;re ranked on Amazon for hot keywords, your ebook(s) may not get very many sales. And thats assuming you actually PUBLISH an ebook in the first place! Many, many people struggle with writing a decent ebook, and many people struggle with getting any lasting, meaningful sales once the book is published. AK Elite CAN drive traffic to your ebook and get you lots of exposure, but that doesn&#039;t mean anything if you can&#039;t get a lot of sales. If you really wanna take your sales to the NEXT level, there are some specific, killer strategies that can help you get there...</description>
<category>Kindle Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-p4Jmxz2cETc/Uc21B2BkviI/AAAAAAAAAro/RZnCxNSnYNs/s920/land_scrs3.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 20:27:54 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Effortlessly rank for long tail phrases that pin point potential buyers and suck them ino your funnel NEVER have to worry about creating original content... and all the headaches that come from THAT process ALWAYS have the hottest, freshest, highest converting stuff on your site... to ensure a loyal fanbase and RAPID growth in a short amount of time Generate TONS of traffic... without spending a DIME! Quickly demonstrate &quot;Authority By Association&quot; which lets you charge MORE for whatever it is you are trying to sell Immediately tap into trending topics for MAX viral exposure And much more... Manage multiple blogs in one location (depending on the license you choose) Quickly find targeted articles through multiple “Feeds” Insert the curated articles with one click Format your post for SEO with the click of your mouse (h1 tags and all that stuff are normally so confusing - not here!) Quickly search for images which are legal to use (that&#039;s important -- The ability to make sure the images you get have rights for you to use them saves your ass legally!) Quickly search for and review targeted YouTube videos -- Insert media you find into your post with one click (NO embed code - now that&#039;s what I like!) Create crazy looking memes in the meme editor with a royalty free image that you obtain using the image browser – post directly to your blog, Facebook timeline or schedule to fan pages.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/H4BHL0A9_xs?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Effortlessly rank for long tail phrases that pin point potential buyers and suck them ino your funnel<br /></li><li> NEVER have to worry about creating original content... and all the headaches that come from THAT process<br /></li><li> ALWAYS have the hottest, freshest, highest converting stuff on your site... to ensure a loyal fanbase and RAPID growth in a short amount of time<br /></li><li> Generate TONS of traffic... without spending a DIME!<br /></li><li> Quickly demonstrate "Authority By Association" which lets you charge MORE for whatever it is you are trying to sell<br /></li><li> Immediately tap into trending topics for MAX viral exposure<br /></li><li> And much more...<br /></li><li> Manage multiple blogs in one location (depending on the license you choose)<br /></li><li> Quickly find targeted articles through multiple “Feeds”<br /></li><li> Insert the curated articles with one click<br /></li><li> Format your post for SEO with the click of your mouse (h1 tags and all that stuff are normally so confusing - not here!)<br /></li><li> Quickly search for images which are legal to use (that's important -- The ability to make sure the images you get have rights for you to use them saves your ass legally!)<br /></li><li> Quickly search for and review targeted YouTube videos -- Insert media you find into your post with one click (NO embed code - now that's what I like!)<br /></li><li> Create crazy looking memes in the meme editor with a royalty free image that you obtain using the image browser – post directly to your blog, Facebook timeline or schedule to fan pages.<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-p4Jmxz2cETc/Uc21B2BkviI/AAAAAAAAAro/RZnCxNSnYNs/s920/land_scrs3.jpg" alt="AK Elite 1.3" title="AK Elite 1.3"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="AK Elite 1.3" title="AK Elite 1.3"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>KinSEO Agent 1.0.4</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1969-kinseo-agent.html</link>
<description>Name : KinSEO Agent Version : 1.0.4 OS : Windows Type : Kindle Tools Price : $17 Homepage : SalePage Finds Keywords for Your Book - Provides Potential Keyword/Book Ideas From Both Google and Amazon Discover The Single 60 – Second Trick That Will Instantly Boost Your Book in The Amazon Search Rankings! Inside I’m going to blow open this “trick” that Amazon doesn’t tell you about, most of the top authors keep secret, and my team and I most recently discovered. It has a huge effect on your book promotions and you probably have neglected it (or haven’t actively used it like we’ll show you). It’s so important to Amazon search rankings! And no one else has talked about it. No one has mentioned it. And none of the top authors want me to tell you.</description>
<category>Kindle Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://i.imgur.com/0iuZukh.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2016 21:15:54 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features How to Quickly Dominate the Amazon Search Results Page! How A 60 – Second Trick Will Make the Difference Between A #1 Spot in Amazon and #200. This Hidden Secret Amazon Has Been Keeping From Authors…And How Only A Few Have Discovered It (And Been Using It) Why Target Keywords In Your Title, Descriptions and Keyword Box Are Not Enough To Rank Your Book…and How to Change It Why You’ve Been Wasting Time and Money On Book Promotions – Causing Your Book to Not Stick In Amazon! Location, Location, Location! Where You Put Your Keywords Makes The Difference…I’ll Show You Where! And More!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/XS_-MjLF0SM?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> How to Quickly Dominate the Amazon Search Results Page!<br /></li><li> How A 60 – Second Trick Will Make the Difference Between A #1 Spot in Amazon and #200.<br /></li><li> This Hidden Secret Amazon Has Been Keeping From Authors…And How Only A Few Have Discovered It (And Been Using It)<br /></li><li> Why Target Keywords In Your Title, Descriptions and Keyword Box Are Not Enough To Rank Your Book…and How to Change It<br /></li><li> Why You’ve Been Wasting Time and Money On Book Promotions – Causing Your Book to Not Stick In Amazon!<br /></li><li> Location, Location, Location! Where You Put Your Keywords Makes The Difference…I’ll Show You Where!<br /></li><li> And More!<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://i.imgur.com/0iuZukh.png" alt="KinSEO Agent 1.0.4" title="KinSEO Agent 1.0.4"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="KinSEO Agent 1.0.4" title="KinSEO Agent 1.0.4"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>KD Researcher 2.3</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1682-kd-researcher.html</link>
<description>Name : KD Researcher Version : 2.3 OS : Windows Type : Kindle Marketing Tools Price : $19 Homepage : SalePage With our KD Researcher, you will instantly find out what your market wants and expects from you and your book. What the best selling covers, titles, reviews, price points, and page counts are, all at the tip of your fingers. With version 2.0, we have added the ability to search any of the 20,000 plus Amazon categories in Amazon.com and the 20,000 plus categories in Amazon.co.uk. By the way, if you want to save the information we capture on your behalf, there is a Save button that will allow you to export that data to a CSV file. By finding out this important information, and finding it out fast, you will be able to do what Carl did with his book, and finally make all that work you&#039;ve done translate into money!</description>
<category>Kindle Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://kdresearcher.com/images/kdr-update-073114.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2016 03:57:00 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Instant researching software that will shave hours off of your work. Instantly know, in a single window, what your market&#039;s top sellers are doing – Cover, Titles, Price, Page count and more... Meet your markets expectations by mimicking the titles/covers/descriptions and more of your market</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/c9mk5Iib5Zs?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Instant researching software that will shave hours off of your work. <br></li><li> Instantly know, in a single window, what your market's top sellers are doing – Cover, Titles, Price, Page count and more... <br></li><li> Meet your markets expectations by mimicking the titles/covers/descriptions and more of your market <br></li></ul><br><img src="http://kdresearcher.com/images/kdr-update-073114.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt="KD Researcher 2.3"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>KDPulse 4.2</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1630-kdpulse.html</link>
<description>Name : KDPulse Version : 4.2 OS : Windows/MAC Type : Kindle Research Marketing Price : $27 Homepage : SalePage The Complete Kindle Stats Dashboard that Amazon forgot to give us Authors All your Kindle stats in 1 click! KDPulse shows all your Kindle stats in one dashboard. Just click to see sales, KU pages, rank, reviews, stars, more - all in 1 screen! Amazon didn&#039;t make it easy. You want sales stats - login to KDP. You want reviews, go to the book page, or Author Central. It&#039;s gonna take you a while to get all those stats together and then they&#039;ll be out of date quickly. KDPulse has all stats and your book link/ASIN and makes doing promotions easier too.When you want to do promotions, you need access to your book and stats. KDPulse gives you the link to each book. No longer do you need to remember the link or ASIN to your book. Just click or copy the link to paste into all those promotion forms. Easily track the Kindle stats of competitors! With a simple click, import the stats of any competitor&#039;s Kindle book and keep track of it. Great for comparing and also to see how their books are doing during their promotions.</description>
<category>Kindle Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://kdpulse.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2015/07/Screen-Shot-2015-07-24-at-9.43.30-AM.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2016 15:08:39 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Live Sales and Pages Read : You can see Today, Yesterday, Last 7 days, Last 30 days worth of Live sales, pages read, and free downloads. Reviews and Stars : Easily see your review counts and stars for each book. You can always know which books need more reviews. Auto Finds All Your Books : Once it&#039;s installed, just click Import My Books. If you&#039;re logged into KDP, it auto finds all books &amp; grabs all stats. Makes Book Promos Easier : Every Title is a link to your book. Click to get description, or right-click &amp; copy/paste to give Amazon Link or ASIN. Links to Important Kindle URLs : Links to KDP Bookshelf, Reports, Author Central, Best Sellers, New Releases, Manage Devices, &amp; Send to Kindle. Best Sellers Rank : It&#039;s not the most important stat, but it sure gives you an idea of where your book is, and it&#039;s good to see. Never forget to change the price again : Ever change a price to try to get a little sales love and forget to change it back? See the price of every book. Even More Stats... KDPulse shows Author/Pen Name, Publish Date, Pages, and every title is a link to the book - click or copy/paste. Track Other Books for Sport : Keep track of a favorite author&#039;s or competitor&#039;s books.Add &#039;em to the Other Books tab to get all stats except sales. Current Book Promotion Sites List : Always on the hunt for book promotion sites? Now you can get an up-to-date list just a click away in KDPulse.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/w5MCNM_5wVg?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Live Sales and Pages Read : You can see Today, Yesterday, Last 7 days, Last 30 days worth of Live sales, pages read, and free downloads.<br /></li><li> Reviews and Stars : Easily see your review counts and stars for each book. You can always know which books need more reviews.<br /></li><li> Auto Finds All Your Books : Once it's installed, just click Import My Books. If you're logged into KDP, it auto finds all books & grabs all stats.<br /></li><li> Makes Book Promos Easier : Every Title is a link to your book. Click to get description, or right-click & copy/paste to give Amazon Link or ASIN.<br /></li><li> Links to Important Kindle URLs : Links to KDP Bookshelf, Reports, Author Central, Best Sellers, New Releases, Manage Devices, & Send to Kindle.<br /></li><li> Best Sellers Rank  : It's not the most important stat, but it sure gives you an idea of where your book is, and it's good to see.<br /></li><li> Never forget to change the price again : Ever change a price to try to get a little sales love and forget to change it back? See the price of every book.<br /></li><li> Even More Stats... KDPulse shows Author/Pen Name, Publish Date, Pages, and every title is a link to the book - click or copy/paste.<br /></li><li> Track Other Books for Sport : Keep track of a favorite author's or competitor's books.Add 'em to the Other Books tab to get all stats except sales.<br /></li><li> Current Book Promotion Sites List : Always on the hunt for book promotion sites? Now you can get an up-to-date list just a click away in KDPulse.<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://kdpulse.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2015/07/Screen-Shot-2015-07-24-at-9.43.30-AM.png" alt="KDPulse 4.2" title="KDPulse 4.2"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="KDPulse 4.2" title="KDPulse 4.2"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>eBook Converter Bundle 3.17</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1465-ebook-converter-bundle.html</link>
<description>Name : eBook Converter Bundle Version : 3.17 OS : Windows Type : Kindle Marketing Tools/ Ebook Marketing Tools Price : $74.95 Homepage : SalePage eBook Converter Bundle is tools decrypt and convert eBooks purchased from Kindle, Nook, Google Play, Sony, Kobo and other online eBook stores in batch with 1-click. it is the most easy-to-use eBook conversion software ever, convert ebook to PDF / ePub / Kindle / Word / Html / Text format with 1-click, it is award-winning and a “must-have” tool for all eBook reader. 100% safe with no adware, spyware, or viruses. Using this straightforward application you can convert your electronic books to various formats and you can also remove their DRM protection</description>
<category>Kindle Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://i1-win.softpedia-static.com/screenshots/eBook-Converter-Bundle_3.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2016 22:01:18 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features support NOOK ebook again, fetch drm key from server. Improve page margin for pdf file. Support all DRM ebooks download in Adobe Digital Editions : Support purchased ebooks in amazon, Google Play,Sony ebook store, Kobo ebook store, Public library ePub PDF acsm files. Remove DRM and Convert eBooks: Integrate both DRM decryption and format conversion features, remove protection and conversion with 1-click, read your purchased ebook in any device anywhere. Auto Import eBook Library: Import Adobe digital editions,Kindle, Barnes &amp; Noble, Nook, Sony books automatically. Decrypt and convert Kindle,Adobe digital editions, NOOK eBook. Support Kindle,Adobe ADE, NOOK DRM protection. Support Google ebook, Kobo eBook, Sony eBook. Support Public library eBook. Convert eBook to PDF, ePub,Kindle, Word, HTML, Text Easy to use, 1-click converter.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/oMfQSsMrbHw?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> support NOOK ebook again, fetch drm key from server.<br /></li><li> Improve page margin for pdf file.<br /></li><li> Support all DRM ebooks download in Adobe Digital Editions : <br /></li><li> Support purchased ebooks in amazon, Google Play,Sony ebook store, Kobo ebook store, Public library ePub PDF acsm files.<br /></li><li> Remove DRM and Convert eBooks: Integrate both DRM decryption and format conversion features, remove protection and conversion with 1-click, read your purchased ebook in any device anywhere.  <br /></li><li> Auto Import eBook Library: Import Adobe digital editions,Kindle, Barnes & Noble, Nook, Sony books automatically.<br /></li><li> Decrypt and convert Kindle,Adobe digital editions, NOOK eBook.<br /></li><li> Support Kindle,Adobe ADE, NOOK DRM protection.<br /></li><li> Support Google ebook, Kobo eBook, Sony eBook.<br /></li><li> Support Public library eBook.<br /></li><li> Convert eBook to PDF, ePub,Kindle, Word, HTML, Text<br /></li><li> Easy to use, 1-click converter.<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://i1-win.softpedia-static.com/screenshots/eBook-Converter-Bundle_3.png" alt="eBook Converter Bundle 3.17" title="eBook Converter Bundle 3.17"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="eBook Converter Bundle 3.17" title="eBook Converter Bundle 3.17"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Content Competition Assassin 1.09 Gold</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1318-content-competition-assassin.html</link>
<description>Name : Content Competition Assassin Version : 1.09 Gold OS : Windows Type : Kindle Marketing Tools Price : $247 Homepage : SalePage Brand New Software finds high search low competition opportunities for your content. Coming Soon! Finally...Make Book Sales Without More Promotion Discover How I Published A Book and Continue to Sell Dozens of Copies Each Month Without Any Promotion…In a Highly Competitive and Super Hot Niche And How You Can Do The Same in Nearly Any Niche! Content Competition Assassin Finds Untapped Publishing Opportunities Ripe For the Taking</description>
<category>Kindle Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://contentcompetitionassassin.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/вЂ№-Content-Competition-Assassin-вЂ”-WordPress.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2015 05:42:36 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Take Out Your Kindle Competition : Easily Discover the Best Places to Sell Your Book Fast....Kindle might be jam packed in the weight loss niche, while iBookstore might be wide open for the taking! Find Popular Niches in Your Genre Fast : Discover hundreds of potential keywords and niches in minutes, instead of days. Find Fiction and Non-fiction Niches fast. Grab Traffic Without Book Marketing Or Promotion : Rank high in the iBookstore, Nook, Smashwords, or multiple other sites by simply using the right keyword in your title and description: The software will show you which keyword to use for easy ranking and more book sales. Get More Buyers for Your Book. : Get your book or content in front of tons of interested prospects without battling endless competition Simple and Easy to Use Three Step Researching Process Finds New Keywords and Niches Easily Shaves off Days of Work And Effort Enables you to find hot, hidden niches quickly! Exports Results to a Simple CSV File for Later Viewing Grabs Traffic Numbers from Google Adwords (Adwords Account Needed – It’s Free) And more! The software compares search volume to exact keyword in title for over 14 different sites and services, including: Kindle Nook IBookstore (Gold Version) Udemy Apple App Store (Gold Version) Google Play Books And more!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/SRViKzYLyAc?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Take Out Your Kindle Competition : Easily Discover the Best Places to Sell Your Book Fast....Kindle might be jam packed in the weight loss niche, while iBookstore might be wide open for the taking!<br /></li><li> Find Popular Niches in Your Genre Fast : Discover hundreds of potential keywords and niches in minutes, instead of days. Find Fiction and Non-fiction Niches fast.<br /></li><li> Grab Traffic Without Book Marketing Or Promotion : Rank high in the iBookstore, Nook, Smashwords, or multiple other sites by simply using the right keyword in your title and description: The software will show you which keyword to use for easy ranking and more book sales.<br /></li><li> Get More Buyers for Your Book. : Get your book or content in front of tons of interested prospects without battling endless competition <br /></li><li> Simple and Easy to Use<br /></li><li> Three Step Researching Process Finds New Keywords and Niches Easily<br /></li><li> Shaves off Days of Work And Effort<br /></li><li> Enables you to find hot, hidden niches quickly!<br /></li><li> Exports Results to a Simple CSV File for Later Viewing<br /></li><li> Grabs Traffic Numbers from Google Adwords (Adwords Account Needed – It’s Free)<br /></li><li> And more!<br /></li></ul><br />The software compares search volume to exact keyword in title for over 14 different sites and services, including:<br /><ul><li> Kindle<br /></li><li> Nook<br /></li><li> IBookstore (Gold Version)<br /></li><li> Udemy<br /></li><li> Apple App Store (Gold Version)<br /></li><li> Google Play Books<br /></li><li> And more!<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://contentcompetitionassassin.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/вЂ№-Content-Competition-Assassin-вЂ”-WordPress.png" alt="Content Competition Assassin 1.09 Gold" title="Content Competition Assassin 1.09 Gold"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Content Competition Assassin 1.09 Gold" title="Content Competition Assassin 1.09 Gold"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Kindle Researcher 1.10</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1151-kindle-researcher.html</link>
<description>Name : Kindle Researcher Version : 1.10 OS : Windows Type : Amazon Kindle Researcher Price : $18 Homepage : SalePage Kindle Researcher – Great Software contains 4 beast Kindle software that will make money on Kind and can Bost your sales in no Time Stunning All-In-One Software Makes Kindle Marketing Easier Than Ever! Kindle Researcher is Great Software contains 4 beast Kindle software that will make money on Kind with easy Kindle Researcher includes Competition Analyzer, The Bestseller Creator, The Fiverr Cash Cow, Long Tail Keyword Harvester, Mass Review Blaster. Kindle Researcher is much better and cheaper then those cited above even considering all their features combined. you able to save lots of time when trying to put a perfect product together! Kindle Researcher is a program with a real practical value that goes way beyond its natural usage.</description>
<category>Kindle Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2015 15:42:26 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Module 1: Competition Analyzer Quickly extract relevant data for your keyword and get a nice clean overview of the competition for your keyword. The data will be displayed in a simple manner and should give you all the information you need in order to make a proper decision for your keyword. View full details of all the competition Quickly sort the competition based on different parameters Use to quickly determine if it’s worth the effort Module 2: The “Bestseller” Creator Use our “Bestseller” module to turn your eBook into a winner each and every time. In this module we’ll give you step-by-step guidance to creating a Bestseller. Out neat looking design combined with powerful algorithms will leave no stones unturned and will give you all the details you need to get a fully optimized eBook for Kindle. We’ve also created a live search function, which makes you able to find relevant words on the fly without leaving the software. Calculate the right price for you eBook Determine if your title and description is correctly optimized Get instant optimized words suggestions Module 3: The Fiverr Cash Cow you’ll be able to create a nice looking report with all your gathered information along with all the harvested long tail keywords from the harvester module. These reports will easily sell on Fiverr and takes no time for you to create. You’ll be able to customize the entire design so it suites your needs. Easily customize the look and feel of your report Include or exclude various data Export to html-file, ready to sell on Fiverr or any place you please. Module 4: Long Tail Keyword Harvester One click and you’ll know all the important phrases and keywords to include in your description and title. These words are proven to be important in the Kindle ranking process and not using these could have a negative influence. 1 button click Find all the relevant words and must have phrases Quickly sort them based on their occurrence or their length Module 5 (OTO): Mass Review Blaster This module will find all revious reviewers of your keyword, and gather relevant information such as e-mail, name, country and their websites! This will give you a HUGE advantage, as you’ll be able to ask these people to review you eBook! Scrape reviewers for any given keyword Gather their name, location, e-mail and website Filter and export them to a separate file to save on your computer (or sell)</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/xpYl_XKqFro?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br />Module 1: Competition Analyzer<br />Quickly extract relevant data for your keyword and get a nice clean overview of the competition for your keyword. The data will be displayed in a simple manner and should give you all the information you need in order to make a proper decision for your keyword.<br /><ul><li> View full details of all the competition<br /></li><li> Quickly sort the competition based on different parameters<br /></li><li> Use to quickly determine if it’s worth the effort<br /></li></ul><br />Module 2: The “Bestseller” Creator<br />Use our “Bestseller” module to turn your eBook into a winner each and every time. In this module we’ll give you step-by-step guidance to creating a Bestseller. Out neat looking design combined with powerful algorithms will leave no stones unturned and will give you all the details you need to get a fully optimized eBook for Kindle. We’ve also created a live search function, which makes you able to find relevant words on the fly without leaving the software.<br /><ul><li> Calculate the right price for you eBook<br /></li><li> Determine if your title and description is correctly optimized<br /></li><li> Get instant optimized words suggestions<br /></li></ul><br />Module 3: The Fiverr Cash Cow<br />you’ll be able to create a nice looking report with all your gathered information along with all the harvested long tail keywords from the harvester module. These reports will easily sell on Fiverr and takes no time for you to create. You’ll be able to customize the entire design so it suites your needs.<br /><ul><li> Easily customize the look and feel of your report<br /></li><li> Include or exclude various data<br /></li><li> Export to html-file, ready to sell on Fiverr or any place you please.<br /></li></ul><br />Module 4: Long Tail Keyword Harvester<br />One click and you’ll know all the important phrases and keywords to include in your description and title. These words are proven to be important in the Kindle ranking process and not using these could have a negative influence.<br /><ul><li> 1 button click<br /></li><li> Find all the relevant words and must have phrases<br /></li><li> Quickly sort them based on their occurrence or their length<br /></li></ul><br />Module 5 (OTO): Mass Review Blaster<br />This module will find all revious reviewers of your keyword, and gather relevant information such as e-mail, name, country and their websites! This will give you a HUGE advantage, as you’ll be able to ask these people to review you eBook!<br /><ul><li> Scrape reviewers for any given keyword<br /></li><li> Gather their name, location, e-mail and website<br /></li><li> Filter and export them to a separate file to save on your computer (or sell)	<br /></li></ul><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Kindle Researcher 1.10" title="Kindle Researcher 1.10"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>