<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Dailymotion Marketing - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Dailymotion Marketing - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>Daimo Demon 1.1</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1479-daimo-demon.html</link>
<description>Name : Daimo Demon – The Ultimate Dailymotion Bot Version : 1.1 OS : Windows Type : Dailymotion Marketing Bot Price : $299 Homepage : SalePage Basically, by using this Dailymotion tool, it will help to increase the number of hits to your website, increase visits to your blog, drive traffic to your online marketing methods. This Dailymotion bot is easy to use and it is also packed full of features that you will undoubtedly find to be useful. However, the key features are as follows. First, you are able to run multiple accounts via this bot and that does make life so much easier. However, if you do not have multiple accounts, then the bot also helps with this part as it allows you to create bulk fake accounts, which is usually a time consuming process. Next, it has several features to do with the videos themselves. You can use it as a video scraper whereby it scrapes different videos according to their keywords, the channels that they are on, as well as any playlists. With the video, it also allows you to bulk upload them to your accounts with just a click of a few buttons. There are a number of other features to be aware of with this bot that will also just make the process work more smoothly. For example, it will allow you to post mass comments at the same time, it will solve those annoying captchas, it works with proxies, you can check your various accounts and their status, and finally it uses multi-threading to speed up the entire process. Basically, by using this Dailymotion tool, it will help to increase the number of hits to your website, increase visits to your blog, drive traffic to your online marketing methods. Also, if you are running a pay per install or CPA offer, then this can boost figures and ultimately help you to earn more money.</description>
<category>Dailymotion Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://smmbots.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/07/daimo3.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2016 01:39:52 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Multi Account Management: Add Unlimited Accounts Support Proxies: User/Pass Authentication, IP authentication Bypass API: Acts Like A Browser User Fully Multi-Threaded Built In Proxy Checker Spintax Compatible: For Use With Poster Captcha Support: De-Captcher, DeathByCaptcha Random Delay Feature</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/ITlypAzHG1w?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Multi Account Management: Add Unlimited Accounts<br /></li><li> Support Proxies: User/Pass Authentication, IP authentication<br /></li><li> Bypass API: Acts Like A Browser User<br /></li><li> Fully Multi-Threaded<br /></li><li> Built In Proxy Checker<br /></li><li> Spintax Compatible: For Use With Poster<br /></li><li> Captcha Support: De-Captcher, DeathByCaptcha<br /></li><li> Random Delay Feature<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://smmbots.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/07/daimo3.png" alt="Daimo Demon 1.1" title="Daimo Demon 1.1"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Daimo Demon 1.1" title="Daimo Demon 1.1"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>