<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>WSO - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>WSO - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>Audience Explosion 2.0 (2016) – By Bill Guthrie</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1654-audience-explosion-20.html</link>
<description>Name : Audience Explosion 2.0 (2016) – By Bill Guthrie IM Type : Instagram Marketing Course Price : $$147 Homepage : SalePage A Complete System for Driving Massive Traffic, Generating Quick Paydays, and Building Huge Email Lists with Instagram in 2016 and Beyond! Audience Explosion 2.0 is video-based training, consisting of 7 in-depth modules that you can watch on your smartphone, tablet or computer. In fact, you will be amazed at your experience with this video course... Because Ryan will TAKE YOU INSIDE HIS iPHONE AS HE SHOWS YOU EVERYTHING YOU NEED TO QUICKLY SUCCEED WITH INSTAGRAM! We&#039;ve ensured that this system is perfect for marketers of all experience levels. And with version 2.0, we&#039;ve rebuilt our entire set of processes based on the actual student feedback we&#039;ve received over the last several months. We understand that starting something new, especially something as potentially foreign as Instagram, can be a bit nerve-wracking. That&#039;s why we have revamped everything and restructured the training...to guarantee that you can be up and running in no time flat!</description>
<category>WSO</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2016 01:49:05 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Details Module 1: Getting To Know Instagram We&#039;re betting you&#039;re completely new to Instagram, so we&#039;re going to spend this module getting you familiar with this powerful social.comwork. Instagram overview for those who don&#039;t know a thing about it The depth and breadth of Instagram, so you can see the various ways to leverage it How to position your current business on Instagram How to start a brand new business from from within Instagram (no website required) Finding your niche and your target audience on Instagram (they&#039;re there, we promise!) Reverse engineering authority accounts so you can see what success looks like Module 2: Creating an Optimized Instagram Account Anyone with a mobile phone or tablet can create an Instagram account...but marketers need to set their accounts up in a special way to maximize their opportunities. Optimizing your account for free traffic and lots of clicks Brainstorming your username Deciding on your username and account name How to download the Instagram app and create your account Writing the perfect account bio (that gets you traffic) Setting up your profile pic and verifying your new account Module 3: Flooding Your Account With Content You can have a huge, successful Instagram account without ever creating a single unique image. We recommend some unique content from time to time, so that others will have your content to share too :) The different types of content that work on Instagram Why it&#039;s essential that you &quot;BE AN ACCOUNT WORTH FOLLOWING&quot; The Curation Blueprint for Instagram and how to leverage the work of others The apps that make reposting to Instagram each (for iOS and Android) Kicking it up a notch: Working from your computer for massive content curation Organizing your content to make your life easier Original content and how to create it quickly Module 4: Calls to Action That Achieve Your Goals Every time you post, you must have a purpose...and an ACTION you want your followers to take. The purpose and opportunity of great Calls to Action Calls to Action for account growth Calls to Action for getting traffic How to get comments on your posts How to attribute your curated content (be a good citizen of Instagram) Our sneaky Location Hack The &quot;Double Post&quot; strategy that generates traffic spikes PLUS: Our never-before-seen Calls to Action Swipe File (see below for details) Module 5: Posting to Instagram Do&#039;s and Don&#039;t&#039;s Yes, there is actually a WRONG WAY of posting to Instagram, at least for marketers. We&#039;ll show you how to do it correctly in this module. How to post to Instagram How to add your Calls to Action How to add Tags and Emojis Shortcuts we use to speed up the posting process The power of Hashtags: How to find and choose the right ones, and how to post them for maximum benefit (free traffic) The best times to post for increased post views and engagement How to leverage &quot;The Cloud&quot; for posting Module 6: Instagram Growth Hacks Revealed You&#039;re on your way, but you need to grow your account! You need followers, lots of them, and this is our speciality! Here we dig into: Ryan&#039;s Instagram story. Yes, he was once just like you! How to tap people on the shoulder for new follower growth How content curation and being cool will get you new followers Organic growth through account optimization and hashtags Running contests that get your account in the spotlight The power of strategic alliances -- your &quot;competition&quot; becomes your new best friends PLUS: Exclusive Bonus Training Session (see below for details) Module 7: M.comizing Your Instagram Traffic Your biggest goal is getting the click. But what happens next? Here we reveal some critical tactics you must use so you won&#039;t waste all the good stuff you&#039;re doing in Instagram! How Calls to Action can be wasted if you don&#039;t get THIS right The importance of being mobile-friendly The thing you should do the least can make or break your goals PLUS...this is where will put our ongoing Case Studies so you can see how other authority accounts leverage Instagram: Ecommerce and Instagram List Building and Instagram Affiliate Marketing and Instagram Blogging and Instagram App Sales and Instagram Books Sales and Instagram Product Sales and Instagram CPA Marketing and Instagram Brick-and-Mortar and Instagram</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/2JzZ_4YHCbs?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Details</h3><br /><br />Module 1: Getting To Know Instagram<br />We're betting you're completely new to Instagram, so we're going to spend this module getting you familiar with this powerful social.comwork.<br /><br />Instagram overview for those who don't know a thing about it<br />The depth and breadth of Instagram, so you can see the various ways to leverage it<br />How to position your current business on Instagram<br />How to start a brand new business from from within Instagram (no website required)<br />Finding your niche and your target audience on Instagram (they're there, we promise!)<br />Reverse engineering authority accounts so you can see what success looks like<br />Module 2: Creating an Optimized Instagram Account<br />Anyone with a mobile phone or tablet can create an Instagram account...but marketers need to set their accounts up in a special way to maximize their opportunities.<br /><br />Optimizing your account for free traffic and lots of clicks<br />Brainstorming your username<br />Deciding on your username and account name<br />How to download the Instagram app and create your account<br />Writing the perfect account bio (that gets you traffic)<br />Setting up your profile pic and verifying your new account<br />Module 3: Flooding Your Account With Content<br />You can have a huge, successful Instagram account without ever creating a single unique image. We recommend some unique content from time to time, so that others will have your content to share too :)<br /><br />The different types of content that work on Instagram<br />Why it's essential that you "BE AN ACCOUNT WORTH FOLLOWING"<br />The Curation Blueprint for Instagram and how to leverage the work of others<br />The apps that make reposting to Instagram each (for iOS and Android)<br />Kicking it up a notch: Working from your computer for massive content curation<br />Organizing your content to make your life easier<br />Original content and how to create it quickly<br />Module 4: Calls to Action That Achieve Your Goals<br />Every time you post, you must have a purpose...and an ACTION you want your followers to take.<br /><br />The purpose and opportunity of great Calls to Action<br />Calls to Action for account growth<br />Calls to Action for getting traffic<br />How to get comments on your posts<br />How to attribute your curated content (be a good citizen of Instagram)<br />Our sneaky Location Hack<br />The "Double Post" strategy that generates traffic spikes<br />PLUS: Our never-before-seen Calls to Action Swipe File (see below for details)<br />Module 5: Posting to Instagram Do's and Don't's<br />Yes, there is actually a WRONG WAY of posting to Instagram, at least for marketers. We'll show you how to do it correctly in this module.<br /><br />How to post to Instagram<br />How to add your Calls to Action<br />How to add Tags and Emojis<br />Shortcuts we use to speed up the posting process<br />The power of Hashtags: How to find and choose the right ones, and how to post them for maximum benefit (free traffic)<br />The best times to post for increased post views and engagement<br />How to leverage "The Cloud" for posting<br />Module 6: Instagram Growth Hacks Revealed<br />You're on your way, but you need to grow your account! You need followers, lots of them, and this is our speciality! Here we dig into:<br /><br />Ryan's Instagram story. Yes, he was once just like you!<br />How to tap people on the shoulder for new follower growth<br />How content curation and being cool will get you new followers<br />Organic growth through account optimization and hashtags<br />Running contests that get your account in the spotlight<br />The power of strategic alliances -- your "competition" becomes your new best friends<br />PLUS: Exclusive Bonus Training Session (see below for details)<br />Module 7: M.comizing Your Instagram Traffic<br />Your biggest goal is getting the click. But what happens next? Here we reveal some critical tactics you must use so you won't waste all the good stuff you're doing in Instagram!<br /><br />How Calls to Action can be wasted if you don't get THIS right<br />The importance of being mobile-friendly<br />The thing you should do the least can make or break your goals<br />PLUS...this is where will put our ongoing Case Studies so you can see how other authority accounts leverage Instagram:<br />Ecommerce and Instagram<br />List Building and Instagram<br />Affiliate Marketing and Instagram<br />Blogging and Instagram<br />App Sales and Instagram<br />Books Sales and Instagram<br />Product Sales and Instagram<br />CPA Marketing and Instagram<br />Brick-and-Mortar and Instagram<br /><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Audience Explosion 2.0 (2016) – By Bill Guthrie" title="Audience Explosion 2.0 (2016) – By Bill Guthrie"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Fast Traffic Secrets 2.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1198-fast-traffic-secrets.html</link>
<description>Name : Fast Traffic Secrets 2.0 IM Type : Traffic Course Price : $4 Homepage : SalePage Phil Steptoe&#039;s new report is called Fast traffic Secrets and contains 10 sources for free, or very cheap, traffic. I have purchased several traffic WSOs recently and reviewed a few of them on our website. When I received my review copy from Phil I had expected a short PDF file showing me around a number of social media sites. However what Phil has written is very different and you could say you are getting 10 WSOs not one with this report!</description>
<category>WSO</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2015 01:50:22 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>I have been in the Inte.com Marketing world for 6 years and I am not using one of these methods! Neither have I seen these methods talked about anywhere else. Phil even includes a strategy for YouTube traffic that I have not used until today and a way to get free traffic from CNN. So what are you going to get with Phil&#039;s Fast traffic Secrets WSO? It&#039;s Simple. A well written, and in places funny, 88 page PDF file detailing each method with step by step instructions on how to set up them up. You also get 3 bonuses which are great to help you write copy and ads and help convert the traffic once you have created it. The biggest problem with this WSO is working out which methods to try first? Phil - thank you and congratulations on a 1st class and highly original WSO. I highly recommend everyone grabs a copy of your report and clears a few hours in their diary to start implementing what you show them. outofthebox One of Phil&#039;s graphics in his report really sums up this WSO for me and reminds me of a fantastic Quote. &quot;There are people that think out of the box, people who think in the box and people who don&#039;t know a box exists&quot;. Phil&#039;s report is definitely out of the box.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/nd6tmCC4yMk?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br />I have been in the Inte.com Marketing world for 6 years and I am not using one of these methods! Neither have I seen these methods talked about anywhere else. Phil even includes a strategy for YouTube traffic that I have not used until today and a way to get free traffic from CNN.<br /><br />So what are you going to get with Phil's Fast traffic Secrets WSO? It's Simple. A well written, and in places funny, 88 page PDF file detailing each method with step by step instructions on how to set up them up. You also get 3 bonuses which are great to help you write copy and ads and help convert the traffic once you have created it.<br /><br />The biggest problem with this WSO is working out which methods to try first? Phil - thank you and congratulations on a 1st class and highly original WSO. I highly recommend everyone grabs a copy of your report and clears a few hours in their diary to start implementing what you show them.<br /><br />outofthebox One of Phil's graphics in his report really sums up this WSO for me and reminds me of a fantastic Quote. "There are people that think out of the box, people who think in the box and people who don't know a box exists". Phil's report is definitely out of the box.<br /><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Fast Traffic Secrets 2.0" title="Fast Traffic Secrets 2.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>