<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>LSI Keyword Tools - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>LSI Keyword Tools - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>Power LSI Finder 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4125-power-lsi-finder.html</link>
<description>Name : Power LSI Finder Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : LSI Keyword Tool Price : $200 Homepage : SalePage Power LSI Finder is a desktop application that allows users to enter their niches keywords and Power LSI Finder will scrape Google in the background finding all the websites (up to 500 deep) that rank for that keyword. Once these websites (Google results) have been scraped it will crawl them all extracting their article content. Once its collected all this information it will aggregate all found LSIs from single 1 word LSIs to long tail 4 word LSIs. It not only does this for the content of all these websites it does it for the headers (h1 through to h6), keywords, title and description also. This is an extremely powerful keyword tool.</description>
<category>LSI Keyword Tools</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 06:12:42 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features SEO has amazing ROI (return on investment), if you write a fantastic indepth article it can bring you traffic for years. However many SEO novices neglect to do indepth research and find all the possible LSIs for their primary keywords. If those LSIs are not present then Google can not be sure you&#039;ve covered the topic indepth or at least to the same level as your competitors. This tool s allows you to find these gems and make use of them easily. You don&#039;t need to be technical at all you just enter your keyword and click start.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/AXya9S3w9RQ?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> SEO has amazing ROI (return on investment), if you write a fantastic indepth article it can bring you traffic for years. However many SEO novices neglect to do indepth research and find all the possible LSIs for their primary keywords. If those LSIs are not present then Google can not be sure you've covered the topic indepth or at least to the same level as your competitors. This tool s allows you to find these gems and make use of them easily. You don't need to be technical at all you just enter your keyword and click start.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Power LSI Finder 1.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Ultimate Keyword Hunter 1.2.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1739-ultimate-keyword-hunter.html</link>
<description>Name : Ultimate Keyword Hunter Version : 1.2.0 OS : Windows Type : LSI Keyword Tools Price : $0 Homepage : SalePage Ultimate Keyword Hunter is a simple, free LSI keywords research tool but extremely powerful with it! Check it out!</description>
<category>LSI Keyword Tools</category>
<enclosure url="http://ultimatekeywordhunter.com/images/infographics.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2016 08:37:14 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Find perfect words based on Google&#039;s top sites content Configure number of Google&#039;s Top Pages to analyze Configure target list of sites to analyze Configure list of stop words Configure words count in theme phrases Real-time validation of your article towards chosen theme words Advanced word/phrases list sorting and filtering Load words/phrases list from/to csv file Captcha basic handling added - NEW! Any Language Keywords Support - NEW! Morpho word analisys (stemming) Extended search engines lists supported</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/T5GqLygUfzw?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Find perfect words based on Google's top sites content<br /></li><li> Configure number of Google's Top Pages to analyze<br /></li><li> Configure target list of sites to analyze<br /></li><li> Configure list of stop words<br /></li><li> Configure words count in theme phrases<br /></li><li> Real-time validation of your article towards chosen theme words<br /></li><li> Advanced word/phrases list sorting and filtering<br /></li><li> Load words/phrases list from/to csv file<br /></li><li> Captcha basic handling added - NEW!<br /></li><li> Any Language Keywords Support - NEW!<br /></li><li> Morpho word analisys (stemming)<br /></li><li> Extended search engines lists supported<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://ultimatekeywordhunter.com/images/infographics.jpg" alt="Ultimate Keyword Hunter 1.2.0" title="Ultimate Keyword Hunter 1.2.0"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Ultimate Keyword Hunter 1.2.0" title="Ultimate Keyword Hunter 1.2.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Keyword G.comics 1.0.0.13</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1701-keyword-g.comics.html</link>
<description>Name : Keyword G.comics Version : 1.0.0.13 OS : Windows Type : LSI Research Tools Price : $97 Homepage : SalePage Keyword G.comics has SERP Analayses to build up your keyword theme and LSI keyword discovery from Google to create complete Authority Website Keyword Blueprints. SEO Methods That Were Once Safe Now Trigger Penalties! Optimizing Your Content Based On Keywords Will Now Get You Penalized By Google! Latent Semantic Indexing (LSI) is a part of Google’s algorithm that will put words into a matrix for analysis in order to identify semantically related terms. Google will link related words together by analysing how certain keywords on webpages appear in combination with other related keywords, it will then correlate them to a particular concept or theme. The example image below shows how the word Chocolate can be semantically related to different themes. LSI is the reason why Google is smart enough to see that David Beckham plays football; and that Obama is related to politics and the economy. LSI also allows Google to better decipher webpages to provide more relevant search results with higher quality content - free from keyword stuffing and spam. And If You Want To Rank On Page 1 For Your Keywords Then Using LSI keywords Is A Must Finding out what your keyword theme and LSI keywords are is actually quite simple. But there’s always been a slight problem. There has never really been an easy or time effective way to do this. That was until we came up with an automated solution.</description>
<category>LSI Keyword Tools</category>
<enclosure url="https://cdn3.f-cdn.com/contestentries/68767/10388086/5336efb8ada0d_thumb900.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/kwg/2scripts.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/kwg/10.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2016 00:07:48 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/NAJogiF5JpM?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><img src="https://cdn3.f-cdn.com/contestentries/68767/10388086/5336efb8ada0d_thumb900.jpg" alt="Keyword G.comics 1.0.0.13" title="Keyword G.comics 1.0.0.13"  /><br /><img src="https://s3.amazonaws.com/kwg/2scripts.png" alt="Keyword G.comics 1.0.0.13" title="Keyword G.comics 1.0.0.13"  /><br /><img src="https://s3.amazonaws.com/kwg/10.png" alt="Keyword G.comics 1.0.0.13" title="Keyword G.comics 1.0.0.13"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Keyword G.comics 1.0.0.13" title="Keyword G.comics 1.0.0.13"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>LSI Demon 1.5</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1639-lsi-demon.html</link>
<description>Name : LSI Demon Version : 1.5 OS : Windows Type : Keyword Research Tools Price : $67 Homepage : SalePage LSI Demon is a unique new software which is designed to generate keyword lists with a unique approach which will explore highly relevant and profitable keywords in your niche. LSI Demon isn’t just a single feature tool, it’s a combination of many keyword research features in one, designed with full SEO automation in mind. We have made it very intuitive, fully integrated with Keywords Demon &amp; newbie friendly. LSI Demon will do the hard work by absolutely automating the data collection process on different sources &amp; make a multi-tier keyword hierarchy for your research niche. The software will automatically research DEEP into a niche by digging into the LSI keyword relation between phrases to uncover the best keywords the search engines LOVE. There is NO other keyword research tool that is doing this. This’s a UNIQUE approach to find the most PROFITABLE keywords with zero efforts from the user’s end.</description>
<category>LSI Keyword Tools</category>
<enclosure url="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/WVaC3kF1dic/hqdefault.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2016 15:51:16 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Data from multiple sources to find the best, higly relevant and most profitable keywords you’d otherwise NEVER find with other software… Fully automates the whole data collection process and even does the DEEP niche research by digging into the LSI relationship between keywords… Generates a Keyword Hierarchy 2 tiers under your main keyword for content perfection using the best relevant keywords based on LSI… “One-Click” Solution for getting the best (already researched) keywords and One-Click to see all the important keyword data from many different sources… Super intuitive, easy to use, newbie friendly software… Results without any Specialized SEO knowledge or technical skills required !</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/WVaC3kF1dic?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Data from multiple sources to find the best, higly relevant and most profitable keywords you’d otherwise NEVER find with other software…<br /></li><li> Fully automates the whole data collection process and even does the DEEP niche research by digging into the LSI relationship between keywords…<br /></li><li> Generates a Keyword Hierarchy 2 tiers under your main keyword for content perfection using the best relevant keywords based on LSI…<br /></li><li> “One-Click” Solution for getting the best (already researched) keywords and One-Click to see all the important keyword data from many different sources…<br /></li><li> Super intuitive, easy to use, newbie friendly software… Results without any Specialized SEO knowledge or technical skills required !<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/WVaC3kF1dic/hqdefault.jpg" alt="LSI Demon 1.5" title="LSI Demon 1.5"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="LSI Demon 1.5" title="LSI Demon 1.5"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Market Spy 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1641-market-spy.html</link>
<description>Name : Market Spy Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Keyword Research Tools Price : $47 Homepage : SalePage Market SPY is the final check point to confirm a winner, it will analyze many SEO factors such as onpage, offpage, social signal and backlink pointing to the page, giving you the best &amp; accurate keyword result for maximum profits. &quot;When a niche passing through LSI Demon to Keywords Demon and finally passed Market SPY, it is not possible to not make money with the keyword.&quot;</description>
<category>LSI Keyword Tools</category>
<enclosure url="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/Z7sDucS2E-A/hqdefault.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2016 13:29:17 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Research top 10 in google and youtube and find out the ranking difficulty by checking their backlinks and social proof. Input your own url list for analysis. This is very useful if you have a url list from another software, of you only want to find out the competition of a particular youtube video or website in G&#039;s top 10, and out rank them HANDS DOWN ! Scrape a pages/post of your own site or a competitor&#039;s site and analyze the competition&#039;s strength ... the onpage SEO, offpage SEO, and social.comwork . Scrape a list of pages that have a backlink pointing to your site or a competitor&#039;s site for onpage/offpage/social optimize</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/Z7sDucS2E-A?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Research top 10 in google and youtube and find out the ranking difficulty by checking their backlinks and social proof.<br /></li><li> Input your own url list for analysis. This is very useful if you have a url list from another software, of you only want to find out the competition of a particular youtube video or website in G's top 10, and out rank them HANDS DOWN !<br /></li><li> Scrape a pages/post of your own site or a competitor's site and analyze the competition's strength ... the onpage SEO, offpage SEO, and social.comwork .<br /></li><li> Scrape a list of pages that have a backlink pointing to your site or a competitor's site for onpage/offpage/social optimize<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/Z7sDucS2E-A/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Market Spy 1.0" title="Market Spy 1.0"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Market Spy 1.0" title="Market Spy 1.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>