<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Backlinks Indexers - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Backlinks Indexers - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>GSA SEO Indexer 2.19</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1030-gsa-seo-indexer.html</link>
<description>Along with GSA SEO Indexer you will get your webpage into the major search engines like yahoo or Bing within minutes where you previously had to wait days or perhaps several weeks. The method is very popular to SEO experts and works by publishing your website to a lot whois and statistics websites and search engines by itself, resulting in many backlinks.</description>
<category>Backlinks Indexers</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-05/1431542544_1zf7i83.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-05/1431542806_gsa-ser-extension.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-05/1431542756_gsa-trial-reset.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2018 23:01:08 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Even though these created backlinks are just dynamic generally (they aren&#039;t visible to someone who browses that webpage), you are going to still take advantage of this submission type since your website will be seen in all type of log files as well as databases that get checked as well by search engines. Our own software can also submit a number of URLs/Domains at the same time when you have several to index. There are more than 1400 websites where your website can be posted with our software (50 in demo version) all happening in a short time.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[Even though these created backlinks are just dynamic generally (they aren't visible to someone who browses that webpage), you are going to still take advantage of this submission type since your website will be seen in all type of log files as well as databases that get checked as well by search engines.<br><br>Our own software can also submit a number of URLs/Domains at the same time when you have several to index. There are more than 1400 websites where your website can be posted with our software (50 in demo version) all happening in a short time.<br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="GSA SEO Indexer 2.19"></div><br><div class="quote"><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Magic Indexer 1.7</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2155-magic-indexer.html</link>
<description>Name : Magic Indexer Version : 1.7 OS : Windows Type : BackLink Index Price : $67 Homepage : SalePage Are You Tired of Not Getting Your Links Indexed? ?Watch this video to discover Powerful Indexing method that can index up to 70% - 80% of all links submitted in a matter of minutes! Do you want to start generating Massive amounts of traffic? We&#039;re talking about ranking on Page 1 of both Google &amp;amp; YouTube for keywords with a lot of competition and thousands of monthly searches! This will easily 10x the amount of income you&#039;ll be able to generate with Traffic Xtractor alone!</description>
<category>Backlinks Indexers</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2017 04:18:46 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Rank for more search terms faster than ever… in some cases, within MINUTES! Unlock the advanced features inside Traffic Xtractor to rank for even more competitive search terms… That means MORE traffic and MORE money in your pocket! Keep your websites and videos ranking longer… The longer you rank, the more money you’ll make for each keyword…</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/4d5AbFhD20U?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Rank for more search terms faster than ever… in some cases, within MINUTES!<br></li><li> Unlock the advanced features inside Traffic Xtractor to rank for even more competitive search terms… That means MORE traffic and MORE money in your pocket!<br></li><li> Keep your websites and videos ranking longer… The longer you rank, the more money you’ll make for each keyword…<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Magic Indexer 1.7"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>SEO Ping Master 1.51 Pro</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1454-seo-ping-master.html</link>
<description>Name : SEO Ping Master Version : 1.51 Pro OS : Windows Type : Backlink index Tools Price : $59 Homepage : SalePage SEO Ping Master is the ultimate tool that every SEO specialist don&#039;t want to give you! ... ping and submit your site to more than 12800 services (more sites coming soon)</description>
<category>Backlinks Indexers</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.maxwebtraffic.com/images/SEO_Ping_Master-scn_1.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2016 13:30:31 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features ping and submit your site to more than 12800 services (more sites coming soon) the db contains: search engines / EDU &amp; GOV sites / social media &amp; bookmarking sites / general websites automatic db updates automatic software updates multithreading (up to 20 thread) (*) fully portable: to use the software just unzip the archive and execute the exe! report created automatically (csv format) (*) by default the software use 4 threads. To increment the threads add this parameter in the file SEO_Ping_Master.ini thread_max=xx where xx is the number of threads (max 20!) Requirements: - Framework .COM 3.5 ---- WHAT IS A PING? ---- Ping services notify search engines (like Google, Bing, Yahoo), blog and RSS directories that your site / blog has been updated. This increase the indexing speed of your site. ---- THIS SOFTWARE CREATE ALSO BACKLINKS? ---- Yes, some services present in the db create also a backlink to your site. ---- HOW MUCH I MUST WAIT BEFORE I SEE SOME BENEFIT? ---- It&#039;s not simple to reply to this question :) some sites have reported an increment in traffic after some weeks, others after a month. ScreenShot</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/vn0XO5-IaYM?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> ping and submit your site to more than 12800 services (more sites coming soon)<br /></li><li> the db contains: search engines / EDU & GOV sites / social media & bookmarking sites / general websites<br /></li><li> automatic db updates<br /></li><li> automatic software updates<br /></li><li> multithreading (up to 20 thread) (*)<br /></li><li> fully portable: to use the software just unzip the archive and execute the exe!<br /></li><li> report created automatically (csv format)<br /></li></ul><br /><br /><span style="color:#CC0000">(*) by default the software use 4 threads. To increment the threads add this parameter in the file SEO_Ping_Master.ini<br />thread_max=xx<br />where xx is the number of threads (max 20!)</span><br /><br /><b>Requirements:</b><br />- Framework .COM 3.5<br /><br /><b>---- WHAT IS A PING? ----</b><br />Ping services notify search engines (like Google, Bing, Yahoo), blog and RSS directories that your site / blog has been updated.<br />This increase the indexing speed of your site.<br /><br /><b>---- THIS SOFTWARE CREATE ALSO BACKLINKS? ----</b><br />Yes, some services present in the db create also a backlink to your site.<br /><br /><b>---- HOW MUCH I MUST WAIT BEFORE I SEE SOME BENEFIT? ----</b><br />It's not simple to reply to this question :) some sites have reported an increment in traffic after some weeks, others after a month.<br /><br /><h3>ScreenShot</h3><br /><img src="http://www.maxwebtraffic.com/images/SEO_Ping_Master-scn_1.png" alt="SEO Ping Master 1.51 Pro" title="SEO Ping Master 1.51 Pro"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="SEO Ping Master 1.51 Pro" title="SEO Ping Master 1.51 Pro"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>SEONeos Elite 1.2.50</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1722-seoneos.html</link>
<description>Name : SEONeos Version : Elite 1.2.50 OS : Windows Type : Link Building Tools Price : $75 Homepage : SalePage SEONeos is a stop solution for your customers to get their websites and blogs Penguin and Panda penalty fixes and start getting ranked and traffic from Google once again! It analyzes both Off-page and On-page SEO for your website and tells you exactly what you need to do to get the best SERP rankings and protection from the dreaded Panda and Penguin updates. Google’s Penguin and Panda algorithm update affected millions of websites and they still are. The problem is that most people don’t know what they’re doing wrong and how to fix the penalties and start getting indexed again and start getting organic traffic again. That’s exactly what SEONeos helps fix automatically. SEONeos is a desktop app that helps your customer find out all the issues they have on their on-page and off-page SEO and automatically gets those problems fixes.</description>
<category>Backlinks Indexers</category>
<enclosure url="http://seoneos.in/Content/img1/img_seoneos/01.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2016 21:49:23 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features [+] Deep On-page &amp;amp; Off page analysis: SEONeos conducts an audit of both your own website, and also the backlinks that point to you from outside your site, inspecting EVERY FACTOR that’s important to your rankings. [+] 40+ Checks On your webpages: SEONeos checks for everything that could potentially be dragging your rankings down. Analyzing more than 40 different factors. Making sure nothing that affects your website escapes unchecked. [+] 30+ Backlinks Checks: Bad backlinks get a site deranked in no time at all, and there’s no way to detect them. Until now, that is. SEONeos will look at all your backlinks and subject to over 30 quality check parameters, making sure that no bad backlink survives. [+] Automatic Disavow file for bad backlinks: Google lets you escape the penalty of bad-backlinks by disavowing them. Only SEONeos detects all your bad backlinks on 100% auto, and generates a Google compatible Disavow file that you can submit to Google and avoid Penguin penalty with one click. [+] Deep-Scan Site Analysis Report: SEONeos subjects your webpages to the most intensive examination and gives you a very comprehensive report that tells you about every single thing that you need to improve on the site to make Google love it more. [+] Works On Any Website: SEONeos works on any website. Whether it’s a Wordpress blog, an e-commerce website, a corporate site, or an online news magazine. Just type the URL, and unleash it. [+] Simple &amp;amp; Ultra- Fast: SEONeos is so easy to use that even newbies will be able to use it effectively. No need to be a SEO wizard, no need to know mumbo-jumbo. It’s all calibrated already. And our multi-threaded technology makes all that analysis a thing of seconds!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/fZvwRZa2OSI?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br>[+] Deep On-page &amp; Off page analysis:<br>SEONeos conducts an audit of both your own website, and also the backlinks that point to you from outside your site, inspecting EVERY FACTOR that’s important to your rankings.<br>[+] 40+ Checks On your webpages:<br>SEONeos checks for everything that could potentially be dragging your rankings down. Analyzing more than 40 different factors. Making sure nothing that affects your website escapes unchecked.<br>[+] 30+ Backlinks Checks:<br>Bad backlinks get a site deranked in no time at all, and there’s no way to detect them. Until now, that is. SEONeos will look at all your backlinks and subject to over 30 quality check parameters, making sure that no bad backlink survives.<br>[+] Automatic Disavow file for bad backlinks:<br>Google lets you escape the penalty of bad-backlinks by disavowing them. Only SEONeos detects all your bad backlinks on 100% auto, and generates a Google compatible Disavow file that you can submit to Google and avoid Penguin penalty with one click.<br>[+] Deep-Scan Site Analysis Report:<br>SEONeos subjects your webpages to the most intensive examination and gives you a very comprehensive report that tells you about every single thing that you need to improve on the site to make Google love it more.<br>[+] Works On Any Website:<br>SEONeos works on any website. Whether it’s a Wordpress blog, an e-commerce website, a corporate site, or an online news magazine. Just type the URL, and unleash it.<br>[+] Simple &amp; Ultra- Fast:<br>SEONeos is so easy to use that even newbies will be able to use it effectively. No need to be a SEO wizard, no need to know mumbo-jumbo. It’s all calibrated already. And our multi-threaded technology makes all that analysis a thing of seconds!<br><br><img src="http://seoneos.in/Content/img1/img_seoneos/01.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="SEONeos Elite 1.2.50"><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Power Indexer Pro 3.0.1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1662-power-indexer-pro.html</link>
<description>Name : Power Indexer Pro Version : 3.0.1.0 OS : Windows Type : Index Tools Price : $37 Homepage : SalePage Power Indexer Pro Will Index Your Links In A Single Click!! Stage 1 : Pings your urls to rpc ping sites Stage 2: Submits your urls to meta stat sites</description>
<category>Backlinks Indexers</category>
<enclosure url="http://powerindexpro.com/images/act.gif" type="image/gif" />
<enclosure url="https://s1.bukalapak.com/img/1/4/5/4/4/5/8/2/1/large/power-indexer-pro-gratis.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2016 22:20:54 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/m_YH5FtAXAY?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><img src="http://powerindexpro.com/images/act.gif" alt="Power Indexer Pro 3.0.1.0" title="Power Indexer Pro 3.0.1.0"  /><br /><img src="https://s1.bukalapak.com/img/1/4/5/4/4/5/8/2/1/large/power-indexer-pro-gratis.jpg" alt="Power Indexer Pro 3.0.1.0" title="Power Indexer Pro 3.0.1.0"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Power Indexer Pro 3.0.1.0" title="Power Indexer Pro 3.0.1.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Indexing Nuke 1.26</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1503-indexing-nuke.html</link>
<description>Name : Indexing Nuke Version : 1.26 OS : Windows Type : Backlink Index Tools Price : $27 Homepage : SalePage Get indexed all your backlinks created by Senuke, Xrumer, Magic Submitter or any other backlink tool! Discover all non indexed posts in your website! Did you know that being able to dominate all the major search engines is an incredibly difficult task to do with regular inte.com marketing methods? With that said, there is a big problem for any business that wants to be successful without being Able to reach the first page in search engines such as Google, Yahoo and Bing. The difficulty of achieving this is going to be higher is your niche is crowded, and in modern times, any niche can become crowded with after a while. The only way to start climbing the search engines is to make sure that you can get your content indexed. The problem is that you usually have to wait a certain amount of time to find out if you have been able to index any of the links in your website.</description>
<category>Backlinks Indexers</category>
<enclosure url="http://ytimg.googleusercontent.com/vi/xCv97jzgpQo/hqdefault.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2016 02:07:59 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features With Indexing Nuke, you will be able to get your URL’s indexed faster, but most importantly, it helps you to discover all the non-indexed URL’s in your website!This is the kind of control that is going to allow you to increase your chances for conversions because you will be able to get as much of your content indexed as possible in a shorter amount of time. The best thing is that it support any kind of URL that you want to get indexed. You can perform these tests was often as needed and this takes your inte.com marketing strategies to a whole new level! Supercharge your SEO efforts! Just think of the simple statistics that explain the importance of Index Nuke. If you have a website that contains 300 pages and you only have 10 of those pages indexed, you might want to increase that number as much as possible because this will allow you to start using other keyword combinations in other indexed pages to make ensure that more people will find your page when they are performing a search. If your conversions are good with less than 30% of your page indexed, imagine how they could be if you can get all of your pages listed in the results?</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/xCv97jzgpQo?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> With Indexing Nuke, you will be able to get your URL’s indexed faster, but most importantly, it helps you to discover all the non-indexed URL’s in your website!This is the kind of control that is going to allow you to increase your chances for conversions because you will be able to get as much of your content indexed as possible in a shorter amount of time. The best thing is that it support any kind of URL that you want to get indexed.<br /></li><li> You can perform these tests was often as needed and this takes your inte.com marketing strategies to a whole new level! Supercharge your SEO efforts! Just think of the simple statistics that explain the importance of Index Nuke. If you have a website that contains 300 pages and you only have 10 of those pages indexed, you might want to increase that number as much as possible because this will allow you to start using other keyword combinations in other indexed pages to make ensure that more people will find your page when they are performing a search.<br /></li><li> If your conversions are good with less than 30% of your page indexed, imagine how they could be if you can get all of your pages listed in the results?<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://ytimg.googleusercontent.com/vi/xCv97jzgpQo/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Indexing Nuke 1.26" title="Indexing Nuke 1.26"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Indexing Nuke 1.26" title="Indexing Nuke 1.26"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>PingBox 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1457-pingbox.html</link>
<description>Name : PingBox Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Ping Index Tools Price : $9 Homepage : SalePage Lightweight software for SEO. With more than 1000+ websites, Pingbox bring your website, url or the post to the top search engines as quickly as possible. Pingbox working by send query (ping) to the huge of websites on REAL BROWSERS. With the Pingbox, you can also check mass pagerank and alexa rank for list of websites(urls). Further, you don&#039;t need verify the list of backlinks manualy. Simple input your backlinks list and click start with Pingbox Backlink Verifier.</description>
<category>Backlinks Indexers</category>
<enclosure url="https://i.imgur.com/Cvq2WBu.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2015 22:49:50 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Pingbox provide 2 difference url list for website pinger. List #1 using for domain pinger and ranked websites (which has alexa rank under 500k). List #2 using for any site or url. website pinger, check pr, check page rank, check alexa rank, backlink verify, get free backlinks, backlink free, free backlink software, backlink software</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/Jop6CsxEMO0?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Pingbox provide 2 difference url list for website pinger. List #1 using for domain pinger and ranked websites (which has alexa rank under 500k). List #2 using for any site or url.<br /></li><li> website pinger, check pr, check page rank, check alexa rank, backlink verify, get free backlinks, backlink free, free backlink software, backlink software<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="https://i.imgur.com/Cvq2WBu.png" alt="PingBox 1.0" title="PingBox 1.0"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="PingBox 1.0" title="PingBox 1.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>No Hands Indexer 1.10.0.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1359-no-hands-indexer.html</link>
<description>Name : No Hands Indexer Version : 1.10.0.0 OS : Windows Type : Backlink Index Tools Price : $20 Homepage : SalePage No Hands Indexer uses a technique called multi-threading to create many links simultaneously, this means that it is incredibly fast at creating thousands of links for each of your webpages. It used to be hard to get your newly created websites and backlinks indexed in google, yahoo and bing but now with No Hands Indexer you can reduce the time to indexing from a possible weeks to less than a day.</description>
<category>Backlinks Indexers</category>
<enclosure url="http://nohandsindexer.com/images/No-Hands-Indexer-Main.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2015 22:22:59 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Very easy to use Very little setup Import lists of pages for indexing Index as many pages as you want Fully Multi-Threaded Updated Regularly Easily customisable Integrates with No Hands SEO with just one checkbox Full Money Back Guarantee Totally free updates</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/AuK97Kwb4rM?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Very easy to use<br /></li><li> Very little setup<br /></li><li> Import lists of pages for indexing<br /></li><li> Index as many pages as you want<br /></li><li> Fully Multi-Threaded<br /></li><li> Updated Regularly<br /></li><li> Easily customisable<br /></li><li> Integrates with No Hands SEO with just one checkbox<br /></li><li> Full Money Back Guarantee<br /></li><li> Totally free updates<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://nohandsindexer.com/images/No-Hands-Indexer-Main.png" alt="No Hands Indexer 1.10.0.0" title="No Hands Indexer 1.10.0.0"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="No Hands Indexer 1.10.0.0" title="No Hands Indexer 1.10.0.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Pinger Jeet 1.1</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1285-pinger-jeet.html</link>
<description>Name : Pinger Jeet Version : 1.1 OS : Windows Type : BackLink Indexer Price : $8 Homepage : SalePage The fastest Pinger on the Inte.com! Pinger Jeet is a blog pinging tool that will ping your blog to over 80 Inte.com search engines or blog services faster than any other pinging software. Give your website or blog the maximum exposure instantly with Pinger Jeet. Pinger Jeet is a very fast pinging software that you can use to ping search engines and other content websites when you update the content on your blog. Pinging tells the search engines to come collect the fresh content from your blog and it brings your content to the Inte.com faster. That&#039;s why Pinging is very important and every blogger should ping the search engines whenever she creates new content. Pinger Jeet does the job for you.</description>
<category>Backlinks Indexers</category>
<enclosure url="http://teknikforce.com/img/pingerjeetshot.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2015 22:09:16 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Big ping list covers all major search engines and blog lists. Ping all your websites at the same time. Together! Load your list of websites from text files. Live updation of the ping queue tells you how fast you&#039;re going and how much work is left. Easy too use software works on the push of a button. The fastest pinger on the Inte.com. Did we tell you that earlier? Yes, it&#039;s the fastest pinger. It saves you time!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/dSB1ZTRTHZo?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Big ping list covers all major search engines and blog lists.<br /></li><li> Ping all your websites at the same time. Together!<br /></li><li> Load your list of websites from text files.<br /></li><li> Live updation of the ping queue tells you how fast you're going and how much work is left.<br /></li><li> Easy too use software works on the push of a button.<br /></li><li> The fastest pinger on the Inte.com. Did we tell you that earlier? Yes, it's the fastest pinger. It saves you time!<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://teknikforce.com/img/pingerjeetshot.png" alt="Pinger Jeet 1.1" title="Pinger Jeet 1.1"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Pinger Jeet 1.1" title="Pinger Jeet 1.1"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Penguin Recovery Jeet 1.2.5</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/910-penguin-recovery-jeet.html</link>
<description>Name : Penguin Recovery Jeet Version : 1.2.5 OS : Windows Type : BlackLink Scraper, Penguin Recovery Tools Price : $37 Homepage : SalePage Automated software integrates with Google, finds bad backlinks and creates a disavow file Penguin Recovery Jeet Automatically gets the domains linking to you, fetches all backlinks and conducts an in-depth analysis to find out which backlinks are toxic to you. Creates a Google Disavow file that you can submit and get rid of the Penguin Penalty on your site. This is a 100% automated product, that you can just run and it&#039;ll do all the work required.</description>
<category>Backlinks Indexers</category>
<enclosure url="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/penguinrecoveryjeet/Content/Images/box2.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/penguinrecoveryjeet/Content/Images/H1.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2015 18:47:37 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Doing this analysis 100% manually will take days for just one big site if you were to subject every single link to the scrutiny it deserves. Just have a look at the factors:</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/CI4wLriwXN8?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br />Doing this analysis 100% manually will take days for just one big site if you were to subject every single link to the scrutiny it deserves. Just have a look at the factors:<br /><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/penguinrecoveryjeet/Content/Images/box2.png" alt="Penguin Recovery Jeet 1.2.5" title="Penguin Recovery Jeet 1.2.5"  /><br /><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/penguinrecoveryjeet/Content/Images/H1.png" alt="Penguin Recovery Jeet 1.2.5" title="Penguin Recovery Jeet 1.2.5"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Penguin Recovery Jeet 1.2.5" title="Penguin Recovery Jeet 1.2.5"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>