<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Membership Plugins - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Membership Plugins - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>Ultimate Membership Pro 6.7</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1727-ultimate-membership-pro.html</link>
<description>Name : Ultimate Membership Pro Version : 6.7 OS : Linux Type : Membership Plugins Price : $30 Homepage : SalePage Ultimate Membership Pro is the newest and the best Membership WordPress Plugin that allow you to create and work with multi-level exclusive access for your Users based on simple Free packages or Payed packages. You can turn on your Website into a income supply by protecting your valuable content or only part of it. Protect your: Pages, Products, Categories, any URL, Content Sections, Images, Menu, anything and set a Redirect or Replace Content Rule.</description>
<category>Membership Plugins</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2018 05:20:18 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Multi-Levels Unlimited Paid/Free Membership Levels Content Lockers protect Payments Gateway: PayPal, Authorize.com, Stripe, 2CheckOut, Bank Transfer Trial Free/Paid period Drip Content protection Restrict Pages or any URL Subscriptions Plan MultiPayments option Login Predefined Templates Register Predefined Templates Menu Protection 9 Email Marketing Platforms integrated Visual Composer Integrated Keywords Restrictions Social Login with 7 Social Networks:Facebook,Twitter,Google,LinkedIn,Instagram,VKontakte,Tumblr 5 Predefined Social Buttons Layouts Double Email Verification Dashboard Stats Unlimited Registration/Profile Fields Restricted Fields based on Levels Redirect or Replace Content Page WordPress Users Synchronize Members List Showcases Custom Currencies Coupon Codes discount Bulk Coupons builder Customizable Email Notification Templates Custom Inside Content Locker Special Custom Fields:Profile Image, Upload Files, Multi-Select Conditional Logic Register Form Verify Code/Question field Professional Account Page - Custom Content, Subscription actions (Renew,Cancel,Delete) Custom Redirect Links Multiple Predefined Shortcodes Custom Dashboard Access</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/jQ5EuAmyKAA?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Multi-Levels<br></li><li> Unlimited Paid/Free Membership Levels<br></li><li> Content Lockers protect<br></li><li> Payments Gateway: PayPal, Authorize.com, Stripe, 2CheckOut, Bank Transfer<br></li><li> Trial Free/Paid period<br></li><li> Drip Content protection<br></li><li> Restrict Pages or any URL<br></li><li> Subscriptions Plan<br></li><li> MultiPayments option<br></li><li> Login Predefined Templates<br></li><li> Register Predefined Templates<br></li><li> Menu Protection<br></li><li> 9 Email Marketing Platforms integrated<br></li><li> Visual Composer Integrated<br></li><li> Keywords Restrictions<br></li><li> Social Login with 7 Social Networks:Facebook,Twitter,Google,LinkedIn,Instagram,VKontakte,Tumblr<br></li><li> 5 Predefined Social Buttons Layouts<br></li><li> Double Email Verification<br></li><li> Dashboard Stats<br></li><li> Unlimited Registration/Profile Fields<br></li><li> Restricted Fields based on Levels<br></li><li> Redirect or Replace Content Page<br></li><li> WordPress Users Synchronize<br></li><li> Members List Showcases<br></li><li> Custom Currencies<br></li><li> Coupon Codes discount<br></li><li> Bulk Coupons builder<br></li><li> Customizable Email Notification Templates<br></li><li> Custom Inside Content Locker<br></li><li> Special Custom Fields:Profile Image, Upload Files, Multi-Select<br></li><li> Conditional Logic Register Form<br></li><li> Verify Code/Question field<br></li><li> Professional Account Page - Custom Content, Subscription actions (Renew,Cancel,Delete)<br></li><li> Custom Redirect Links<br></li><li> Multiple Predefined Shortcodes<br></li><li> Custom Dashboard Access<br></li></ul><br><img src="https://d1a6a9r46cnyll.cloudfront.com/af683fa73937c5b55f85c320e61d3814fd1133c1/687474703a2f2f64656d6f69756d702e7770696e646565642e636f6d2f77702d636f6e74656e742f75706c6f6164732f323031352f30372f696d705f6f70742e706e67" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Ultimate Membership Pro 6.7"><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>UserPro 4.9.11</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/830-userpro.html</link>
<description>Name : UserPro - User Profiles with Social Login Version : 4.9.11 Type : Membership Plugin Price : $28 Homepage : SalePage UserPro offers beautiful front-end profiles, login and registration for WordPress. UserPro is packed with so many features and control, It is more than just a user profiles plugin. UserPro comes with many extra features in addition to the beautiful user profiles, login and registration, member directory. It offers social connect and integration (1 click auto signup/signin), viral marketing, user badges, file upload, photo uploads with lightbox support, responsive videos, follow/unfollow users, verified accounts, content restriction (private content), frontend publisher, posts by user, public/private activity feed, and more. - That&#039;s why UserPro gives you more than frontend profiles and registration system for WordPress, It&#039;s simply all-in-one plugin! (See below for detailed features)</description>
<category>Membership Plugins</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2017 22:10:32 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>[media=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gpOyscHUM80] Features Build your own community of searchable members directory Give each user a customized, elegant profile Add front-end, customized registration and login to your website Fully responsive and looks perfect on any screen size Easily create and apply custom css and styles to the plugin Compatible with all properly coded WP themes and plugins! 5 skins already included and unlimited CSS support Includes RTL Stylesheet (right-to-left language supported) Unlimited Google Fonts Support 350+ FontAwesome Icons for your profile fields and social.comworks! Automatic SEO-Friendly URL for every user (see example) Available in 12 Languages Translation Ready! Userpro4.9.4.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Userpro4.9.4.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Userpro4.9.4.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Userpro4.9.4.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar Userpro4.9.4.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;">[media=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gpOyscHUM80]</div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li>Build your own community of searchable members directory<br></li><li>Give each user a customized, elegant profile<br></li><li>Add front-end, customized registration and login to your website<br></li><li>Fully responsive and looks perfect on any screen size<br></li><li>Easily create and apply custom css and styles to the plugin<br></li><li>Compatible with all properly coded WP themes and plugins!<br></li><li>5 skins already included and unlimited CSS support<br></li><li>Includes RTL Stylesheet (right-to-left language supported)<br></li><li>Unlimited Google Fonts Support<br></li><li>350+ FontAwesome Icons for your profile fields and social.comworks!<br></li><li>Automatic SEO-Friendly URL for every user (see example)<br></li><li>Available in 12 Languages<br></li><li>Translation Ready!<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="UserPro 4.9.11"><br><div class="quote"><br><a href="https://clicknupload.link/ndv282bknoxw"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Userpro4.9.4.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://dailyuploads.com/8453apdpfrzc"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Userpro4.9.4.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://uploadocean.com/kwk06wj7034h"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Userpro4.9.4.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://uplod.ws/1rr4xwq0mbl1"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Userpro4.9.4.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br><a href="https://userscloud.com/9sbzbfwekx1e"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">Userpro4.9.4.PHP.NULLED-tgMember.rar</a><br></div><br></div><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""> <br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Restrict Content Pro 2.8.6 Full Plugin Pack</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/820-restrict-content-pro.html</link>
<description>Name : Restrict Content Pro Version : 2.8.6 + Add-ons Type : Membership Plugin Price : $155 Homepage : SalePage Restrict Content Pro is a complete membership and premium content manager plugin for WordPress. Create an unlimited number of memberships levels, including free, trial and premium. Manage members and their subscriptions, track payments, offer discounts with a complete discount code system, and provide premium, members-only content to your subscribers.</description>
<category>Membership Plugins</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 03:43:32 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Simple Setup Members Management Unlimited Subscription Packages Integrated with PayPal Payments Discount Codes Reports Data Export Extensive Help Restrict Content Pro stripe Payment Gateway v1.5.4 Restrict Content Pro paypal-pro-express Payment Gateway v1.1.4 Restrict Content Pro - Math Verification v1.0.1 Restrict Content Pro Braintree Payment Gateway v1.0.4</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Chl6G0dYoaA?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Simple Setup<br></li><li> Members Management<br></li><li> Unlimited Subscription Packages<br></li><li> Integrated with PayPal Payments<br></li><li> Discount Codes<br></li><li> Reports<br></li><li> Data Export<br></li><li> Extensive Help<br></li><li> Restrict Content Pro stripe Payment Gateway v1.5.4<br></li><li> Restrict Content Pro paypal-pro-express Payment Gateway v1.1.4<br></li><li> Restrict Content Pro - Math Verification v1.0.1<br></li><li> Restrict Content Pro Braintree Payment Gateway v1.0.4<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Restrict Content Pro 2.8.6 Full Plugin Pack"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>WishList Member 2.90.2515</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/833-wishlist-member.html</link>
<description>Name : WishList Member for WordPress Version : 2.90.2515 Type : Membership plugin Price : $297 Homepage : SalePage WishList Member™ is a powerful, yet easy to use membership solution that can turn any WordPress site into a full-blown membership site.</description>
<category>Membership Plugins</category>
<enclosure url="http://member.wishlistproducts.com/wp-content/themes/wishlist-member-1.5/images/integration-logos.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 11:02:43 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Unlimited Membership Levels : Create &quot;Silver&quot;, &quot;Gold&quot;, &quot;Platinum&quot;, or any other &quot;levels&quot; you want! Charge more for higher levels of access - all within the same site. Integrates With Your WordPress Site : Whether you&#039;re building a new site or integrating with an existing WordPress site, installing WishList Member™ is a breeze. Just unzip the file, upload to your plugins folder and activate! Flexible Membership Options : Create Free, Trial, or Paid membership levels - or any combination of the three. Easy Member Management : View your members, their registration status, membership level, and much more. Easily upgrade members, move them to different levels, pause their membership, or delete them entirely. Sequential Content Delivery : Graduate your members from one level to the next. For example, after 30 days, you can automatically upgrade members from a Free Trial to the &quot;Silver&quot; level. Control Viewed Content : Just click the &quot;Hide&quot; button to protect exclusive content for members of a particular level. Create &quot;modular&quot; memberships and hide content from other levels. Shopping Cart Integration : Seamlessly integrates with the most popular shopping cart systems, including PayPal, ClickBank, and many more. Plus, WishList Member™ now integrates with Cydec and Infusionsoft. Multi-Level Access : Give your members access to multiple levels within your membership. For example, create a central download location with access granted to members of all levels. Integrates with these and more!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<br><div style="text-align:center;"><div class="dlevideoplayer" style="width:100%;max-width:425px;"><ul data-theme="default" data-preload="metadata"><li data-title="" data-type="youtube" data-url="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JuB_43z8ZPQ"></li></ul></div></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Unlimited Membership Levels : Create "Silver", "Gold", "Platinum", or any other "levels" you want! Charge more for higher levels of access - all within the same site.<br></li><li> Integrates With Your WordPress Site : Whether you're building a new site or integrating with an existing WordPress site, installing WishList Member™ is a breeze. Just unzip the file, upload to your plugins folder and activate!<br></li><li> Flexible Membership Options : Create Free, Trial, or Paid membership levels - or any combination of the three.<br></li><li> Easy Member Management : View your members, their registration status, membership level, and much more. Easily upgrade members, move them to different levels, pause their membership, or delete them entirely.<br></li><li> Sequential Content Delivery : Graduate your members from one level to the next. For example, after 30 days, you can automatically upgrade members from a Free Trial to the "Silver" level.<br></li><li> Control Viewed Content : Just click the "Hide" button to protect exclusive content for members of a particular level. Create "modular" memberships and hide content from other levels.<br></li><li> Shopping Cart Integration : Seamlessly integrates with the most popular shopping cart systems, including PayPal, ClickBank, and many more. Plus, WishList Member™ now integrates with Cydec and Infusionsoft.<br></li><li> Multi-Level Access : Give your members access to multiple levels within your membership. For example, create a central download location with access granted to members of all levels.<br></li></ul><br>Integrates with these and more!<br><img src="http://member.wishlistproducts.com/wp-content/themes/wishlist-member-1.5/images/integration-logos.png" alt="WishList Member 2.90.2515"><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>InstaMember 1.23</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1396-instamember.html</link>
<description>Name : InstaMember Version : 1.23 Unlimited OS : linux Type : Membership Marketing Price : $97 Homepage : SalePage InstaMember - The Ultimate Wordpress Membership Plugin Ask most Inte.com marketers and they will tell you that membership sites ... which provide recurring income month after month ... are the easiest and most reliable way to create high-profit revenue streams. But unless you have a computer engineering degree or decades of programming experience, building membership sites is nearly impossible ... Until now, that is! InstaMember is your key to building high-profit, high-performance membership sites almost instantly!</description>
<category>Membership Plugins</category>
<enclosure url="http://insta-member.com/launch/images/sales/sales_01.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2016 16:49:00 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features This new version includes a number of enhancements and fixes including - New Feature: Users Notes - Improvement: Ability to search license key by a domain name - Fix email problem in CB INS v6 - Fix widget compatibility problem with WP 3.4.1 - Fix refund processing problem in Zaxaa Payment - Fix one-time payment expired problem</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<br /><div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/cNSKPU8ICPY?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br />This new version includes a number of enhancements and fixes including<br />- New Feature: Users Notes<br />- Improvement: Ability to search license key by a domain name<br />- Fix email problem in CB INS v6<br />- Fix widget compatibility problem with WP 3.4.1<br />- Fix refund processing problem in Zaxaa Payment<br />- Fix one-time payment expired problem<br /><img src="http://insta-member.com/launch/images/sales/sales_01.jpg" alt="InstaMember 1.23" title="InstaMember 1.23"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="InstaMember 1.23" title="InstaMember 1.23"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>User Profiles Made Easy v2.0.25</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/829-user-profiles-made-easy.html</link>
<description>Name : User Profiles Made Easy - WordPress Plugin Version : 2.0.25 Type : Membership Plugin Price : $28 Homepage : SalePage User Profiles Made Easy (UPME) is a full featured front-end profile, login and registration plugin for WordPress. It is user-friendly, fully responsive and works with any theme. With this plugin you can stop sending your users to the ugly back-end profile, registration and login pages, and instead give your users a seamless front-end experience on pages that match the rest of your website.</description>
<category>Membership Plugins</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2015 00:48:07 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Elegant, responsive front-end profiles with unlimited custom fields Beautiful front-end Login &amp;amp; Registration forms with shortcodes Compatible with all (properly coded) themes SEO Friendly profile permalink options Works automatically with any existing usermeta data and usermeta fields from other plugins Show/promote a specific user or group of users anywhere with shortcode Fully responsive, adjusts beautifully to any screen size Easy to use shortcode generator Fully translatable to any language using .po files Import/Export custom fields. Import/Export UPME settings. Export UPME users. Custom actions and filters for adding more features using other plugins UPME Developer API for retriving UPME data for other plugins and themes New features added regularly! Dedicated support forum! Enable/Disable third party script and styles</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/41Sy-ok8cBU?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div>
<p></p>
<h3>Features</h3>
<p><br><ul><li> Elegant, responsive front-end profiles with unlimited custom fields<br></li><li> Beautiful front-end Login &amp; Registration forms with shortcodes<br></li><li> Compatible with all (properly coded) themes<br></li><li> SEO Friendly profile permalink options <br></li><li> Works automatically with any existing usermeta data and usermeta fields from other plugins<br></li><li> Show/promote a specific user or group of users anywhere with shortcode<br></li><li> Fully responsive, adjusts beautifully to any screen size<br></li><li> Easy to use shortcode generator<br></li><li> Fully translatable to any language using .po files<br></li><li> Import/Export custom fields.<br></li><li> Import/Export UPME settings.<br></li><li> Export UPME users.<br></li><li> Custom actions and filters for adding more features using other plugins<br></li><li> UPME Developer API for retriving UPME data for other plugins and themes <br></li><li> New features added regularly!<br></li><li> Dedicated support forum!<br></li><li> Enable/Disable third party script and styles<br></li></ul></p>
<div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="User Profiles Made Easy v2.0.25"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Membership 2 PRO 1.0.3.3</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/813-membership-pro.html</link>
<description>Name : Membership 2 PRO Version : 1.0.3.3 Type : Membership Plugin Price : $19 Homepage : SalePage A complete, scalable membership system that can be configured to offer multi-tier subscriptions, recurring payments and drip content in minutes.</description>
<category>Membership Plugins</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2015 00:47:35 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Downloads paywall Video content paywall Image file paywall Protect specific URLs Audio file paywall Plugin paywall Protect pages, posts or comments Support paywall Create exclusive forums Recurring payment options Dripped content settings Simple drag-n-drop setup Unlimited custom subscription plans Paid and free subscriptions PayPal Express 2Checkout Authorize.com Coupons Invitation-only registration Shortcode catalog Remote ping Seamless BuddyPress integration Automated email campaign system Statistics Graphs and reports</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<p></p>
<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/4FREdy9e5dc?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div>
<p></p>
<h3>Features</h3>
<p><br><ul><li> Downloads paywall<br></li><li> Video content paywall<br></li><li> Image file paywall<br></li><li> Protect specific URLs<br></li><li> Audio file paywall<br></li><li> Plugin paywall<br></li><li> Protect pages, posts or comments<br></li><li> Support paywall<br></li><li> Create exclusive forums<br></li><li> Recurring payment options<br></li><li> Dripped content settings<br></li><li> Simple drag-n-drop setup<br></li><li> Unlimited custom subscription plans<br></li><li> Paid and free subscriptions<br></li><li> PayPal Express<br></li><li> 2Checkout<br></li><li> Authorize.com<br></li><li> Coupons<br></li><li> Invitation-only registration<br></li><li> Shortcode catalog<br></li><li> Remote ping<br></li><li> Seamless BuddyPress integration<br></li><li> Automated email campaign system<br></li><li> Statistics<br></li><li> Graphs and reports<br></li></ul></p>
<div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Membership 2 PRO 1.0.3.3"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Link Gate v9.1.0.1</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/812-link-gate.html</link>
<description>Name : Link Gate Version : 9.1.0.1 Type : Email Marketing Plugin Price : $28 Homepage : SalePage &quot;Increase Reader Engagement, Ensure Important Messages Get Seen, And Grow Your Mailing List...&quot; Are your readers missing important pieces of information? Chances are, the answer is yes. Here&#039;s why... We simply don&#039;t have time. We&#039;re always in a hurry to get to the next email, the next video, the next social media site. The result? We scan the content, click the links, and move on. For the website owner, that means you have to work even harder to get a reader&#039;s attention and get him to take action.</description>
<category>Membership Plugins</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2015 00:47:33 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Installs quickly and easily right from your WordPress dashboard. Works with any mailing list provider--no complex configuration needed. Use for opt-ins, information and more. Easily include images and HTML in your pop-ups. Unlimited color choices to match any theme. Opt-in forms use both name and email or only email for total flexibility. Add background images, borders and more with the simple point and click interface. Create unlimited Link-Gates for use on any page or post on your site. Add customized calls to action to every post--give your readers exactly what they need, right when they need it. Create informative, pop-up &quot;Learn more&quot; content to make training programs or step-by-step instructions easier to follow. Add multiple Link-Gates to single posts or pages. A button added to your post editing screen makes inserting Link-Gates fast and easy. Works with shortcodes so thise&#039;s no j&amp;#097;vascript to break during post editing. Use on blog posts, sales pages, contact pages and more. Style the text and images for maximum impact.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/wCG0eaO0QJw?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Installs quickly and easily right from your WordPress dashboard. <br /></li><li> Works with any mailing list provider--no complex configuration needed. <br /></li><li> Use for opt-ins, information and more. <br /></li><li> Easily include images and HTML in your pop-ups. <br /></li><li> Unlimited color choices to match any theme.<br /></li><li> Opt-in forms use both name and email or only email for total flexibility. <br /></li><li> Add background images, borders and more with the simple point and click interface. <br /></li><li> Create unlimited Link-Gates for use on any page or post on your site. <br /></li><li> Add customized calls to action to every post--give your readers exactly what they need, right when they need it. <br /></li><li> Create informative, pop-up "Learn more" content to make training programs or step-by-step instructions easier to follow. <br /></li><li> Add multiple Link-Gates to single posts or pages. <br /></li><li> A button added to your post editing screen makes inserting Link-Gates fast and easy. <br /></li><li> Works with shortcodes so thise's no j&#097;vascript to break during post editing. <br /></li><li> Use on blog posts, sales pages, contact pages and more. <br /></li><li> Style the text and images for maximum impact. <br /></li></ul><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Link Gate v9.1.0.1" title="Link Gate v9.1.0.1"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>aMember Pro v5.1.3</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/799-amember-pro.html</link>
<description>Name : aMember Pro Version : 5.1.3 Type : Membership Plugin Price : $179.95 Homepage : SalePage Accept subscription payments, manage customer profiles, deliver digital content, integrate with your blog, forum, or CMS, send opt-in newsletters, run your own affiliate program - everything is easy with aMember Pro.</description>
<category>Membership Plugins</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2015 00:47:07 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Easy web-based administration : Quick access to the most useful functions, and advanced settings for professionals Multiple payment systems : PayPal, ClickBank, 2Checkout, Wordpay and 100+ more integrations support out of the box Translated into 6 languages : German, Spanish, French, Greek, Russian and Chinese translations are available Integration plugins : Easy and powerful integration with Wordpress, XenForo, vBulletin, and others Free installation included : Professionals will install aMember to your website and help you with the first steps Full-featured affiliate module : Thanks to subscription system integration, you can precisely track recurring commissions Integrated Helpdesk : The customer support module helps you keep customer requests and responses organized Easy Protection : aMember Pro can protect your site folders, files, scripts, blog posts, forums, and more</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/S_AW9XyYC0w?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div>
<p></p>
<h3>Features</h3>
<p><br><ul><li> Easy web-based administration : Quick access to the most useful functions, and advanced settings for professionals<br></li><li> Multiple payment systems : PayPal, ClickBank, 2Checkout, Wordpay and 100+ more integrations support out of the box<br></li><li> Translated into 6 languages : German, Spanish, French, Greek, Russian and Chinese translations are available<br></li><li> Integration plugins : Easy and powerful integration with Wordpress, XenForo, vBulletin, and others<br></li><li> Free installation included : Professionals will install aMember to your website and help you with the first steps<br></li><li> Full-featured affiliate module : Thanks to subscription system integration, you can precisely track recurring commissions<br></li><li> Integrated Helpdesk : The customer support module helps you keep customer requests and responses organized<br></li><li> Easy Protection : aMember Pro can protect your site folders, files, scripts, blog posts, forums, and more<br></li></ul></p>
<div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="aMember Pro v5.1.3"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>