<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Social Lead Extractor - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Social Lead Extractor - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>Social Interest Freak 2.0.8</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1261-social-interest-freak.html</link>
<description>Name : Social Interest Freak + Bonus Diagnostic Tool Version : 2.0.8 + 1.0.0 OS : Windows/MAC Type : Facebook Marketing Tools Price : $247 Homepage : SalePage Social Interest Freak is an amazing new Facebook targeting tool that lets you uncover interests, behaviors, demographics and other advanced targets and then target a combination of these targets using intersection, union and exclusion. To date, no other software tool out there lets you do this in such an easy drag and drop manner. It is a powerful Facebook Software that allows you to LASER-TARGET your Facebook Ad Campaigns like never before. This technology was only available to Facebook Managed Corporate Clients before Social Interest Freak was created. Now, this power is at the Finger-Tips of the ‘Average Joe &amp;amp; Jane’ marketers in the world. All built off the latest Facebook API (Application Program Interface) that was released to developers only a few weeks ago! With Social Interest Freak, the average user now has the same power as the select few advertisers who are able to utilize this powerful targeting capability on the Facebook ads platform. The first Facebook targeting tool of its kind with a killer sales page to ensure high EPCs (Earnings Per Click) for the best Facebook software tool of the year. Letting you know of a NEW Facebook software tool that has JUST hit the market… by the creator of Social Lead Freak, which was one of the biggest Facebook Marketing products to ever be released in early 2013. Now, he’s released his new ‘Social Interest Freak‘ desktop software that is built on Adobe AIR just like Social Lead Freak, so it’s fully compatible for both PC’s &amp;amp; Macs. New for 2015 &amp;amp; Beyond. You want to see the new Social Interest Freak in action? Just keep reading…</description>
<category>Social Lead Extractor</category>
<enclosure url="http://socialinterestfreak.com/images/header-mod3.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="http://socialinterestfreak.com/images/bonus.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="https://i.stack.imgur.com/0CYEl.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 20:47:17 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Facebook Interest ‘AND’ targeting with as many levels as you would like. Super focus on your audience. (never possible before) Ability to omit details of pre-set Interest(s) in Facebook Ads Manager. (never possible before) Now you can fine tune your Facebook Ad campaign with Demographic parameters of Facebook Users. (education, job title, etc.) You can also add that your Facebook Ad campaigns are only targeting Facebook Users with ‘certain online behaviors’, for example Facebook Users that have spent $$$ online. [VERY powerful and smart] (never waste ads on Facebook users that have never spent $ online). Advanced Targeting Parameters based on Facebook Users Income Levels and so much more. ALL this done with super-simple ‘Drag &amp;amp; Drop’ Ease AND all linked to your Facebook Ads Manager… So everything you do in Social Interest Freak is automatically updated in your Facebook Ads Account(s).</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/uyujDlWCfVE?start=15&feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Facebook Interest ‘AND’ targeting with as many levels as you would like. Super focus on your audience. (never possible before)<br></li><li> Ability to omit details of pre-set Interest(s) in Facebook Ads Manager. (never possible before)<br></li><li> Now you can fine tune your Facebook Ad campaign with Demographic parameters of Facebook Users. (education, job title, etc.)<br></li><li> You can also add that your Facebook Ad campaigns are only targeting Facebook Users with ‘certain online behaviors’, for example Facebook Users that have spent $$$ online. [VERY powerful and smart] (never waste ads on Facebook users that have never spent $ online).<br></li><li> Advanced Targeting Parameters based on Facebook Users Income Levels and so much more.<br></li><li> ALL this done with super-simple ‘Drag &amp; Drop’ Ease AND all linked to your Facebook Ads Manager… So everything you do in Social Interest Freak is automatically updated in your Facebook Ads Account(s).<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://socialinterestfreak.com/images/header-mod3.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Social Interest Freak 2.0.8"><br><img src="http://socialinterestfreak.com/images/bonus.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Facebook Graph Search 1.1.5.15 Premium</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1312-facebook-graph-search.html</link>
<description>Name : Facebook Graph Search Version : 1.1.5.15 Premium OS : Windows Type : Facebook Marketing Tools Price : $40 Homepage : SalePage Facebook Graph Search - Facebook Data Scraper Facebook Graph Search help you to finding peoples, stories/posts, groups, pages, events, places, apps with more criteria. Searching for the the best selling and trending products explore new ideas. Searching and mapping the interest to sharpen or expand the range of ad targeting ads. Easy to scrape/extract details (id, name, email ...) of peoples, stories, groups, events.</description>
<category>Social Lead Extractor</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 17:21:01 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Searching for the viral post, video, pictures, articles, etc. Searching for the best selling and trending products in teespring, viralstyle, amazon, etc. Looking for peoples who are currently in need of your product with more criteria. Searching and building relationships with people who potentially. Potential business partners, distributors, resellers, recruiting a downline, looking for employees, etc. Searching for a group that contains people who want your product. Searching for pages that liked by target audience. Mapping the topic and explore new ideas for your next product. Searching and mapping the interest to sharpen or expand the range of ad targeting ads. Knowing who your competitors and Dismantling of their marketing strategy on Facebook. Scraping user details (id, facebook email, location ...) from ids. Scraping users from joined to a group, pages or an event ... Scraping group details (id, name, status joined/unjoin, members ...) from ids. Scraping page details (id, name, category, email, website, phone ...) from ids. Scraping users who liked a post, go/went/invited to an event, liked a page ... There are still dozens of other benefits that you can get ... ARE YOU SMART MARKETER? Did you knew, Facebook is a giant database? With 1.3 billion users from around the world, 30 billion content in the post every month (photo, video, link ...), interact with 900+ million objects (fans page, group, place ...). Facebook know all thing about you? From the age, gender, occupation, hobbies, interests, and even anything that we talked about on Facebook, all recorded and stored neatly in their database. But this makes up into a best Place to Perform RESEARCH. Suppose you want selling tshirt. It would be more effective if tshirt design that you sell proven preferred by users of Facebook, right? Or you are planning to market a product on facebook? You want a specific users to know this product? All you need to do is searching for the data and information you need. The software help you on &quot;facebook graph search&quot;? The data that we get from a particular search, can sharpen our ad targeting capabilities. FACEBOOK GRAPH SEARCH At the December 2014 Facebook Search Engine has changed. There are hundreds of search criteria that you need to combine. With the Facebook Graph Search, you can search and filter various search criteria quickly and easily, without having to memorize. So you can find any data on Facebook, which you can use as a basis to formulate your marketing strategy on Facebook. USAGE IDEAS Looking for viral content Photo, Video, Articles which you can use to * Boost the post on your fanpage. * Increase CTR ads on Facebook. * Bring new users to your website/blog. Break the marketing strategies of competitors. You can know: * How competitors are doing promotions. AND MORE Even if you do not use Facebook for your BUSINESS MARKETING, The Facebook Graph Search can make your activities on Facebook become more enjoyable. You can search for posts from your friends. Revived old memories together with a friend. Facebook Graph Search help you to searching for peoples by specify criteria. Here is the complete list of filters that you can use</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/NyWtmDqIhz4?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Searching for the viral post, video, pictures, articles, etc.<br></li><li> Searching for the best selling and trending products in teespring, viralstyle, amazon, etc.<br></li><li> Looking for peoples who are currently in need of your product with more criteria.<br></li><li> Searching and building relationships with people who potentially. Potential business partners, distributors, resellers, recruiting a downline, looking for employees, etc.<br></li><li> Searching for a group that contains people who want your product.<br></li><li> Searching for pages that liked by target audience.<br></li><li> Mapping the topic and explore new ideas for your next product.<br></li><li> Searching and mapping the interest to sharpen or expand the range of ad targeting ads.<br></li><li> Knowing who your competitors and Dismantling of their marketing strategy on Facebook.<br></li><li> Scraping user details (id, facebook email, location ...) from ids.<br></li><li> Scraping users from joined to a group, pages or an event ...<br></li><li> Scraping group details (id, name, status joined/unjoin, members ...) from ids.<br></li><li> Scraping page details (id, name, category, email, website, phone ...) from ids.<br></li><li> Scraping users who liked a post, go/went/invited to an event, liked a page ...<br></li><li> There are still dozens of other benefits that you can get ...<br></li></ul><br><br>ARE YOU SMART MARKETER?<br><ul><li> Did you knew, Facebook is a giant database? With 1.3 billion users from around the world, 30 billion content in the post every month (photo, video, link ...), interact with 900+ million objects (fans page, group, place ...).<br></li><li> Facebook know all thing about you? From the age, gender, occupation, hobbies, interests, and even anything that we talked about on Facebook, all recorded and stored neatly in their database.<br></li><li> But this makes up into a best Place to Perform RESEARCH.<br></li><li> Suppose you want selling tshirt. It would be more effective if tshirt design that you sell proven preferred by users of Facebook, right? Or you are planning to market a product on facebook? You want a specific users to know this product? All you need to do is searching for the data and information you need.<br></li><li> The software help you on "facebook graph search"?<br></li><li> The data that we get from a particular search, can sharpen our ad targeting capabilities.<br></li></ul><br><br>FACEBOOK GRAPH SEARCH<br><ul><li> At the December 2014 Facebook Search Engine has changed.<br></li><li> There are hundreds of search criteria that you need to combine. With the Facebook Graph Search, you can search and filter various search criteria quickly and easily, without having to memorize. So you can find any data on Facebook, which you can use as a basis to formulate your marketing strategy on Facebook.<br></li></ul><br><br>USAGE IDEAS<br><ul><li> Looking for viral content Photo, Video, Articles which you can use to<br></li><li> * Boost the post on your fanpage.<br></li><li> * Increase CTR ads on Facebook.<br></li><li> * Bring new users to your website/blog.<br></li><li> Break the marketing strategies of competitors. You can know:<br></li><li> * How competitors are doing promotions.<br></li></ul><br><br>AND MORE<br><ul><li> Even if you do not use Facebook for your BUSINESS MARKETING, The Facebook Graph Search can make your activities on Facebook become more enjoyable. You can search for posts from your friends. Revived old memories together with a friend.<br></li><li> Facebook Graph Search help you to searching for peoples by specify criteria. Here is the complete list of filters that you can use<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Facebook Graph Search 1.1.5.15 Premium"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Facebook B2B Leads Scraper 1.81.17 Pro</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/869-facebook-b2b-leads-scraper.html</link>
<description>Name : Facebook B2B Leads Scraper Version : 1.81.17 Pro OS : Windows Type : FB Lead Scraper Price : $200 Homepage : SalePage The easiest way to find and scrape targeted business leads on Facebook Use harvested business information to reach out to your potential customers via email/phone or upload the data to Facebook and create a highly-targeted custom audiences for your ads.</description>
<category>Social Lead Extractor</category>
<enclosure url="https://i1.wp.com/i68.tinypic.com/10xbi9i.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2018 12:58:33 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Facebook was always an interesting platform for me since it had so much more than Google Maps which gives around 200 results per search, 40-80 emails if you are lucky but it was not organized well enough. This process was also very slow and enjoying for me. I needed at least a day or two to get a list of leads worth of my attention. It turned out that Facebook was a goldmine of &quot;small business&quot; leads! Premium business listing website are not free and they demand a lot of information. Creating a Facebook Business Page is a piece of cake. That’s why we (our team) started working on a piece of software which will later be named Facebook B2B Leads Scraper</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br>Facebook was always an interesting platform for me since it had so much more than Google Maps which gives around 200 results per search, 40-80 emails if you are lucky but it was not organized well enough. This process was also very slow and enjoying for me. I needed at least a day or two to get a list of leads worth of my attention. <br><br>It turned out that Facebook was a goldmine of "small business" leads! Premium business listing website are not free and they demand a lot of information. Creating a Facebook Business Page is a piece of cake. That’s why we (our team) started working on a piece of software which will later be named Facebook B2B Leads Scraper<br><img src="https://i1.wp.com/i68.tinypic.com/10xbi9i.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Facebook B2B Leads Scraper 1.81.17 Pro"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>XTRACTOR 2.8 Pro v24.8.4</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1627-xtractor-pro.html</link>
<description>Name : XTRACTOR 2.8 Pro Version : 24.8.4 OS : Windows/MAC/Linux Type : Facebook Marketing Tools Price : $49 Homepage : SalePage One Click FB Emails Extractor UPDATE!!! Now you can SEND MESSAGES to @facebook emails, users get it into their primary email! Hi, Want to target the right people, but worried about the costs it would incur? Worry no more! With XTractor 2.0, you can advertise to targeted people and save ad costs at the same time. XTractor 2.0 can extract Facebook emails from Groups, Search, Image/Video Page and Events. The extracted emails can then be used to target custom audience on Facebook campaigns. As it’s a Chrome Extension, XTractor can be used everywhere! Just click on the extension and you will get all the audience you see. You will immediately get 100 UIDs/emails when you download Xtractor 2.0 today. A Pro version of XTractor is also available. It offers unlimited FB UIDs/emails and fast auto scroll. You don’t need to spend ridiculous amounts of cash just to advertise to the right people. With XTractor 2.0, you can do all of that for a much lower price!</description>
<category>Social Lead Extractor</category>
<enclosure url="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/NYJgm_Lv2Fs/maxresdefault.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2018 00:01:04 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Extract From Search : Search for people Click Get FB Emails &amp;amp; UIDs Extract From Groups : Go to the Group &quot;Members&quot; Page Click Get FB Emails &amp;amp; UIDs Extract From Page : Go to the page Click Get FB Emails &amp;amp; UIDs Extract From Event : Go to the event page, click on &#039;going&#039; / &#039;maybe&#039; / &#039;invited&#039; Click Get FB Emails &amp;amp; UIDs Extract From Post : Go to the post page, you can click on the date of the post Click Get FB Emails &amp;amp; UIDs Extract From Image / Video : Go to the image/video post, you can click on the date of the post Click Get FB Emails &amp;amp; UIDs</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/gFFMErNWlqo?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Extract From Search : Search for people  Click  Get FB Emails &amp; UIDs<br></li><li> Extract From Groups : Go to the Group "Members" Page  Click  Get FB Emails &amp; UIDs<br></li><li> Extract From Page : Go to the page  Click  Get FB Emails &amp; UIDs<br></li><li> Extract From Event : Go to the event page, click on 'going' / 'maybe' / 'invited'  Click  Get FB Emails &amp; UIDs<br></li><li> Extract From Post : Go to the post page, you can click on the date of the post  Click  Get FB Emails &amp; UIDs<br></li><li> Extract From Image / Video : Go to the image/video post, you can click on the date of the post  Click  Get FB Emails &amp; UIDs<br></li></ul><br><img src="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/NYJgm_Lv2Fs/maxresdefault.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt="XTRACTOR 2.8 Pro v24.8.4"><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Xtra Pro 2018 v7.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1208-xtra-pro.html</link>
<description>Name : Xtra Pro 2018 Version : 7.0 OS : Windows/MAC Type : Facebook Marketing Price : $47 Homepage : SalePage Xtra Pro is a Must Have tool For Any Professional Marketer to Extract REAL Email Addresses from Facebook !, fast and precisely. It retrieves all valid email addresses by Subjects, Keywords, Interests, automatically removes duplicates, and intelligently takes off false email addresses. Extract REAL EMAILS From FACEBOOK How Xtra Pro Power Tool Can Help You to Obtain Real Emails From Facebook Do not believe it possible ? .... Watch !</description>
<category>Social Lead Extractor</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.xtra.pro/wp-content/uploads/2015/06/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 06:31:25 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features “Search by Subjects, Keywords, Interests,” “Extract REAL Email Addresses from Facebook” “Once extracted, you can save the email addresses”</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/iQ9Wullj848?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> “Search by Subjects, Keywords, Interests,”<br></li><li> “Extract REAL Email Addresses from Facebook”<br></li><li> “Once extracted, you can save the email addresses”<br><br></li></ul><br><img src="http://www.xtra.pro/wp-content/uploads/2015/06/image.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Xtra Pro 2018 v7.0"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>FB Leads Extractor 2.21</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1561-fb-leads-extractor.html</link>
<description>Name : FB Leads Extractor Version : 2.21 OS : Windows Type : Facebook Marketing Tools Price : $97 Homepage : SalePage FB Leads Extractor is a tool that captures contact information such as business name, address, phone number, websites, number of likes and other important information from Facebook. Our software use Facebook.comwork to generate a list of leads in few seconds. You can search by any category or keyword like restaurants, coffee-clubs, and hotels and in any location, city, state or country. You can use zip codes or a radius in meters to get more specific results. Now you will be able to generate sales leads right from Facebook pages, you can make more business contacts and be productive like never before.</description>
<category>Social Lead Extractor</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.touchesoftware.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/12/scrfle2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 09:11:20 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Extract Data from Facebook with just one click. You can enter any category and location to start searching business leads in any region of the world. You can enter a Radius to target the results inside an specific area. You get THOUSANDS of leads ready to export to Excel. Extract business and geographical data. You can get all the business data of your leads like Name, Address, Website, Phone, Fax and Email. If you are interested in create your own business directory you can extract also the latitude and longitude where it?€™s located. Extract custom Facebook data. Extract custom information from Facebook, like number of likes, number of check-ins and number of people talking about each business. Open business in Google Maps. You can locate every result in Google Maps with one single click. Since we track the address and Geo-location is very easy to see the results in a Map. Support Multiple Proxies. You can use one or several proxies to protect your identity. Application can change randomly the current proxy in each request from a list that you provide. Besides the tool add random delays between requests to simulate a human surfing in a browser. Export capabilities: After get your leads you can export them to Excel using the CSV format. You can also export to KML format so you can open in Google Earth. Auto save feature to save results in files with category names. ScreenShot</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/lWN5dTVL6wE?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Extract Data from Facebook with just one click.    You can enter any category and location to start searching business leads in any region of the world. You can enter a Radius to target the results inside an specific area. You get THOUSANDS of leads ready to export to Excel.<br></li><li> Extract business and geographical data.    You can get all the business data of your leads like Name, Address, Website, Phone, Fax and Email. If you are interested in create your own business directory you can extract also the latitude and longitude where it?€™s located.<br></li><li> Extract custom Facebook data.    Extract custom information from Facebook, like number of likes, number of check-ins and number of people talking about each business.<br></li><li> Open business in Google Maps.    You can locate every result in Google Maps with one single click. Since we track the address and Geo-location is very easy to see the results in a Map.<br></li><li> Support Multiple Proxies.    You can use one or several proxies to protect your identity. Application can change randomly the current proxy in each request from a list that you provide. Besides the tool add random delays between requests to simulate a human surfing in a browser.<br></li><li> Export capabilities:    After get your leads you can export them to Excel using the CSV format. You can also export to KML format so you can open in Google Earth. Auto save feature to save results in files with category names.<br></li></ul><br><br><h3>ScreenShot</h3><br><img src="http://www.touchesoftware.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/12/scrfle2.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt="FB Leads Extractor 2.21"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Viral Spy 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3729-viral-spy.html</link>
<description>Name : Viral Spy Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Social Viral Scraper Price : $0 Homepage : SalePage Viral Spy is a 100% free desktop application that will crawl your competitors website checking each page to see how many Facebook shares, Google Plus Tweets and LinkedIn shares it has. It it can extract a date from the page it will even calculate the share velocity for you so you can tell which pages were shared the fastest.</description>
<category>Social Lead Extractor</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 05:28:14 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>[media=https://youtu.be/sLZcH7UGO5Q] Features How does Viral Spy work? Simply enter your competitors website and click start, its that simple. All links are extracted as the crawl goes along so you don&#039;t have to do anything. Why should I use Viral Spy? If you want your content to go viral then you need to know what people want to share in your niche, a great way to do that is to simply look at what your competitors website visitors are sharing on social media.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;">[media=https://youtu.be/sLZcH7UGO5Q]</div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br>How does Viral Spy work?<br>Simply enter your competitors website and click start, its that simple. All links are extracted as the crawl goes along so you don't have to do anything.<br><br>Why should I use Viral Spy?<br>If you want your content to go viral then you need to know what people want to share in your niche, a great way to do that is to simply look at what your competitors website visitors are sharing on social media.<br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Viral Spy 1.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>FB Audience Blaster 4.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3994-fb-audience-blaster.html</link>
<description>Name : FB Audience Blaster Version : 4.0 OS : Windows Type : FB ID Scraper Price : $97 Homepage : SalePage FB Audience Blaster 4.0, a brand new software, automatically search for the anpages, group by some keywords which set up inside. After that, grab post’s interaction (likes, shares, comments) to all those which are group’s members, fanpage owner’s infomation. Then, Fb Audience Blaster will convert user to location, gender, uid, birthday, public email, public phone.</description>
<category>Social Lead Extractor</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 17:30:10 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FE - LIFETIME - $97 1 PC / LICENSE LIFETIME SUPPORT Get all public emails and phones. -FB Audience Blaster 3.0 provides you a key to reach all of the public emails and phones from likes, shares and comments from the Fanpages, Profiles and Groups’ members for you from Facebooks which you can use as your customers list. Get all Fanpage owers informations. -FB Audience Blaster 3.0 can also help you to get the information of Fanpage owners (all of their public informations that you need such as email, phone and address) by using the target keywords. You don’t have to worry about a thing, you only need to stay and get the result. Check the dulicate information -FB Audience Blaster 3.0 will check all of dulicate information which you had scanned on completed. Then, you can use directly those particulars. – The How to extract real email addresses of all your friends in your Facebook friend lists. That’s mean if you friends in a target niche, it will be a wonderful chance for you to make money. – The Youtube Rank Tips which can help you make about 5 thousand dollars per month. – 10 Psychological Theories to persuade people. – 700 emails subject lines from the successful marketers. – The list of 200 buyers’ keyword to get your sales in any niche. – The Mother of All Profit “List Building” eBook.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/jCiwcJ9rbi4?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><a href="https://fbaudienceblaster.com/"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer"><b>FE - LIFETIME - </b></a><br><ul><li> 1 PC / LICENSE<br></li><li> LIFETIME SUPPORT<br></li><li> Get all public emails and phones.<br></li><li> -FB Audience Blaster 3.0 provides you a key to reach all of the public emails and phones from likes, shares and comments from the Fanpages, Profiles and Groups’ members for you from Facebooks which you can use as your customers list.<br></li><li> Get all Fanpage owers informations.<br></li><li> -FB Audience Blaster 3.0 can also help you to get the information of Fanpage owners (all of their public informations that you need such as email, phone and address) by using the target keywords. You don’t have to worry about a thing, you only need to stay and get the result.<br></li><li> Check the dulicate information<br></li><li> -FB Audience Blaster 3.0 will check all of dulicate information which you had scanned on completed. Then, you can use directly those particulars.<br></li><li> – The How to extract real email addresses of all your friends in your Facebook friend lists. That’s mean if you friends in a target niche, it will be a wonderful chance for you to make money.<br></li><li> – The Youtube Rank Tips which can help you make about 5 thousand dollars per month.<br></li><li> – 10 Psychological Theories to persuade people.<br></li><li> – 700 emails subject lines from the successful marketers.<br></li><li> – The list of 200 buyers’ keyword to get your sales in any niche.<br></li><li> – The Mother of All Profit “List Building” eBook.<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="FB Audience Blaster 4.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Facebook Data Scraper 1.47</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1307-facebook-data-scraper.html</link>
<description>Name : Facebook Data Scraper Version : 1.47 OS : Windows Type : Facebook Lead Extractor Price : $60 Homepage : SalePage Facebook Data Scraper is a Facebook custom audience creation tool. It will helps you to find potential customers from Facebook, who were interested in the type of product or service that you are providing. This will increase the conversion rates for your Facebook Ads. Also it helps you to reduce cost by focusing potential customers. Facebook Data Scraper extracts user’s Facebook user id and Facebook email and lets you to export it as either cvs to text file. That you can import to create custom audience while creating your Facebook Add.</description>
<category>Social Lead Extractor</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 00:47:12 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Graph Search : Facebook Data Scraper supports Facebook Graph Search. You can execute Facebook Graph Search query on Facebook Data Scraper and you can export User ID, Email, Page User Name, Page ID, Event ID and Group ID. Generic placeholder image Page Fans : You can extract Facebook Page fans so easily. Facebook Data Scraper allows you to export peoples who likes your page, peoples who are commenting on recent posts in your page and also peoples who liked recent posts in your page. Generic placeholder image Group Members : You can search for Facebook Groups and Export members in Facebook Groups. Also you can import Facebook group Ids to extract members. You can include multiple groups for extraction members. Generic placeholder image Event Attending : Facebook Data Scraper can scrap peoples who are going for an event. You can export these users Facebook User ID and Facebook Email as in all others exports. Generic placeholder image Post Audience : Facebook Data Scraper allows you to export Facebook post audience&#039;s user id and Facebook email. You can export details of peoples who liked the post and users commented of it. Generic placeholder image Auto Invite : Auto invite feature lets you to automatically invite your all or selected friends to like your Facebook Page. You can also invite your friends to other pages that you are not admin.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/hhnkZjDvAwI?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><br><ul><li> Graph Search : Facebook Data Scraper supports Facebook Graph Search. You can execute Facebook Graph Search query on Facebook Data Scraper and you can export User ID, Email, Page User Name, Page ID, Event ID and Group ID. Generic placeholder image<br></li><li> Page Fans : You can extract Facebook Page fans so easily. Facebook Data Scraper allows you to export peoples who likes your page, peoples who are commenting on recent posts in your page and also peoples who liked recent posts in your page. Generic placeholder image<br></li><li> Group Members : You can search for Facebook Groups and Export members in Facebook Groups. Also you can import Facebook group Ids to extract members. You can include multiple groups for extraction members. Generic placeholder image<br></li><li> Event Attending : Facebook Data Scraper can scrap peoples who are going for an event. You can export these users Facebook User ID and Facebook Email as in all others exports. Generic placeholder image<br></li><li> Post Audience : Facebook Data Scraper allows you to export Facebook post audience's user id and Facebook email. You can export details of peoples who liked the post and users commented of it. Generic placeholder image<br></li><li> Auto Invite : Auto invite feature lets you to automatically invite your all or selected friends to like your Facebook Page. You can also invite your friends to other pages that you are not admin.<br></li></ul><br><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ea2Bw723gFE?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Facebook Data Scraper 1.47"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>F Targeter 1.37</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1776-fb-target-audience-finder.html</link>
<description>Name : F Targeter + Facebook User ID Converter Version : 1.37 + 2.0 OS : Windows Type : Facebook Lead Extractor, Twitter Lead Extractor Price : $237$/yearly Homepage : SalePage Facebook ID Scraper Scrape Facebook Emails and ID&#039;s from Graph Search, Pages, Groups and Events. This is facebook ID Scraper (FB Target Audience Finder) , a software to search and extract unique Facebook emails and user ID&#039;s from Graph Search, facebook pages(Exports ID&#039;s of people who have liked pages,commented or liked page posts),open or closed groups, posts and events to a text file.You can import Facebook Emails text file easily to facebook power editor to get custom audience.</description>
<category>Social Lead Extractor</category>
<enclosure url="http://facebookidscraper.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/08/solution_sitesweb_satellitecomm1-680x361.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 20:44:55 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Extract Facebook Emails from Facebook : Target active and most Passionate facebook users.Search in Graph Search, Fan pages, Groups and Events with a specific keyword or graph search query and extract Facebook Emails or ID&#039;s of users who liked pages, and who liked or commented page posts and save it to a text file. Export user Emails using Graph Search Queries : Use built in Facebook Graph Search options to narrow down your target audience!.You can find users based on location, gender, age group and more with graph search scraping.So get more potential customers using facebook id scraper. Import Facebook Emails To Custom Audience : Set up a Facebook custom audience campaign with your extracted targeted Facebook Emails.Import text Facebook Emails, extracted using Facebook ID Scraper, to Custom audience in Facebook Ads to get a massive amount of Targeted Traffic from Facebook Facebook User ID Converter</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/omfqtvSATOM?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" gesture="media" allow="encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><p><br></p><br><h3>Features</h3><br><p><br><ul><li> Extract Facebook Emails from Facebook : Target active and most Passionate facebook users.Search in Graph Search, Fan pages, Groups and Events with a specific keyword or graph search query and extract Facebook Emails or ID's of users who liked pages, and who liked or commented page posts and save it to a text file.<br></li><li> Export user Emails using Graph Search Queries : Use built in Facebook Graph Search options to narrow down your target audience!.You can find users based on location, gender, age group and more with graph search scraping.So get more potential customers using facebook id scraper.<br></li><li> Import Facebook Emails To Custom Audience : Set up a Facebook custom audience campaign with your extracted targeted Facebook Emails.Import text Facebook Emails, extracted using Facebook ID Scraper, to Custom audience in Facebook Ads to get a massive amount of Targeted Traffic from Facebook<br><br></li></ul><br><img src="http://facebookidscraper.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/08/solution_sitesweb_satellitecomm1-680x361.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="F Targeter 1.37"><br><br></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br><br></div></div><br><p><br><br></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><b>Facebook User ID Converter</b><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>