<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Fiverr Marketing - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Fiverr Marketing - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>AU Black Label Edition  5.3</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/868-arbitrage-underdog-reloaded.html</link>
<description>Name : Arbitrage Underdog RELOADED Black Label Edition + OTO1 + OTO2 Version : 5.3 OS : Windows Type : Fiverr Marketing, Craigslist Marketing,Elance Marketing, Odesk Marketing and Gumtree Marketing Price : $97 Homepage : SalePage Turn $5 Into $100-$1000...over and over with the most Successful, PROVEN Software of its kind! Arbitrage Underdog RELOADED is a business in a box; a career-making tool that has turned countless marketers, including newbies, into accomplished business owners. It also lends itself perfectly to outsourcing, making it ideal for advanced marketers looking to add another business to their bottom line. Since 2013, Arbitrage Underdog has given thousands of marketers an unfair advantage with Craigslist and Fiverr. Now updated for speed and 2014 changes, it has gone from powerful to industry-leading when it comes to online arbitrage. Arbitrage Underdog RELOADED is the only software of its kind that pulls results directly from Craigslist&#039;s database, producing leads in real time as they are posted on Craigslist. Within seconds Arbitrage Underdog RELOADED produces fresh, paying leads on one side of the screen, while matching those leads up with top rated sellers willing to do the job for $5 on the other side of the screen, eliminating hours of manual detective work. This allows you the user to be the middle-man, profiting handsomely every time!</description>
<category>Fiverr Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.arbitrageunderdogreloaded.com/jv/assets/img/softwarebox.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://antigurus.com/images/page4.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 04:06:50 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Quickly arbitrages suppliers on Fiverr with buyers on Craigslist FRESH leads DIRECTLY from Craigslist mainframe Uses Proprietary Smart Bot Technology Produces hundreds of FRESH leads in minutes Highly effective for both arbitrage and job search Doubles as the ultimate automated Fiverr, and Craigslist search tool The Ultimate All-In-One Arbitrage &amp;amp; Search Interface AU Black Label Edition (OTO) All the features of the Front End product, plus: Produces THOUSANDS of leads instead of hundreds, dramatically increasing profitability Searches all US states plus Canada, UK &amp;amp; Australia simultaneously, at the click of one button 50+ times faster search results Prevents duplicate emails Built in fully customizable email templates Also pulls leads from Elance, Odesk and Gumtree</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ttlJcCElUmU?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><p><br></p><br><h3>Features</h3><br><p><br><ul><li> Quickly arbitrages suppliers on Fiverr with buyers on Craigslist<br></li><li> FRESH leads DIRECTLY from Craigslist mainframe<br></li><li> Uses Proprietary Smart Bot Technology<br></li><li> Produces hundreds of FRESH leads in minutes<br></li><li> Highly effective for both arbitrage and job search<br></li><li> Doubles as the ultimate automated Fiverr, and Craigslist search tool<br></li><li> The Ultimate All-In-One Arbitrage &amp; Search Interface<br></li></ul><br>AU Black Label Edition (OTO)<br><ul><li> All the features of the Front End product, plus:<br></li><li> Produces THOUSANDS of leads instead of hundreds, dramatically increasing profitability<br></li><li> Searches all US states plus Canada, UK &amp; Australia simultaneously, at the click of one button<br></li><li> 50+ times faster search results<br></li><li> Prevents duplicate emails<br></li><li> Built in fully customizable email templates<br></li><li> Also pulls leads from Elance, Odesk and Gumtree<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://www.arbitrageunderdogreloaded.com/jv/assets/img/softwarebox.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="AU Black Label Edition  5.3"><br><img src="http://antigurus.com/images/page4.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Opportunity Bot 1.16</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1172-opportunity-bot.html</link>
<description>Name : Opportunity Bot Version : 1.16 OS : Windows Type : Fiverr Marketing, Craigslist Marketing, SeoClerks Marketing, Elance Marketing, Kijiji Marketing, GumTree Marketing, Upwork Marketing Price : $47 Homepage : SalePage Find 1000&#039;s of Hidden Deals up to 2000x Faster on 8 Biggest Arbitrage Sites Bypass Search Limits ~ Expose ALL Results</description>
<category>Fiverr Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://opportunitybot.com/BBHF-Thread.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2017 00:42:19 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Discover Deals &amp;amp; Opportunities Before Others Do Rapidly Harvest Info From 8 Authority Sites Save Hours/Days of Time Spot Instant Fulfilment Opportunities CraigsList Module : Gigs, Deals, Clients, Flips + more Fiverr Module : Find the best graphics outsourcers in minutes Kijiji Module : Gigs, Deals, Clients, Flips + more Upwork Module : Find miss-categorized gigs with no competition SeoClerks Module : Find the best SEO specialists in minutes GumTree Module : Gigs, Deals, Clients, Flips + more Elance Module : Find miss-categorized gigs with no competition</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><div class="dlevideoplayer" style="width:100%;max-width:425px;"><ul data-theme="default" data-preload="metadata"><li data-title="" data-type="youtube" data-url="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tsHxnSCoZZY"></li></ul></div></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Discover Deals &amp; Opportunities Before Others Do<br></li><li> Rapidly Harvest Info From 8 Authority Sites<br></li><li> Save Hours/Days of Time<br></li><li> Spot Instant Fulfilment Opportunities<br></li><li> CraigsList Module : Gigs, Deals, Clients, Flips + more<br></li><li> Fiverr Module : Find the best graphics outsourcers in minutes<br></li><li> Kijiji Module : Gigs, Deals, Clients, Flips + more<br></li><li> Upwork Module : Find miss-categorized gigs with no competition<br></li><li> SeoClerks Module : Find the best SEO specialists in minutes<br></li><li> GumTree Module : Gigs, Deals, Clients, Flips + more<br></li><li> Elance Module : Find miss-categorized gigs with no competition<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://opportunitybot.com/BBHF-Thread.jpg" alt="Opportunity Bot 1.16"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Realtor Suite 1.0.24</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1628-realtor-suite.html</link>
<description>Name : Realtor Suite Version : 1.0.24 OS : Windows Type : Realsteal Marketing Tools, Arbitrage Marketing Price : $57 Homepage : SalePage Email Millions of business people Are you constantly struggling to get more clients and it always feels like you are back to square one after you are done with a client you managed to catch? Realtor Suite Gives you the option to send automatic email message to every realtor registered in Realtor.Com (about two millions) Realtor Suite that is going to allow you to get in touch with literally millions of realtors all over the United States. The good thing about realtors is that they are always looking for talented people to hire for all kinds of jobs that are related to their field. This means that graphic and websites designers, marketers,SEO services, coaching, Virtual Assistance, Inte.com marketing, cleaning services, contractors, painting, remodeling, security, financing and all kinds of freelancing jobs are always on demand in their field.</description>
<category>Fiverr Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://automaticrealtor.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/software_001.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2016 03:39:31 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Live Sales and Pages Read : You can see Today, Yesterday, Last 7 days, Last 30 days worth of Live sales, pages read, and free downloads. Reviews and Stars : Easily see your review counts and stars for each book. You can always know which books need more reviews. Auto Finds All Your Books : Once it&#039;s installed, just click Import My Books. If you&#039;re logged into KDP, it auto finds all books &amp; grabs all stats. Makes Book Promos Easier : Every Title is a link to your book. Click to get description, or right-click &amp; copy/paste to give Amazon Link or ASIN. Links to Important Kindle URLs : Links to KDP Bookshelf, Reports, Author Central, Best Sellers, New Releases, Manage Devices, &amp; Send to Kindle. Best Sellers Rank : It&#039;s not the most important stat, but it sure gives you an idea of where your book is, and it&#039;s good to see. Never forget to change the price again : Ever change a price to try to get a little sales love and forget to change it back? See the price of every book. Even More Stats... KDPulse shows Author/Pen Name, Publish Date, Pages, and every title is a link to the book - click or copy/paste. Track Other Books for Sport : Keep track of a favorite author&#039;s or competitor&#039;s books.Add &#039;em to the Other Books tab to get all stats except sales. Current Book Promotion Sites List : Always on the hunt for book promotion sites? Now you can get an up-to-date list just a click away in KDPulse.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Q-Gx7Udm0jQ?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Live Sales and Pages Read : You can see Today, Yesterday, Last 7 days, Last 30 days worth of Live sales, pages read, and free downloads.<br /></li><li> Reviews and Stars : Easily see your review counts and stars for each book. You can always know which books need more reviews.<br /></li><li> Auto Finds All Your Books : Once it's installed, just click Import My Books. If you're logged into KDP, it auto finds all books & grabs all stats.<br /></li><li> Makes Book Promos Easier : Every Title is a link to your book. Click to get description, or right-click & copy/paste to give Amazon Link or ASIN.<br /></li><li> Links to Important Kindle URLs : Links to KDP Bookshelf, Reports, Author Central, Best Sellers, New Releases, Manage Devices, & Send to Kindle.<br /></li><li> Best Sellers Rank  : It's not the most important stat, but it sure gives you an idea of where your book is, and it's good to see.<br /></li><li> Never forget to change the price again : Ever change a price to try to get a little sales love and forget to change it back? See the price of every book.<br /></li><li> Even More Stats... KDPulse shows Author/Pen Name, Publish Date, Pages, and every title is a link to the book - click or copy/paste.<br /></li><li> Track Other Books for Sport : Keep track of a favorite author's or competitor's books.Add 'em to the Other Books tab to get all stats except sales.<br /></li><li> Current Book Promotion Sites List : Always on the hunt for book promotion sites? Now you can get an up-to-date list just a click away in KDPulse.<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://automaticrealtor.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/software_001.png" alt="Realtor Suite 1.0.24" title="Realtor Suite 1.0.24"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Realtor Suite 1.0.24" title="Realtor Suite 1.0.24"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Fiverr Automatic Seller 2.0.57</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1259-fiverr-automatic-seller.html</link>
<description>Name : Fiverr Automatic Seller Version : 2.0.57 OS : Windows Type : Fiverr Marketing Tools Price : $17 Homepage : SalePage &quot;New Fiverr Automatic Seller - Introducing The Best Bot Software for Fiverr Sellers&quot; Fiverr Automatic Seller software marketing gigs auto delivery messages</description>
<category>Fiverr Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/PfZ7lSCYBqc/hqdefault.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2016 02:12:19 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features The new Fiverr Automatic Seller support unlimited accounts and gigs. This is an advanced software that automates the delivery and messaging labor. The program checks every 30 seconds each account to detect new orders, modification requests, cancellation requests and messages. The software can control unlimited accounts at the same time. You can create unlimited projects in the program, one for each one of your accounts and add unlimited gigs for each project. In any one project, you can select the file from your computer have it sent to the buyers. The program immediately delivers the file after detecting a new order. In case that any client asks for a modification, a small window will appear on your computer’s desk showing the notification of the modification request and the client’s message. You can establish if you want to receive an alert sound or if you prefer the silent mode. You will be able to resend the modified file through that window with just push of a button. It&#039;s really that simple to use. And, in the case of messages, the software uses the same system than with the modification requests. You can talk with the clients through those windows without opening your browser. The delivery system is 100% automatic and in autopilot, while the messaging and sending system of modified files is semi-automatic to ensure a personalized attention to the client.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/PfZ7lSCYBqc?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> The new Fiverr Automatic Seller support unlimited accounts and gigs. <br /></li><li> This is an advanced software that automates the delivery and messaging labor. <br /></li><li> The program checks every 30 seconds each account to detect new orders, modification requests, cancellation requests and messages. <br /></li><li> The software can control unlimited accounts at the same time.<br /></li><li> You can create unlimited projects in the program, one for each one of your accounts and add unlimited gigs for each project. <br /></li><li> In any one project, you can select the file from your computer have it sent to the buyers.<br /></li><li> The program immediately delivers the file after detecting a new order.<br /></li><li> In case that any client asks for a modification, a small window will appear on your computer’s desk showing the notification of the modification request and the client’s message. <br /></li><li> You can establish if you want to receive an alert sound or if you prefer the silent mode. You will be able to resend the modified file through that window with just push of a button. <br /></li><li> It's really that simple to use.<br /></li><li> And, in the case of messages, the software uses the same system than with the modification requests. <br /></li><li> You can talk with the clients through those windows without opening your browser. <br /></li><li> The delivery system is 100% automatic and in autopilot, while the messaging and sending system of modified files is semi-automatic to ensure a personalized attention to the client.<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/PfZ7lSCYBqc/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Fiverr Automatic Seller 2.0.57" title="Fiverr Automatic Seller 2.0.57"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Fiverr Automatic Seller 2.0.57" title="Fiverr Automatic Seller 2.0.57"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Fiverr Demon 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1480-fiverr-demon.html</link>
<description>Name : Fiverr Demon – The Ultimate Fiverr Bot Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Fiverr Marketing Bot Price : $299 Homepage : SalePage Multi-threaded Fiverr bot with bulk account creator. This bot has been developed to work with Windows system only.</description>
<category>Fiverr Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://i.imgur.com/tCSbfjw.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2016 01:48:05 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Multi Account Management: Add Unlimited Accounts Support Proxies: User/Pass Authentication, IP authentication Bypass API: Acts Like A Browser User Fully Multi-Threaded Built In Proxy Checker Spintax Compatible: For Use With Poster Captcha Support: De-Captcher, DeathByCaptcha Random Delay Feature</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/ITlypAzHG1w?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Multi Account Management: Add Unlimited Accounts<br /></li><li> Support Proxies: User/Pass Authentication, IP authentication<br /></li><li> Bypass API: Acts Like A Browser User<br /></li><li> Fully Multi-Threaded<br /></li><li> Built In Proxy Checker<br /></li><li> Spintax Compatible: For Use With Poster<br /></li><li> Captcha Support: De-Captcher, DeathByCaptcha<br /></li><li> Random Delay Feature<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://i.imgur.com/tCSbfjw.png" alt="Fiverr Demon 1.0" title="Fiverr Demon 1.0"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Fiverr Demon 1.0" title="Fiverr Demon 1.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>GIG Prospector Pro 2.0.9</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1099-gig-prospector.html</link>
<description>Name : GIG Prospector Version : Pro 2.0.9 OS : Windows Type : Fiver Marketing Price : $47 Homepage : SalePage GIG Prospector – Best Software to loads all the information from Fiverr directly and scale your business to make more money faster GIG Prospector is Best software to find best service to outsource your job right from Fiverr and Gig. With GIG Prospector it is possible to locate every one of the top people in whatsoever category you’ll need. There’s no more experimentation dealing with bad workers. You will help the best contractors on the market.Gig Prospector sits on your desktop – and loads every piece of information straight to it. You’ll never again should check out fiverr to dig all night determing the best Gig.Just light up Gig Prospector and still have many incredible, time saving, income generating Fiverr experts when you need it! Gig Prospector Software Is an Adobe Air Software that sits right on your desktop and loads all the information from Fiverr directly to it. You’ll never again need to head to fiverr to dig for hours finding the right Gig. Just fire up Gig Prospector and have hundreds of incredible, time saving, money making Fiverr experts at your fingertips! It is extremely essential for any business to outsource things such as web design, graphics, sales copy, sales videos, and the list goes on and on.</description>
<category>Fiverr Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/iE8TVc-EfbI/hqdefault.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2015 02:38:38 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features One click search and blazing fast results! Easy sort features gives you the highest, fastest, best gigs on fiverr according to your search terms Everyone can use Gig Prospector – Affiliate Marketers, Product Creators, CPA, Offline marketers, or any other online business! All the relevant information at your finger tips – saves hours of work over time Eliminate stress and save hours and hours of time by outsourcing the hard stuff to the pro’s… for only five bucks! Cut down on the risk of getting screwed by only seeing the best gigs Never leave your desktop! Grab all the gig info without ever opening a browser window! Works On PC and Mac – Utilizing Adobe Air With Gig Prospector you can instantly find people to help you : Write content Build backlinks Design graphics Set up webpages Make videos Upload content Do social media And much more!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/l63KA7WNcj4?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> One click search and blazing fast results!<br /></li><li> Easy sort features gives you the highest, fastest, best gigs on fiverr according to your search terms<br /></li><li> Everyone can use Gig Prospector – Affiliate Marketers, Product Creators, CPA, Offline marketers, or any other online business!<br /></li><li> All the relevant information at your finger tips – saves hours of work over time<br /></li><li> Eliminate stress and save hours and hours of time by outsourcing the hard stuff to the pro’s… for only five bucks!<br /></li><li> Cut down on the risk of getting screwed by only seeing the best gigs<br /></li><li> Never leave your desktop! Grab all the gig info without ever opening a browser window!<br /></li><li> Works On PC and Mac – Utilizing Adobe Air<br /></li></ul><br />With Gig Prospector you can instantly find people to help you :<br /><ul><li> Write content<br /></li><li> Build backlinks<br /></li><li> Design graphics<br /></li><li> Set up webpages<br /></li><li> Make videos<br /></li><li> Upload content<br /></li><li> Do social media<br /></li><li> And much more!<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/iE8TVc-EfbI/hqdefault.jpg" alt="GIG Prospector Pro 2.0.9" title="GIG Prospector Pro 2.0.9"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="GIG Prospector Pro 2.0.9" title="GIG Prospector Pro 2.0.9"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Arbitrage Cash Cow 1.13</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/867-arbitrage-cash-cow.html</link>
<description>Name : Arbitrage Cash Cow Version : 1.13 OS : Windows Type : Fiverr Marketing, Craigslist Marketing, Aliexpress Marketing, SeoClerks Marketing, Elance Marketing, Kijiji Marketing, GumTree Marketing, Odesk Marketing Price : $17 Homepage : SalePage Search On Aliexpress , Fiverr, CraigsList, SeoClerks, Elance, Kijiji, GumTree, Odesk in Seconds Hey there, if you want to learn exactly how to make a solid income on CraigsList and Elance without ANY prior skills, experience or knowledge, you&#039;re in the right place. I simply couldn&#039;t believe just how easy this process was when I discovered it, and since I have, hundreds of other people around the world are making a KILLING by just following this system.</description>
<category>Fiverr Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2015 14:55:25 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Search ALL of CraigsList, Aliexpress , Fiverr, SeoClerks, Elance, Kijiji, GumTree, Odesk in Seconds Learn to Sell Services You Don&#039;t Even Do! Start an Import Empire 5 Different Ways to Start Earning TODAY! Module #1 - Arbi Module #2 - Gig Arbitrage Module #3 - Building the Empire Module #4 - Drop Shipper Module #5 - Outsource Like A Pro</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/cNHjNFh-rXI?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Search ALL of  CraigsList, Aliexpress , Fiverr, SeoClerks, Elance, Kijiji, GumTree, Odesk in Seconds<br></li><li> Learn to Sell Services You Don't Even Do!<br></li><li> Start an Import Empire<br></li><li> 5 Different Ways to Start Earning TODAY!<br></li><li> Module #1 - Arbi<br></li><li> Module #2 - Gig Arbitrage<br></li><li> Module #3 - Building the Empire<br></li><li> Module #4 - Drop Shipper<br></li><li> Module #5 - Outsource Like A Pro<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Arbitrage Cash Cow 1.13"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Buyer Arbitrage 1.0.7</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1160-buyer-arbitrage.html</link>
<description>Name : Buyer Arbitrage Version : 1.0.7 OS : Windows/MAC Type : Fiver Marketing, Craigslist Marketing Price : $47 Homepage : SalePage Buyer Arbitrage 1.0 is powerful desktop software (for pc or mac) that lets the user find hundreds of buyers for specific products or services. The software also finds top notch providers ready to fulfull the product or service the buyer is looking for. The user then has the option of personally providing the service, or simply hiring the third party to fulfill the order. Arbitrage is the near simultaneous purchase and sale of an asset in order to profit from the difference in price. Buyer Arbitrage 1.0 allows users to exploit this difference in price to achieve profits up to 95%.</description>
<category>Fiverr Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2015 08:59:52 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features This software really could help you make money online (a rare quality in IM software) Putting the software to use and then doing some work yourself you could make money in your first 24 hours. Easy to use. Not much of a learning curve. The software installs quickly and doesn’t seem to cause any system slow downs. This software is available for both PC &amp; Mac. Provides tons of results based on virtually any keyword of your choosing. It’s a truly unique software that fills a gap that the other IM applications have yet to address. The searches sometimes seem to drag on for several minutes for higher action keywords. There are very few filters that can be used to customize your search results. You’ll need to be a bit creative or have a bunch of existing search criteria in mind to make the most of this software. Possibility of saturation if you stick with the more common niches</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><video width="640" height="480" preload="metadata" poster="rss.xml" controls="controls">
						<source type="video/mp4" src="https://s3.amazonaws.com/protechmarketing/BuyerArbitrage/FrontSalesVideoJR.mp4"></source>
						</video></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> This software really could help you make money online (a rare quality in IM software)<br /></li><li> Putting the software to use and then doing some work yourself you could make money in your first 24 hours.<br /></li><li> Easy to use. Not much of a learning curve.<br /></li><li> The software installs quickly and doesn’t seem to cause any system slow downs.<br /></li><li> This software is available for both PC & Mac.<br /></li><li> Provides tons of results based on virtually any keyword of your choosing.<br /></li><li> It’s a truly unique software that fills a gap that the other IM applications have yet to address.<br /></li><li> The searches sometimes seem to drag on for several minutes for higher action keywords.<br /></li><li> There are very few filters that can be used to customize your search results.<br /></li><li> You’ll need to be a bit creative or have a bunch of existing search criteria in mind to make the most of this software.<br /></li><li> Possibility of saturation if you stick with the more common niches<br /></li></ul><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Buyer Arbitrage 1.0.7" title="Buyer Arbitrage 1.0.7"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Gig Commander 1.0.5</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1141-gig-commander.html</link>
<description>Name : Gig Commander Version : 1.0.5 OS : Windows/MAC Type : FIverr Marketing Tools, SEO clerks Marketing Tools Price : $47 Homepage : SalePage GIG Commander is a new, powerful tool that gives you the ability to quickly find, organize and order outsourcing help for Gig categories offered on FIverr and SEO clerks. This tool enables you to see a quick view of all gigs that meet your search criteria so you can quickly find the help you need. By being able to filter by Delivery Time, Positive Feedback Ratio and Number of Reviews your results will match the project without having to search through pages of gigs that don&#039;t meet that criteria!</description>
<category>Fiverr Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2015 05:07:34 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features All outsourcer leads/gigs are generated from either Fiverr or SEO Clerks depending on your search criteria filter/save/Favorites/Order Gig :::Free Members ::: Download Now Password : www.tgmember.com :::ViP Only:::</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><video width="640" height="480" preload="metadata" poster="rss.xml" controls="controls">
						<source type="video/mp4" src="http://embed.wistia.com/deliveries/c2b10b3417a6985a2fd7dd2f99160abd270eea9b/file.mp4"></source>
						</video></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> All outsourcer leads/gigs are generated from either Fiverr or SEO Clerks depending on your search criteria<br /></li><li> filter/save/Favorites/Order Gig<br /></li></ul><br /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><span style="font-size:12pt;"><b><span style="color:#006600">:::Free Members :::</span></b></span><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" alt="Gig Commander 1.0.5" title="Gig Commander 1.0.5"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><a href="http://www.tgmember.com/engine/go.php?url=aHR0cDovL3VzZXJzZmlsZXMuY29tL253OW03MXYybTk4cw%3D%3D"  target="_blank">Download Now</a><br />Password : www.tgmember.com<br /></div><br /></div><br /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><span style="font-size:12pt;"><b><span style="color:#FF0000">:::ViP Only:::</span></b></span><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Gig Commander 1.0.5" title="Gig Commander 1.0.5"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>