<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Viber Marketing - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Viber Marketing - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>SpamViber 2.5</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3479-spam-viber.html</link>
<description>Name : SpamViber Version : 2.5 OS : Windows Type : Viber Marketing Price : $50 Homepage : SalePage Mass Sending Viber Support Multi Account</description>
<category>Viber Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://joxi.ru/Y2L0JQNF6ZN126.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2017 17:39:27 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Convenient and simple interface Sending text messages up to 1000 symbols long with images Possibility of identification of mobile numbers which aren’t connected to Viber Possibility of adjustment of message sending speed Possibility of sending active links Delivery report after sending a message Import of phone numbers Possibility to generate numbers for sending messages High sending speed – 1200 messages per hour Multiaccount</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/A5tyeXYUs4U?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Convenient and simple interface<br></li><li> Sending text messages up to 1000 symbols long with images<br></li><li> Possibility of identification of mobile numbers which aren’t connected to Viber<br></li><li> Possibility of adjustment of message sending speed<br></li><li> Possibility of sending active links<br></li><li> Delivery report after sending a message<br></li><li> Import of phone numbers<br></li><li> Possibility to generate numbers for sending messages<br></li><li> High sending speed – 1200 messages per hour<br></li><li> Multiaccount<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://joxi.ru/Y2L0JQNF6ZN126.jpg" alt="SpamViber 2.5"><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Viber Demon 2017 2.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2170-viber-demon.html</link>
<description>Name : Viber Demon 2017 Version : 2.0 OS : Windows Type : Viber Sender Price : $97 Homepage : SalePage Viber Demon is new software that help you send messager to viber in bulk fast and more than..</description>
<category>Viber Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="https://www.turboware.com/wp-content/uploads/format_5.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2017 07:20:21 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Bulk Sender Very Fast! Easy to use.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><div class="dlevideoplayer" style="width:100%;max-width:425px;"><ul data-theme="default" data-preload="metadata"><li data-title="" data-type="youtube" data-url="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ly-kNElz8eM"></li></ul></div></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Bulk Sender<br></li><li> Very Fast!<br></li><li> Easy to use.<br></li></ul><br><img src="https://www.turboware.com/wp-content/uploads/format_5.png" alt="Viber Demon 2017 2.0"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Soft4 Viber Marketing 6.3</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2046-soft4-viber-marketing.html</link>
<description>Name : Soft4 Viber Marketing Version : 6.3 OS : Windows Type : Viber Marketing Tools Price : $125 Homepage : SalePage Viber Marketing Software - Bulk Message Sender on Viber With Viber, everyone in the world are able to connect for free. Viber number of users more and more, accompanied by huge demand in new market segments this potential. Stemming from that demand, we have completed and provide adware on Viber - products support users to send advertising messages to all those who use Viber,</description>
<category>Viber Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://bptech.solid.vn/ImgUpload/Viber%20Marketing%2022.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2016 14:15:00 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Automatically send messages and pictures to bulk users Viber Users automatically filter and connect with the phone number are using Viber Automatically follow the birth of the first available phone number (If you do not have a list of numbers available) Enter a list of files automatically from .txt, .csv Automatically send bulk message to a phone number with a speed 2-3 seconds / news Save results on Viber messaging when the machine is turned off suddenly Enter your phone number from Excel: you can enter a list of phone number from a text file or series excel. Statistics detailing the message was sent, the message received, the message is waiting Automatic stop when weak.comwork connection, automatically run when the.comwork stability program While software runs not affect other activities of users Account manually change viber (This feature only premium version) Send Message multinational</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/lswM7vpnY94?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Automatically send messages and pictures to bulk users Viber<br /></li><li> Users automatically filter and connect with the phone number are using Viber<br /></li><li> Automatically follow the birth of the first available phone number (If you do not have a list of numbers available)<br /></li><li> Enter a list of files automatically from .txt, .csv<br /></li><li> Automatically send bulk message to a phone number with a speed 2-3 seconds / news<br /></li><li> Save results on Viber messaging when the machine is turned off suddenly<br /></li><li> Enter your phone number from Excel: you can enter a list of phone number from a text file or series excel.<br /></li><li> Statistics detailing the message was sent, the message received, the message is waiting<br /></li><li> Automatic stop when weak.comwork connection, automatically run when the.comwork stability program<br /></li><li> While software runs not affect other activities of users<br /></li><li> Account manually change viber (This feature only premium version)<br /></li><li> Send Message multinational<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://bptech.solid.vn/ImgUpload/Viber%20Marketing%2022.png" alt="Soft4 Viber Marketing 6.3" title="Soft4 Viber Marketing 6.3"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Soft4 Viber Marketing 6.3" title="Soft4 Viber Marketing 6.3"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Queensoft - ViberMarketing 6.42</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1934-queensoft-viber-marketing.html</link>
<description>Name : Queensoft - ViberMarketing 2016 Version : 6.42 OS : Windows Type : Viber Marketing Tool Price : $99 Homepage : SalePage Queensoft - ViberMarketing is Bulk Sender to Viber and Viber Register Marketing Tools, Also have Filter Number</description>
<category>Viber Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2016-08/thumbs/1471446326_ejbodkr.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2016 21:55:48 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Register Channels For Sending Send text message and image Basic Filter (should use Viber Filter instead of this function) Send From Queue : This function allows automatic pickup a new data to send Tips : - should share the queue folder, so u can add new data to queue at run time.Therefore you can run 24hours without any manual controls Monitor tool : This function allow to monitor progress of Viber Marketings From a computer Save and Restore : This function allows save an incomplete task and restore later</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/HtXrOWZuw80?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Register Channels For Sending<br /></li><li> Send text message and image<br /></li><li> Basic Filter (should use Viber Filter instead of this function)<br /></li><li> Send From Queue : This function allows automatic pickup a new data to send<br /></li><li> Tips : - should share the queue folder, so u can add new data to queue at run time.Therefore you can run 24hours without any manual controls<br /></li><li> Monitor tool : This function allow to monitor progress of Viber Marketings From a computer<br /></li><li> Save and Restore : This function allows save an incomplete task and restore later<br /></li></ul><br /><a href="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2016-08/1471446326_ejbodkr.png" rel="highslide" class="highslide" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2016-08/thumbs/1471446326_ejbodkr.png" alt='Queensoft - ViberMarketing 6.42' title='Queensoft - ViberMarketing 6.42'  /></a><br /><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/vBpBctL-QEM?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Queensoft - ViberMarketing 6.42" title="Queensoft - ViberMarketing 6.42"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Viber Marketing Ads 3.5.1.1 Pro</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1340-viber-marketing-ads.html</link>
<description>Name : Viber Marketing Ads Version : 3.5.1.1 Pro OS : Windows Type : Viber Marketing Tools Price : $559 Homepage : SalePage Viber mass advertising software (Viber Marketing Software): Bank country mobile numbers to 12 million daily download number with 25 thousand numbers in 24 hours Web services provide a virtual line online, the software provided virtual lines Viber for download moments after payment Bank unions and various businesses in the capacity of 43 MB in the form of Excel file Usability on the virtual Windows system does not Drgbr you can work with the same system</description>
<category>Viber Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://dpws.ir/img/Viber/ViberMarketing4.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2015 20:20:17 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features User-friendly interface and simple Group of numbers and contacts and reporting to the separation group Send Text Messages Without Limits (1000 characters) as well as photo and file 8 messages are sent in the forms of text, image, sound and flame and links ... Send messages to get 100% even without one message has been received The ability to recognize numbers that are not already have Viber Adjustable speed of sending messages Send a link to the product website Viber messages with unlimited free advertising Creating a virtual number for activation America Viber for free and unlimited Easy installation and a year of free support Rae various reports: successful posts, posts failed to provide output files in formats Txt, Xls, Xlsx, Pdf Send report as an Excel file Enter the number of recipients from Excel file Enter the number of recipients manually Number of recipients on the basis of the range Entering multiple text messages at random each text recipients Sending variable text with keyword (insert number of the recipient, time and number of letters in the history of the solar and ad text) Chshgmyr reduce the number of virtual blocks by selecting the advanced formula to send Allowing multiple virtual register Installed on the virtual server Importantly, the use of this application: Circulating use virtual lines to prevent the closure of the virtual lines High transmission speed</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><object id="mediaPlayer" width="640" height="480" classid="CLSID:6BF52A52-394A-11d3-B153-00C04F79FAA6" standby="Loading Microsoft Windows Media Player components..." type="application/x-oleobject">
				<param name="url" VALUE="http://hn6.asset.aparat.com/aparat-video/7cb6bd1c560f4468b6245de819ddc2222366296-360p__25671.apt" />
				<param name="autoStart" VALUE="0" />
				<param name="showControls" VALUE="true" />
				<param name="TransparentatStart" VALUE="false" />
				<param name="AnimationatStart" VALUE="true" />
				<param name="StretchToFit" VALUE="true" />
				<embed pluginspage="http://www.microsoft.com/Windows/Downloads/Contents/MediaPlayer/" src="http://hn6.asset.aparat.com/aparat-video/7cb6bd1c560f4468b6245de819ddc2222366296-360p__25671.apt" width="640" height="480" type="application/x-mplayer2" autorewind="1" showstatusbar="1" showcontrols="1" autostart="0" allowchangedisplaysize="1" volume="70" stretchtofit="1"></embed>
				</object></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> User-friendly interface and simple<br /></li><li> Group of numbers and contacts and reporting to the separation group<br /></li><li> Send Text Messages Without Limits (1000 characters) as well as photo and file<br /></li><li> 8 messages are sent in the forms of text, image, sound and flame and links ...<br /></li><li> Send messages to get 100% even without one message has been received<br /></li><li> The ability to recognize numbers that are not already have Viber<br /></li><li> Adjustable speed of sending messages<br /></li><li> Send a link to the product website<br /></li><li> Viber messages with unlimited free advertising<br /></li><li> Creating a virtual number for activation America Viber for free and unlimited<br /></li><li> Easy installation and a year of free support<br /></li><li> Rae various reports: successful posts, posts failed to provide output files in formats Txt, Xls, Xlsx, Pdf<br /></li><li> Send report as an Excel file<br /></li><li> Enter the number of recipients from Excel file<br /></li><li> Enter the number of recipients manually<br /></li><li> Number of recipients on the basis of the range<br /></li><li> Entering multiple text messages at random each text recipients<br /></li><li> Sending variable text with keyword (insert number of the recipient, time and number of letters in the history of the solar and ad text)<br /></li><li> Chshgmyr reduce the number of virtual blocks by selecting the advanced formula to send<br /></li><li> Allowing multiple virtual register<br /></li><li> Installed on the virtual server<br /></li><li> Importantly, the use of this application:<br /></li><li> Circulating use virtual lines to prevent the closure of the virtual lines<br /></li><li> High transmission speed<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://dpws.ir/img/Viber/ViberMarketing4.png" alt="Viber Marketing Ads 3.5.1.1 Pro" title="Viber Marketing Ads 3.5.1.1 Pro"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Viber Marketing Ads 3.5.1.1 Pro" title="Viber Marketing Ads 3.5.1.1 Pro"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Viber Mint Checker 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1335-viber-mint-checker.html</link>
<description>Name : Viber Mint Checker Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Viber Marketing Tools Price : $99 Homepage : [leech=]SalePage[/leech] Viber Phone Number Checker Program checks phone numbers and have them in check or not v Quick checker rooms for the presence of Viber. It works through a proxy. Checa at 100 000 numbers per hour! In contrast, our program distribution service guarantees a high conversion and a lot of targeted traffic at a reasonable cost.</description>
<category>Viber Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-09/1443466357_249852632.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2015 23:01:20 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Import Numbers: Import excel/csv file containing whatsapp numbers and it will find active channels Numbers in range (From-To): You have to enter range of channels and it will find active channels. You can save these channels into csv or text file and use it for social marketing by yourself.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/LEyUlbzicE8?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Import Numbers: Import excel/csv file containing whatsapp numbers and it will find active channels<br /></li><li> Numbers in range (From-To): You have to enter range of channels and it will find active channels.<br /></li><li> You can save these channels into csv or text file and use it for social marketing by yourself.<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-09/1443466357_249852632.jpg" alt="Viber Mint Checker 1.0" title="Viber Mint Checker 1.0"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Viber Mint Checker 1.0" title="Viber Mint Checker 1.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>VirberAd 1.7 Pro</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1134-virberad.html</link>
<description>Name : VirberAd Version : Pro 1.7.0.0 OS : Windows Type : Viber Marketing Tools Price : $113 Homepage : SalePage Enjoy free advertising on Viber with VirberAd software. Send your bulk text and multimedia ads to anyone, anywhere, FREELY on Viber ! ViberAd is an advertisement manager software that allows you to send your advertisement messages freely. You can send your messages as text or image with live links for all viber users all over the world. With vibers 500 million active users it’s the best advertisement opportunity.</description>
<category>Viber Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-09/thumbs/1441149084_20.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2015 03:10:33 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Comfortable and simple software interface Send text messages up to 1000 character with images Ability to recognize mobile numbers that are not Viber users Ability to adjust messages sending speed Ability to send live links Send unlimited messages Not need to install Viber for Desktop With tutorial of purchasing unlimited free virtual mobile numbers from USA to activate Viber Simple installation prosess Delivery report after sending messages (excel export and screenshots) Import phone numbers from excel Ability to inserting numbers manually Ability to generate batch numbers with range Ability to send special messages to specified numbers from excel High sending speed (approximately 1200 message per hour) :::Free Members ::: Download Now Password : www.tgmember.com :::ViP Only:::</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/WLbMJDmjsco?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Comfortable and simple software interface<br /></li><li> Send text messages up to 1000 character with images<br /></li><li> Ability to recognize mobile numbers that are not Viber users<br /></li><li> Ability to adjust messages sending speed<br /></li><li> Ability to send live links<br /></li><li> Send unlimited messages<br /></li><li> Not need to install Viber for Desktop<br /></li><li> With tutorial of purchasing unlimited free virtual mobile numbers from USA to activate Viber<br /></li><li> Simple installation prosess<br /></li><li> Delivery report after sending messages (excel export and screenshots)<br /></li><li> Import phone numbers from excel<br /></li><li> Ability to inserting numbers manually<br /></li><li> Ability to generate batch numbers with range<br /></li><li> Ability to send special messages to specified numbers from excel<br /></li><li> High sending speed (approximately 1200 message per hour)<br /></li></ul><br /><a href="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-09/1441149084_20.png" rel="highslide" class="highslide"><img src="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-09/thumbs/1441149084_20.png" alt='VirberAd 1.7 Pro' title='VirberAd 1.7 Pro'  /></a><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><span style="font-size:12pt;"><b><span style="color:#006600">:::Free Members  :::</span></b></span><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" alt="VirberAd 1.7 Pro" title="VirberAd 1.7 Pro"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><a href="http://www.tgmember.com/engine/go.php?url=aHR0cDovL3VzZXJzZmlsZXMuY29tL2x0djA2MDZnMXdxYg%3D%3D"  target="_blank">Download Now</a><br />Password : www.tgmember.com<br /></div><br /></div><br /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><span style="font-size:12pt;"><b><span style="color:#FF0000">:::ViP Only:::</span></b></span><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="VirberAd 1.7 Pro" title="VirberAd 1.7 Pro"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Viber Bulk Sender VBS 2.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1132-viber-bulk-sender.html</link>
<description>Name : Viber Bulk Sender VBS Version : Elite 2.0 OS : Windows Type : Viber Marketing Tools Price : $113 Homepage : SalePage Viber VBS is an advertisement manager software, that allows you to send your advertisement messages. You can send your messages as text or image with live links for all Viber users all over the world. 500 million active Viber users - it’s the best advertisement opportunity. It’s incredibly simple to launch an effective marketing campaign to bring in business with a low-cost advertising tool. With this unique system You can send messages without any speed loss and time loss to unlimited Viber users! Viber VBS software does not violate the law on advertising, because they are not SMS. Viber VBS software has a unique anti blocking system for preventing of Viber account blockage.</description>
<category>Viber Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2015 01:00:19 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Comfortable and simple software interface Send text messages up to 1000 character with images Ability to recognize mobile numbers that are not Viber users Ability to adjust messages sending speed Ability to send live links Send unlimited messages Not need to install Viber for Desktop With tutorial of purchasing unlimited free virtual mobile numbers from USA to activate Viber Simple installation prosess Delivery report after sending messages (excel export and screenshots) Import phone numbers from excel Ability to inserting numbers manually Ability to generate batch numbers with range Ability to send special messages to specified numbers from excel High sending speed (approximately 1200 message per hour)</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/R_zgHmj2AJI?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Comfortable and simple software interface<br /></li><li> Send text messages up to 1000 character with images<br /></li><li> Ability to recognize mobile numbers that are not Viber users<br /></li><li> Ability to adjust messages sending speed<br /></li><li> Ability to send live links<br /></li><li> Send unlimited messages<br /></li><li> Not need to install Viber for Desktop<br /></li><li> With tutorial of purchasing unlimited free virtual mobile numbers from USA to activate Viber<br /></li><li> Simple installation prosess<br /></li><li> Delivery report after sending messages (excel export and screenshots)<br /></li><li> Import phone numbers from excel<br /></li><li> Ability to inserting numbers manually<br /></li><li> Ability to generate batch numbers with range<br /></li><li> Ability to send special messages to specified numbers from excel<br /></li><li> High sending speed (approximately 1200 message per hour)<br /></li></ul><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Viber Bulk Sender VBS 2.0" title="Viber Bulk Sender VBS 2.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>