<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Autoresponder - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Autoresponder - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>TEAR 3.2.5 Pro</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1917-tear.html</link>
<description>Name : Total Email Auto Responder Version : 3.2.5 Pro OS : Windows Type : Email Marketing Tool Price : $69.99 / month Homepage : SalePage TEAR can completely replace your sales force &amp; deliver you qualified leads,ready to buy your product or service every day. Automated Prospect Finder to Qualified Lead Converter TEAR is the #1 Mass Emailing Software that allows you to setup mutli-series autoresponders to replicate real conversations, increasing conversions exponentially! Anything you do online can be put under the scope &amp; improved. Finish any other job that you might have done before, better.</description>
<category>Autoresponder</category>
<enclosure url="https://totalemailautoresponder.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/11/Autoresponder-templates.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2016 10:15:55 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Multi-Response AR : Create long conversations with your leads to help maintain healthy IP’s and boost conversions through the roof! Email List Importer : Upload your own list of email leads into this software. Don’t wait for list approval from other services like Aweber! Custom Smtp/Pop3 : Use your own hosted smtp/pop3 for sending and receiving emails! Or even use gmail, yahoo, hotmail, etc services! Proxy Importer : Easily import unlimited proxy’s into the system from a file or url link. Bind them to SMTP accounts to mass mail Gmail, AOL Yahoo. Custom Variables : Tons of tokens available such as: #ToName #Today #Month #FromFirstName. Or make your own custom Variables! Text Spinner : Easily spin words, sentences, names and urls in your email bodies to ensure unique content and higher inbox rates! Keyword Triggers : Boost Sales by setting custom responses triggered by keywords. Ex. Email Ghosting : Keep your IP’s clean. Send email from example@hotmail.com and receiver will see sent from: name@yourdomain.com Filters : Many custom filters offer extremely flexible responses to incoming emails. Feature not available in email services like Aweber and GetResponse! Live Statistics : Always keep track of sent and pending emails! Break down your daily statistics to the minute! Data Exporter : Easily export email lists into and out of the software. Your leads are always at your fingertips ready to make you money. Timer Settings : Easily select specific hours of the day to stop the program from sending emails to replicate a real person. Blacklist : Keep your IP’s and safe and clean. Import a blacklist of email addresses you want to avoid at all times. Account Unlocking : Unlock your SMTP accounts at any time if blocked (Hotmail, Yahoo, Aol) A Decaptcher account is required… Attachments : Easily attach images or other files to your email templates. A awesome feature restricted by other email services! Tutorials : Don’t feel alone and helpless with our easy to follow tutorials! Let us help you start making money right away! IP Tester : Always know which of your IP’s are working to ensure the best possible connections and success rates! Always Updated : Not only has our programming team created this epic software, but we use it daily constantly making sure it’s working. Email Leads Extractor : Extract your leads from your gmail/yahoo/etc… accounts into txt file. Re-m.comize Pre-Built Email Campaigns : Don’t know how to setup your autoresponder? Try out one of our free pre-built email campaigns! Set Hourly Sending Limits : Have the ability to set sending limits that work best with the various requirements of your email accounts.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><div class="dlevideoplayer" style="width:100%;max-width:425px;"><ul data-theme="default" data-preload="metadata"><li data-title="" data-type="youtube" data-url="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LLCsfzhBJHo"></li></ul></div></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Multi-Response AR : Create long conversations with your leads to help maintain healthy IP’s and boost conversions through the roof!<br /></li><li> Email List Importer : Upload your own list of email leads into this software. Don’t wait for list approval from other services like Aweber!<br /></li><li> Custom Smtp/Pop3 : Use your own hosted smtp/pop3 for sending and receiving emails! Or even use gmail, yahoo, hotmail, etc services!<br /></li><li> Proxy Importer : Easily import unlimited proxy’s into the system from a file or url link. Bind them to SMTP accounts to mass mail Gmail, AOL Yahoo.<br /></li><li> Custom Variables : Tons of tokens available such as: #ToName #Today #Month #FromFirstName. Or make your own custom Variables!<br /></li><li> Text Spinner : Easily spin words, sentences, names and urls in your email bodies to ensure unique content and higher inbox rates!<br /></li><li> Keyword Triggers : Boost Sales by setting custom responses triggered by keywords. Ex. <Are you i am /><br /></li><li> Email Ghosting : Keep your IP’s clean. Send email from example@hotmail.com and receiver will see sent from: name@yourdomain.com<br /></li><li> Filters : Many custom filters offer extremely flexible responses to incoming emails. Feature not available in email services like Aweber and GetResponse!<br /></li><li> Live Statistics : Always keep track of sent and pending emails! Break down your daily statistics to the minute!<br /></li><li> Data Exporter : Easily export email lists into and out of the software. Your leads are always at your fingertips ready to make you money.<br /></li><li> Timer Settings : Easily select specific hours of the day to stop the program from sending emails to replicate a real person.<br /></li><li> Blacklist : Keep your IP’s and safe and clean. Import a blacklist of email addresses  you want to avoid at all times.<br /></li><li> Account Unlocking : Unlock your SMTP accounts at any time if blocked (Hotmail, Yahoo, Aol) A Decaptcher account is required…<br /></li><li> Attachments : Easily attach images or other files to your email templates. A awesome feature restricted by other email services!<br /></li><li> Tutorials : Don’t feel alone and helpless with our easy to follow tutorials! Let us help you start making money right away!<br /></li><li> IP Tester : Always know which of your IP’s are working to ensure the best possible connections and success rates!<br /></li><li> Always Updated : Not only has our programming team created this epic software, but we use it daily constantly making sure it’s working.<br /></li><li> Email Leads Extractor : Extract your leads from your gmail/yahoo/etc… accounts into txt file. Re-m.comize<br /></li><li> Pre-Built Email Campaigns : Don’t know how to setup your autoresponder? Try out one of our free pre-built email campaigns!<br /></li><li> Set Hourly Sending Limits : Have the ability to set sending limits that work best with the various requirements of your email accounts.<br /><br /></li></ul><br /><img src="https://totalemailautoresponder.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/11/Autoresponder-templates.jpg" alt="TEAR 3.2.5 Pro" title="TEAR 3.2.5 Pro"  /><br /><div class="dlevideoplayer" style="width:100%;max-width:425px;">
			<ul data-theme="default" data-preload="metadata">
				<li data-title="tear-gif-hp-edited" data-type="m4v" data-url="https://totalemailautoresponder.com/tear-gif-hp-edited.mp4" ></li>
			</ul>
		</div><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="TEAR 3.2.5 Pro" title="TEAR 3.2.5 Pro"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Email Autoresponder Pro 3.1.5</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1469-email-autoresponder.html</link>
<description>Name : Email Autoresponder Version : Pro 3.1.5 OS : Windows Type : Email Marketing Tools Price : $74.95 Homepage : SalePage Email Autoresponder is an easy desktop email marketing software that delivers your auto responders ranging from the simplest &quot;I&#039;m out of office&quot; to personalized HTML messages and newsletters. &quot;Email Autoresponder is the most comprehensive and simple email marketing software. With excellent designs and powerful features you can get best results and beat your competitors.&quot;</description>
<category>Autoresponder</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.email-unlimited.com/images/email-autoresponder/autoresponder-contacts.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2016 21:57:35 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Powerful Contact Lists Management Powerful HTML Editor: Flash, Images, Attachments. Looping protection Processes bounced emails Import and Export Features: Easy import/export email address list files. Imports from Microsoft Outlook, Windows Address Book , Excel, CSV, Text Imports from External Data Sources through ODBC/OLE DB: Access, MS SQL, Oracle, MySQL, Dbase, Foxpro, Paradox. Exports to Excel, Text, External Data Sources through ODBC/OLE DB. Sending Features: Ability to resend unlimited times to failed recipients Creates a detailed log for every operation Other Features: Text/HTML Email formats Full support for international characters. Multiple customizable easy-to-use mail accounts. Styled text support Process tags in subject Email Autoresponder Awards High Personalization. With Email Autoresponder you can send highly customized messages including personalized message bodies and subject to every recipient using the powerful Merge feature. This is the most efficient way to make contact with your clients, that will bring you the highest response rate. Make Rich Colorful HTML Messages. Our software allows you to include any fonts, graphics and colors turning your messages into professional online newsletters. Flash Animation Movies You can send Flash movies embedded inside the message itself. So your message will deliver a high quality content as sound and video. File Attachment. Send attached documents and files as many as you need. Powerful List Management. Manage an unlimited number of groups/lists with an unlimited number of recipients in each. Merge lists, extract , remove duplicates and perform many other operations. Support of HTML and Text email formats Email Autoresponder provides you with a fully featured message editor. In addition to the plain text message format, there is a HTML editor. Program automatically creates a plain text message alternative while you are editing. By default recipients view HTML part of message, if their mail reader does not support HTML the message will be shown in plain text so everyone can view it. You can design your email message directly within Software, or in another program and then load it into Email Autoresponder.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Powerful Contact Lists Management<br /></li><li> Powerful HTML Editor: Flash, Images, Attachments.<br /></li><li> Looping protection<br /></li><li> Processes bounced emails<br /></li><li> Import and Export Features:<br /></li><li> Easy import/export email address list files.<br /></li><li> Imports from Microsoft Outlook, Windows Address Book , Excel, CSV, Text<br /></li><li> Imports from External Data Sources through ODBC/OLE DB: Access, MS SQL, Oracle, MySQL, Dbase, Foxpro, Paradox.<br /></li><li> Exports to Excel, Text, External Data Sources through ODBC/OLE DB.<br /></li></ul><br />Sending Features:<ul><li> Ability to resend unlimited times to failed recipients<br /></li><li> Creates a detailed log for every operation<br /></li></ul><br />Other Features:<br /><ul><li> Text/HTML Email formats<br /></li><li> Full support for international characters.<br /></li><li> Multiple customizable easy-to-use mail accounts.<br /></li><li> Styled text support<br /></li><li> Process tags in subject<br /></li><li> Email Autoresponder Awards<br /></li><li> High Personalization.<br /></li></ul><br />With Email Autoresponder you can send highly customized messages including personalized message bodies and subject to every recipient using the powerful Merge feature. This is the most efficient way to make contact with your clients, that will bring you the highest response rate.<br /><br /><b>Make Rich Colorful HTML Messages. <br /></b><br />Our software allows you to include any fonts, graphics and colors turning your messages into professional online newsletters.<br /><br /><b>Flash Animation Movies<br /></b><br />You can send Flash movies embedded inside the message itself. So your message will deliver a high quality content  as sound and video.<br /><br />File Attachment. Send attached documents and files as many as you need.<br /><br /><b>Powerful List Management.<br /></b><br />Manage an unlimited number of groups/lists with an unlimited number of recipients in each. Merge lists, extract , remove duplicates and perform many other operations.<br /><br /><b>Support of  HTML and Text email formats<br /></b><br />Email Autoresponder provides you with a fully featured message editor. In addition to the plain text message format, there is a HTML editor. <br /><br />Program automatically creates a plain text message alternative while you are editing. By default recipients view HTML part of message, if their mail reader does not support HTML the message will be shown in plain text so everyone can view it. <br /><br />You can design your email message directly within Software, or in another program and then load it into Email Autoresponder.<br /><br /><br /><img src="http://www.email-unlimited.com/images/email-autoresponder/autoresponder-contacts.jpg" alt="Email Autoresponder Pro 3.1.5" title="Email Autoresponder Pro 3.1.5"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Email Autoresponder Pro 3.1.5" title="Email Autoresponder Pro 3.1.5"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>GR Jeet 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1291-gr-jeet.html</link>
<description>Name : GR Jeet Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Email Marketing Tools Price : $0 Homepage : SalePage GR Jeet - Email Scheduler For GetResponse Mail using your Getresponse account very quickly. Use this utility.</description>
<category>Autoresponder</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2015 18:45:42 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Fast Email to your camp at Getresponse</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/erO4FXIuwSE?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Fast Email to your camp at Getresponse<br /></li></ul><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="GR Jeet 1.0" title="GR Jeet 1.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>