<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Image &amp; Design - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Image &amp; Design - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>Memester Video Edition 1.3.4 Agency</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4072-memester.html</link>
<description>Name : Memester Video Edition Version : 1.3.4 Agency OS : Windows Type : meme Creator, GIF Creator Price : $575 Homepage : SalePage The best video and gif meme creating software made for Facebook and YouTube and Twitter. Create video memes and animated gifs easily and post automatically to multiple social media platforms. Memester is a desktop based software made for Facebook and YouTube with features you’ve never seen earlier. It helps you create awesome viral videos and animated gifs that attract viewer attention and explode fanpage reach. You can pick any video source and turn it into a viral video. Including video from your computer, or even videos from YouTube.</description>
<category>Image &amp; Design</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 13:17:18 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Dashboard : Get a bird’s eye view of how your traffic tactics are working, and see how each profile is performing. Search Videos : Put in a keyword and find videos that you can easily turn into memes with just some clicks. Video Memes : Find all your ready video memes here, or create new video memes for publishing easily. Search GIFs : Put in a keyword and find GIFs that you can turn into a meme instantly. GIF Memes : See all your GIF memes and publish them, or create fresh GIF memes fast. Scheduled Memes : Take a look at the memes you’ve scheduled for publishing later, or publish fresh memes. Profiles : Add your Facebook pages, profiles, YouTube channels or Twitter IDs to publish memes on.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Shmpklicavg?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Dashboard : Get a bird’s eye view of how your traffic tactics are working, and see how each profile is performing.<br></li><li> Search Videos : Put in a keyword and find videos that you can easily turn into memes with just some clicks.<br></li><li> Video Memes : Find all your ready video memes here, or create new video memes for publishing easily.<br></li><li> Search GIFs : Put in a keyword and find GIFs that you can turn into a meme instantly.<br></li><li> GIF Memes : See all your GIF memes and publish them, or create fresh GIF memes fast.<br></li><li> Scheduled Memes : Take a look at the memes you’ve scheduled for publishing later, or publish fresh memes.<br></li><li> Profiles : Add your Facebook pages, profiles, YouTube channels or Twitter IDs to publish memes on.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Memester Video Edition 1.3.4 Agency"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>TeKnife Images Manager 1.0.1</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4455-teknife-images-manager.html</link>
<description>Name : TeKnife Images Manager Version : 1.0.1 OS : Windows Type : Image Scraper Price : $47 Homepage : SalePage TeKnife Images Manager : Google Images Scraper Bulk images type converter Bulk images watermark by text bulk images watermark by image bulk images convert to black &amp;amp; white style (grey style)</description>
<category>Image &amp; Design</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 09:22:06 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Tools Included : - Google Images Scraper - Bulk images type converter - Bulk images watermark by text - bulk images watermark by image - bulk images convert to black &amp;amp; white style (grey style) Main Features : 1. Multi threaded , any time stop resume the process . 2. easy to use and friendly user interface . 3. Three Days FREE trail with full functionality . 4. lifetime updates . 5. 30 days refund policy after purchase .</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Tools Included :<br></li><li> - Google Images Scraper<br></li><li> - Bulk images type converter<br></li><li> - Bulk images watermark by text<br></li><li> - bulk images watermark by image<br></li><li> - bulk images convert to black &amp; white style (grey style)<br></li><li> Main Features :<br></li><li> 1. Multi threaded , any time stop resume the process .<br></li><li> 2. easy to use and friendly user interface .<br></li><li> 3. Three Days FREE trail with full functionality .<br></li><li> 4. lifetime updates .<br></li><li> 5. 30 days refund policy after purchase .<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="TeKnife Images Manager 1.0.1"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>EximiousSoft Banner Maker 5.46</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4230-eximioussoft-banner-maker.html</link>
<description>Name : EximiousSoft Banner Maker Version : 5.46 OS : Windows Type : Tool to Create, Design GIF Banner ads Price : $44.95 Homepage : SalePage It is a great application for ceating GIF banner ads. web buttons and headers etc. web graphics. It has all essential vector-based drawing tools and supports layer editing fully. Banner Maker (Pro) comes with 500+ banner &amp;amp; 200+ web button templeates, 5000+ preseted symbols and many pre-designed gradient style for every designer. It also provides 60+ visual effects to build impressive animations or GIF banners by one click. Each drawing shape object can be made with drop shadow, glow, reflection, 3D bevel etc. visual effects.</description>
<category>Image &amp; Design</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 06:41:03 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features - Edit web graphics with full image painted tools and vctor-based drawing tools. - Provides 60+ effects to build animated attractive GIF banners by one click. - Provides 500+ banner &amp;amp; 200+ button pre-designed templates and 5000+ symbols and many preseted gardient sytle, textures. - Supports layer editing and each object can be rendered with drop shadow, glow, reflection,3d bevel effects.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> - Edit web graphics with full image painted tools and vctor-based drawing tools.<br></li><li> - Provides 60+ effects to build animated attractive GIF banners by one click.<br></li><li> - Provides 500+ banner &amp; 200+ button pre-designed templates and 5000+ symbols and many preseted gardient sytle, textures.<br></li><li> - Supports layer editing and each object can be rendered with drop shadow, glow, reflection,3d bevel effects.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="EximiousSoft Banner Maker 5.46"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>LabelJoy 6.0.0.611</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4169-labeljoy.html</link>
<description>Name : LabelJoy Version : 6.0.0.611 OS : Windows Type : Barcode Labeling Software Price : $50 Homepage : SalePage Labeljoy is a professional, advanced, user-friendly barcode labeling software. It allows you to generate linear and 2D barcodes, design and print custom labels, and import data from external sources. It is an application that can be used with standard laser, inkjet or roll printers.</description>
<category>Image &amp; Design</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 06:41:03 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Generate Barcode - With Labeljoy Barcode generator software it’s possile to create custom barcode simply and quickly. You have just to import or write a code and then click “OK”. - Use the Professional Barcode Printing Software to generate Qr Codes offline, or online using our QR Code generetor tool. - Labeljoy enables you to generate a barcode (17 different types of barcode) for every commodity sector as Code 39, Ean13, ITF14, UPC, Code 93, Interleaved 2/5, Codabar and more. - Create custom product labels, price tag, or barcode labels for your business importing codes from external databases. Create and print labels and price tag - Labeljoy is a software engineered to create and print labels for folders, badges, cards, letters and anything other item that needs to be fully or partially replicated and printed. - Labeljoy creates also price tag easily and quickly, with dozens of template already preset for any kind of use. - Labeljoy is the first label printing software that features a full WYSIWYG user interface: the computer screen displays paper and label elements exactly as they will be printed. - Labeljoy can also connect to external data sources to create labels with dynamic information. - Labeljoy supports exporting to the most common graphic formats, such as jpg, png, gif and pdf.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Generate Barcode<br></li><li> - With Labeljoy Barcode generator software it’s possile to create custom barcode simply and quickly. You have just to import or write a code and then click “OK”.<br></li><li> - Use the Professional Barcode Printing Software to generate Qr Codes offline, or online using our QR Code generetor tool.<br></li><li> - Labeljoy enables you to generate a barcode (17 different types of barcode) for every commodity sector as Code 39, Ean13, ITF14, UPC, Code 93, Interleaved 2/5, Codabar and more.<br></li><li> - Create custom product labels, price tag, or barcode labels for your business importing codes from external databases.<br></li><li> Create and print labels and price tag<br></li><li> - Labeljoy is a software engineered to create and print labels  for folders, badges, cards, letters and anything other item that needs to be fully or partially replicated and printed.<br></li><li> - Labeljoy creates also price tag easily and quickly, with dozens of template already preset for any kind of use. <br></li><li> - Labeljoy is the first label printing software that features a full WYSIWYG user interface: the computer screen displays paper and label elements exactly as they will be printed.<br></li><li> - Labeljoy can also connect to external data sources to create labels with dynamic information.<br></li><li> - Labeljoy supports exporting to the most common graphic formats, such as jpg, png, gif and pdf.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="LabelJoy 6.0.0.611"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Jixipix Watercolor Studio 1.2.3</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3937-jixipix-watercolor-studio.html</link>
<description>Name : Jixipix Watercolor Studio Version : 1.2.3 OS : Windows Type : Automated Photo to Watercolor Software Price : $0 Homepage : SalePage Watercolor Studio creates fluid, liquidy, translucent watercolors with paint that flows naturally. Built on-top of an incredible rendering system that uses real-world techniques, this application does the initial work, producing a watercolor instantly, then allows you to customize your paintings using an array of Sliders, Layers, Brushes, Color Washes and Artistic finishes. The end result—print quality watercolors filled with transparent luminosity and sheer beauty.</description>
<category>Image &amp; Design</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 06:40:45 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Artificial Intelligence and Image Recognition A powerful wetness algorithm with full control. Decide how wet the edges become or how much the color spreads. Smart layers with options to reorder, duplicate and delete. This powerful feature allows you to stack and blend watercolor layers, washes and spatter for one-of-a-kind artwork. Landscape settings for an ultra wet watercolor Portrait settings for controlled color and detail Smart Brushes to remove areas or add them back in Mask option to invert, clear or fill brushed areas Detail and Shade controls 70 Artistic Finishes adjusts the color scheme to warm or cool bias, and modifies the intensity of color creating unity and altered moods that blends seamlessly. Smart links to globally unify artstic finishes across all layers Ink and Color washes that stack and blend Adjustable water Splatter for texture Granulating Texture slider to pool pigment naturally throughout the watercolor Canvas Layer with Cold Press, Hot Press and Rough paper texture Presets for saving custom paint palettes and to keep layers and settings intact for future projects Save Layer Preset allows one or more layers to be saved for future use. You know it&#039;s a layer present when an icon appears on the corner of the preset thumbnail.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Artificial Intelligence and Image Recognition<br></li><li> A powerful wetness algorithm with full control. Decide how wet the edges become or how much the color spreads.<br></li><li> Smart layers with options to reorder, duplicate and delete. This powerful feature allows you to stack and blend watercolor layers, washes and spatter for one-of-a-kind artwork.<br></li><li> Landscape settings for an ultra wet watercolor<br></li><li> Portrait settings for controlled color and detail<br></li><li> Smart Brushes to remove areas or add them back in<br></li><li> Mask option to invert, clear or fill brushed areas<br></li><li> Detail and Shade controls<br></li><li> 70 Artistic Finishes adjusts the color scheme to warm or cool bias, and modifies the intensity of color creating unity and altered moods that blends seamlessly.<br></li><li> Smart links to globally unify artstic finishes across all layers<br></li><li> Ink and Color washes that stack and blend<br></li><li> Adjustable water Splatter for texture<br></li><li> Granulating Texture slider to pool pigment naturally throughout the watercolor<br></li><li> Canvas Layer with Cold Press, Hot Press and Rough paper texture<br></li><li> Presets for saving custom paint palettes and to keep layers and settings intact for future projects<br></li><li> Save Layer Preset allows one or more layers to be saved for future use. You know it's a layer present when an icon appears on the corner of the preset thumbnail.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Jixipix Watercolor Studio 1.2.3"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Silkypix Developer Studio Pro 8.0.18.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4370-silkypix-developer-studio-pro.html</link>
<description>Name : Silkypix Developer Studio Pro Version : 8.0.18.0 OS : Windows Type : RAW Development Graphic Price : $59 Homepage : SalePage SILKYPIX is “RAW development software” that generates a high-resolution picture from the RAW data of a digital camera and offers accurate color from shadows through to highlights. This is pure made in Japan software. SILKYPIX corresponds to more than 650 different models digital camera and are supported from professional photographers and shutter bugs. SILKYPIX is selected as digital camera manufacturers’ standard bundled software over the world. Since 2004 when we released “SILKYPIX series”, we are always pursuing “High Quality Image” and SILKYPIX can represent it to customers.</description>
<category>Image &amp; Design</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 08:33:09 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features &quot;SILKYPIX Developer Studio 8&quot; realized a low price as a function-limited version that narrowed down the functions of the professional version &quot;Pro8&quot;. It is RAW development software excellent in cost performance that can make works easily and beautifully even for those who are challenged with RAW for the first time with excellent basic functions and easy-to-use interface.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> "SILKYPIX Developer Studio 8" realized a low price as a function-limited version that narrowed down the functions of the professional version "Pro8". It is RAW development software excellent in cost performance that can make works easily and beautifully even for those who are challenged with RAW for the first time with excellent basic functions and easy-to-use interface.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Silkypix Developer Studio Pro 8.0.18.0 "><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Adobe Illustrator CC 2018 v22.1.0.312</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4364-adobe-illustrator-cc-2018.html</link>
<description>Name : Adobe Illustrator CC 2018 Version : v22.1.0.312 OS : Windows Type : Vector Graphics App Price : $999 Homepage : SalePage The state of the art of illustration. The industry-standard vector graphics app lets you create logos, icons, drawings, typography, and illustrations for print, web, video, and mobile.</description>
<category>Image &amp; Design</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 08:16:27 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Fast asset export for screens Select assets from your artboards and export them to multiple sizes, resolutions, and formats with one click. Puppet Warp Modify a graphic naturally, without having to adjust individual paths or anchor points. SVG color fonts Design with SVG OpenType fonts that include multiple colors, gradients, and transparencies. Artboard enhancements Create up to a thousand artboards on your canvas, and select multiple artboards at one time to move, resize, and more.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/RbbQl2sU-ag?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Fast asset export for screens<br></li><li> Select assets from your artboards and export them to multiple sizes, resolutions, and formats with one click.<br></li><li> Puppet Warp<br></li><li> Modify a graphic naturally, without having to adjust individual paths or anchor points.<br></li><li> SVG color fonts<br></li><li> Design with SVG OpenType fonts that include multiple colors, gradients, and transparencies.<br></li><li> Artboard enhancements<br></li><li> Create up to a thousand artboards on your canvas, and select multiple artboards at one time to move, resize, and more.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Adobe Illustrator CC 2018 v22.1.0.312"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>ShutterStock Images Downloader 1.3.8</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3977-shutterstock-images-downloader.html</link>
<description>Name : ShutterStock Images Downloader Version : 1.3.8 OS : Windows Type : ShutterStock Download Tools Price : $39 Homepage : SalePage ShutterStock Images Downloader is a standalone offline setup for Windows 32-bit and 64-bit. ShutterStock Images Downloader Portable 1.2.7 is a reliable application for downloading Shutterstock images without any watermark. Shutterstock images are very high-quality royalty free images which include numerous, images, vector graphics, videos for bloggers. The preview feature let you see the images before downloading it. Shutterstock is a Splendid Premium Image Source, which Offers More than 30 Billion Pics Represented by Various Categories. Shutterstock maintains a library of over 50 million royalty-free stock photos, vector graphics, and illustrations, and 2 million video clips.</description>
<category>Image &amp; Design</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 00:19:33 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>[media=https://youtu.be/V0PzVw_H5tE] Features - Lightweight and simple application. - Allow you to download Shutterstock images without watermark. - Easily understandable user interface with clear cut instructions. - Paste the URL of the image and preview the images before downloading. - Many other powerful options and features. - Download premium images on shutterstock.com - Preview Images -The license attached to this program is unlimited and never-expiring so you will need to worry about - the quantities or the time. - Auto Download.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;">[media=https://youtu.be/V0PzVw_H5tE]</div><br><h3>Features</h3><br> - Lightweight and simple application.<br> - Allow you to download Shutterstock images without watermark.<br> - Easily understandable user interface with clear cut instructions.<br> - Paste the URL of the image and preview the images before downloading.<br> - Many other powerful options and features.<br> - Download premium images on shutterstock.com<br> - Preview Images -The license attached to this program is unlimited and never-expiring so you will need to worry about<br> - the quantities or the time.<br> - Auto Download.<br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="ShutterStock Images Downloader 1.3.8"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>HappyCard 2018 v2.2.80</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4105-happycard-2018.html</link>
<description>Name : HappyCard 2018 Version : v2.2.80 OS : Windows Type : CREATE INVITATION CARDS TOOL Price : $0 Homepage : SalePage Some invitation cards are so special that you’ll want to keep them forever. HappyCard enables you to create this kind of cards yourself using only a few clicks. HappyCard helps users with its simple to use interface to create invitation cards with just a few clicks. Creatively done cards, without any previous knowledge.</description>
<category>Image &amp; Design</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 00:18:40 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features - Design Assistant Even untrained makers will come to great results quickly with the help of the HappyCard design assistant. Very simple, step by step. - Serial Card Feature Invitation cards get created once and are made for sending them out to many different guests. With HappyCard the names change according to your list and are correctly exported for every card. - Instant Sharing If you want to send your card quickly to your friends, the most comfortable way to do so is the online view. Simply copy the link and send it to your friends. - Versatile Export Functions As soon as your masterpiece is done, you can print it out, export it as PDF, JPG, PNG or BMP, or get a link to share via Facebook, Twitter and your other apps.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br>- Design Assistant<br>Even untrained makers will come to great results quickly with the help of the HappyCard design assistant. Very simple, step by step.<br>- Serial Card Feature<br>Invitation cards get created once and are made for sending them out to many different guests. With HappyCard the names change according to your list and are correctly exported for every card.<br>- Instant Sharing<br>If you want to send your card quickly to your friends, the most comfortable way to do so is the online view. Simply copy the link and send it to your friends.<br>- Versatile Export Functions<br>As soon as your masterpiece is done, you can print it out, export it as PDF, JPG, PNG or BMP, or get a link to share via Facebook, Twitter and your other apps.<br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="HappyCard 2018 v2.2.80"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>DaVinci Resolve 14.3</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3944-davinci-resolve.html</link>
<description>Name : DaVinci Resolve Version : 14.3 OS : Windows Type : Editor Audio Tools Price : $0 Homepage : SalePage Revolutionary new tools for editing, color correction and professional audio post production, all in a single application!</description>
<category>Image &amp; Design</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 00:13:36 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Professional Editing DaVinci Resolve includes virtually every imaginable editing and trimming tool available, making it perfect for both creative and online editing! The new high performance playback engine, which is up to 10x faster, makes playback instantaneous and trimming more responsive than ever, even for processor intensive formats such as H.264 and RAW. Color Correction DaVinci Resolve has been used on more feature films and television shows than any other grading system! You get the industry’s most powerful primary and secondary correction tools, advanced curve editor, tracking and stabilization, noise reduction and grain tools, Resolve FX and more. Fairlight Audio New professional tools for audio post production! DaVinci Resolve now includes fully featured Fairlight audio in the same software you use for editing and color correction! You get high end mixing for up to 1,000 channels in real time, plus support for massive Fairlight audio consoles. It’s a true end to end workflow that supports recording and ADR, sound editing, sound effects, sweetening and mixing. You can even mix down and master to multiple formats, including 3D audio space formats such as 5.1, 7.1 and even 22.2! Media and Delivery DaVinci Resolve 14 makes importing, syncing and organizing footage fast! Whether you’re going out to the web, tape, or theatrical distribution, DaVinci Resolve features everything you need to deliver projects in virtually any format! You’ll be able to get to work quickly and output files fast, so you’ll never miss a deadline! Multi User Collaboration Revolutionary new tools allow simultaneous editing, color correction and audio post! DaVinci Resolve 14 completely redefines post production workflows! Assistant editors can prepare footage while editors cut the picture, colorists grade the shots, and sound editors mix and finish audio, all in the same project at the same time! You no longer have to waste time conforming and you no longer have to wait for a locked edit before starting color and audio work! That means picture editors, colorists, and sound editors can now work in parallel, leaving more time for everyone to be creative! DaVinci Resolve Studio Upgrade to DaVinci Resolve Studio for even more creative tools and options! The free version of DaVinci Resolve has all of the professional editing, legendary color correction and Fairlight audio tools you need for SD, HD and Ultra HD work at up to 60 frames per second. DaVinci Resolve Studio adds support for 4K and higher, along with frame rates up to 120 fps. It also includes dozens of additional image processing features and filters that are not in the free version. This includes film grain, temporal and spatial noise reduction, amazing new face enhancement tools, lens flares, lens distortion correction, optical quality blur and mist effects, match move, warping and much more! New High Performance Playback Engine Fly through edits and color correction with up to 10x the performance!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Professional Editing<br></li><li> DaVinci Resolve includes virtually every imaginable editing and trimming tool available, making it perfect for both creative and online editing! The new high performance playback engine, which is up to 10x faster, makes playback instantaneous and trimming more responsive than ever, even for processor intensive formats such as H.264 and RAW.<br></li><li> Color Correction<br></li><li> DaVinci Resolve has been used on more feature films and television shows than any other grading system! You get the industry’s most powerful primary and secondary correction tools, advanced curve editor, tracking and stabilization, noise reduction and grain tools, Resolve FX and more.<br></li><li> Fairlight Audio<br></li><li> New professional tools for audio post production! DaVinci Resolve now includes fully featured Fairlight audio in the same software you use for editing and color correction! You get high end mixing for up to 1,000 channels in real time, plus support for massive Fairlight audio consoles. It’s a true end to end workflow that supports recording and ADR, sound editing, sound effects, sweetening and mixing. You can even mix down and master to multiple formats, including 3D audio space formats such as 5.1, 7.1 and even 22.2!<br></li><li> Media and Delivery<br></li><li> DaVinci Resolve 14 makes importing, syncing and organizing footage fast! Whether you’re going out to the web, tape, or theatrical distribution, DaVinci Resolve features everything you need to deliver projects in virtually any format! You’ll be able to get to work quickly and output files fast, so you’ll never miss a deadline!<br></li><li> Multi User Collaboration<br></li><li> Revolutionary new tools allow simultaneous editing, color correction and audio post!<br></li><li> DaVinci Resolve 14 completely redefines post production workflows! Assistant editors can prepare footage while editors cut the picture, colorists grade the shots, and sound editors mix and finish audio, all in the same project at the same time! You no longer have to waste time conforming and you no longer have to wait for a locked edit before starting color and audio work! That means picture editors, colorists, and sound editors can now work in parallel, leaving more time for everyone to be creative!<br></li><li> DaVinci Resolve Studio<br></li><li> Upgrade to DaVinci Resolve Studio for even more creative tools and options!<br></li><li> The free version of DaVinci Resolve has all of the professional editing, legendary color correction and Fairlight audio tools you need for SD, HD and Ultra HD work at up to 60 frames per second. DaVinci Resolve Studio adds support for 4K and higher, along with frame rates up to 120 fps. It also includes dozens of additional image processing features and filters that are not in the free version. This includes film grain, temporal and spatial noise reduction, amazing new face enhancement tools, lens flares, lens distortion correction, optical quality blur and mist effects, match move, warping and much more!<br></li><li> New High Performance Playback Engine<br></li><li> Fly through edits and color correction with up to 10x the performance!<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="DaVinci Resolve 14.3"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>