<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Telegram Marketing - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Telegram Marketing - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>Telegram Auto 2.18.4</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4066-telegram-auto.html</link>
<description>Name : Telegram Auto Version : 2.18.4 OS : Windows Type : Telegram Marketing Bot Price : $97 Homepage : SalePage Telegram Auto is an all in one Telegram marketing software. You can export members from your competitors Telegram group and add members to your group. You can also send bulk messages to any group members.You can also send bulk automated messages to telegram user&#039;s by using our tool. It&#039;s safe with Telegram TOS because we are using Telegram API. Exporting your competitor’s most active group members is the best way to grow your bsuiness or group.If they are interested in your competitor’s products or services, why won’t they be interested in yours as well? Start marketing with your competitor’s group members now!</description>
<category>Telegram Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 23:44:35 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Export Competitor’s Members : Export your competitor’s group members and add to your own group. Excellent way to grow your telegram group. Export Telegram User ID&#039;s : Search by group address and export telegram group members ID&quot;s (@username format) to a text file. Send Bulk Message : Import telegram user id&#039;s and send bulk messages to them. Start promoting your product or service. Group Bulk Message Sender : Send bulk messages to group members. You don&#039;t need to a member of that group. Search Group : Enter group url and search. You can get group info. Export Members : You can export group members to text file. Send Message : You can send bulk telegram messages. Add Members : You can add members to your group. .</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/azKWXAICtJc?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Export Competitor’s Members : Export your competitor’s group members and add to your own group. Excellent way to grow your telegram group.<br></li><li> Export Telegram User ID's : Search by group address and export telegram group members ID"s (@username format) to a text file.<br></li><li> Send Bulk Message : Import telegram user id's and send bulk messages to them. Start promoting your product or service.<br></li><li> Group Bulk Message Sender : Send bulk messages to group members. You don't need to a member of that group.<br></li><li> Search Group : Enter group url and search. You can get group info.<br></li><li> Export Members : You can export group members to text file.<br></li><li> Send Message : You can send bulk telegram messages.<br></li><li> Add Members : You can add members to your group. .<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Telegram Auto 2.18.4"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Telegram Royal 1.74</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1880-telegram-royal.html</link>
<description>Name : Telegram Royal Version : 1.74 OS : Windows Type : Telegram Bulk Sender Price : $1000 Homepage : SalePage Telegram Royal (Bulk sending and advertising) Send virtualization software and advertising Telegram + add member of the channel (sending and advertising)</description>
<category>Telegram Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="https://sheypoorak.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/07/royal1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2016 21:21:15 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features No need to install and setup (simple and fast) No need for technical knowledge to work with this app High speed and stability Send Message Registration and delivery of complete and accurate Posts Anti-block system Smart Lines (new) Hide automated spam reporting system bar (new) The ability to import virtual lines and channels and visit Posts (X deleted!) Make a list of the number range Number Number way, (X deleted!) Full stability program submitted very dense (no problem and crash the application) Installation and deployment of application servers You can add or save a virtual number (to send messages) Automated fault detection and fix flaws virtual lines Support for encryption on virtual lines (Two Step Verification) for the stability of your lines (X deleted!) Ability to send messages to all users telegram (sending out) Sending of any kind virtual lines and safe post Storage facilities and backup of virtual lines and reporting posts Ability to load Excel or text file number recipients Allows you to send text, picture with no restriction on the size of the desired subtitle Sending a channel, group and individual Svprgrvh (X only group !!!) Send a picture and description and the names of your favorite channels and groups (X deleted!) Lets you specify the name and number display virtual image Possibility of adjusting the speed of transmission and number of the band and channel and ceiling write of each line Possibility to stop the post and hang on to it Without involving your system without using the mouse and keyboard Install and compatible with all versions of Windows and Linux Permanent and free support and updates And hundreds of other special features Design and Programming: Programming specialized team and Shypvrk</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> No need to install and setup (simple and fast)<br /></li><li> No need for technical knowledge to work with this app<br /></li><li> High speed and stability Send Message<br /></li><li> Registration and delivery of complete and accurate Posts<br /></li><li> Anti-block system Smart Lines (new)<br /></li><li> Hide automated spam reporting system bar (new)<br /></li><li> The ability to import virtual lines and channels and visit Posts (X deleted!)<br /></li><li> Make a list of the number range Number Number way, (X deleted!)<br /></li><li> Full stability program submitted very dense (no problem and crash the application)<br /></li><li> Installation and deployment of application servers<br /></li><li> You can add or save a virtual number (to send messages)<br /></li><li> Automated fault detection and fix flaws virtual lines<br /></li><li> Support for encryption on virtual lines (Two Step Verification) for the stability of your lines (X deleted!)<br /></li><li> Ability to send messages to all users telegram (sending out)<br /></li><li> Sending of any kind virtual lines and safe post<br /></li><li> Storage facilities and backup of virtual lines and reporting posts<br /></li><li> Ability to load Excel or text file number recipients<br /></li><li> Allows you to send text, picture with no restriction on the size of the desired subtitle<br /></li><li> Sending a channel, group and individual Svprgrvh (X only group !!!)<br /></li><li> Send a picture and description and the names of your favorite channels and groups (X deleted!)<br /></li><li> Lets you specify the name and number display virtual image<br /></li><li> Possibility of adjusting the speed of transmission and number of the band and channel and ceiling write of each line<br /></li><li> Possibility to stop the post and hang on to it<br /></li><li> Without involving your system without using the mouse and keyboard<br /></li><li> Install and compatible with all versions of Windows and Linux<br /></li><li> Permanent and free support and updates<br /></li><li> And hundreds of other special features<br /></li><li> Design and Programming: Programming specialized team and Shypvrk<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="https://sheypoorak.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/07/royal1.jpg" alt="Telegram Royal 1.74" title="Telegram Royal 1.74"  /><br /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Telegram Royal 1.74" title="Telegram Royal 1.74"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Telegram Titanium 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1879-telegram-titanium.html</link>
<description>Name : Telegram Titanium Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Telegram Channel Member Adder Price : $700 Homepage : SalePage Telegram Titanium (Add member by token) The app enhances cable channel members and visitors using the robot (Add member of Fick robot)</description>
<category>Telegram Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="https://sheypoorak.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/06/Titanium0.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2016 21:20:52 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features No need to install and setup (simple and fast) No need for technical knowledge to work with this app High speed and stability in the Add Members unrealistic robot cable channel Each virtual dedicated line for the constructions of 5 to 10 robots in their day !!! Ability to load files in the program numbers (format STAT) ( there is a separate application to convert all formats ) Possibility of visiting the channels using virtual lines loaded (robots do not visit) Without involving your system without the need for mouse and keyboard (no need to program Telegram Desktop) Allows speed control and automatic adjustment program hits per cycle Enable image and name on the robot Persian or English (Change Profile) Unable to parse numbers unusable and burned Possibility of building a robot token or visit the Kidney channel content in an operation in the shortest time !!! Very easy to apply and use Can be used in servers and virtual instruments It is based on the API and without involving the mouse and keyboard (for the background to do that) Install and compatible with all versions of Windows Permanent and free support and updates And hundreds of other special features Design and Programming: Programming specialized team and Shypvrk</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> No need to install and setup (simple and fast)<br /></li><li> No need for technical knowledge to work with this app<br /></li><li> High speed and stability in the Add Members unrealistic robot cable channel<br /></li><li> Each virtual dedicated line for the constructions of 5 to 10 robots in their day !!!<br /></li><li> Ability to load files in the program numbers (format STAT) ( there is a separate application to convert all formats )<br /></li><li> Possibility of visiting the channels using virtual lines loaded (robots do not visit)<br /></li><li> Without involving your system without the need for mouse and keyboard (no need to program Telegram Desktop)<br /></li><li> Allows speed control and automatic adjustment program hits per cycle<br /></li><li> Enable image and name on the robot Persian or English (Change Profile)<br /></li><li> Unable to parse numbers unusable and burned<br /></li><li> Possibility of building a robot token or visit the Kidney channel content in an operation in the shortest time !!!<br /></li><li> Very easy to apply and use<br /></li><li> Can be used in servers and virtual instruments<br /></li><li> It is based on the API and without involving the mouse and keyboard (for the background to do that)<br /></li><li> Install and compatible with all versions of Windows<br /></li><li> Permanent and free support and updates<br /></li><li> And hundreds of other special features<br /></li><li> Design and Programming: Programming specialized team and Shypvrk<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="https://sheypoorak.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/06/Titanium0.png" alt="Telegram Titanium 1.0" title="Telegram Titanium 1.0"  /><br /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Telegram Titanium 1.0" title="Telegram Titanium 1.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Telegram Soren 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1878-telegram-soren.html</link>
<description>Name : Telegram Soren Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Telegram Group Adder Price : $450 Homepage : SalePage Telegram Soren (Add channel member to group) Most professional software to increase organ and channel views and telegram API (Adad member of Fick Channel)</description>
<category>Telegram Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="https://sheypoorak.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/07/photo_2016-08-14_04-53-51.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2016 21:18:36 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features No need to install and setup (simple and fast) No need for technical knowledge to work with this app High speed and stability in the Add Non-real (virtual or real line), cable channel S ability to increase and at the same time or separately (Automatic devices for periodic visits) At the same time be able to upload all types of files in the program numbers (STAT and TGS and TGA formats and KEY) ( There is also a separate application to convert all formats ) Ability to load line for open or closed files for packages The possibility of an increase in accounts loaded at once (or file loading multiple packages at the same time) Allows you to adjust the engine number from 1 to 10 motors simultaneously (Multi Thread) Allows you to adjust the number of channel content to visit Ability to add the channel or group visit, delete, image and name on the line and start the robot and lines all in one app! Take advantage of a general or specific link channel or group without having to do anything else! Possibility of visiting the channel or other facilities for electric and automated custom schedule The possibility of scheduling software for automatic activity at the specified time or connecting it to panels or other applications. Automatic devices for task specific applications easily and simply Connectivity to other applications and panels quickly and easily Allows speed control and automatic adjustment program hits per cycle Enable image and name Persian or English on account of (change profile) Unable to parse numbers unusable and burned The possibility of increasing the robots (the so-called robot start) with arbitrary parameters Provide complete and accurate report of any operation and storage reports Without involving your system without the need for mouse and keyboard (no need to program Telegram Desktop) Very easy to apply and use Can be used in servers and virtual instruments It is based on the API and without involving the mouse and keyboard (for the background to do that) Install and compatible with all versions of Windows Permanent and free support and updates And hundreds of other special features Design and Programming: Programming specialized team and Shypvrk</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> No need to install and setup (simple and fast)<br /></li><li> No need for technical knowledge to work with this app<br /></li><li> High speed and stability in the Add Non-real (virtual or real line), cable channel<br /></li><li> S ability to increase and at the same time or separately (Automatic devices for periodic visits)<br /></li><li> At the same time be able to upload all types of files in the program numbers (STAT and TGS and TGA formats and KEY) ( There is also a separate application to convert all formats )<br /></li><li> Ability to load line for open or closed files for packages<br /></li><li> The possibility of an increase in accounts loaded at once (or file loading multiple packages at the same time)<br /></li><li> Allows you to adjust the engine number from 1 to 10 motors simultaneously (Multi Thread)<br /></li><li> Allows you to adjust the number of channel content to visit<br /></li><li> Ability to add the channel or group visit, delete, image and name on the line and start the robot and lines all in one app!<br /></li><li> Take advantage of a general or specific link channel or group without having to do anything else!<br /></li><li> Possibility of visiting the channel or other facilities for electric and automated custom schedule<br /></li><li> The possibility of scheduling software for automatic activity at the specified time or connecting it to panels or other applications.<br /></li><li> Automatic devices for task specific applications easily and simply<br /></li><li> Connectivity to other applications and panels quickly and easily<br /></li><li> Allows speed control and automatic adjustment program hits per cycle<br /></li><li> Enable image and name Persian or English on account of (change profile)<br /></li><li> Unable to parse numbers unusable and burned<br /></li><li> The possibility of increasing the robots (the so-called robot start) with arbitrary parameters<br /></li><li> Provide complete and accurate report of any operation and storage reports<br /></li><li> Without involving your system without the need for mouse and keyboard (no need to program Telegram Desktop)<br /></li><li> Very easy to apply and use<br /></li><li> Can be used in servers and virtual instruments<br /></li><li> It is based on the API and without involving the mouse and keyboard (for the background to do that)<br /></li><li> Install and compatible with all versions of Windows<br /></li><li> Permanent and free support and updates<br /></li><li> And hundreds of other special features<br /></li><li> Design and Programming: Programming specialized team and Shypvrk<br /> </li></ul><br /><img src="https://sheypoorak.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/07/photo_2016-08-14_04-53-51.jpg" alt="Telegram Soren 1.0" title="Telegram Soren 1.0"  /><br /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Telegram Soren 1.0" title="Telegram Soren 1.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Telegram Tranx 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1877-telegram-tranx.html</link>
<description>Name : Telegram Tranx Version : 1.0 Pro Paid Version OS : Windows Type : Telegram Filter &amp; Channel Checker Price : $200 Homepage : SalePage Telegram Tranx (Pro Paid Version) - Telegram Filter &amp; Channel Checker ISOLATION robot software token API (Token Czech)</description>
<category>Telegram Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="https://sheypoorak.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/07/trax.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2016 21:18:01 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features No need to install and setup (simple and fast) No need for technical knowledge to work with this app High speed and stability in the investigation and resolution of non-healthy healthy tokens Without involving your system without the need for mouse and keyboard (no need to program Telegram Desktop) Allows speed control program and set the number of concurrent review Unable to parse token unusable and burned Very easy to apply and use Can be used in servers and virtual instruments It is based on the API and without involving the mouse and keyboard (for the background to do that) Install and compatible with all versions of Windows Permanent and free support and updates And hundreds of other special features Design and Programming: Programming specialized team and Shypvrk</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> No need to install and setup (simple and fast)<br /></li><li> No need for technical knowledge to work with this app<br /></li><li> High speed and stability in the investigation and resolution of non-healthy healthy tokens<br /></li><li> Without involving your system without the need for mouse and keyboard (no need to program Telegram Desktop)<br /></li><li> Allows speed control program and set the number of concurrent review<br /></li><li> Unable to parse token unusable and burned<br /></li><li> Very easy to apply and use<br /></li><li> Can be used in servers and virtual instruments<br /></li><li> It is based on the API and without involving the mouse and keyboard (for the background to do that)<br /></li><li> Install and compatible with all versions of Windows<br /></li><li> Permanent and free support and updates<br /></li><li> And hundreds of other special features<br /></li><li> Design and Programming: Programming specialized team and Shypvrk<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="https://sheypoorak.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/07/trax.jpg" alt="Telegram Tranx 1.0" title="Telegram Tranx 1.0"  /><br /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Telegram Tranx 1.0" title="Telegram Tranx 1.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Telegram Reborn 4.6</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1874-telegram-reborn.html</link>
<description>Name : Telegram Reborn Version : 4.6 OS : Windows Type : Telegram Profiles Updater Price : $1000 Homepage : SalePage Telegram Reborn (the most powerful API toolset Telegram) Software reviews, reset and optimized, profiles and avatars are (healthy and promotes longevity accounts telegram)</description>
<category>Telegram Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="https://sheypoorak.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/06/Titanium0.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2016 21:17:08 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features No need to install and setup (simple and fast) No need for technical knowledge to work with this app High speed and stability of lines Complete and accurate recording and reporting lines Sustainability program in check, reset, fresh and optimization of very dense line (no problem and crash the application) Ability to block and remove accounts telegram Reports The ability to reset and refresh accounts telegram The name and ID on the telegram accounts The avatars and posting pictures on account of a telegram The ability to check the health of their separate accounts telegram The ability to verify the integrity of the accounts and the possibility of sending a telegram accounts and separating them STAT format functionality into a secure format to protect TGS accounts cable (not reset and destruction) Ability to optimize the line for greater stability and not burning them and also fixes a telegram accounts Reports After restarting and refresh feature optimizes line accounts for more stability telegram The ability to close other accounts cable connections (so-called Terminate Session) The two-phase locking or unlocking them on account of a telegram The two-stage lock with closing other connections Reproducibility telegram with the new connection account (the so-called Duplicate the Session) The telegram Tmyzsazy account, delete all groups and channels and contacts together (so-called Clear out) Installation and deployment of application servers Without involving your system without using the mouse and keyboard Install and compatible with all versions of Windows and Linux Permanent and free support and updates And hundreds of other special features Design and Programming: Programming specialized team and Shypvrk</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> No need to install and setup (simple and fast)<br /></li><li> No need for technical knowledge to work with this app<br /></li><li> High speed and stability of lines<br /></li><li> Complete and accurate recording and reporting lines<br /></li><li> Sustainability program in check, reset, fresh and optimization of very dense line (no problem and crash the application)<br /></li><li> Ability to block and remove accounts telegram Reports<br /></li><li> The ability to reset and refresh accounts telegram<br /></li><li> The name and ID on the telegram accounts<br /></li><li> The avatars and posting pictures on account of a telegram<br /></li><li> The ability to check the health of their separate accounts telegram<br /></li><li> The ability to verify the integrity of the accounts and the possibility of sending a telegram accounts and separating them<br /></li><li> STAT format functionality into a secure format to protect TGS accounts cable (not reset and destruction)<br /></li><li> Ability to optimize the line for greater stability and not burning them and also fixes a telegram accounts Reports<br /></li><li> After restarting and refresh feature optimizes line accounts for more stability telegram<br /></li><li> The ability to close other accounts cable connections (so-called Terminate Session)<br /></li><li> The two-phase locking or unlocking them on account of a telegram<br /></li><li> The two-stage lock with closing other connections<br /></li><li> Reproducibility telegram with the new connection account (the so-called Duplicate the Session)<br /></li><li> The telegram Tmyzsazy account, delete all groups and channels and contacts together (so-called Clear out)<br /></li><li> Installation and deployment of application servers<br /></li><li> Without involving your system without using the mouse and keyboard<br /></li><li> Install and compatible with all versions of Windows and Linux<br /></li><li> Permanent and free support and updates<br /></li><li> And hundreds of other special features<br /></li><li> Design and Programming: Programming specialized team and Shypvrk<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="https://sheypoorak.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/06/Titanium0.png" alt="Telegram Reborn 4.6" title="Telegram Reborn 4.6"  /><br /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Telegram Reborn 4.6" title="Telegram Reborn 4.6"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Telegram Phoenix 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1871-telegram-phoenix.html</link>
<description>Name : Telegram Phoenix Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Telegram Joiner Bot Price : $300 Homepage : SalePage Telegram Phoenix (Telegram Joiner Bot) The app enhances cable channel members and visitors using the robot (Add member of Fick robot) Also Join Channel &amp; Group</description>
<category>Telegram Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="https://sheypoorak.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/06/Titanium0.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2016 21:16:06 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features No need to install and setup (simple and fast) No need for technical knowledge to work with this app High speed and stability in the Add Members unrealistic robot cable channel Each virtual dedicated line for the constructions of 5 to 10 robots in their day !!! Ability to load files in the program numbers (format STAT) ( there is a separate application to convert all formats ) Possibility of visiting the channels using virtual lines loaded (robots do not visit) Without involving your system without the need for mouse and keyboard (no need to program Telegram Desktop) Allows speed control and automatic adjustment program hits per cycle Enable image and name on the robot Persian or English (Change Profile) Unable to parse numbers unusable and burned Possibility of building a robot token or visit the Kidney channel content in an operation in the shortest time !!! Very easy to apply and use Can be used in servers and virtual instruments It is based on the API and without involving the mouse and keyboard (for the background to do that) Install and compatible with all versions of Windows Permanent and free support and updates And hundreds of other special features Design and Programming: Programming specialized team and Shypvrk</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> No need to install and setup (simple and fast)<br /></li><li> No need for technical knowledge to work with this app<br /></li><li> High speed and stability in the Add Members unrealistic robot cable channel<br /></li><li> Each virtual dedicated line for the constructions of 5 to 10 robots in their day !!!<br /></li><li> Ability to load files in the program numbers (format STAT) ( there is a separate application to convert all formats )<br /></li><li> Possibility of visiting the channels using virtual lines loaded (robots do not visit)<br /></li><li> Without involving your system without the need for mouse and keyboard (no need to program Telegram Desktop)<br /></li><li> Allows speed control and automatic adjustment program hits per cycle<br /></li><li> Enable image and name on the robot Persian or English (Change Profile)<br /></li><li> Unable to parse numbers unusable and burned<br /></li><li> Possibility of building a robot token or visit the Kidney channel content in an operation in the shortest time !!!<br /></li><li> Very easy to apply and use<br /></li><li> Can be used in servers and virtual instruments<br /></li><li> It is based on the API and without involving the mouse and keyboard (for the background to do that)<br /></li><li> Install and compatible with all versions of Windows<br /></li><li> Permanent and free support and updates<br /></li><li> And hundreds of other special features<br /></li><li> Design and Programming: Programming specialized team and Shypvrk<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="https://sheypoorak.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/06/Titanium0.png" alt="Telegram Phoenix 1.0" title="Telegram Phoenix 1.0"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Telegram Phoenix 1.0" title="Telegram Phoenix 1.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Telegram Phantom 3.5</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1869-telegram-phantom.html</link>
<description>Name : Telegram Phantom Version : 3.5 OS : Windows Type : Telegram ID Converter Price : $300 Homepage : SalePage Telegram Phantom (the most professional converter cable accounts) Telegram conversion software accounts (accounts Fast and accurate conversion of all formats Telegram)</description>
<category>Telegram Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="https://sheypoorak.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/08/TGPhantom-e1462256896616-600x500.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2016 21:15:34 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features No need to install and setup (simple and fast) No need for technical knowledge to work with this app Very high conversion speed and stability on large accounts telegram No need for any ancillary costs !!! Converter and Creator has two modes for different applications. Take into account by creating a new connection (the so-called Create Session) Possibility to connect directly without creating a new account (so-called Convert Session) Unable to upload large numbers of files in the program (all formats) Support converting TGA, STAT, TDATA, TPA, KEY, TG to each other TDATA converted to other formats, even with two-stage lock without difficulty and requires a two-step password (in Version Converter program) !!! Czech double mechanism to investigate and meticulous accounts (in the Creator&#039;s Edition) Without involving your system without the need for mouse and keyboard (all versions of the program is fully automated and as API) More than 10,000 accounts TDATA telegram to convert to other formats (convert TDATA to STAT and TGA and KEY) in 24 hours for API !!! The ability to turn over account 10000000 telegram TGA, STAT and KEY to each other in 24 hours for API !!! Convert and then TDATA TPA to other formats for API and fast, without restrictions on the conversion? It is based on the API and without involving the mouse and keyboard (for the background to do that) Install and compatible with all versions of Windows Permanent and free support and updates And hundreds of other special features Design and Programming: Programming specialized team and Shypvrk</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> No need to install and setup (simple and fast)<br></li><li> No need for technical knowledge to work with this app<br></li><li> Very high conversion speed and stability on large accounts telegram<br></li><li> No need for any ancillary costs !!!<br></li><li> Converter and Creator has two modes for different applications.<br></li><li> Take into account by creating a new connection (the so-called Create Session)<br></li><li> Possibility to connect directly without creating a new account (so-called Convert Session)<br></li><li> Unable to upload large numbers of files in the program (all formats)<br></li><li> Support converting TGA, STAT, TDATA, TPA, KEY, TG to each other<br></li><li> TDATA converted to other formats, even with two-stage lock without difficulty and requires a two-step password (in Version Converter program) !!!<br></li><li> Czech double mechanism to investigate and meticulous accounts (in the Creator's Edition)<br></li><li> Without involving your system without the need for mouse and keyboard (all versions of the program is fully automated and as API)<br></li><li> More than 10,000 accounts TDATA telegram to convert to other formats (convert TDATA to STAT and TGA and KEY) in 24 hours for API !!!<br></li><li> The ability to turn over account 10000000 telegram TGA, STAT and KEY to each other in 24 hours for API !!!<br></li><li> Convert and then TDATA TPA to other formats for API and fast, without restrictions on the conversion?<br></li><li> It is based on the API and without involving the mouse and keyboard (for the background to do that)<br></li><li> Install and compatible with all versions of Windows<br></li><li> Permanent and free support and updates<br></li><li> And hundreds of other special features<br></li><li> Design and Programming: Programming specialized team and Shypvrk<br></li></ul><br><img src="https://sheypoorak.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/08/TGPhantom-e1462256896616-600x500.jpg" alt="Telegram Phantom 3.5"><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Telegram Filter 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1788-telegram-filter.html</link>
<description>Name : Telegram Filter Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Telegram Marketing Tools Price : $97 Homepage : SalePage Telegram Filter is usefull tools help u Filter Telegram numbers</description>
<category>Telegram Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://s3.picofile.com/file/8201939918/telegramfilter.gif" type="image/gif" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2016 21:20:57 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Fliter Telegram Filter - No number - No Chanel - No TelegramPC</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/IIukKoiwEeI?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Fliter<br /></li><li> Telegram Filter - No number - No Chanel - No TelegramPC<br /><br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://s3.picofile.com/file/8201939918/telegramfilter.gif" alt="Telegram Filter 1.0" title="Telegram Filter 1.0"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Telegram Filter 1.0" title="Telegram Filter 1.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>AniAd 4.9.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1769-aniad.html</link>
<description>Name : AniAd Version : Pro 4.9.0 OS : Windows Type : Telegram Marketing Tools, Telegram Bulk Message Price : $47 Homepage : SalePage AniAd - Ultimate bulk messages Sender on Telegram</description>
<category>Telegram Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="https://www.aniad.ir/wp-content/uploads/2015/12/03-800x489.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2016 23:26:41 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Runs on all Windows A simple and Persian Ability to send text, images, audio, video Ability to send emoticons Import phone numbers from txt file The ability to recognize numbers telegram Ability to generate mobile numbers suffering You can save and load text message No need to telegram Desktop Automated software updates Backup and recovery of virtual lines Change password software allows real-Ed Cable and non-cable enables automated reporting Send via Api -Telegram Without engaging keyboard and mouse No need to code to enable hardware Quickly send 2000 messages in 1 minute The possibility of correcting defects virtual lines Allows you to adjust profile contours with your name Line virtual instrument automatic telegram Ability to send group messages, private, on cable channel Software line automatic mechanism Telegram, Viber, Whatsapp With Mobile Banking postcode Tehran and other cities (Irancell, MCI)</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/GPZjRTWz42I?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Runs on all Windows<br /></li><li> A simple and Persian<br /></li><li> Ability to send text, images, audio, video<br /></li><li> Ability to send emoticons<br /></li><li> Import phone numbers from txt file<br /></li><li> The ability to recognize numbers telegram<br /></li><li> Ability to generate mobile numbers suffering<br /></li><li> You can save and load text message<br /></li><li> No need to telegram Desktop<br /></li><li> Automated software updates<br /></li><li> Backup and recovery of virtual lines<br /></li><li> Change password software allows real-Ed<br /></li><li> Cable and non-cable enables automated reporting<br /></li><li> Send via Api -Telegram<br /></li><li> Without engaging keyboard and mouse<br /></li><li> No need to code to enable hardware<br /></li><li> Quickly send 2000 messages in 1 minute<br /></li><li> The possibility of correcting defects virtual lines<br /></li><li> Allows you to adjust profile contours with your name<br /></li><li> Line virtual instrument automatic telegram<br /></li><li> Ability to send group messages, private, on cable channel<br /></li><li> Software line automatic mechanism Telegram, Viber, Whatsapp<br /></li><li> With Mobile Banking postcode Tehran and other cities (Irancell, MCI)<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="https://www.aniad.ir/wp-content/uploads/2015/12/03-800x489.jpg" alt="AniAd 4.9.0" title="AniAd 4.9.0"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="AniAd 4.9.0" title="AniAd 4.9.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>