<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Facebook Marketing - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Facebook Marketing - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>FaceDominator 3.5.0.39</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/879-facedominator.html</link>
<description>Name :FaceDominator Agency Version : 3.5.0.39 OS : Windows Type : Facebook Marketing Price : $499 Homepage : SalePage FaceDominator is a tool which is very useful for managing and automating your facebook advertising campaign. Learn more about FaceDominator Features with our Case Studies to help your business. Facebook marketing of your products through Facedominator To Promote Your Product through Wall Using Wall Poster,Manage Group,Photo Tagging,Manage Pages &amp;amp; Fan Page Poster</description>
<category>Facebook Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 27 May 2018 11:22:20 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FB Event Manager : Complete management of Events on facebook, Scrape users, Ask users to join it, etc. Customize Your Account : You can upload accounts,Check active and deactive accounts of facebook to upload a huge text file of accounts easily change the accout profile name and language of the accounts. Fanpage Manager : It can create Fanpage automatically or with your custom data. You can also use your keywords and categories to create pages Friend Adder :You can add targeted friends in your account. Targeting can be done based on Geo-Location or from fanpages. Wall Poster : You can post your message on the wall of friends or walls of fanpages with your targated keywords. Group Manager : you can invite your friends to join the groups,send request to groups,Post photo,url and messages on groups easily. Supports IP Proxies : It support both private and public proxies for all its features. You can also use Hide my Ass VPN to use with this tool. Automatic Captcha : It support Decaptcher.com and Deathbycaptcha.com for decoding captcha Auto Group Joiner Group Scraper Fans Scraper Multithreaded &amp;amp; Proxy Support Group Campaign Manager Group Request Manager Free For All http://mir.cr/AWYD8MSI</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/o592U_gke4I?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> FB Event Manager : Complete management of Events on facebook, Scrape users, Ask users to join it, etc.<br></li><li> Customize Your Account : You can upload accounts,Check active and deactive accounts of facebook to upload a huge text file of accounts easily change the accout profile name and language of the accounts.<br></li><li> Fanpage Manager : It can create Fanpage automatically or with your custom data. You can also use your keywords and categories to create pages<br></li><li> Friend Adder :You can add targeted friends in your account. Targeting can be done based on Geo-Location or from fanpages.<br></li><li> Wall Poster : You can post your message on the wall of friends or walls of fanpages with your targated keywords.<br></li><li> Group Manager : you can invite your friends to join the groups,send request to groups,Post photo,url and messages on groups easily.<br></li><li> Supports IP Proxies : It support both private and public proxies for all its features. You can also use Hide my Ass VPN to use with this tool.<br></li><li> Automatic Captcha : It support Decaptcher.com and Deathbycaptcha.com for decoding captcha<br></li><li> Auto Group Joiner<br></li><li> Group Scraper<br></li><li> Fans Scraper<br></li><li> Multithreaded &amp; Proxy Support<br></li><li> Group Campaign Manager<br></li><li> Group Request Manager<br></li></ul><br><div class="quote">Free For All<br><a href="http://mir.cr/AWYD8MSI"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">http://mir.cr/AWYD8MSI</a><br></div><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="FaceDominator 3.5.0.39"><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Simple Facebook Auto Poster 11.1.1.8</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1597-simple-facebook-auto-poster.html</link>
<description>Name : Simple Facebook Auto Poster Version : Pro 11.1.1.8 OS : Windows Type : Facebook Marketing Tools Price : $22 Homepage : SalePage Simple Facebook Auto Poster , is designed to help users to publishe their messages , links , photos , videos , in all their facebook groups ,pages ,liked pages and friends with a single click, in a simple way.</description>
<category>Facebook Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.simplefbautoposter.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/02/444.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 23:35:15 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Post To Groups You’re A Member Of. Post To Your Liked Pages. Post To Your Pages. Post With API Or Like a Human Send A Private Message To your Friends. Search groups , pages by number of members. Join – Leave selected groups. Like – Unlike selected pages. Leave – Unlike the groups and pages that do not allow you to post. Add the name of the target in the post automatically. Add 8 types of posts. Filter groups , pages , likes , groups You Want To Post To. Unlimited Facebook Accounts. (ONE AT A TIME) Post text , link , image or video. Delay Between Each Post. No Facebook App Needed. Sleep posting for a specified time and continue after. Save and load posts. Post on owner wall. Very Easy To Use. Massive Time Saving. All On Autopilot.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/XVnWf08_scM?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Post To Groups You’re A Member Of.<br></li><li> Post To Your Liked Pages.<br></li><li> Post To Your Pages.<br></li><li> Post With API Or Like  a Human<br></li><li> Send A Private Message To your Friends.<br></li><li> Search groups , pages by number of members.<br></li><li> Join – Leave selected groups.<br></li><li> Like – Unlike selected pages.<br></li><li> Leave – Unlike the groups and pages that do not allow you to post.<br></li><li> Add the name of the target in the post automatically.<br></li><li> Add 8 types of posts.<br></li><li> Filter groups , pages , likes , groups You Want To Post To.<br></li><li> Unlimited Facebook Accounts. (ONE AT A TIME)<br></li><li> Post text , link , image or video.<br></li><li> Delay Between Each Post.<br></li><li> No Facebook App Needed.<br></li><li> Sleep posting for a specified time and continue after.<br></li><li> Save and load posts.<br></li><li> Post on owner wall.<br></li><li> Very Easy To Use.<br></li><li> Massive Time Saving.<br></li><li> All On Autopilot.<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://www.simplefbautoposter.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/02/444.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Simple Facebook Auto Poster 11.1.1.8"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Qilio 3.0.2 Pro</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1268-qilio-pro.html</link>
<description>Name : Qilio /Social Maximiser Version : 3.0.2 OS : Windows/MAC Type : Facebook Marketing Tools Price : $197 Homepage : SalePage Build, Grow &amp;amp; Scale FB Fanpages without spending a dime or your time... THIS SOFTWARE IS BROUGHT TO YOU BY Watch How We Manage Fan Page Communities,And Profit BIG, on Complete AUTOPILOT</description>
<category>Facebook Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://commentmaximiser.com/new/oto1/images/intro.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 22:56:18 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Built-in RSS Feed Reader Content Library For Evergreen Niche Specific Content 15 Top Google trending topics in real time Smileys And Special Objects Library Image Background Library Public Domain Image Sources Powerful Image Editor Module Video Posts Module Hashtags And Keywords Maintenance Module Post Schedule Maintenance Module Download CSV Reports Post Content From Top News Sources Holiday Calendar Popup Post To User&#039;s Personal Profile Post To Multiple Fan Pages Or All Fan Pages At Once Recent Posts Summary View Notes Section Improved UI Layout Post Analytics Module 5 Extra Installation License Keys Viral Post Templates</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/-Kwqs7iOsdQ?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Built-in RSS Feed Reader<br></li><li> Content Library For Evergreen Niche Specific Content<br></li><li> 15 Top Google trending topics in real time<br></li><li> Smileys And Special Objects Library<br></li><li> Image Background Library<br></li><li> Public Domain Image Sources<br></li><li> Powerful Image Editor Module<br></li><li> Video Posts Module <br></li><li> Hashtags And Keywords Maintenance Module<br></li><li> Post Schedule Maintenance Module<br></li><li> Download CSV Reports<br></li><li> Post Content From Top News Sources<br></li><li> Holiday Calendar Popup<br></li><li> Post To User's Personal Profile<br></li><li> Post To Multiple Fan Pages Or All Fan Pages At Once<br></li><li> Recent Posts Summary View<br></li><li> Notes Section<br></li><li> Improved UI Layout<br></li><li> Post Analytics Module<br></li><li> 5 Extra Installation License Keys<br></li><li> Viral Post Templates<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://commentmaximiser.com/new/oto1/images/intro.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Qilio 3.0.2 Pro"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Facebook Automation 6.7 Premium</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1428-facebook-automation.html</link>
<description>Name : Facebook Automation Version : 6.7 Premium OS : Windows Type : Facebook Marketing Tools Price : $40 Homepage : SalePage Facebook Automation is Facebook Poster &amp;amp; Scheduler, a lightweight tool designed to help users post mass private facebook message, group post, groups searching and joining, post to wall, post to public pages, post to fan page, posts searchign and commenting, auto likes bot, schedule your posts. The great tool allow you advertising and driving traffic to your website your website. You can get from hundreds to thousands Facebook visitors daily WITHOUT CLICK. The program have a good scheduler manager for you.</description>
<category>Facebook Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://i1-win.softpedia-static.com/screenshots/Facebook-Auto-Poster_5.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 17:20:23 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features - Easy to fetch your groups list, friends list, pages. - Searching for groups by keyword, checking for status (joined, un-join, privacy open-close-secret group, members count, notify ...). - Easy to filter groups list. Join to any groups that you want. Leave bad groups (no more members, not allow to post ...) by one click. Turn on/off notify from groups which you want. - Mass invite friends to group. Mass invite users via email to group - Post a message, single photo or multi-photos to groups which you chosed. You can also post your photo album to groups. - Tag specify friends to a post or random tag friends to a post. - Post a message, single photo or multi-photos to your wall or friend wall. - Post a mass private message to users which you chosed. - RANDOM/SPIN your message, link, images, photo ... while posting for prevent spam detection by facebook. - Sharing a your photo album/post to groups/pages/users ... - Searching for users by keyword, automatic sending friend request to users which you chosed. Get friend requests, accept or deny requests. - Convert users id to facebook emails. - Searching for pages by keyword, checking for details of these pages (likes count, can post, website, email, phone, country ...). Mass invite friend like the page. More filter options for you. - Export emails, phone, website from public pages. - Post a message, single photo, private message to public pages which you chosed. - Bump your posts in groups or bump specify posts ids. - Searching for events. Attending to events which you chosed. Mass invite friends to event. - Post a message, single photo to events which you chosed. - Schedule your posts to anywhere (groups, public pages, friend wall, private message, comment). - Schedule bumping your posts in groups or specify posts ids. - Schedule joining to groups. - Settings time interval while posting, joining to groups, friend request sending ... Prevent spam detection from facebook. - Easy to manage multi-facebook accounts. Proxy support for each account. Simple to post for specify account which you chosed. - Portable software, you do not need install to run it. WHY SHOULD I USE FB POSTER &amp;amp; SCHEDULER INSTEAD OF COMPETITOR PRODUCTS? 1. Features - FPS giving you some features which are not any program available. We also working on ideas about new features that clients want to have. 2. Price - The cost for program is $39.95 its one time payment and you will get all upgrade version for future. 3. Trial - We are offering FREE and PREMIUM version. So you can trial forever on FREE version and upgrade to PREMIUM if you like it. SEEM TOO GOOD TO BE TRUE? Don&#039;t take our word for it. You can looking for Video demo or download it now. AWARDS FPS got 5 stars by www.softpedia.com editor and &quot;Excellent&quot; by users. (FPS on Softpedia) FPS got 5 stars by users on download..com.com (FPS on Download..COM)</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/2-Y71az8bZI?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br>- Easy to fetch your groups list, friends list, pages.<br>- Searching for groups by keyword, checking for status (joined, un-join, privacy open-close-secret group, members count, notify ...).<br>- Easy to filter groups list. Join to any groups that you want. Leave bad groups (no more members, not allow to post ...) by one click. Turn on/off notify from groups which you want.<br>- Mass invite friends to group. Mass invite users via email to group<br>- Post a message, single photo or multi-photos to groups which you chosed. You can also post your photo album to groups.<br>- Tag specify friends to a post or random tag friends to a post.<br>- Post a message, single photo or multi-photos to your wall or friend wall.<br>- Post a mass private message to users which you chosed.<br>- RANDOM/SPIN your message, link, images, photo ... while posting for prevent spam detection by facebook.<br>- Sharing a your photo album/post to groups/pages/users ...<br>- Searching for users by keyword, automatic sending friend request to users which you chosed. Get friend requests, accept or deny requests.<br>- Convert users id to facebook emails.<br>- Searching for pages by keyword, checking for details of these pages (likes count, can post, website, email, phone, country ...). Mass invite friend like the page. More filter options for you.<br>- Export emails, phone, website from public pages.<br>- Post a message, single photo, private message to public pages which you chosed.<br>- Bump your posts in groups or bump specify posts ids.<br>- Searching for events. Attending to events which you chosed. Mass invite friends to event.<br>- Post a message, single photo to events which you chosed.<br>- Schedule your posts to anywhere (groups, public pages, friend wall, private message, comment).<br>- Schedule bumping your posts in groups or specify posts ids.<br>- Schedule joining to groups.<br>- Settings time interval while posting, joining to groups, friend request sending ... Prevent spam detection from facebook.<br>- Easy to manage multi-facebook accounts. Proxy support for each account. Simple to post for specify account which you chosed.<br>- Portable software, you do not need install to run it.<br><br>WHY SHOULD I USE FB POSTER &amp; SCHEDULER INSTEAD OF COMPETITOR PRODUCTS?<br>1. Features - FPS giving you some features which are not any program available. We also working on ideas about new features that clients want to have.<br>2. Price - The cost for program is .95 its one time payment and you will get all upgrade version for future.<br>3. Trial - We are offering FREE and PREMIUM version. So you can trial forever on FREE version and upgrade to PREMIUM if you like it.<br><br>SEEM TOO GOOD TO BE TRUE?<br>Don't take our word for it. You can looking for Video demo or download it now.<br><br>AWARDS<br>FPS got 5 stars by www.softpedia.com editor and "Excellent" by users. (FPS on Softpedia)<br>FPS got 5 stars by users on download..com.com (FPS on Download..COM)<br><img src="http://i1-win.softpedia-static.com/screenshots/Facebook-Auto-Poster_5.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Facebook Automation 6.7 Premium"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>VidPush - Pro 3.04</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1533-vidpush.html</link>
<description>Name : VidPush - Pro Version : 3.04 OS : Windows Type : Fanpage Poster, Facebook Marketing Price : $37 Homepage : SalePage Autoposting + Unlimited Fan pages + Channel Shadowing - Make Your FB Profits Zoom 300% to 1500%! Manipulate A Platform Bigger Than YouTube That Nobody Knows About Yet! Facebook Algorithm Has Changed Give Your Customers This Software So Their Videos Get More Visibility Utilizing FB API, Vidpush holds videos from YouTube as well as uploads them to your enthusiast pages. All it takes is actually one-time setup, and you as well as your customers can upload movies from YouTube straight to Facebook. This is a simple, but BRILLIANT workaround that could dramatically enhance social media and video marketing outcomes.</description>
<category>Facebook Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://d3nl8b68wbpojg.cloudfront.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/VidPush-cover.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 13:16:09 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Search YouTube for new videos automatically Post to Facebook automatically Draft Post &amp;amp; Schedule Uploads Add videos to queue automatically Schedule with a minimum gap between posts (in minutes)</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/CantjJ7FZAs?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><p><br></p><br><h3>Features</h3><br><p><br><ul><li> Search YouTube for new videos automatically<br></li><li> Post to Facebook automatically<br></li><li> Draft Post &amp; Schedule Uploads<br></li><li> Add videos to queue automatically<br></li><li> Schedule with a minimum gap between posts (in minutes)<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://d3nl8b68wbpojg.cloudfront.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/VidPush-cover.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="VidPush - Pro 3.04"><br><br></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Facebook Group Poster 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3913-facebook-group-poster.html</link>
<description>Name : Facebook Group Poster Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Facebook Groups Tools Price : $59 Homepage : SalePage Facebook Group Poster is a software tool that allows its users to post in all their Facebook groups automatically. You simply enter your facebook account details and it will login as you then browse to your groups and post your message in each group you are a member of. Facebook groups can be excluded and spintax is supported if you want to vary the messages you&#039;re posting into groups.</description>
<category>Facebook Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 03:21:21 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features This free poster software has its own embedded browser and can browse facebook clicking links and automatically posting messages so you don&#039;t have to. You simply enter your account and click &quot;start posting&quot;.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Pv72BNco59E?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> This free poster software has its own embedded browser and can browse facebook clicking links and automatically posting messages so you don't have to. You simply enter your account and click "start posting".<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Facebook Group Poster 1.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>ViralPics Pro 1.40</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1535-viralpics.html</link>
<description>Name : ViralPics Pro Version : 1.40 OS : Windows Type : Facebook Poster, Facebook Marketing Tools Price : $49 Homepage : SalePage So, Here&#039;s The ULTIMATE Facebook Viral Images Tool So YOU Can Turn Your FB Pages Into Money Spinners Faster Than Ever! Outstanding &amp;amp; The Most Intelligent Viral Images Software For Facebook, A Product And A Strategy That Would Let You Get UNLIMITED Viral Images For The Rest Of Your Life That Will Randomizes The Styling Of Each Image, Making It Absolutely Unique And State Of The Art Then Give A Highly Engaged Facebook Audience In Any Niche</description>
<category>Facebook Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 11:37:40 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features This Is What I Call DONKEY WORK! I mean think about it. Start with finding some really good photos. Good, decent shots online, Make sure there’s no copyright infringement, ensure they’re acceptable quality and then process them. Select a great quote that’s generic and works mostly for everyone, work through stylizing fonts and applying them on the photo, then design a border you like with a color coding that matches your photograph, then apply your branding logo I bet you’re exhausted just from reading it. Doing it is even tougher It’d be easier too get a dog to speak French. We know because we’ve been through it! We’ve been there, done that and and created a better way! ViralPics connects to Flickr using keywords from any niche and sources the freshest photographs from there according to your filter and settings. You can randomize or select any design you want &amp;amp; and even select image licensing to make sure you get only authorized images.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ey_S45Vppyk?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><p><br></p><br><h3>Features</h3><br><p><br><ul><li> This Is What I Call DONKEY WORK!<br></li><li> I mean think about it. Start with finding some really good photos.<br></li><li> Good, decent shots online, Make sure there’s no copyright infringement, ensure they’re acceptable quality and then process them.<br></li><li> Select a great quote that’s generic and works mostly for everyone, work through stylizing fonts and applying them on the photo, then design a border you like with a color coding that matches your photograph, then apply your branding logo<br></li><li> I bet you’re exhausted just from reading it. Doing it is even tougher It’d be easier too get a dog to speak French.<br></li><li> We know because we’ve been through it! We’ve been there, done that and and created a better way!<br></li><li> ViralPics connects to Flickr using keywords from any niche and sources the freshest photographs from there according to your filter and settings.<br></li><li> You can randomize or select any design you want &amp; and even select image licensing to make sure you get only authorized images.<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="ViralPics Pro 1.40"><br><div class="quote"></div></div></p>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Comment Maximiser 2.0.4</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1295-comment-maximiser.html</link>
<description>Name : Comment Maximiser Version : 2.0.4 OS : Windows/MAC Type : Facebook Marketing Tools Price : $197 Homepage : SalePage Comment Maximiser Is definitely the Ultimate Fanpage Automation Suite – Set It Up Once, And it’ll Run Hands-Free Forever! Want to get the greatest traffic on Fb… for free? People try to make Facebook marketing sound complicated, but strip away all the jargon and BS, it just comes down to engagement. The more you engage with your audience, the more sales you get. Comment Maximiser is poised to blow up in to the Huge Fb market… and also you will be the one reaping the early rewards.</description>
<category>Facebook Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://i.imgur.com/HEM1TE9.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="http://commentmaximiser.com/images/newfeatures.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 22:55:20 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Date Range Now, you can sort through status updates be-tween two dates. This was not possible before, but now this filtering lets you save more time. Mass Likes This feature lets you click once, and automatically place dozens of likes – saving you even MORE time than the Date Range feature. Foreign Language Support for Spun Text We are the first software on the market to allow this. Three-deep Commenting Level Lets you bring the same people back to your pages not once, but three times.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/_WpQDX2pkEY?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Date Range Now, you can sort through status updates be-tween two dates. This was not possible before, but now this filtering lets you save more time.<br></li><li> Mass Likes This feature lets you click once, and automatically place dozens of likes – saving you even MORE time than the Date Range feature.<br></li><li> Foreign Language Support for Spun Text We are the first software on the market to allow this.<br></li><li> Three-deep Commenting Level Lets you bring the same people back to your pages not once, but three times.<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://i.imgur.com/HEM1TE9.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Comment Maximiser 2.0.4"><br><img src="http://commentmaximiser.com/images/newfeatures.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Facebook Bot v.10.11 Emerald</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3747-facebook-bot-emerald.html</link>
<description>Name : Facebook Bot Version : v.10.11 Emerald OS : Windows Type : Facebook Scraper Tools Price : $67 Homepage : SalePage Facebook Bot v.10 Emerald is one of the most powerful Bot , this bot can make thousands of facebook Accounts easily . This bot has extremely powerful features like , Auto Account Creation , Mail.ru Creation , Friend Adder , Profile Complete , Profile Generator etc .</description>
<category>Facebook Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://i.imgur.com/OSSNTiK.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2017 20:32:27 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FB like Auto Account Creation Mail.ru Creation Friend Adder Profile Complete Profile Generator</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Y6lcJUF4Y0Y?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> FB like <br></li><li> Auto Account Creation<br></li><li> Mail.ru Creation<br></li><li> Friend Adder <br></li><li> Profile Complete<br></li><li> Profile Generator<br></li></ul><br><br><img src="http://i.imgur.com/OSSNTiK.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Facebook Bot v.10.11 Emerald"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>TFacebook Adds Friends 2017 3.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2074-tfacebook-adds-friends.html</link>
<description>Name : Facebook Adds Friends 2017 Version : 3.0 OS : Windows Type : Facebook Marketing Tools Price : $57 Homepage : SalePage TFacebook Adds Friends - Make friend requests on Facebook groups</description>
<category>Facebook Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://i.imgur.com/PKCEJsF.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 05:22:31 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features When you use AdvantageBot to score your text you are effectively eliminating guesswork and prolonged, expensive testing. This affords you faster results and minimizes ‘bad ad’ spend. You can optimize any copy, across multiple niches, market sectors and regions quickly for yourself and/or your clients. Perfect for marketers, business owners, copywriters and ad/marketing agencies. Built-in database of hundreds of thousands of ads – We’d argue the most powerful advertising and marketing tool ever created. Instant results from Scientific Proven Methods – AdvantageBot has taken over 7 years to become fully realized and presented as it is today with tens of thousands of dollars spent in testing and data analysis.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/4VhRq62Ss0I?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> When you use AdvantageBot to score your text you are effectively eliminating guesswork and prolonged, expensive testing.  This affords you faster results and minimizes ‘bad ad’ spend.<br></li><li> You can optimize any copy, across multiple niches, market sectors and regions quickly for yourself and/or your clients.  Perfect for marketers, business owners, copywriters and ad/marketing agencies.<br></li><li> Built-in database of hundreds of thousands of ads – We’d argue the most powerful advertising and marketing tool ever created.<br></li><li> Instant results from Scientific Proven Methods – AdvantageBot has taken over 7 years to become fully realized and presented as it is today with tens of thousands of dollars spent in testing and data analysis.<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://i.imgur.com/PKCEJsF.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="TFacebook Adds Friends 2017 3.0"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>