<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Clone Script - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Clone Script - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>AdLinkFly 3.5.2</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2131-adlinkfly.html</link>
<description>Name : AdLinkFly - M.comized URL Shortener Version : 3.5.2 Type : Short URL Script Price : $29 Homepage : Salepage Earn money by starting your own m.comized link shortening service, just like adf.ly adfly clone, ouo.io clone, linkshrink.com clone or shorte.st clone! Allow members to shorten links &amp;amp; earn money, and keep a share of the profit. AdLinkFly includes a complete publisher and advertiser system, campaigns, referrals, withdrawals, API, translation ready, PayPal, Payza, Bitcoin, Webmoney &amp;amp; Bank Transfer integration, reCAPTCHA integration and much more!</description>
<category>Clone Script</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2017 15:40:18 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features PUBLISHERS Publishers and you can earn money by showing ads when users click on shortened links Ability to change the CPM (Cost Per Mille, thousands) for each country Different ad types Interstitial ? Full page ad Banner ? 728?90, 468?60 &amp;amp; 336?280 No ad ? will work as redirect servise like bit.ly Publishers have access to a powerful dashboard Statistics sorted by Month &amp;amp; Year Auto-generated line graphs Can view, edit, and hide links ADVERTISER SYSTEM Each visitor you will purchase will meet the following criteria: Unique within a 24 hour time frame They are not using Adblocker extenstions They will have j&amp;#097;vascript enabled They will have Cookies enabled Must view your website for at least 5 seconds Advertisers can create campaigns for the below adertisments: Interstitial ? Full page ad Banner ? 728?90, 468?60 &amp;amp; 336?280 Pop Up Advertisers can select campaigns target sources like Desktop Mobile/tablests All sources Advertisers can pause, resume and monitor their campaigns PAYMENT GATEWAYS PayPal with sandbox support Payza Bitcoin WebMoney Bank Transfer And more is coming …. WITHDRAWAL SYSTEM Publishers can withdraw their earned profits using PayPal or Payza Turn off withdrawals if funds are low REFERRALS SYSTEM The AdLinkFly referral program is a great way to spread the word of this great service and to earn even more money with your short links! Refer friends and receive 20% of their earnings for life! MEMBERS SYSTEM visitors can sign up and activation e-mails will be sent out reCAPTCHA verification on reset password and signup pages Allow users to reset their passwords Allow users to change their email address Users can add add their billing information like first name, last name, address, country, city, state and phone number API TOOLS Quick Link: Everyone can use the shortest way to shorten links with AdLinkFly. Mass Shrinker: Enter up to 20 URLs (one per line) to be shrunk and added to your account Full Page Script: If you have a website with 100’s or 1000’s of links you want to change over to short then tool will be helpful for you. Developers API: For developers AdLinkFly prepared API which returns responses in JSON format. CAPTCHA SYSTEM Enable/Disable Captcha Enable/Disable on Short Links Page Enable/Disable on Signup Form Enable/Disable on Forgot Password Form TRANSLATION READY Easliy translate AdLinkFly to the language of your choice. MULTILINGUAL READY Visitors can choose ftheir language from the dropdown. PAGES You can add unlimited pages with the ability to edit and delete. GENERAL Multi domains for short links Testimonials system Support form for member area AdLinkFly includes two themes: Classic and Modern Ajax contact form. Copy button(No flash required anymore) for shotned links ADMINISTRATION PANEL Easily accessible &amp;amp; make users admins View site statistics on the dashboard Change website name &amp;amp; description Change default site language and timezone Add your website logo in two versions Enable/Disable Account Activation by Email Enable/Disable advertising features Change Referral Percentage earning Ability to add Head Code into front area pages Ability to add Head Code into Auth pages like signin, sinup, forgot password pages Ability to add Head Code into member area Ability to add Head Code into admin area Disallow certain domains from be shortened Change alias min length &amp;amp; max length Enable/Disable Interstitial Advertisement Enable/Disable Banner Advertisement Enable/Disable No Advert Set default advertisement type for anonymous and members Set counter value into short links pages Set Mass Shrinker Limit Admin can ads into various positions like: Member Area Captcha page Interstitial Page Ad: This ad will be displayed between logo and counter. Banner 728?90 Banner 468?60 Banner 336?280 Ability to change currency code Ability to change Currency symbol Ability to ad Facebook Page URL Ability to ad Twitter Profile URL Ability to ad Google Plus URL SMTP email support Ability to filter campaigns Ability to filter users Ability to filter links</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<b>Features</b><br><br><br>PUBLISHERS<br><br>Publishers and you can earn money by showing ads when users click on shortened links<br>Ability to change the CPM (Cost Per Mille, thousands) for each country<br>Different ad types<br>Interstitial ? Full page ad<br>Banner ? 728?90, 468?60 &amp; 336?280<br>No ad ? will work as redirect servise like bit.ly<br>Publishers have access to a powerful dashboard<br>Statistics sorted by Month &amp; Year<br>Auto-generated line graphs<br>Can view, edit, and hide links<br>ADVERTISER SYSTEM<br><br>Each visitor you will purchase will meet the following criteria:<br>Unique within a 24 hour time frame<br>They are not using Adblocker extenstions<br>They will have j&#097;vascript enabled<br>They will have Cookies enabled<br>Must view your website for at least 5 seconds<br>Advertisers can create campaigns for the below adertisments:<br>Interstitial ? Full page ad<br>Banner ? 728?90, 468?60 &amp; 336?280<br>Pop Up<br>Advertisers can select campaigns target sources like<br>Desktop<br>Mobile/tablests<br>All sources<br>Advertisers can pause, resume and monitor their campaigns<br>PAYMENT GATEWAYS<br><br>PayPal with sandbox support<br>Payza<br>Bitcoin<br>WebMoney<br>Bank Transfer<br>And more is coming ….<br>WITHDRAWAL SYSTEM<br><br>Publishers can withdraw their earned profits using PayPal or Payza<br>Turn off withdrawals if funds are low<br>REFERRALS SYSTEM<br><br>The AdLinkFly referral program is a great way to spread the word of this great service and to earn even more money with your short links! Refer friends and receive 20% of their earnings for life!<br><br>MEMBERS SYSTEM<br><br>visitors can sign up and activation e-mails will be sent out<br>reCAPTCHA verification on reset password and signup pages<br>Allow users to reset their passwords<br>Allow users to change their email address<br>Users can add add their billing information like first name, last name, address, country, city, state and phone number<br>API TOOLS<br><br>Quick Link: Everyone can use the shortest way to shorten links with AdLinkFly.<br>Mass Shrinker: Enter up to 20 URLs (one per line) to be shrunk and added to your account<br>Full Page Script: If you have a website with 100’s or 1000’s of links you want to change over to short then tool will be helpful for you.<br>Developers API: For developers AdLinkFly prepared API which returns responses in JSON format.<br>CAPTCHA SYSTEM<br><br>Enable/Disable Captcha<br>Enable/Disable on Short Links Page<br>Enable/Disable on Signup Form<br>Enable/Disable on Forgot Password Form<br>TRANSLATION READY<br><br>Easliy translate AdLinkFly to the language of your choice.<br><br>MULTILINGUAL READY<br><br>Visitors can choose ftheir language from the dropdown.<br><br>PAGES<br><br>You can add unlimited pages with the ability to edit and delete.<br><br>GENERAL<br><br>Multi domains for short links<br>Testimonials system<br>Support form for member area<br>AdLinkFly includes two themes: Classic and Modern<br>Ajax contact form.<br>Copy button(No flash required anymore) for shotned links<br>ADMINISTRATION PANEL<br><br>Easily accessible &amp; make users admins<br>View site statistics on the dashboard<br>Change website name &amp; description<br>Change default site language and timezone<br>Add your website logo in two versions<br>Enable/Disable Account Activation by Email<br>Enable/Disable advertising features<br>Change Referral Percentage earning<br>Ability to add Head Code into front area pages<br>Ability to add Head Code into Auth pages like signin, sinup, forgot password pages<br>Ability to add Head Code into member area<br>Ability to add Head Code into admin area<br>Disallow certain domains from be shortened<br>Change alias min length &amp; max length<br>Enable/Disable Interstitial Advertisement<br>Enable/Disable Banner Advertisement<br>Enable/Disable No Advert<br>Set default advertisement type for anonymous and members<br>Set counter value into short links pages<br>Set Mass Shrinker Limit<br>Admin can ads into various positions like:<br>Member Area<br>Captcha page<br>Interstitial Page Ad: This ad will be displayed between logo and counter.<br>Banner 728?90<br>Banner 468?60<br>Banner 336?280<br>Ability to change currency code<br>Ability to change Currency symbol<br>Ability to ad Facebook Page URL<br>Ability to ad Twitter Profile URL<br>Ability to ad Google Plus URL<br>SMTP email support<br>Ability to filter campaigns<br>Ability to filter users<br>Ability to filter links<br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="AdLinkFly 3.5.2"><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>SiteSpy 3.3</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2137-sitespy.html</link>
<description>Name : SiteSpy - Complete Visitor &amp;amp; SEO Analytics Version : 3.3 Type : SEO Script, Ratings and Charts Price : $30 Homepage : Salepage Complete visitor and SEO anlytics package including visitor analytics (unique visitor, page view, bounce rate, average stay time, average visit, traffic analysis, top refferer, new &amp;amp; returning visitor, content overview, country &amp;amp; browser report, os &amp;amp; device report etc.) , web analytics (alexa data,similarWeb data, whois data, social media data, moz check, dmoz check, search engine index, google page rank, IP analysis, malware check ) , SEO tools (link analysis, keyword position analysis, auto keyword suggestion,page status check, backlink creation/search, website ping, google adword scraper etc.) You will also get several bonus utility tools such as email encoder/decoder, metatag generator, ogtag generator, plgiarism check, valid email check, duplicate email filter, url encode/decode, robot code generator etc. It?s a multi-user SaaS application means you can resell the Software as a Service. PayPal &amp;amp; Stripe are integrated so that you can receive payment from your end users. If you want to use the SaaS features and charge your end user for using the service you have to buy extended license. It has native API by which developers can integrate it’s facilities with another app. Nice colorful widgets are available. You can simply copy &amp;amp; paste some line of codes to any page you want and can display site information.</description>
<category>Clone Script</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 19:21:02 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Visitor Analytics : own site Unique Visitor Page View Bounce Rate Average Stay Time Average Visit Traffic Analysis Top Refferer New &amp;amp; Returning Visitor Content Overview Country &amp;amp; Browser Report OS &amp;amp; Device Report Website Analytics : any site (pdf report) Whois Info MOZ Info, DMOZ Listing Google Back Link IP Info Malware Scan Report Search Engine Index Social Network Traffic Keyword &amp;amp; Meta Info Alexa Info SimilarWeb Info Mobile Friendly Check Social Network Analysis (SEO Tool) Facebook Like, Share, Comment Google+ Comment LinkedIn, Xing, Buffer Share Reddit Score, Up, Down Pinterest Pin StumbleUpon List,View, Like, Comment Rank &amp;amp; Index Analysis (SEO Tool) Alexa Rank/Data SimilarWeb Rank &amp;amp; Data MOZ Check Google Index Yahoo Index Bing Index Domain Analysis (SEO Tool) Whois Search Data DMOZ Directory Listing Expired (Auction) Domain List IP Analysis (SEO Tool) What is my IP Domain IP Information Sites in Same IP IPv6 Compatibility Check Keyword Analysis (SEO Tool) Keyword Analyzer Keyword Position &amp;amp; Suggestion Correlated Trending Keywords Backlink &amp;amp; Ping (SEO Tool) Google Backlink Search Backlink Generator Website/Blog Ping Malware Scan (SEO Tool) Google Safe Browser Norton,McAfee,AVG Link Analysis (SEO Tool) Link Analyzer Page Status Check Google Adwords Scraper (SEO Tool) get paid google adwards links Google URL Shortener (SEO Tool) Google URL Shortener (bulk) Shortened URL Analytics (graphical) Code Minifier (SEO Tool) HTML Minifer CSS Minifier j&amp;#097;vascript Minifier Bonus Utilities (Utility Tool) Email Encoder/ Decoder URL Encoder/ Decoder Meta Tag Generator Robot Code Generator Plagiarism Check (unicode support) Valid Email Check Duplicate Email Filter Native API (25 APIs) + Native Widget (3 Widgets) Use our awesome native APIS And Widgets Responsive design Social login (Google + Facebook) Dashboard of Recent Activities Multilingual Use awesome services in your own language Multi-user, SaaS Pack, PayPal + Stripe Create packages, resell awesome services, setup your business and receive payment via PayPal / Stripe.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<b>Features</b><br><ul><li> Visitor Analytics : own site<br></li><li> Unique Visitor<br></li><li> Page View<br></li><li> Bounce Rate<br></li><li> Average Stay Time<br></li><li> Average Visit<br></li><li> Traffic Analysis<br></li><li> Top Refferer<br></li><li> New &amp; Returning Visitor<br></li><li> Content Overview<br></li><li> Country &amp; Browser Report<br></li><li> OS &amp; Device Report<br></li><li> <br></li><li> Website Analytics : any site (pdf report)<br></li><li> Whois Info<br></li><li> MOZ Info, DMOZ Listing<br></li><li> Google Back Link<br></li><li> IP Info<br></li><li> Malware Scan Report<br></li><li> Search Engine Index<br></li><li> Social Network Traffic<br></li><li> Keyword &amp; Meta Info<br></li><li> Alexa Info<br></li><li> SimilarWeb Info<br></li><li> Mobile Friendly Check<br></li><li> <br></li><li> Social Network Analysis (SEO Tool)<br></li><li> Facebook Like, Share, Comment<br></li><li> Google+ Comment<br></li><li> LinkedIn, Xing, Buffer Share<br></li><li> Reddit Score, Up, Down<br></li><li> Pinterest Pin<br></li><li> StumbleUpon List,View, Like, Comment<br></li><li> <br></li><li> Rank &amp; Index Analysis (SEO Tool)<br></li><li> Alexa Rank/Data<br></li><li> SimilarWeb Rank &amp; Data<br></li><li> MOZ Check<br></li><li> Google Index<br></li><li> Yahoo Index<br></li><li> Bing Index<br></li><li> <br></li><li> Domain Analysis (SEO Tool)<br></li><li> Whois Search Data<br></li><li> DMOZ Directory Listing<br></li><li> Expired (Auction) Domain List<br></li><li> <br></li><li> IP Analysis (SEO Tool)<br></li><li> What is my IP<br></li><li> Domain IP Information<br></li><li> Sites in Same IP<br></li><li> IPv6 Compatibility Check<br></li><li> <br></li><li> Keyword Analysis (SEO Tool)<br></li><li> Keyword Analyzer<br></li><li> Keyword Position &amp; Suggestion<br></li><li> Correlated Trending Keywords<br></li><li> <br></li><li> Backlink &amp; Ping (SEO Tool)<br></li><li> Google Backlink Search<br></li><li> Backlink Generator<br></li><li> Website/Blog Ping<br></li><li> <br></li><li> Malware Scan (SEO Tool)<br></li><li> Google Safe Browser<br></li><li> Norton,McAfee,AVG<br></li><li> <br></li><li> Link Analysis (SEO Tool)<br></li><li> Link Analyzer<br></li><li> Page Status Check<br></li><li> <br></li><li> Google Adwords Scraper (SEO Tool)<br></li><li> get paid google adwards links<br></li><li> Google URL Shortener (SEO Tool)<br></li><li> Google URL Shortener (bulk)<br></li><li> Shortened URL Analytics (graphical)<br></li><li> <br></li><li> Code Minifier (SEO Tool)<br></li><li> HTML Minifer<br></li><li> CSS Minifier<br></li><li> j&#097;vascript Minifier<br></li><li> <br></li><li> Bonus Utilities (Utility Tool)<br></li><li> Email Encoder/ Decoder<br></li><li> URL Encoder/ Decoder<br></li><li> Meta Tag Generator<br></li><li> Robot Code Generator<br></li><li> Plagiarism Check (unicode support)<br></li><li> Valid Email Check<br></li><li> Duplicate Email Filter<br></li><li> <br></li><li> Native API (25 APIs) + Native Widget (3 Widgets)<br></li><li> Use our awesome native APIS And Widgets <br></li><li> <br></li><li> Responsive design <br></li><li> <br></li><li> Social login (Google + Facebook) <br></li><li> <br></li><li> Dashboard of Recent Activities <br></li><li> <br></li><li> Multilingual<br></li><li> Use awesome services in your own language <br></li><li> <br></li><li> Multi-user, SaaS Pack, PayPal + Stripe<br></li><li> Create packages, resell awesome services, setup your business and receive payment via PayPal / Stripe.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="SiteSpy 3.3"> <br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>SiteDoctor 1.2</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2136-sitedoctor.html</link>
<description>Name : SiteDoctor - website health checker Version : 1.2 Type : Onpage SEO Script Price : $19 Homepage : Salepage SideDoctor can check your website’s health status within a minute. Follow the suggestion provided by the SiteDoctor and make your site more SEO friendly. SiteDoctor will analysis all metrics of your website such as title, description, keyword, tag, page size, page speed, server status, compression status, mobile friendly status, image/css/javacript status and many more other important metrics of your website. It has built in support for 11 languages and you can add any language easily. Awesome website will be provided and system collects emails of your visitors. Mailchimp is also integrated.</description>
<category>Clone Script</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 19:17:55 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Website health checker Google page speed insight Google mobile ready Website health comparison PDF report generation (own branding) Lead collection and Mailchimp integration Advertise ready Multilingual Powerful dashboard with visitor info Unique visitor Page view Average stay time Average visit Bounce rate Traffic source Visitor type Country-wise report Browser report OS report Device report 100% responsive design and many more Health check metrics Page title Page meta keyword Page meta description Keyword usage Text/HTML ratio robot.txt Sitemap Internal vs external links NoIndex, noFollow, doFollow links SEO friendly link Favicon Image alt text Doc type Depreciated HTML tag HTML page size Inline CSS Internal CSS Micro data scheme test IP &amp;amp; DNS report IP canonicalization test URL canonicalization test Plain text email test cURL response Mobile friendly check Page speed Usability score Avoid install interstitials that hide content Avoid plugins Configure viewport Size content to viewport Size tap target Landing page redirects GZIP compression Leverage browsing caching Server reponse time Minify CSS Minify HTML Minify j&amp;#097;vascript Render-blocking j&amp;#097;vascript &amp;amp; CSS Optimize Images Priotirize visible content</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<b>Features</b><br><ul><li> Website health checker<br></li><li> Google page speed insight<br></li><li> Google mobile ready<br></li><li> Website health comparison<br></li><li> PDF report generation (own branding)<br></li><li> Lead collection and Mailchimp integration<br></li><li> Advertise ready<br></li><li> Multilingual<br></li><li> Powerful dashboard with visitor info<br></li><li> Unique visitor<br></li><li> Page view<br></li><li> Average stay time<br></li><li> Average visit<br></li><li> Bounce rate<br></li><li> Traffic source<br></li><li> Visitor type<br></li><li> Country-wise report<br></li><li> Browser report<br></li><li> OS report<br></li><li> Device report<br></li><li> 100% responsive design and many more<br></li></ul><br>Health check metrics<br><ul><li> Page title<br></li><li> Page meta keyword<br></li><li> Page meta description<br></li><li> Keyword usage<br></li><li> Text/HTML ratio<br></li><li> robot.txt<br></li><li> Sitemap<br></li><li> Internal vs external links<br></li><li> NoIndex, noFollow, doFollow links<br></li><li> SEO friendly link<br></li><li> Favicon<br></li><li> Image alt text<br></li><li> Doc type<br></li><li> Depreciated HTML tag<br></li><li> HTML page size<br></li><li> Inline CSS<br></li><li> Internal CSS<br></li><li> Micro data scheme test<br></li><li> IP &amp; DNS report<br></li><li> IP canonicalization test<br></li><li> URL canonicalization test<br></li><li> Plain text email test<br></li><li> cURL response<br></li><li> Mobile friendly check<br></li><li> Page speed<br></li><li> Usability score<br></li><li> Avoid install interstitials that hide  content<br></li><li> Avoid plugins<br></li><li> Configure viewport<br></li><li> Size content to viewport<br></li><li> Size tap target<br></li><li> Landing page redirects<br></li><li> GZIP compression<br></li><li> Leverage browsing caching<br></li><li> Server reponse time<br></li><li> Minify CSS<br></li><li> Minify HTML<br></li><li> Minify j&#097;vascript<br></li><li> Render-blocking j&#097;vascript &amp; CSS<br></li><li> Optimize Images<br></li><li> Priotirize visible content<br><br></li></ul><br><img src="https://d1a6a9r46cnyll.cloudfront.com/1971b04b7f7fbc240e841be9a56c28b048071398/687474703a2f2f7865726f6e6569742e6e65742f64656d6f2f73697465646f635f656e7661746f5f696d6167652f707265766965772e706e67" alt="SiteDoctor 1.2"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>MobileX Pro 1.5</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1856-mobilex.html</link>
<description>Name : MobileX Pro WhiteLabel Version : 1.5 OS : Linux Type : Mobile Marketing/Email Marketing Price : $67 Homepage : SalePage Reach Out Via Multiple Channels, Increase Engagement And Set-Up New Side-Business To Generate 5-figure Months! From ANYWHERE In The World!!! I want to introduce you to MobileX Pro - which contains some POWERFUL features reserved for advanced members only. Only the most serious folks should consider this. If you brought MobileX because you thought it looks nice and MIGHT use it - this PRO upgrade might not be right for you. But if you TRULY saw the money making potential in MobileX and want to EXTEND it with additional features ONLY reserved for advanced players - consider this! Don’t worry though - MobileX Pro comes with all the essential training you need to get up and running within a couple of hours (if that!).</description>
<category>Clone Script</category>
<enclosure url="http://mobilex.io/wp-content/uploads/2016/06/06-change-logo.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2016 20:53:13 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Here’s Why You Need To Add Mobile X To Your Arsenal : Every month, about Over 6 billion text messages are sent in the U.S. each day Individuals will sign up at your portal to buy and send SMS to their family, friends and other contacts. These are your “Personal Users”. Organizations, companies and churches will sign up to buy and send SMS to their members, clients for invitation, meetings, reminder etc. These are your “Group users” Resellers (Entrepreneurs who also want to own their own BULK SMS/Autoresponder Website) will pay you huge money (you can charge as high as $997–$5,000 or even higher) Mobile X Features : Support Ticket System Import All Users Account Details Smart SMS Options Smart SMS Options View Transaction Records Country Code formatting API Routing Dynamic Reporting Short Code Autoresponder How Mobile X Works : Connect SMS with Email campaign and don’t ever miss the expected action from your leads anymore. This enables your clients to create an instant automated SMS campaign along with your running Email Campaign.MobileX: Bulk SMS Delivery Platform SMS Autoresponder allows you to track the open rate of text message and integrate SMS into your marketing mix. You can set SMS Auto Responder with up to 10 automated scheduled SMS Delivery Set in Minutes, Hours, and Days, for your required Campaign Design Flow. You can generate optin code for your SMS autoresponder campaign or import verified mobile list into the campaign.MobileX: Bulk SMS Delivery Platform API Routing connects several SMS APIs and use them simultaneously. Assign users to Specific Choice API for effective delivery. Auto Crediting allows instant online payment with credit card for account auto crediting…never run out from SMS credits. Users Credit Other Users offers users the leverage on the portal to have their clients register as users which will pay them directly and they can credit the users via Credit Transfer Function. SMS Personalization gives that personal feel with all SMS sent out. Don’t miss the sales conversion again! Touch a cord by mentioning recipient name in your bulk SMS campaign. Email Newsletter System to always keep your users up to date with new prices, products and discounts to step up your sales frequency. Blast Rich Content Email Newsletter to all users on your SMS portal. Message All Users by automatically sending tailored SMS to all users of your portal for specific price discounts, new products and create a rush for your service as you relate to your users more closely. Smart Bulk SMS Aggregator System allows your customers to connect with a gateway and resell the sums credit at a higher rate to end users for profit. 2-Way Premium SMS Short code Connectivity allows your prospects to text their name and email address with a keyword to a short code that automatically adds their details to your choice of email campaign list of either Mailchimp, Aweber or GetResponse. What makes Mobile X even more exciting is that it can be applied to almost any business model.Like say : All Stores (Grocery, Department, Shoe, Clothing, etc.) Restaurants (all types) Religious Organizations ( churches, mosques, etc) Bakeries/Coffee Shops Bars/Night Clubs Health/Sports Clubs Video Rental Stores Car/Motorcycle/Boat Dealerships Recreational/Social Organizations (Scouting, Rotary, Youth, Alumni, etc.) Media Stations (Television, Radio, etc.) Universities/Colleges Governments/Counties</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="325" src="http://player.vimeo.com/video/575442714" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><br />Here’s Why You Need To Add Mobile X To Your Arsenal :<br /><ul><li> Every month, about Over 6 billion text messages are sent in the U.S. each day<br /></li><li> Individuals will sign up at your portal to buy and send SMS to their family, friends and other contacts. These are your “Personal Users”.<br /></li><li> Organizations, companies and churches will sign up to buy and send SMS to their members, clients for invitation, meetings, reminder etc. These are your “Group users”<br /></li><li> Resellers (Entrepreneurs who also want to own their own BULK SMS/Autoresponder Website) will pay you huge money (you can charge as high as 7–,000 or even higher)<br /></li></ul><br />Mobile X Features :<br /><ul><li> Support Ticket System<br /></li><li> Import All Users Account Details<br /></li><li> Smart SMS Options<br /></li><li> Smart SMS Options<br /></li><li> View Transaction Records<br /></li><li> Country Code formatting<br /></li><li> API Routing<br /></li><li> Dynamic Reporting<br /></li><li> Short Code<br /></li><li> Autoresponder<br /></li></ul><br />How Mobile X Works :<br /><ul><li> Connect SMS with Email campaign and don’t ever miss the expected action from your leads anymore. This enables your clients to create an instant automated SMS campaign along with your running Email Campaign.MobileX: Bulk SMS Delivery Platform<br /></li><li> SMS Autoresponder allows you to track the open rate of text message and integrate SMS into your marketing mix. You can set SMS Auto Responder with up to 10 automated scheduled SMS Delivery Set in Minutes, Hours, and Days, for your required Campaign Design Flow. You can generate optin code for your SMS autoresponder campaign or import verified mobile list into the campaign.MobileX: Bulk SMS Delivery Platform<br /></li><li> API Routing connects several SMS APIs and use them simultaneously. Assign users to Specific Choice API for effective delivery.<br /></li><li> Auto Crediting allows instant online payment with credit card for account auto crediting…never run out from SMS credits.<br /></li><li> Users Credit Other Users offers users the leverage on the portal to have their clients register as users which will pay them directly and they can credit the users via Credit Transfer Function.<br /></li><li> SMS Personalization gives that personal feel with all SMS sent out. Don’t miss the sales conversion again! Touch a cord by mentioning recipient name in your bulk SMS campaign.<br /></li><li> Email Newsletter System to always keep your users up to date with new prices, products and discounts to step up your sales frequency. Blast Rich Content Email Newsletter to all users on your SMS portal.<br /></li><li> Message All Users by automatically sending tailored SMS to all users of your portal for specific price discounts, new products and create a rush for your service as you relate to your users more closely.<br /></li><li> Smart Bulk SMS Aggregator System allows your customers to connect with a gateway and resell the sums credit at a higher rate to end users for profit.<br /></li><li> 2-Way Premium SMS Short code Connectivity allows your prospects to text their name and email address with a keyword to a short code that automatically adds their details to your choice of email campaign list of either Mailchimp, Aweber or GetResponse.<br /></li></ul><br />What makes Mobile X even more exciting is that it can be applied to almost any business model.Like say :<br /><ul><li> All Stores (Grocery, Department, Shoe, Clothing, etc.)<br /></li><li> Restaurants (all types)<br /></li><li> Religious Organizations ( churches, mosques, etc)<br /></li><li> Bakeries/Coffee Shops<br /></li><li> Bars/Night Clubs<br /></li><li> Health/Sports Clubs<br /></li><li> Video Rental Stores<br /></li><li> Car/Motorcycle/Boat Dealerships<br /></li><li> Recreational/Social Organizations (Scouting, Rotary, Youth, Alumni, etc.)<br /></li><li> Media Stations (Television, Radio, etc.)<br /></li><li> Universities/Colleges<br /></li><li> Governments/Counties<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://mobilex.io/wp-content/uploads/2016/06/06-change-logo.png" alt="MobileX Pro 1.5" title="MobileX Pro 1.5"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="MobileX Pro 1.5" title="MobileX Pro 1.5"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>AVS - Adult Video Script 4.01 Full Plugins</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1034-avs-adult-video-script.html</link>
<description>Name : AVS - Adult Video Script Version : 4.01 Full Plugins Type : Pornhub Clone Price : $356 Homepage : SalePage Using our flexible, powerful and reliable video, photo gallery and game hosting solution, you can now easily turn great ideas into highly profitable adult tube sites, just like pornhub, redtube, youjizz, xvideos, tube8, youporn or xhamster.</description>
<category>Clone Script</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2015 01:33:35 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features fully redesigned/rewritten template, with several color schemes available responsive template, based on Bootstrap, that adapts for any device screen premium membership system, with limits and permissions for different user levels mobile phone and tablet video/photo uploads, including directly from their camera redesigned video player html5 video player fallback responsive video player, on video pages, blog pages, etc (both Flash and HTML5 players) new voting system, based on likes/dislikes responsive ads support (Google AdSense Responsive Ads, etc) responsive embedded videos several interface/functionality tweaks and improvemen Includes both AVS Adult &amp; Non-Adult 3.1 Responsive Templates Branding Free Option Video Grabber Plugin -0.13 Mass Embedder Plugin 1.5 (for v.3.1) Multi-Server Plugin 3.1 (for v.3.1)</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/rBgrrupM3i0?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> fully redesigned/rewritten template, with several color schemes available<br /></li><li> responsive template, based on Bootstrap, that adapts for any device screen<br /></li><li> premium membership system, with limits and permissions for different user levels<br /></li><li> mobile phone and tablet video/photo uploads, including directly from their camera<br /></li><li> redesigned video player<br /></li><li> html5 video player fallback<br /></li><li> responsive video player, on video pages, blog pages, etc (both Flash and HTML5 players)<br /></li><li> new voting system, based on likes/dislikes<br /></li><li> responsive ads support (Google AdSense Responsive Ads, etc)<br /></li><li> responsive embedded videos<br /></li><li> several interface/functionality tweaks and improvemen<br /></li><li> Includes both AVS Adult & Non-Adult 3.1<br /></li><li> Responsive Templates<br /></li><li> Branding Free Option<br /></li><li> Video Grabber Plugin -0.13<br /></li><li> Mass Embedder Plugin 1.5 (for v.3.1)<br /></li><li> Multi-Server Plugin 3.1 (for v.3.1)<br /></li></ul><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="AVS - Adult Video Script 4.01 Full Plugins" title="AVS - Adult Video Script 4.01 Full Plugins"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>YetiShare - File Hosting Script 4.3.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/858-yetishare-file-hosting-script.html</link>
<description>Name : YetiShare - File Hosting Script Version : 4.3.0 + Plugin Packs Type : File Hosting Script Price : $99 Homepage : SalePage The file upload script comes with a full admin area for managing the site, a modern multi-file upload interface, user registration &amp; members area, premium upgrades via PayPal, easy advert integration and much more.</description>
<category>Clone Script</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2015 00:50:04 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Multi-File Upload: With percentage progress, speed and time left. Pure HTML5 with support for Drag &amp; Drop. No reliance on Flash! Large uploads supported, 2GB+. Earn Money: Integration into PayPal for automatic premium account upgrades. Other payment gateways such as Authorize.com, OKPay &amp; BitPay also available. Download Managers: Full support for download managers with http auth. Resume broken downloads and enable multiple concurrent connections. Enable for all users or just premium. Plugins: Additional payment gateways, rewards program, media streamer, image viewer, FTP upload plugin and more. Create your own custom plugins using the plugin framework. External File Servers: Integrate any number of external file servers for additional storage. Any FTP server can be used. 100% Source Supplied: None of the source code is encoded, enabling you to amend the file sharing script and change the styles as needed. Feature Rich Admin Area: Usually overlooked in other scripts, the admin area to key to managing your website. Manage files, users, site settings, plugins, even monitor file downloads as they happen. Secure &amp; Well Established: Externally checked for XSS &amp; common SQL injection techniques before every release. If any are found after a release, they&#039;re fixed as a priority.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/gPNYdgetr98?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Multi-File Upload: With percentage progress, speed and time left. Pure HTML5 with support for Drag & Drop. No reliance on Flash! Large uploads supported, 2GB+.<br /></li><li> Earn Money: Integration into PayPal for automatic premium account upgrades. Other payment gateways such as Authorize.com, OKPay & BitPay also available.<br /></li><li> Download Managers: Full support for download managers with http auth. Resume broken downloads and enable multiple concurrent connections. Enable for all users or just premium.<br /></li><li> Plugins: Additional payment gateways, rewards program, media streamer, image viewer, FTP upload plugin and more. Create your own custom plugins using the plugin framework.<br /></li><li> External File Servers: Integrate any number of external file servers for additional storage. Any FTP server can be used.<br /></li><li> 100% Source Supplied: None of the source code is encoded, enabling you to amend the file sharing script and change the styles as needed.<br /></li><li> Feature Rich Admin Area: Usually overlooked in other scripts, the admin area to key to managing your website. Manage files, users, site settings, plugins, even monitor file downloads as they happen.<br /></li><li> Secure & Well Established: Externally checked for XSS & common SQL injection techniques before every release. If any are found after a release, they're fixed as a priority.<br /></li></ul><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="YetiShare - File Hosting Script 4.3.0" title="YetiShare - File Hosting Script 4.3.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Wurlie Short URL Script v3.3</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/857-wurlie-short-url-script-v33.html</link>
<description>Name : Wurlie Short URL Script Version : 3.3 Type : Short URL CMS Price : $49 Homepage : SalePage This PHP site script enables you to setup and maintain a url shortening service. Just upload the code, set the config and site details and you&#039;re ready to go. It comes with a full admin area for managing the site, 3 coloured templates, user registration, stats, easy advert integration and much more.</description>
<category>Clone Script</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2015 00:50:02 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Easy Setup &amp;amp; Configuration Extendable Using Plugins Scalable &amp;amp; Secure 100% Source Supplied</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<p></p>
<h3>Features</h3>
<p><br><ul><li> Easy Setup &amp; Configuration<br></li><li> Extendable Using Plugins<br></li><li> Scalable &amp; Secure<br></li><li> 100% Source Supplied<br></li></ul></p>
<div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Wurlie Short URL Script v3.3"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>WHMCS v7.4.2</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/856-whmcs-v5312.html</link>
<description>Name : WHMCS Version : 7.4.2 Type : Hosting Ecomerce Price : $324 Homepage : SalePage WHMCS gives you the power and the flexibility you need to do business the way you want the complete automation solution for web hosts,hosting, domain management, recurring billing and intergrated support</description>
<category>Clone Script</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2015 00:50:00 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Billing Features Automation Products/Ordering Domain Management Support Tools Reporting &amp;amp; Statistics Simple &amp;amp; Secure Customisable Developer Friendly Mobile</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/1fgcU4le318?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><p><br></p><br><h3>Features</h3><br><p><br><ul><li> Billing Features<br></li><li> Automation<br></li><li> Products/Ordering<br></li><li> Domain Management<br></li><li> Support Tools<br></li><li> Reporting &amp; Statistics<br></li><li> Simple &amp; Secure<br></li><li> Customisable<br></li><li> Developer Friendly<br></li><li> Mobile<br></li></ul></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="WHMCS v7.4.2"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Statamic v1.9.2</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/855-statamic-v192.html</link>
<description>Name : Statamic Version : 1.9.2 Type : CMS Price : $199 Homepage : SalePage Statamic is a flat-file CMS built on PHP 5.3, making your sites 100% version controllable. Extend to your heart&#039;s content with a robust API.</description>
<category>Clone Script</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2015 00:49:58 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Flexible Taxonomies: Make no mistake. Statamic is anything but static. Relate your content with practically anything. Full Version Control: Everything, from content to config, can be version controlled. Hello there, peace of mind. How&#039;ve you been? Easily Themable: Creating a theme is as easy as zipping up your assets. Design and build it your way, every time. Powerful Search: Powerful and highly customizable search is made available by our 1st party add-on Bloodhound. Form Builder: Build forms how you&#039;ve always imagined, complete with automatic validation &amp; emails. Check out Raven! Mapping Made Easy: Craft maps with markers, tooltips, and more with robust tools built right into the core. Members and Groups: From simple site users to full admins, Statamic lets you set up permissions and control any way you like. Runs Anywhere: With PHP 5.3 as the only requirement, Statamic can power websites on almost any web server, anywhere. Endlessly Extendable: Statamic has a robust API and library of hooks available to developers. Make Statamic your own.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<br /><div style="text-align:center;"><div class="dlevideoplayer" style="width:100%;max-width:425px;"><ul data-theme="default" data-preload="metadata"><li data-title="" data-type="youtube" data-url="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=s72r_wu_NVY"></li></ul></div></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Flexible Taxonomies: Make no mistake. Statamic is anything but static. Relate your content with practically anything.<br /></li><li> Full Version Control: Everything, from content to config, can be version controlled. Hello there, peace of mind. How've you been?<br /></li><li> Easily Themable: Creating a theme is as easy as zipping up your assets. Design and build it your way, every time.<br /></li><li> Powerful Search: Powerful and highly customizable search is made available by our 1st party add-on Bloodhound.<br /></li><li> Form Builder: Build forms how you've always imagined, complete with automatic validation & emails. Check out Raven!<br /></li><li> Mapping Made Easy: Craft maps with markers, tooltips, and more with robust tools built right into the core.<br /></li><li> Members and Groups: From simple site users to full admins, Statamic lets you set up permissions and control any way you like.<br /></li><li> Runs Anywhere: With PHP 5.3 as the only requirement, Statamic can power websites on almost any web server, anywhere.<br /></li><li> Endlessly Extendable: Statamic has a robust API and library of hooks available to developers. Make Statamic your own.<br /></li></ul><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Statamic v1.9.2" title="Statamic v1.9.2"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Host Bill v4.9.8</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/853-host-bill-v498.html</link>
<description>Name : Host Bill Version : 4.9.8 Type : CMS Price : $99 Homepage : SalePage Billing &amp; Automation Software</description>
<category>Clone Script</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2015 00:49:54 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Sell Products &amp; Services Automate Billing CRM - Client management Cloud Automation Hosting Automation Domain Management Client Portals Order Pages Ticketing System DCIM Live Chat IP Management Inventory Management DNS Management</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<br /><div style="text-align:center;"><div class="dlevideoplayer" style="width:100%;max-width:425px;"><ul data-theme="default" data-preload="metadata"><li data-title="" data-type="youtube" data-url="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=K-RAenYNuy8"></li></ul></div></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Sell Products & Services<br /></li><li> Automate Billing<br /></li><li> CRM - Client management<br /></li><li> Cloud Automation<br /></li><li> Hosting Automation<br /></li><li> Domain Management<br /></li><li> Client Portals<br /></li><li> Order Pages<br /></li><li> Ticketing System<br /></li><li> DCIM<br /></li><li> Live Chat<br /></li><li> IP Management<br /></li><li> Inventory Management<br /></li><li> DNS Management<br /></li></ul><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Host Bill v4.9.8" title="Host Bill v4.9.8"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>