<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>SMS Marketing Tools - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>SMS Marketing Tools - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>Call Recorder Pro 6.1</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3941-call-recorder-pro.html</link>
<description>Name : Call Recorder Pro Version : 6.1 OS : Android Type : Call Recording Application on iPhone Price : $119,309 Homepage : SalePage Call Recorder Pro (starting from ver 6.6) will no longer be updated by new functionality but will be working like a license activator to enable premium features for standard Free version.</description>
<category>SMS Marketing Tools</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 06:40:45 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Call Recorder Pro (starting from ver 6.6) will no longer be updated by new functionality but will be working like a license activator to enable premium features for standard Free version. It still will be working as before, but without new features like: - New UI with possibility to switch between Light and Dark themes - Notes for recordings. Add, edit, remove notes and search by notes. - Dial number from recording. - and more that will be adding in the next releases. So it is recommended to install standard free version and restore your license there.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Call Recorder Pro (starting from ver 6.6) will no longer be updated by new functionality but will be working like a license activator to enable premium features for standard Free version.<br></li><li> It still will be working as before, but without new features like:<br></li><li> - New UI with possibility to switch between Light and Dark themes<br></li><li> - Notes for recordings. Add, edit, remove notes and search by notes.<br></li><li> - Dial number from recording.<br></li><li> - and more that will be adding in the next releases.<br></li><li> So it is recommended to install standard free version and restore your license there.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Call Recorder Pro 6.1"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Automatic Call Recorder Pro v5.28</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3943-automatic-call-recorder-pro.html</link>
<description>Name : Automatic Call Recorder Pro Version : v5.28 OS : Android Type : Phone Call Recording Price : $0 Homepage : SalePage Auto Call Recorder, Best Call Recorder, Phone Call Recorder Call Recorder is the best solution for phone call recording. How to record a phone call on your Android? The easiest way is to choose Automatic Call Recorder Pro - best phone call recording app with a beautiful redesign in 2018! Auto call recorder is your new choice for phone call recording.</description>
<category>SMS Marketing Tools</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 06:40:45 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Functions: - Record your calls automatically while calling - Automatic Call Recorder - Advanced File Manager - You can play back, or save your call to mp3 files on your SD card - Record all outgoing calls - Record all incoming calls - Record all phone call conversations - Play audio recorded conversations - Delete recorded conversations - Send calls to email - After Call confirmation dialog for saving the recorded call - Set Audio Quality Auto call recorder is a the best free call recorder application with these features: - Record incoming call - Record Outgoing call - Favorite - Search - Marking recordings as important - Multi select, delete, send - Excluded numbers - Set password to protect privacy - Set different audio format (MP3, WAV) - Different recording modes by number, contact, non-contact or just selected contacts - Enable/Disable call recording - Records all your phone calls - Play recorded audio - Share recorded items - Playback through speaker or earpiece on your phone Share files: - Dropbox - Google Drive - SMS - Whatsapp - Viber - Skype</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Functions:<br></li><li> - Record your calls automatically while calling<br></li><li> - Automatic Call Recorder<br></li><li> - Advanced File Manager<br></li><li> - You can play back, or save your call to mp3 files on your SD card<br></li><li> - Record all outgoing calls<br></li><li> - Record all incoming calls<br></li><li> - Record all phone call conversations<br></li><li> - Play audio recorded conversations<br></li><li> - Delete recorded conversations<br></li><li> - Send calls to email<br></li><li> - After Call confirmation dialog for saving the recorded call<br></li><li> - Set Audio Quality<br></li><li> Auto call recorder is a the best free call recorder application with these features:<br></li><li> - Record incoming call<br></li><li> - Record Outgoing call<br></li><li> - Favorite<br></li><li> - Search<br></li><li> - Marking recordings as important<br></li><li> - Multi select, delete, send<br></li><li> - Excluded numbers<br></li><li> - Set password to protect privacy<br></li><li> - Set different audio format (MP3, WAV)<br></li><li> - Different recording modes by number, contact, non-contact or just selected contacts<br></li><li> - Enable/Disable call recording<br></li><li> - Records all your phone calls<br></li><li> - Play recorded audio<br></li><li> - Share recorded items<br></li><li> - Playback through speaker or earpiece on your phone<br></li><li> Share files:<br></li><li> - Dropbox<br></li><li> - Google Drive<br></li><li> - SMS<br></li><li> - Whatsapp<br></li><li> - Viber<br></li><li> - Skype<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Automatic Call Recorder Pro v5.28"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Multiple Phone Bulk SMS Sender 6.1.2.26</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1602-multiple-phone-bulk-sms-sender.html</link>
<description>Name : Multiple Phone Bulk SMS Sender Version : 6.1.2.26 + 2.4 + 2.0 OS : Windows Type : SMS Marketing Tools Price : $120 Homepage : SalePage Bulk sms sender is the best answer to all the problems related to SMS marketing campaign. This innovative software for bulk sms can send messages both in bulk and personalized ways to as many people as you want. You can either select whole list of numbers or can select a group to fulfill your purpose. It has multiple choices rigged that make the work adventurous for the users. This Bulk sms sender tool works by just connecting your phone to your PC. It automatically recognizes the cell phone and starts working. Users have the freedom to connect 10 cell phones in one go. You can either dump numbers one by one or file with numbers saved in it. It’s time saving to arrange list of numbers prior. The content you have used can be used for further planning or sending message to a new client. The USP of this tool is its ability to present reports on the messages delivered successfully and failed ones. The report gives user a clear picture of his reach in the market by giving the exact status of the messages he/she has sent. Starting from connecting to till sending of messages the bulk sms sender software does everything required. You can send sms from pc to mobile within minutes and can accomplish your target. This tool is undeniably the best software for bulk sms.</description>
<category>SMS Marketing Tools</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.technocomsolutions.com/images/10-phone-sms-sender/img1.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 01:21:22 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features No DND( Do not disturb) Restriction. Send SMS to individuals or list of phone numbers. Load Contact Numbers from File Send unique or personalized SMS to every Contact using Excel File Data. Send message in many different Languages (Unicode). Provides facility to send SMS using Delayed Delivery Options Add Custom Field value to generate unique SMS for Every Contact. Send Flash or Standard SMS. Sent messages can easily be saved and viewed by the user. Compatible with USB GSM technology based mobile devices. No inte.com connection is required to send SMS. Supports Multi Lingual SMS so that you can send SMS in Hindi, Gujarati, Urdu, Punjabi, Bengali, Tamil, Telugu, Kannada, Malayalam, German, French, Italian, Japanese, Arabic.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><div class="dlevideoplayer" style="width:100%;max-width:425px;"><ul data-theme="default" data-preload="metadata"><li data-title="" data-type="youtube" data-url="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nEO6tYANC8U"></li></ul></div></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> No DND( Do not disturb) Restriction.<br></li><li> Send SMS to individuals or list of phone numbers.<br></li><li> Load Contact Numbers from File<br></li><li> Send unique or personalized SMS to every Contact using Excel File Data.<br></li><li> Send message in many different Languages (Unicode).<br></li><li> Provides facility to send SMS using Delayed Delivery Options<br></li><li> Add Custom Field value to generate unique SMS for Every Contact.<br></li><li> Send Flash or Standard SMS.<br></li><li> Sent messages can easily be saved and viewed by the user.<br></li><li> Compatible with USB GSM technology based mobile devices.<br></li><li> No inte.com connection is required to send SMS.<br></li><li> Supports Multi Lingual SMS so that you can send SMS in Hindi, Gujarati, Urdu, Punjabi, Bengali, Tamil, Telugu, Kannada, Malayalam, German, French, Italian, Japanese, Arabic.<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://www.technocomsolutions.com/images/10-phone-sms-sender/img1.png" alt="Multiple Phone Bulk SMS Sender 6.1.2.26"><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Soild SMS Marketing 3.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/2047-soild-sms-marketing.html</link>
<description>Name : Soild SMS Marketing Version : 3.0 OS : Windows Type : SMS Marketing Tools Price : $125 Homepage : SalePage Solid SMS messaging software is automatically via USB 3G, messaging across.comworks Viettel, Vina, Mobi. Solid SMS messaging solutions for business efficiency, customer service and brand promotion. SMS Marketing is considered effective advertising channel is very high, over 90% of customers can not ignore or delete the message from your phone as unread. Statistics coming months the country has nearly 123 05/2012 million mobile subscribers. This figure is 1.5 times higher than the national population, an average of 1 people will use 1.5 sim mobile subscribers. With a young population structure, this number will continue to rise, you imagine just 1% above figures become your customers? Following the success of SMS Basic Solid, Solid sanpham SMS Pro born to serve better, more intensive for the needs of your SMS Marketing with SMS features multi-threaded, multi-device will turn on SMS Marketing into one story easy and fun ...</description>
<category>SMS Marketing Tools</category>
<enclosure url="http://solid.com.vn/ImgUpload/anh-QC.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2016 14:20:16 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Features support helps to send messages at a low cost (To send the message you need low cost buy sim sim promotion and register students for that promotion sim) Send multiple devices simultaneously from a USB 3G Automatically selects the.comwork to send device Actively install time, speed, sending limit of each device. Features personalized (Send a message with name of recipient supports professional customer care) The feature automatically changes the contents Solid messages first development in Vietnam. Import contacts from excel files automatically, txt Report results send Simple operation, only take 3 minutes to complete and submit! Support various languages of China, Japan, Korea .... To use SMS software Solid you need: - 01 computers with USB port (no need to use the Inte.com) - 01 or more USB devices 3G - 01 or more SIM mobile.comwork (3G sim need not be) - Software Solid SMS messaging</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="425" height="325" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/S1pz0e_ahGY?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Features support helps to send messages at a low cost (To send the message you need low cost buy sim sim promotion and register students for that promotion sim)<br /></li><li> Send multiple devices simultaneously from a USB 3G<br /></li><li> Automatically selects the.comwork to send device<br /></li><li> Actively install time, speed, sending limit of each device.<br /></li><li> Features personalized (Send a message with name of recipient supports professional customer care)<br /></li><li> The feature automatically changes the contents Solid messages first development in Vietnam.<br /></li><li> Import contacts from excel files automatically, txt<br /></li><li> Report results send<br /></li><li> Simple operation, only take 3 minutes to complete and submit!<br /></li><li> Support various languages of China, Japan, Korea ....<br /></li></ul><br /><b>To use SMS software Solid you need:</b><br />- 01 computers with USB port (no need to use the Inte.com)<br />- 01 or more USB devices 3G<br />- 01 or more SIM mobile.comwork (3G sim need not be)<br />- Software Solid SMS messaging<br /><img src="http://solid.com.vn/ImgUpload/anh-QC.jpg" alt="Soild SMS Marketing 3.0" title="Soild SMS Marketing 3.0"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Soild SMS Marketing 3.0" title="Soild SMS Marketing 3.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>SMSGadget 1.4</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1370-smsgadget.html</link>
<description>Name : SMSGadget Version : 1.4 OS : Windows Type : Bulk SMS Sender Price : $40 Homepage : SalePage SMSGadget is Bulk SMS text messaging software for business to send marketing &amp; advertising SMS messages to customers with mobile phone or GSM Modem from PC. Marketing has never been so cheap and accessible as it is today. A business whether sole proprietor, partnership, or private limited company can easily promote its product or services to their target market instead of spending billions of money on Banner Ads, Newspaper Ads, Television Ads. etc. for a single view. Mobile Messaging is the only way to reach anybody from an educated professional to basic literate person. In this mobile age, people like to make deals directly with the owner/customer as in it is fast to clear apprehension and take decisions accordingly. Schools, colleges, retailers, wholesalers, political parties, designers, Lawyers, Barbers, Accountants, Consultants, Tax Experts, and Solicitors etc can efficiently reach out to their targeted customers just by sending a single SMS. SMSGadget Bulk SMS Sender To promote your product, you need to send SMS in bulk. With SMSGadget you can send thousands of SMS with single click. SMS Gadget has unique features such as unlimited groups creation, unlimited contacts, and import, export facility. With SMSGadget (Bulk SMS Sender), messages like special offers, promotion, reminder and statement are well suited to be delivered time to time. There is no huge investment and hidden cost in using SMSGadget E-Marketer. Just use your existing computer and mobile phone, with connection options of USB data cable, Bluetooth or Infra red, you are equipped with a powerful marketing weapon.</description>
<category>SMS Marketing Tools</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.ahmadsoftware.com/upload/SMSGadget.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2016 03:41:38 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Intuitive and modern look and feel, with ease of use. Auto detects all available COM ports in computer system and automatically finds out the attached/connected GSM based phones or GSM Modem. Compatible with USB or Bluetooth GSM technology based mobile devices. SMS composer with Long SMS, Flash SMS and custom field support and SMS can be Send in different languages. Skip duplicate phone number entries. Sends standard SMS or notifications as per your need. Three Custom fields for each contact to generate unique SMS for every contact. No inte.com connection is required to send SMS. Send SMS to individuals or list of phone numbers. Import contact list or content from text, CSV or Excel file saved on PC. Export contacts in txt and CSV format. Easiest way to Load Recipient Phone Number. Option to skip duplicate number entries. Save sent items for future reference. Advance delayed delivery option while sending SMS. Save send items for future reference. Supports multiple GSM based phone/modems. Error logging and reporting from within the SMSGadget for fast feedback. Can create project files and opened later for different &quot;Marketing Campaigns&quot;. Each project consists of &quot;Devices&quot;, &quot;Contacts&quot;, &quot;Inbox&quot;, &quot;Outbox&quot; and &quot;Sent&quot; System Requirements: GSM supported Mobile(Cell) Phone or GSM Modem Driver of the connected GSM device Windows 8, Windows 7, Windows Vista, Windows XP, Windows 2003, Windows 2000 Net Framework v4.0 GSM (AT Commands) Supported Mobiles Nokia:Nokia C2-01, C101, 6230i, 2690,2730, 2700, 2300, 6021,5230,5400, 3110, 6230, E50, E66, ASHA305 Motorola: L6, L7 etc. Sony Ericsson: All &quot;i&quot; models like K750i etc. Huawei: U636.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/6qJqBbWXDEA?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Intuitive and modern look and feel, with ease of use.<br /></li><li> Auto detects all available COM ports in computer system and automatically finds out the attached/connected GSM based phones or GSM Modem.<br /></li><li> Compatible with USB or Bluetooth GSM technology based mobile devices.<br /></li><li> SMS composer with Long SMS, Flash SMS and custom field support and SMS can be Send in different languages.<br /></li><li> Skip duplicate phone number entries.<br /></li><li> Sends standard SMS or notifications as per your need.<br /></li><li> Three Custom fields for each contact to generate unique SMS for every contact.<br /></li><li> No inte.com connection is required to send SMS.<br /></li><li> Send SMS to individuals or list of phone numbers.<br /></li><li> Import contact list or content from text, CSV or Excel file saved on PC.<br /></li><li> Export contacts in txt and CSV format.<br /></li><li> Easiest way to Load Recipient Phone Number.<br /></li><li> Option to skip duplicate number entries.<br /></li><li> Save sent items for future reference.<br /></li><li> Advance delayed delivery option while sending SMS.<br /></li><li> Save send items for future reference.<br /></li><li> Supports multiple GSM based phone/modems.<br /></li><li> Error logging and reporting from within the SMSGadget for fast feedback.<br /></li><li> Can create project files and opened later for different "Marketing Campaigns". Each project consists of "Devices", "Contacts", "Inbox", "Outbox" and "Sent"<br /></li></ul><br /><br /><br />System Requirements:<br /><ul><li> GSM supported Mobile(Cell) Phone or GSM Modem<br /></li><li> Driver of the connected GSM device<br /></li><li> Windows 8, Windows 7, Windows Vista, Windows XP, Windows 2003, Windows 2000<br /></li><li> Net Framework v4.0<br /></li></ul><br /><br />GSM (AT Commands) Supported Mobiles<br /><ul><li> Nokia:Nokia C2-01, C101, 6230i, 2690,2730, 2700, 2300, 6021,5230,5400, 3110, 6230, E50, E66, ASHA305<br /></li><li> Motorola: L6, L7 etc.<br /></li><li> Sony Ericsson: All "i" models like K750i etc.<br /></li><li> Huawei: U636.<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://www.ahmadsoftware.com/upload/SMSGadget.jpg" alt="SMSGadget 1.4" title="SMSGadget 1.4"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="SMSGadget 1.4" title="SMSGadget 1.4"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>SMSGadget For Android 1.4</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1623-smsgadget-for-android.html</link>
<description>Name : SMSGadget For Android Version : 1.4 OS : Windows Type : Bulk SMS Sender Price : $40 Homepage : SalePage SMSGadget is Bulk SMS text messaging software for business to send marketing &amp; advertising SMS messages to customers with mobile phone or GSM Modem from PC. Marketing has never been so cheap and accessible as it is today. A business whether sole proprietor, partnership, or private limited company can easily promote its product or services to their target market instead of spending billions of money on Banner Ads, Newspaper Ads, Television Ads. etc. for a single view. Mobile Messaging is the only way to reach anybody from an educated professional to basic literate person. In this mobile age, people like to make deals directly with the owner/customer as in it is fast to clear apprehension and take decisions accordingly. Schools, colleges, retailers, wholesalers, political parties, designers, Lawyers, Barbers, Accountants, Consultants, Tax Experts, and Solicitors etc can efficiently reach out to their targeted customers just by sending a single SMS. SMSGadget Bulk SMS Sender To promote your product, you need to send SMS in bulk. With SMSGadget you can send thousands of SMS with single click. SMS Gadget has unique features such as unlimited groups creation, unlimited contacts, and import, export facility. With SMSGadget (Bulk SMS Sender), messages like special offers, promotion, reminder and statement are well suited to be delivered time to time. There is no huge investment and hidden cost in using SMSGadget E-Marketer. Just use your existing computer and mobile phone, with connection options of USB data cable, Bluetooth or Infra red, you are equipped with a powerful marketing weapon.</description>
<category>SMS Marketing Tools</category>
<enclosure url="http://ahmadsoftware.com/upload/2212015104623.gif" type="image/gif" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2016 03:41:21 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Intuitive and modern look and feel, with ease of use. Compatible with most of the Android phones. SMS composer with Long SMS, Flash SMS and custom field support and SMS can be Send in different languages. Skip duplicate phone number entries. Sends standard SMS or notifications as per your need. Three Custom fields for each contact to generate unique SMS for every contact. No inte.com connection is required to send SMS. Send SMS to individuals or list of phone numbers. Import contact list or content from text, CSV or Excel file saved on PC. Export contacts in txt and CSV format. Easiest way to Load Recipient Phone Number. Option to skip duplicate number entries. Save sent items for future reference. Advance delayed delivery option while sending SMS. Save send items for future reference. Supports multiple Android phones. Error logging and reporting from within the SMSGadget for fast feedback. Can create project files and opened later for different &quot;Marketing Campaigns&quot;. Each project consists of &quot;Devices&quot;, &quot;Contacts&quot;, &quot;Inbox&quot;, &quot;Outbox&quot; and &quot;Sent&quot; System Requirements: Android Mobile (Cell) Phone connected to local.comwork through WiFi Limitations: Android OS has 30 SMS limit per 30 minutes (Previous versions has 100 SMS per hour limit) and you cannot send more than this limit. However you can unlock the SMS Limit with any SMS Limit Unlocker software. For example: SMS Limit Unlock Download Note:&quot;SMS Limit Unlock&quot; software is free but use it on your own risk because we are not the vendor of this software. If you are technical then please follow the link: How to increase SMS Limit on Android</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/6qJqBbWXDEA?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Intuitive and modern look and feel, with ease of use.<br /></li><li> Compatible with most of the Android phones.<br /></li><li> SMS composer with Long SMS, Flash SMS and custom field support and SMS can be Send in different languages.<br /></li><li> Skip duplicate phone number entries.<br /></li><li> Sends standard SMS or notifications as per your need.<br /></li><li> Three Custom fields for each contact to generate unique SMS for every contact.<br /></li><li> No inte.com connection is required to send SMS.<br /></li><li> Send SMS to individuals or list of phone numbers.<br /></li><li> Import contact list or content from text, CSV or Excel file saved on PC.<br /></li><li> Export contacts in txt and CSV format.<br /></li><li> Easiest way to Load Recipient Phone Number.<br /></li><li> Option to skip duplicate number entries.<br /></li><li> Save sent items for future reference.<br /></li><li> Advance delayed delivery option while sending SMS.<br /></li><li> Save send items for future reference.<br /></li><li> Supports multiple Android phones.<br /></li><li> Error logging and reporting from within the SMSGadget for fast feedback.<br /></li><li> Can create project files and opened later for different "Marketing Campaigns". Each project consists of "Devices", "Contacts", "Inbox", "Outbox" and "Sent"<br /><br /></li></ul><br /><br /><br />System Requirements:<br /><ul><li> Android Mobile (Cell) Phone connected to local.comwork through WiFi<br /></li></ul><br /><b>Limitations:</b><br />Android OS has 30 SMS limit per 30 minutes (Previous versions has 100 SMS per hour limit) and you cannot send more than this limit. However you can unlock the SMS Limit with any SMS Limit Unlocker software. For example:<br /><a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.mittelmanapps.smslimitunlock&amp;hl=en"  target="_blank">SMS Limit Unlock Download</a><br />Note:"SMS Limit Unlock" software is free but use it on your own risk because we are not the vendor of this software. <br />If you are technical then please follow the link: <a href="http://forum.xda-developers.com/showthread.php?t=1835056"  target="_blank">How to increase SMS Limit on Android</a><br /><img src="http://ahmadsoftware.com/upload/2212015104623.gif" alt="SMSGadget For Android 1.4" title="SMSGadget For Android 1.4"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="SMSGadget For Android 1.4" title="SMSGadget For Android 1.4"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Bulk SMS Sender 1.5</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1601-bulk-sms-sender.html</link>
<description>Name : Bulk SMS Sender Version : 1.5 OS : Windows Type : SMS Marketing Tools Price : $50 Homepage : SalePage Bulk SMS Sender is a software to send SMSes to thousands of Mobile Numbers from PC. You can send multiple SMSes at once through your connected Mobile Phone (GSM Mobile Phone). It also allows you to customize your SMS with many fields such as (Mobile Number Holder&#039;s Name). It automatically detects connected mobile phones and allows to select a mobile number through which you want to send SMSes from PC. It includes many feature such as delayed deliver SMS. You can load a list of mobile numbers from a file on the PC or can manually one by one.</description>
<category>SMS Marketing Tools</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.technocomsolutions.com/bulk_sms_sender/image3.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2016 06:49:44 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features No DND( Do not disturb) Restriction. Bulk SMS Sender to individuals or list of phone numbers from PC via using GSM Mobile Numbers. Import Mobile Phone numbers from files from your hard-drive. Includes Delayed Delivery Option for SMS for mobile numbers. It automatically removes duplicate Mobile Numbers. Advance option to send Flash or Standard SMS. Compatible with major GSM technology based mobile devices. No inte.com connection is required to send SMS. Supports Multi Lingual SMS so that you can send SMS in Hindi, Gujarati, Urdu, Punjabi, Bengali, Tamil, Telugu, Kannada, Malayalam, German, French, Italian, Japanese, Arabic.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/nEO6tYANC8U?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> No DND( Do not disturb) Restriction.<br /></li><li> Bulk SMS Sender to individuals or list of phone numbers from PC via using GSM Mobile Numbers.<br /></li><li> Import Mobile Phone numbers from files from your hard-drive.<br /></li><li> Includes Delayed Delivery Option for SMS for mobile numbers.<br /></li><li> It automatically removes duplicate Mobile Numbers.<br /></li><li> Advance option to send Flash or Standard SMS.<br /></li><li> Compatible with major GSM technology based mobile devices.<br /></li><li> No inte.com connection is required to send SMS.<br /></li><li> Supports Multi Lingual SMS so that you can send SMS in Hindi, Gujarati, Urdu, Punjabi, Bengali, Tamil, Telugu, Kannada, Malayalam, German, French, Italian, Japanese, Arabic.<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://www.technocomsolutions.com/bulk_sms_sender/image3.png" alt="Bulk SMS Sender 1.5" title="Bulk SMS Sender 1.5"  /><br /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Bulk SMS Sender 1.5" title="Bulk SMS Sender 1.5"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Bulk SMS From PC 1.7 Professional Edition</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1209-bulk-sms-from-pc.html</link>
<description>Name : Bulk SMS From PC Version : 1.7 Professional Edition OS : Windows Type : SMS Marketing Bot Price : $297 Homepage : SalePage Bulk sms From PC – Send free text message from your computer Bulk SMS From PC - send free text message worldwideWith Bulk SMS From PC you can Send personalized FREE text messages from your computer to mobile phones. Take advantage of Bulk SMS From PC…Now! No monthly fees, no contracts, no hidden costs SMS…the new way of communication. Text messaging has become a new medium of communication. The market is ready and you, are you ready for the boom? 2004: United States – over 2.5 billion messages sent 2005: Over 900 billion messages sent (worldwide) 2008: Over 1,5 trillion messages (worldwide) With our bulk sms software you can easily Manage &amp; send SMS to multiple phone numbers. Bulk SMS From PC : send messages from your computer to mobile phones.Text messaging has become a new medium of communication. Take advantage of it now…the benefits are incomparable! With text messaging companies can have a one-to-one interaction with their customers and offer superior service. In the same way, Bulk SMS From PC was created. The software allows you to manage and send SMS text messages instantly to groups or individuals via your Inte.com connected computer. Bulk SMS From PC is a versatile, powerful, lightweight software that enables you to create and send, in record time, an unlimited number of personalized SMS text messages. Text messaging has been growing an exponential speed and it is now accepted by the people the same way they view their email, faxes, and even traditional mail. Bulk SMS From PC makes its easy for businesses, work colleagues, clubs and social organizations, friends, and family to stay in touch via text message using a simple PC based application. Take advantage of the power and simplicity of Bulk SMS From PC while personalizing each special offer, promotion or any other advertisement you send! Bulk SMS From PC is the professional SMS mass mailing software you absolutely need! Try it, you’ll love it!</description>
<category>SMS Marketing Tools</category>
<enclosure url="http://i.imgur.com/uvEfMyA.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="http://i.imgur.com/sGm2AEQ.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2016 01:54:43 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Typical Uses of a bulk sms software Send SMS to multiple phone numbers Co-ordinate events and meetings for clubs and teams Send messages to customers, friends, family, work colleagues, etc. Advertise your venue – club, restaurant, store, etc. Used for improved debt collection Used in all industries from clubs to organizations Speak to your customers and teams on the go Notify customers of order status. etc Remind customers of appointments and bookings etc. Some Features &amp; Benefits of our SMS Program A versatile, lightweight program, with heavy commercial capabilities Manage and send SMS Text Messages from your PC as easy as E-Mail Send personalized SMS’s at the touch of a button No monthly fees, no contracts, no hidden costs More cost effective than a telephone call Customized Template messages More immediate than e-mail Very secure and private Messages are retained on phone, can be read later Communicate with large groups of people instantaneously Send unlimited messages Multiple Recipients Bulk SMS From PC does not charge for each message Address Book Manage large phone lists Send mass texts Send a message to as many phone numbers as you want Add as many phone numbers as you need Phone numbers can be removed anytime. Add phone numbers by importing a text file or enter the numbers manually A powerful merge facility allows automatic individualisation of messages to your whole database of contacts Duplicate numbers are automatically removed. Perfect for alerts, marketing or simply communicating with staff and clients Include merge fields to personalise messages Create message templates for frequently used messages</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/otanXnfNL3o?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br />Typical Uses of a bulk sms software<br /><ul><li> Send SMS to multiple phone numbers<br /></li><li> Co-ordinate events and meetings for clubs and teams<br /></li><li> Send messages to customers, friends, family, work colleagues, etc.<br /></li><li> Advertise your venue – club, restaurant, store, etc.<br /></li><li> Used for improved debt collection<br /></li><li> Used in all industries from clubs to organizations<br /></li><li> Speak to your customers and teams on the go<br /></li><li> Notify customers of order status. etc<br /></li><li> Remind customers of appointments and bookings etc.<br /></li></ul><br />Some Features & Benefits of  our SMS Program<br /><ul><li> A versatile, lightweight program, with heavy commercial capabilities<br /></li><li> Manage and send SMS Text Messages from your PC as easy as E-Mail<br /></li><li> Send personalized SMS’s at the touch of a button<br /></li><li> No monthly fees, no contracts, no hidden costs<br /></li><li> More cost effective than a telephone call<br /></li><li> Customized Template messages<br /></li><li> More immediate than e-mail<br /></li><li> Very secure and private<br /></li><li> Messages are retained on phone, can be read later<br /></li><li> Communicate with large groups of people instantaneously<br /></li><li> Send unlimited messages<br /></li><li> Multiple Recipients<br /></li><li> Bulk SMS From PC does not charge for each message<br /></li><li> Address Book<br /></li><li> Manage large phone lists<br /></li><li> Send mass texts<br /></li><li> Send a message to as many phone numbers as you want<br /></li><li> Add as many phone numbers as you need<br /></li><li> Phone numbers can be removed anytime.<br /></li><li> Add phone numbers by importing a text file or enter the numbers manually<br /></li><li> A powerful merge facility allows automatic individualisation of<br /></li><li> messages to your whole database of contacts<br /></li><li> Duplicate numbers are automatically removed.<br /></li><li> Perfect for alerts, marketing or simply communicating with staff and clients<br /></li><li> Include merge fields to personalise messages<br /></li><li> Create message templates for frequently used messages<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://i.imgur.com/uvEfMyA.jpg" alt="Bulk SMS From PC 1.7 Professional Edition" title="Bulk SMS From PC 1.7 Professional Edition"  /><br /><img src="http://i.imgur.com/sGm2AEQ.jpg" alt="Bulk SMS From PC 1.7 Professional Edition" title="Bulk SMS From PC 1.7 Professional Edition"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Bulk SMS From PC 1.7 Professional Edition" title="Bulk SMS From PC 1.7 Professional Edition"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>