<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Url Harvester - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Url Harvester - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>Website Finder 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4215-website-finder.html</link>
<description>Name : Website Finder Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Software Tool for Searching for Websites Price : $59 Homepage : SalePage Website Finder is a software tool for searching for websites by your set criteria. By default the homepage of each website is checked for the criteria but the URL that is returned from Google searches can also be checked.</description>
<category>Url Harvester</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2018 21:54:46 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>[media=https://youtu.be/pZ_IFfKW07Q] Features Website Finder has three methods of finding websites matching your criteria. Crawl a list of websites for matching criteria - If you have a list of websites that you would like to check simply paste them in and Website Finder will check the homepage of each one for your set criteria. Crawl search results by niche related keywords for matching websites/criteria - Enter a list of niche related keywords and Webiste Finder will search Google for all these niche related keywords and check every result (website) for your set criteria. There are two main options with this search, the criteria check can be applied to the result (URL) Google returns or the homepage of the result that is returned. Endless crawl for matching websites - Enter your seed list of websites to start crawling from and Website Finder will check that inital seed website(s) for your criteria but then also crawl a specified amount of URLs on that website (30 by default) extracting all outbound links and then crawling these outbound websites. This process is repeated endlessly. Website Finder will just keep crawling from website to website checking to see if they match your set criteria. Why should I use this tool? List of possible uses are but not limited to... - Find websites with outdated plugins to market to - Find slow websites to sell faster hosting to - Find websites with security issues to offer security patching services to - Find websites to sell themes to, e.g use the Google search option to find all dog related websites running WordPress and sell them dog related WordPress themes</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;">[media=https://youtu.be/pZ_IFfKW07Q]</div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Website Finder has three methods of finding websites matching your criteria.<br></li><li>  Crawl a list of websites for matching criteria<br></li><li>  - If you have a list of websites that you would like to check simply paste them in and Website Finder will check the homepage of each one for your set criteria.<br></li><li>  Crawl search results by niche related keywords for matching websites/criteria<br></li><li>  - Enter a list of niche related keywords and Webiste Finder will search Google for all these niche related keywords and check every result (website) for your set criteria. There are two main options with this search, the criteria check can be applied to the result (URL) Google returns or the homepage of the result that is returned.<br></li><li>  Endless crawl for matching websites<br></li><li>  - Enter your seed list of websites to start crawling from and Website Finder will check that inital seed website(s) for your criteria but then also crawl a specified amount of URLs on that website (30 by default) extracting all outbound links and then crawling these outbound websites. This process is repeated endlessly. Website Finder will just keep crawling from website to website checking to see if they match your set criteria.<br></li><li> Why should I use this tool?<br></li><li>  List of possible uses are but not limited to...<br></li><li>  - Find websites with outdated plugins to market to<br></li><li>  - Find slow websites to sell faster hosting to<br></li><li>  - Find websites with security issues to offer security patching services to<br></li><li>  - Find websites to sell themes to, e.g use the Google search option to find all dog related websites running WordPress and sell them dog related WordPress themes<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Website Finder 1.0 "><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Wireshark 2.4.6</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3936-wireshark.html</link>
<description>Name : Wireshark Version : 2.4.6 OS : Windows Type : Network Protocol Analyzer Price : $50 Homepage : SalePage Wireshark is the world’s foremost and widely-used.comwork protocol analyzer. It lets you see what’s happening on your.comwork at a microscopic level and is the de facto (and often de jure) standard across many commercial and non-profit enterprises, government agencies, and educational institutions. Wireshark development thrives thanks to the volunteer contributions of.comworking experts around the globe and is the continuation of a project started by Gerald Combs in 1998.</description>
<category>Url Harvester</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 06:40:45 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Wireshark has a rich feature set which includes the following: - Deep inspection of hundreds of protocols, with more being added all the time - Live capture and offline analysis - Standard three-pane packet browser - Multi-platform: Runs on Windows, Linux, macOS, Solaris, FreeBSD, NetBSD, and many others - Captured.comwork data can be browsed via a GUI, or via the TTY-mode TShark utility - The most powerful display filters in the industry - Rich VoIP analysis - Read/write many different capture file formats: tcpdump (libpcap), Pcap NG, Catapult DCT2000, Cisco Secure IDS iplog, Microsoft Network Monitor, Network General Sniffer® (compressed and uncompressed), Sniffer® Pro, and NetXray®, Network Instruments Observer, NetScreen snoop, Novell LANalyzer, RADCOM WAN/LAN Analyzer, Shomiti/Finisar Surveyor, Tektronix K12xx, Visual Networks Visual UpTime, WildPackets EtherPeek/TokenPeek/AiroPeek, and many others - Capture files compressed with gzip can be decompressed on the fly - Live data can be read from Ethe.com, IEEE 802.11, PPP/HDLC, ATM, Bluetooth, USB, Token Ring, Frame Relay, FDDI, and others (depending on your platform) - Decryption support for many protocols, including IPsec, ISAKMP, Kerberos, SNMPv3, SSL/TLS, WEP, and WPA/WPA2 - Coloring rules can be applied to the packet list for quick, intuitive analysis - Output can be exported to XML, PostScript®, CSV, or plain text</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/U0QABcTD-xc?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Wireshark has a rich feature set which includes the following:<br></li><li> - Deep inspection of hundreds of protocols, with more being added all the time<br></li><li> - Live capture and offline analysis<br></li><li> - Standard three-pane packet browser<br></li><li> - Multi-platform: Runs on Windows, Linux, macOS, Solaris, FreeBSD, NetBSD, and many others<br></li><li> - Captured.comwork data can be browsed via a GUI, or via the TTY-mode TShark utility<br></li><li> - The most powerful display filters in the industry<br></li><li> - Rich VoIP analysis<br></li><li> - Read/write many different capture file formats: tcpdump (libpcap), Pcap NG, Catapult DCT2000, Cisco Secure IDS iplog, Microsoft Network Monitor, Network General Sniffer® (compressed and uncompressed), Sniffer® Pro, and NetXray®, Network Instruments Observer, NetScreen snoop, Novell LANalyzer, RADCOM WAN/LAN Analyzer, Shomiti/Finisar Surveyor, Tektronix K12xx, Visual Networks Visual UpTime, WildPackets EtherPeek/TokenPeek/AiroPeek, and many others<br></li><li> - Capture files compressed with gzip can be decompressed on the fly<br></li><li> - Live data can be read from Ethe.com, IEEE 802.11, PPP/HDLC, ATM, Bluetooth, USB, Token Ring, Frame Relay, FDDI, and others (depending on your platform)<br></li><li> - Decryption support for many protocols, including IPsec, ISAKMP, Kerberos, SNMPv3, SSL/TLS, WEP, and WPA/WPA2<br></li><li> - Coloring rules can be applied to the packet list for quick, intuitive analysis<br></li><li> - Output can be exported to XML, PostScript®, CSV, or plain text<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Wireshark 2.4.6"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Search Engine Scraper 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3731-search-engine-scraper.html</link>
<description>Name : Search Engine Scraper Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Search Engine Scraper Price : $0 Homepage : SalePage Search Engine Scraper is a 100% free and full (no trail etc) desktop application that allows you to scrape results from search engines such as Google and Bing. It will also allow you to check Moz DA and PA for each URL found if you enter a free Moz API key and can search an unlimited amount of keywords. You can also export all URL&#039;s that search engine scraper finds.</description>
<category>Url Harvester</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 05:28:27 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>[media=https://youtu.be/DCUzyxMzOzE] Features Why should I use Search Engine Scraper? Copying URL&#039;s for each keyword&#039;s search results is a massively tedious task, especially if you have hundreds or even thousands of search queries you want to grab the ranking websites for. Then add the time to check Moz stats if needed and this may take weeks. Search Engine Scraper can do this in minutes. How does Search Engine Scraper work? Search Engine Scraper simply sends HTTP requests to Google and Bing just as your browser normally would then automatically parses the response and extracts the URL&#039;s that are returned for your search keyword / query.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;">[media=https://youtu.be/DCUzyxMzOzE]</div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br>Why should I use Search Engine Scraper?<br>Copying URL's for each keyword's search results is a massively tedious task, especially if you have hundreds or even thousands of search queries you want to grab the ranking websites for. Then add the time to check Moz stats if needed and this may take weeks. Search Engine Scraper can do this in minutes.<br><br>How does Search Engine Scraper work?<br>Search Engine Scraper simply sends HTTP requests to Google and Bing just as your browser normally would then automatically parses the response and extracts the URL's that are returned for your search keyword / query.<br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Search Engine Scraper 1.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>DoComment 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3719-docomment.html</link>
<description>Name : DoComment Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Find DoFollow Blog Comments Price : $0 Homepage : SalePage But fear not DoFollow links still exist however now days they are rare and most comments are moderated first. So to successfully use DoFollow blog comments to help rank your website on Google you need to use software to automatically search the inte.com for these websites that have DoFollow blog comment sections then manually leave a comment and link of value that the website owner will approve. DoComment listens to every tweet that is related to your niche then follows any links it finds in those tweets then checks to see if they&#039;re are any DoFollow blog comment links available on that website.</description>
<category>Url Harvester</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 07:11:12 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>[media=https://youtu.be/06e_FYx47ho] Features What are Do Follow Blog Comments? Ok so everyone knows the more websites/links that are pointing to your website, the higher you appear on the Google search results. Yes I know there are other things like link quality and content etc to consider but generally speaking this is true. These links can either be marked with &quot;Do follow&quot; or &quot;No follow&quot; by the website owner when they create the link. If the link is Do Follow generally it will help boost you up the Google search engine results and if its NoFollow it will have little if any effect at all. So obviously you only want DoFollow links. Now a few years ago when you posted a comment on a blog any links you added were all DoFollow so people wrote software to mass automate this leaving annoying spammy comments that caused website owners and CMS creators to make sure most comments were automatically NoFollow. Why should I use DoComment? You should use DoComment because its a great way of finding 100% free niche related spam free safe backlinks to boost your website up the Google search engine results. How does DoComment work? DoComment uses the twitter streaming API to listen to niche realated keywords you set. It then follows the links in these niche related tweets and analyzes the HTML to see if it thinks its found some DoFollow links in the comments section.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;">[media=https://youtu.be/06e_FYx47ho]</div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br>What are Do Follow Blog Comments?<br>Ok so everyone knows the more websites/links that are pointing to your website, the higher you appear on the Google search results. Yes I know there are other things like link quality and content etc to consider but generally speaking this is true. These links can either be marked with "Do follow" or "No follow" by the website owner when they create the link. If the link is Do Follow generally it will help boost you up the Google search engine results and if its NoFollow it will have little if any effect at all. So obviously you only want DoFollow links. Now a few years ago when you posted a comment on a blog any links you added were all DoFollow so people wrote software to mass automate this leaving annoying spammy comments that caused website owners and CMS creators to make sure most comments were automatically NoFollow.<br><br>Why should I use DoComment?<br>You should use DoComment because its a great way of finding 100% free niche related spam free safe backlinks to boost your website up the Google search engine results.<br><br>How does DoComment work?<br>DoComment uses the twitter streaming API to listen to niche realated keywords you set. It then follows the links in these niche related tweets and analyzes the HTML to see if it thinks its found some DoFollow links in the comments section.<br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="DoComment 1.0"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>HTTP Debugger Pro 8.15</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3935-http-debugger-pro.html</link>
<description>Name : HTTP Debugger Pro Version : 8.15 OS : Windows Type : HTTP API Price : $0 Homepage : SalePage Debug HTTP API calls to a back-end and between back-ends - Compatible with TFS, .COM and JAVA apps - Awesome UI and very easy to use - Not a proxy, no.comwork issues!</description>
<category>Url Harvester</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 00:06:22 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features No Proxying Issues It is really proxy-less and does not cause issues with websites and apps. Very Easy To Use Clean and well organized UI will make your work more productive. Short Ramp-up Time Easy installation and short ramp up time with no learning curve. Just use it. Decrypt SSL Decrypts SSL traffic from &#039;box&#039;. No any additional setup is required! Deep Analysis See all in/out HTTP traffic. Modify and resubmit sessions. Detect security issues. Android Emulators Support Debug HTTP traffic from Android Virtual Devices (Android Emulators).</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> No Proxying Issues<br></li><li> It is really proxy-less and does not cause issues with websites and apps.<br></li><li> Very Easy To Use<br></li><li> Clean and well organized UI will make your work more productive.<br></li><li> Short Ramp-up Time<br></li><li> Easy installation and short ramp up time with no learning curve. Just use it.<br></li><li> Decrypt SSL<br></li><li> Decrypts SSL traffic from 'box'. No any additional setup is required!<br></li><li> Deep Analysis<br></li><li> See all in/out HTTP traffic. Modify and resubmit sessions. Detect security issues.<br></li><li> Android Emulators Support<br></li><li> Debug HTTP traffic from Android Virtual Devices (Android Emulators).<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="HTTP Debugger Pro 8.15"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Xenu&#039;s Link Sleuth 1.3.8</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1728-xenus-link-sleuth.html</link>
<description>Name : Xenu&#039;s Link Sleuth Version : 1.3.8.0 OS : Windows Type : Find broken links on web sites Price : $0 Homepage : SalePage Xenu&#039;s Link Sleuth (TM) checks Web sites for broken links. Link verification is done on &quot;normal&quot; links, images, frames, plug-ins, backgrounds, local image maps, style sheets, scripts and java applets. It displays a continously updated list of URLs which you can sort by different criteria. A report can be produced at any time.</description>
<category>Url Harvester</category>
<enclosure url="http://home.snafu.de/tilman/xenu-1.3.8-screenshot.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 21:20:15 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Simple, no-frills user-interface Can re-check broken links (useful for temporary.comwork errors) Simple report format, can also be e-mailed Executable file smaller than 1MB Supports SSL websites (&quot;https:// &quot;) Partial testing of ftp, gopher and mail URLs Detects and reports redirected URLs Site Map</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/5GqHIjBJdm0?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> Simple, no-frills user-interface<br /></li><li> Can re-check broken links (useful for temporary.comwork errors)<br /></li><li> Simple report format, can also be e-mailed<br /></li><li> Executable file smaller than 1MB<br /></li><li> Supports SSL websites ("https:// ")<br /></li><li> Partial testing of ftp, gopher and mail URLs<br /></li><li> Detects and reports redirected URLs<br /></li><li> Site Map<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://home.snafu.de/tilman/xenu-1.3.8-screenshot.png" alt="Xenu&#039;s Link Sleuth 1.3.8" title="Xenu&#039;s Link Sleuth 1.3.8"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Xenu&#039;s Link Sleuth 1.3.8" title="Xenu&#039;s Link Sleuth 1.3.8"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>A-Parser 1.1.463 Enterprise</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1675-a-parser.html</link>
<description>Name : A-Parser Version : 1.1.463 Enterprise OS : Windows Type : Scraper Tools Price : $279 Homepage : SalePage A-Parser - a multi-threaded parser of search engines, site assessment services, keywords, content(text, links, random data) and much more(youtube, pictures, translators...). A-Parser combines over 60 parsers in total!</description>
<category>Url Harvester</category>
<enclosure url="http://img.a-parser.com/Zf8Ne.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2016 00:08:07 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features A-Parser solves the routine tasks when obtaining, processing and arranging data required for: SEO-optimization of websites and Web-analytics The collection link databases for XRumer, A-Poster, AllSubmitter, ZennoPoster, and many more! Rating websites and domains across the specified parameters Monitoring the position of numerous websites across multiple search engines Collection of text, images and video content for generating gateway websites (doorways) Backlink monitoring Collecting information from websites (e.g. phone/emails, forum messages, adverts...) Obtaining and assessing keywords Collecting and compiling backlink lists ..and much more! Web security Obtaining and filtering link databases by footprints Determination of website CMS Formation of arbitrary GET and POST requests with simultaneous answer filtration Network administration DNS - resolving domains to IP addresses WHOIS - obtaining domain name-servers and the dates when each domain was registered and becomes available A-Parser allows you to solve the most unusual tasks by combining its capabilities. Below are a handful of the many features and variants of the parser application: Query formatting and substitution Processing requests for multiple parsers in a single task Queries Builder and Results Builder Filtering and identifying unique results Powerful result generation template system Tools to deserialize JSON and j&amp;#097;vascript execution Task tester - for quick and effective task preparation A-Parser was created, and continues development, with the more than 10 years of experience and knowledge in the development of parsers and multi-threaded.comwork applications. The production of A-Parser is executed on the following principles: Speed and performance, primarily due to multi-threaded request processing Most effectively use of computer or server resources Functionality and convenience of use - a user focused product Extensive testing to select the best tool or algorithm for each task</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/8a0-IOyF-Ng?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br />A-Parser solves the routine tasks when obtaining, processing and arranging data required for:<br /><ul><li> SEO-optimization of websites and Web-analytics<br /></li><li> The collection link databases for XRumer, A-Poster, AllSubmitter, ZennoPoster, and many more!<br /></li><li> Rating websites and domains across the specified parameters<br /></li><li> Monitoring the position of numerous websites across multiple search engines<br /></li><li> Collection of text, images and video content for generating gateway websites (doorways)<br /></li><li> Backlink monitoring<br /></li><li> Collecting information from websites (e.g. phone/emails, forum messages, adverts...)<br /></li><li> Obtaining and assessing keywords<br /></li><li> Collecting and compiling backlink lists<br /></li><li> ..and much more!<br /></li></ul><br />Web security<br /><ul><li> Obtaining and filtering link databases by footprints<br /></li><li> Determination of website CMS<br /></li><li> Formation of arbitrary GET and POST requests with simultaneous answer filtration<br /></li></ul><br />Network administration<br /><ul><li> DNS - resolving domains to IP addresses<br /></li><li> WHOIS - obtaining domain name-servers and the dates when each domain was registered and becomes available<br /></li></ul><br />A-Parser allows you to solve the most unusual tasks by combining its capabilities. Below are a handful of the many features and variants of the parser application:<br /><ul><li> Query formatting and substitution<br /></li><li> Processing requests for multiple parsers in a single task<br /></li><li> Queries Builder and Results Builder<br /></li><li> Filtering and identifying unique results<br /></li><li> Powerful result generation template system<br /></li><li> Tools to deserialize JSON and j&#097;vascript execution<br /></li><li> Task tester - for quick and effective task preparation<br /></li></ul><br />A-Parser was created, and continues development, with the more than 10 years of experience and knowledge in the development of parsers and multi-threaded.comwork applications. The production of A-Parser is executed on the following principles:<br /><ul><li> Speed and performance, primarily due to multi-threaded request processing<br /></li><li> Most effectively use of computer or server resources<br /></li><li> Functionality and convenience of use - a user focused product<br /></li><li> Extensive testing to select the best tool or algorithm for each task<br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://img.a-parser.com/Zf8Ne.png" alt="A-Parser 1.1.463 Enterprise" title="A-Parser 1.1.463 Enterprise"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="A-Parser 1.1.463 Enterprise" title="A-Parser 1.1.463 Enterprise"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Oscraper 0.2.3</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1117-oscraper.html</link>
<description>Name : Oscraper Version : 0.2.3 OS : Windows/MAC Type : Google Scrape Marketing Price : $17 Homepage : [leech=http://www.oscraper.com/]SalePage[/leeh] Find New Customers with The World&#039;s Most Powerful &amp; Safe Google Results PPV ( Url ) Scraper . Scrape up to 10 pages deep in both Google Organic and Google Paid Results The Must have tool for any PPV / SEO Marketer</description>
<category>Url Harvester</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.roi.im/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/oscraper.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2016 01:34:28 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/67mL6NRTI1U?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><img src="http://www.roi.im/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/oscraper.jpg" alt="Oscraper 0.2.3" title="Oscraper 0.2.3"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Oscraper 0.2.3" title="Oscraper 0.2.3"  /><br /><div class="quote"><br /><br /></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Solid botworks PTCS 1.4.3.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1361-solid-botworks-ptcs.html</link>
<description>Name : Solid botworks PTCS Version : 1.4.3.0 OS : Windows Type : Scraper Tools Price : $2000 Homepage : SalePage Professional Trackback and Comment Submitter (PTCS) Solid botworks PTCS is a powerful software for professional SEO workers. The software is designed to eliminate as much tedious work as possible and to give the highest possible success rate independent of the computer and inte.com connection. Professional Trackback and Comment Submitter has the ability to give you thousands and thousands of verified back links to your sites within a short amount of time. Professional Trackback and Comment Submitter is the most powerful software on the market within its niche.</description>
<category>Url Harvester</category>
<enclosure url="http://solidbotworks.com/images/shoots/settings.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2015 22:22:51 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features High-speed posting : PTCS is optimized to post as fast as possible with as high success rate possible. PTCS do not just remove tedious tasks but is also faster than most of our competitors. Beside trackbacks PTCS also support high-speed commenting on WordPress platform. We dare to say that PTCS is more than twice as fast as competing software. This is because of a unique feature built in that analyzes and stores specific form data for commenting. PTCS also has the feature to work with mixed lists which enables you to have both trackback and comment urls in the same list and don’t need to worry about the platforms at all Powerfull Scraper : As you run your projects you might need to refill your lists with new AA entries. PTCS contains a scraper which automatically fetches urls from Google based on your chosen keywords. PTCS also has the option to AA test the urls directly with different urls and anchors based on if PTCS finds the link in your blacklist or not. After the test it directly sorts the AA found into your specified lists and cleans out bad urls. For the creative one you can use this function to create back links to sites and lists based on niches in a short amount of time. Automatic Link Check : When you work with tools there is often a separate process to link check after you have made your postings. For a professional this is a tedious and annoying task eliminated in Professional Trackback and Comment Submitter. PTCS do the link check in the same thread as posting which will reduce the time consumed drastically. Bandwidth Saver : Professional Trackback and Comment Submitter saves your bandwidth as much as possible. With the support for Gzip and Deflate compression which is normal standard for Webpage transfers on inte.com. PTCS will save up to as much as 70% of the bandwidth. Project Criteria : As a professional worker you deal with many different sizes of projects. Most tools require the user to keep an eye on the projects while it’s running or to keep your AA lists up to date with the exact amount of links to be posted. All this to meet the requirements of the project. Most of the time users also has to make some posts and then do a link check separately which can end up in a restart of posting and re-link check all again. With PTCS you will not only get a link check meanwhile submitting but you can also set the requirements for your project. With simple words you can have a list of 500k URLs and make PTCS stop when 10k is posted and verified. Automatic List Handling : It is a nightmare for professionals of link building that lists will get outdated and stop working. PTCS has a built in list handler that keeps track of failures in your lists. Until now most software lets you dribble with tons of text files and soon you feel lost in which list is containing what. With PTCS you manage your lists inside the software and import all your external lists and sets a number of how many fails each URL should have at max before it’s automatically removed. This will keep your list fast and up-to-date and you will for sure minimize your time consumed extremely. Blacklist Filtering : Many times your orders require you to not post into different niches, this can be gambling and sex for example. With the built in system for blacklist filtering you can with ease filter away URLs that contains blacklisted words. You also have the ability to save those URL into a separate list which will let you take orders in those special niches as well. Detailed Report : When a project is finished you will get a detailed report divided into two parts. The summary and the details. The summary shows how many back links each of your posted URLs got each with its own anchor. The detail goes over each posted link and shows the exact URL where to find the specified back link. You are also able to brand the reports and include your name or company name in the report automatically. PTCS also have the ability to snapshot itself upon completing a poster project. This means you can take a screenshot of PTCS and bundle it with the report. For this to work you don’t need PTCS to be in focus. You can even have PTCS minimized. As an option you can set PTCS to bundle the report and screenshot into a zip file. Proxy Support : Within PTCS you can mange different groups of proxies and can easily switch between different groups for different projects. With extensive link building you might need to use proxy to avoid different traps. PTCS supports the use of http proxies with and without username / password. You can also test your proxies functionality and speed within PTCS and are able to input different sources from where PTCS can grab proxies automatically. Mutithreding : PTCS supports multithreading with unlimited number of threads. In this way you can adjust your threading just as you want it based on proxies and machine capacity.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="640" height="480" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/1mJ94aKrIac?rel=1&amp;wmode=transparent" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br /><h3>Features</h3><br /><ul><li> High-speed posting : PTCS is optimized to post as fast as possible with as high success rate possible. PTCS do not just remove tedious tasks but is also faster than most of our competitors. Beside trackbacks PTCS also support high-speed commenting on WordPress platform. We dare to say that PTCS is more than twice as fast as competing software. This is because of a unique feature built in that analyzes and stores specific form data for commenting. PTCS also has the feature to work with mixed lists which enables you to have both trackback and comment urls in the same list and don’t need to worry about the platforms at all <br /></li><li> Powerfull Scraper : As you run your projects you might need to refill your lists with new AA entries. PTCS contains a scraper which automatically fetches urls from Google based on your chosen keywords. PTCS also has the option to AA test the urls directly with different urls and anchors based on if PTCS finds the link in your blacklist or not. After the test it directly sorts the AA found into your specified lists and cleans out bad urls. For the creative one you can use this function to create back links to sites and lists based on niches in a short amount of time. <br /></li><li> Automatic Link Check : When you work with tools there is often a separate process to link check after you have made your postings. For a professional this is a tedious and annoying task eliminated in Professional Trackback and Comment Submitter. PTCS do the link check in the same thread as posting which will reduce the time consumed drastically. <br /></li><li> Bandwidth Saver : Professional Trackback and Comment Submitter saves your bandwidth as much as possible. With the support for Gzip and Deflate compression which is normal standard for Webpage transfers on inte.com. PTCS will save up to as much as 70% of the bandwidth. <br /></li><li> Project Criteria : As a professional worker you deal with many different sizes of projects. Most tools require the user to keep an eye on the projects while it’s running or to keep your AA lists up to date with the exact amount of links to be posted. All this to meet the requirements of the project. Most of the time users also has to make some posts and then do a link check separately which can end up in a restart of posting and re-link check all again. With PTCS you will not only get a link check meanwhile submitting but you can also set the requirements for your project. With simple words you can have a list of 500k URLs and make PTCS stop when 10k is posted and verified. <br /></li><li> Automatic List Handling : It is a nightmare for professionals of link building that lists will get outdated and stop working. PTCS has a built in list handler that keeps track of failures in your lists. Until now most software lets you dribble with tons of text files and soon you feel lost in which list is containing what. With PTCS you manage your lists inside the software and import all your external lists and sets a number of how many fails each URL should have at max before it’s automatically removed. This will keep your list fast and up-to-date and you will for sure minimize your time consumed extremely. <br /></li><li> Blacklist Filtering : Many times your orders require you to not post into different niches, this can be gambling and sex for example. With the built in system for blacklist filtering you can with ease filter away URLs that contains blacklisted words. You also have the ability to save those URL into a separate list which will let you take orders in those special niches as well. <br /></li><li> Detailed Report : When a project is finished you will get a detailed report divided into two parts. The summary and the details. The summary shows how many back links each of your posted URLs got each with its own anchor. The detail goes over each posted link and shows the exact URL where to find the specified back link. You are also able to brand the reports and include your name or company name in the report automatically. PTCS also have the ability to snapshot itself upon completing a poster project. This means you can take a screenshot of PTCS and bundle it with the report. For this to work you don’t need PTCS to be in focus. You can even have PTCS minimized. As an option you can set PTCS to bundle the report and screenshot into a zip file. <br /></li><li> Proxy Support : Within PTCS you can mange different groups of proxies and can easily switch between different groups for different projects. With extensive link building you might need to use proxy to avoid different traps. PTCS supports the use of http proxies with and without username / password. You can also test your proxies functionality and speed within PTCS and are able to input different sources from where PTCS can grab proxies automatically. <br /></li><li> Mutithreding : PTCS supports multithreading with unlimited number of threads. In this way you can adjust your threading just as you want it based on proxies and machine capacity. <br /></li></ul><br /><img src="http://solidbotworks.com/images/shoots/settings.jpg" alt="Solid botworks PTCS 1.4.3.0" title="Solid botworks PTCS 1.4.3.0"  /><br /><div style="text-align:center;"><br /><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Solid botworks PTCS 1.4.3.0" title="Solid botworks PTCS 1.4.3.0"  /><br /><div class="quote"></div><br /></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Magic Web Finder 5.7</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/900-magic-web-finder.html</link>
<description>Name : Magic Web Finder Version : 5.7 OS : Windows Type : URL Harverster Price : $50 Homepage : SalePage Find The Hidden &#039;Gold&#039; Web 2.0&#039;s That Allow You To Rank For Any Keyword You Want. Plus Get Unlimited Traffic That Converts Like Crazy Hey, Ranking High On Google Is The Key To The I.M Game. Magic Web Finder Is CHANGING That Game. Ranking high is what it is all about. The ability to show your website for specific keywords you know your website deserves to rank for. whether your selling a product or affiliating for one, you have the product but where&#039;s the traffic? Google has it, but it wont send it to you unless you are worthy. So how do we prove we are worthy?</description>
<category>Url Harvester</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2015 21:42:07 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Filters That Allow You To Pick How High Of Authority You Want Your Web 2.0&#039;s To Be. Pick How Many Threads You Want To Use. The More Threads The Quicker You Will Find Powerful Web 2.0&#039;s. Magic Web Finder Has The Ability To Create Up To 250 Threads! Already Scraped Some Web 2.0&#039;s? That&#039;s Fine, Just Simply Click &quot;Import Own Urls&quot; And Away You Go! Since Google&#039;s Page Rank Is Rarely Updated We Have Added In Moz&#039;s Free API To Make Sure The Web 2.0&#039;s Authority Is Updated And Shown. Although Google&#039;s Page Rank Is Rarely Updated, We Thought We Would Add It Just In case There Are Some High PR Web 2.0&#039;s Ready To Register. If Any Web 2.0&#039;s Are Ready To Be Registered, And Are Above Your Chosen Filters They Will Be Highlighted Green To Make It Easier For You To See. Using Moz&#039;s Free API Magic Web Finder Will Tell You How Many Inbound Links Are Coming Into The Web 2.0 That Has Been Found. If The Found Web 2.0 Has A Link Inbound You Can View The Links Moz Authority By Simply Clicking The Web 2.0. Just Look At How Many Available Web 2.0&#039;s Have Been Found! There Are No Limits With Magic Web Finder, Import As Many Keywords As You Want, And Find As Many Web 2.0&#039;s As You Want. Import As Many Proxies As You Wish, The More The Better And Faster Magic Web Finder Can Work To Find You Great Web 2.0&#039;s Use Our Inbuilt Proxy Tester, And Make Sure All Your Proxy&#039;s Are Working Properly. The Less None Working Proxy&#039;s The Better Magic Web Finder Works. With 16 Engine&#039;s You Will Never Run Out Of Web 2.0&#039;s To Find! Plus, There&#039;s More Been Worked On By The Thwaites SEO Team. Software that gives you RELEVANT web 2.0&#039;s ready to register. Using 3RD Party analysis such as MOZ to make sure it&#039;s AUTHORITATIVE. The ability of having HUNDREDS of web 2.0&#039;s ready to be used as a private blog.comwork. Updates always been worked on to bring you MORE platforms.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><div class="dlevideoplayer" style="width:100%;max-width:425px;"><ul data-theme="default" data-preload="metadata"><li data-title="" data-type="youtube" data-url="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PvMUYQK4MJY"></li></ul></div></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Filters That Allow You To Pick How High Of Authority You Want Your Web 2.0's To Be.<br></li><li> Pick How Many Threads You Want To Use. The More Threads The Quicker You Will Find Powerful Web 2.0's.  Magic Web Finder Has The Ability To Create Up To 250 Threads!<br></li><li> Already Scraped Some Web 2.0's? That's Fine, Just Simply Click "Import Own Urls" And Away You Go!<br></li><li> Since Google's Page Rank Is Rarely Updated We Have Added In Moz's Free API To Make Sure The Web 2.0's Authority Is Updated And Shown.<br></li><li> Although Google's Page Rank Is Rarely Updated, We Thought We Would Add It Just In case There Are Some High PR Web 2.0's Ready To Register.<br></li><li> If Any Web 2.0's Are Ready To Be Registered, And Are Above Your Chosen Filters They Will Be Highlighted Green To Make It Easier For You To See.<br></li><li> Using Moz's Free API Magic Web Finder Will Tell You How Many Inbound Links Are Coming Into The Web 2.0 That Has Been Found.<br></li><li> If The Found Web 2.0 Has A Link Inbound You Can View The Links Moz Authority By Simply Clicking The Web 2.0.<br></li><li> Just Look At How Many Available Web 2.0's Have Been Found!<br></li><li> There Are No Limits With Magic Web Finder, Import As Many Keywords As You Want, And Find As Many Web 2.0's As You Want.<br></li><li> Import As Many Proxies As You Wish, The More The Better And Faster Magic Web Finder Can Work To Find You Great Web 2.0's<br></li><li> Use Our Inbuilt Proxy Tester, And Make Sure All Your Proxy's Are Working Properly. The Less None Working Proxy's The Better Magic Web Finder Works.<br></li><li> With 16 Engine's You Will Never Run Out Of Web 2.0's To Find! Plus, There's More Been Worked On By The Thwaites SEO Team.  <br></li><li> Software that gives you RELEVANT web 2.0's ready to register.<br></li><li> Using 3RD Party analysis such as MOZ to make sure it's AUTHORITATIVE.<br></li><li> The ability of having HUNDREDS of web 2.0's ready to be used as a private blog.comwork.<br></li><li> Updates always been worked on to bring you MORE platforms.<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" alt="Magic Web Finder 5.7"><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>