<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>IM Tools - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>IM Tools - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>SEO Content Machine 4.18.4.30</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1476-seo-content-machine.html</link>
<description>Name : SEO Content Machine Version : 4.18.4.30 OS : Windows Type : Content Marketing Tools Price : $237$/yearly Homepage : SalePage Change The Way You Create Content The first multi-language content creator program. You can also generate content specific to your local region. Trouble Creating Content?SEO Content Machine takes the pain out of creating SEO Content.</description>
<category>Content Creator</category>
<enclosure url="http://seocontentmachine.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/SCM-Monitor-Copy-e1408635573145.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2018 09:04:12 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Accelerate Your Link Building Manage Your PBNs : Draft &amp;amp; post to WordPress/Blogger or any site that supports post by email. Schedule drip feed content and keep your blog.comwork fresh indefinitely. Content Toolbag : Get your content tools. Scrape Google Suggest, create Tier 1 Content, create About Me’s. Roll your own content with an Article Downloader, Translator &amp;amp; Content Combiner. Content In Any Language : This program is a multi-language content scraper &amp;amp; generator. Supports all western languages. Create SEO content in Spanish, French, German and more. You can also generate content specific to your local region. Custom Content Sources : Find and download 100s of pages of content on any topic on any site. Customizable content sources means you don’t get caught scraping the same over-used sites as everyone else. Linkbuilding Content Generation : Make the most of your link building programs. Generate keyword targeted articles for unlimited content submissions. Supports popular programs directly such as GSA SER, Senuke &amp;amp; Ultimate Demon. Creates Readable + Keyword Relevant Articles : Special filtering algorithms remove spammy and irrelevant content automatically. This program will individually rank content against your keyword for relevancy before it is used to generate articles. Simple Content Generation : You don’t need proxies, VPS installs or other special tools. A Content Wizard mode for beginners lets you create content in less than 10 clicks. Online help + video tutorials at your finger tips. 100% Automated Content Generation : Create articles with images, videos and links. Translate or re-write articles using spinners to generate 100% unique content. 100% task automation with the option of scheduling it to repeat for as long as you like. http://direct.seocontentmachine.com/download/changelog.txt</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/f1bx-q2dudk?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Accelerate Your Link Building<br></li><li> Manage Your PBNs : Draft &amp; post to WordPress/Blogger or any site that supports post by email.  Schedule drip feed content and keep your blog.comwork fresh indefinitely.<br></li><li> Content Toolbag : Get your content tools. Scrape Google Suggest, create Tier 1 Content, create About Me’s.  Roll your own content with an Article Downloader, Translator &amp; Content Combiner. <br></li><li> Content In Any Language : This program is a multi-language content scraper &amp; generator.  Supports all western languages. Create SEO content in Spanish, French, German and more.  You can also generate content specific to your local region. <br></li><li> Custom Content Sources : Find and download 100s of pages of content on any topic on any site.  Customizable content sources means you don’t get caught scraping the same over-used sites as everyone else.  <br></li><li> Linkbuilding Content Generation : Make the most of your link building programs. Generate keyword targeted articles for  unlimited content submissions.  Supports popular programs directly such as GSA SER, Senuke &amp; Ultimate Demon.  <br></li><li> Creates Readable + Keyword Relevant Articles : Special filtering algorithms remove spammy and irrelevant content automatically.  This program will individually rank content against your keyword for relevancy before it is used to generate articles. <br></li><li> Simple Content Generation : You don’t need proxies, VPS installs or other special tools.  A Content Wizard mode for beginners lets you create content in less than 10 clicks.  Online help + video tutorials at your finger tips.<br></li><li> 100% Automated Content Generation : Create articles with images, videos and links.  Translate or re-write articles using spinners to generate 100% unique content.  100% task automation with the option of scheduling it to repeat for as long as you like.<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://seocontentmachine.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/SCM-Monitor-Copy-e1408635573145.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="SEO Content Machine 4.18.4.30"><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><a href="http://direct.seocontentmachine.com/download/changelog.txt"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">http://direct.seocontentmachine.com/download/changelog.txt</a><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Twt Dominator 5.5.0.21</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/955-twtdominator.html</link>
<description>Name :Twt Dominator Version : 5.5.0.21 OS : Windows Type : Twitter Marketing Price : $499 Homepage : SalePage TwtDominator lets you target with precision, connect directly with your audience, spread your message throughout the day, manage campaigns and do much more to make sure you achieve your marketing goal. There&#039;s no doubt that Twitter, with its more than 600 million users, has become a great marketing tool for business today. With growing targeting, analytics, promotional tactics and marketing tools provided by Twitter, it&#039;s definitely a great arsenal in your digital marketing tool kit. Now Brands have been opening Twitter accounts thick and fast like you, but how confident are you of obtaining real results, and are you able to measure the impact of their messaging on the microblogging.comwork? So the difficulty remains: Who will you reach on Twitter? How will you reach them? How effectively are you using this tool? How can you tell if you&#039;ve done a good job? etc.</description>
<category>Twitter Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 27 May 2018 11:22:36 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Follower : Follow multiple accounts from your accounts uploaded. Tweet : Keep your accounts active. Easily Retweet or Reply using trending keywords. Unfollower : Get rid of users who are not following you back easily with a click Account Actions : Allows you to always use the best accounts for your process and campaigns. Wait &amp;amp; Reply : Upload a list of Messages and Keywords let the software tweet and reply. Scrape Users : Scrape users from keywords, names and also get a list of trending hash tags easily. Tweet Creator : Tweet using keywords to the targeted users. Retweet &amp;amp; Favorite : Resell or increase RTs &amp;amp; FAVs of specific tweets in no time. Campaign Manager : Easily create different campaigns for different process and run them all together.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/haf09BOHCzw?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Follower : Follow multiple accounts from your accounts uploaded. <br></li><li> Tweet : Keep your accounts active. Easily Retweet or Reply using trending keywords. <br></li><li> Unfollower : Get rid of users who are not following you back easily with a click <br></li><li> Account Actions : Allows you to always use the best accounts for your process and campaigns. <br></li><li> Wait &amp; Reply : Upload a list of Messages and Keywords let the software tweet and reply. <br></li><li> Scrape Users : Scrape users from keywords, names and also get a list of trending hash tags easily. <br></li><li> Tweet Creator : Tweet using keywords to the targeted users. <br></li><li> Retweet &amp; Favorite : Resell or increase RTs &amp; FAVs of specific tweets in no time. <br></li><li> Campaign Manager : Easily create different campaigns for different process and run them all together. <br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Twt Dominator 5.5.0.21"><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>FaceDominator 3.5.0.39</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/879-facedominator.html</link>
<description>Name :FaceDominator Agency Version : 3.5.0.39 OS : Windows Type : Facebook Marketing Price : $499 Homepage : SalePage FaceDominator is a tool which is very useful for managing and automating your facebook advertising campaign. Learn more about FaceDominator Features with our Case Studies to help your business. Facebook marketing of your products through Facedominator To Promote Your Product through Wall Using Wall Poster,Manage Group,Photo Tagging,Manage Pages &amp;amp; Fan Page Poster</description>
<category>Facebook Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 27 May 2018 11:22:20 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FB Event Manager : Complete management of Events on facebook, Scrape users, Ask users to join it, etc. Customize Your Account : You can upload accounts,Check active and deactive accounts of facebook to upload a huge text file of accounts easily change the accout profile name and language of the accounts. Fanpage Manager : It can create Fanpage automatically or with your custom data. You can also use your keywords and categories to create pages Friend Adder :You can add targeted friends in your account. Targeting can be done based on Geo-Location or from fanpages. Wall Poster : You can post your message on the wall of friends or walls of fanpages with your targated keywords. Group Manager : you can invite your friends to join the groups,send request to groups,Post photo,url and messages on groups easily. Supports IP Proxies : It support both private and public proxies for all its features. You can also use Hide my Ass VPN to use with this tool. Automatic Captcha : It support Decaptcher.com and Deathbycaptcha.com for decoding captcha Auto Group Joiner Group Scraper Fans Scraper Multithreaded &amp;amp; Proxy Support Group Campaign Manager Group Request Manager Free For All http://mir.cr/AWYD8MSI</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/o592U_gke4I?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> FB Event Manager : Complete management of Events on facebook, Scrape users, Ask users to join it, etc.<br></li><li> Customize Your Account : You can upload accounts,Check active and deactive accounts of facebook to upload a huge text file of accounts easily change the accout profile name and language of the accounts.<br></li><li> Fanpage Manager : It can create Fanpage automatically or with your custom data. You can also use your keywords and categories to create pages<br></li><li> Friend Adder :You can add targeted friends in your account. Targeting can be done based on Geo-Location or from fanpages.<br></li><li> Wall Poster : You can post your message on the wall of friends or walls of fanpages with your targated keywords.<br></li><li> Group Manager : you can invite your friends to join the groups,send request to groups,Post photo,url and messages on groups easily.<br></li><li> Supports IP Proxies : It support both private and public proxies for all its features. You can also use Hide my Ass VPN to use with this tool.<br></li><li> Automatic Captcha : It support Decaptcher.com and Deathbycaptcha.com for decoding captcha<br></li><li> Auto Group Joiner<br></li><li> Group Scraper<br></li><li> Fans Scraper<br></li><li> Multithreaded &amp; Proxy Support<br></li><li> Group Campaign Manager<br></li><li> Group Request Manager<br></li></ul><br><div class="quote">Free For All<br><a href="http://mir.cr/AWYD8MSI"  target="_blank" rel="external noopener noreferrer">http://mir.cr/AWYD8MSI</a><br></div><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="FaceDominator 3.5.0.39"><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>PVA Creator Deluxe 1.54</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1819-pva-creator.html</link>
<description>Name : PVACreator Deluxe Version : 1.54 OS : Windows Type : PVA Account Creator Price : $918 Homepage : SalePage PVACreator is a super accounts bulk creating machine that can creating phone and email verified accounts for different sites. It can also solve captcha automatically and allow you to import proxies to register accounts.</description>
<category>Account Creator</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2018 13:32:37 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Smart Task Manager : PVACreator allows you to create/manage/run/pause/resume multi-accounts creating tasks at the same time. Every task has full stats of account creating, you can manage and check everything easily. Auto/Custom Data Settings : PVACreator can create randomly datas like first name, last name, sex and age etc... to create your accounts, you can also import yourself data to create your accounts. Customized Save Settings : You can custom the register information to save, like you can only save username and password, or you can also set to save username, password, register proxy, register phone number, first name, last name and others. All information can be saved with created accounts if you want. Captcha Auto-Solving and Proxy Support.PVACreator can solve captcha automatically when register accounts, and you can import proxies to use in PVACreator for creating many accounts. Phone Verify Automatically : PVACreator can get phone numbers and receive sms to verify your accounts automatically. Auto-Confirm Email : When some sites need email confirmation, PVACreator can do this for you automatically too. Multi-Threads Support : You can set PVACreator to run with multi-threads to speed up the registration and create accounts for different sites at the same time. Create PVA For : Instagram, Youtube, Gmail, Twitter, Outlook, LinkedIn, Facebook, Pinterest, Reddit, Slickdeals, Amazon, SoundCloud</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/LCEbJNqArsE?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Smart Task Manager : PVACreator allows you to create/manage/run/pause/resume multi-accounts creating tasks at the same time. Every task has full stats of account creating, you can manage and check everything easily.<br></li><li> Auto/Custom Data Settings : PVACreator can create randomly datas like first name, last name, sex and age etc... to create your accounts, you can also import yourself data to create your accounts.<br></li><li> Customized Save Settings : You can custom the register information to save, like you can only save username and password, or you can also set to save username, password, register proxy, register phone number, first name, last name and others. All information can be saved with created accounts if you want.<br></li><li> Captcha Auto-Solving and Proxy Support.PVACreator can solve captcha automatically when register accounts, and you can import proxies to use in PVACreator for creating many accounts.<br></li><li> Phone Verify Automatically : PVACreator can get phone numbers and receive sms to verify your accounts automatically.<br></li><li> Auto-Confirm Email : When some sites need email confirmation, PVACreator can do this for you automatically too.<br></li><li> Multi-Threads Support : You can set PVACreator to run with multi-threads to speed up the registration and create accounts for different sites at the same time.<br></li><li> Create PVA For :  Instagram, Youtube, Gmail, Twitter, Outlook, LinkedIn, Facebook, Pinterest, Reddit, Slickdeals, Amazon, SoundCloud<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="PVA Creator Deluxe 1.54"><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Live Event Blaster 2.02 Pro Local</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1749-live-event-blaster.html</link>
<description>Name : Live Event Blaster Version : 2.02 Pro Local OS : Windows Type : Youtube Marketing Price : $99 Homepage : SalePage We Will Change The Way You Are CREATING – UPLOADING – RANKING Videos On YouTube Find Out Why The Top Video Marketers Are Calling This “The Ultimate YouTube Super Weapon”…</description>
<category>Live Stream Tools</category>
<enclosure url="http://i.imgur.com/QJ0L67F.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="http://liveblaster.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/04/features-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2018 13:32:07 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Step 1 : You schedule a live event, YouTube will already index your event, giving you higher rankings than videos… Step 2 : You start streaming your live event . YouTube promotes your event using it’s internal engine! Step 3 : When you finish streaming, your event TRANSFORMS INTO A VIDEO…but keeps its original event rankings!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/262629560?app_id=122963" width="425" height="239" frameborder="0" title="New Sales Video - LEB 2" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Step 1 : You schedule a live event, YouTube will already index your event, giving you higher rankings than videos…<br></li><li> Step 2 : You start streaming your live event .  YouTube promotes your event using it’s internal engine!<br></li><li> Step 3 : When you finish streaming, your event TRANSFORMS INTO A VIDEO…but keeps its original event rankings!<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://i.imgur.com/QJ0L67F.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Live Event Blaster 2.02 Pro Local"><br><img src="http://liveblaster.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/04/features-2.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Social Page Analyzer 1.0.12</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/941-social-page-analyzer.html</link>
<description>Name : Social Page Analyzer Version : 1.0.12 OS : Windows Type : FB Fanpage Tool Price : $354.95 Homepage : SalePage The NEW Social Page Analyzer, an extremely powerful Mac/PC software that analyzes facebook pages, posts, and comments helping you uncover the top marketing content and strategies for your own social marketing campaigns! A new powerful tool for analyzing Facebook fanpages, fanpage posts and post comments with 5 built-in tools for uncovering the secrets behind any successful fanpage in just seconds!</description>
<category>Social Ads Tools</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2018 13:31:47 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Search thousands of fanpages by keyword or paste in as many facebook page you links want to analyze Check fanpage names for Facebook ad interest keywords for your ad campaigns Generate VERY detailed page score reports for optimizing your fanpages for high natural organic traffic! Get 27 different data metrics for every fanpage Extract emails &amp;amp; websites for fanpages! Contact page owners to build valuable marketing relationships to skyrocket your Facebook marketing success! Works on both Mac and PC computers Get 1000&#039;s of fanpages using sophisticated search features that no other software has! Generate sophisticated page scores for all pages to get the &quot;REAL&quot; sense of the true page value! Extract 1000&#039;s of posts from ANY fanpage in just seconds! Sort by shares, comments, likes, or any other data metric to uncover the content with the best engagement! Preview the top posts in a beautiful post layout preview window! Extract thousands of comments from ANY fanpage post in just seconds! Reveal powerful information using the cutting-edge &quot;Word Analyzer&quot; tool to instantly uncover all the most common word-combinations across thousands of user comments or page posts! Uncover product ideas that are hiding inside your competitors user comments! Use built-in blazing fast filters and custom filters to get the data you really need!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/245289125?app_id=122963" width="425" height="239" frameborder="0" title="Social Page Analyzer - Facebook Fanpage Research Software" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Search thousands of fanpages by keyword or paste in as many facebook page you links want to analyze<br></li><li> Check fanpage names for Facebook ad interest keywords for your ad campaigns<br></li><li> Generate VERY detailed page score reports for optimizing your fanpages for high natural organic traffic!<br></li><li> Get 27 different data metrics for every fanpage<br></li><li> Extract emails &amp; websites for fanpages! Contact page owners to build valuable marketing relationships to skyrocket your Facebook marketing success!<br></li><li> Works on both Mac and PC computers<br></li><li> Get 1000's of fanpages using sophisticated search features that no other software has!<br></li><li> Generate sophisticated page scores for all pages to get the "REAL" sense of the true page value!<br></li><li> Extract 1000's of posts from ANY fanpage in just seconds! Sort by shares, comments, likes, or any other data metric to uncover the content with the best engagement!<br></li><li> Preview the top posts in a beautiful post layout preview window!<br></li><li> Extract thousands of comments from ANY fanpage post in just seconds!<br></li><li> Reveal powerful information using the cutting-edge "Word Analyzer" tool to instantly uncover all the most common word-combinations across thousands of user comments or page posts!<br></li><li> Uncover product ideas that are hiding inside your competitors user comments!<br></li><li> Use built-in blazing fast filters and custom filters to get the data you really need!<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Social Page Analyzer 1.0.12"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Instabot PW 1.0.62 Pro</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1177-instabot-pw.html</link>
<description>Name : Instabot PW Version : 1.0.62 Pro OS : Windows Type : Instagram Marketing Bot Price : $45 Homepage : SalePage Use our instagram bot to get your target audience! Instabot.pw will promote your profile, your product or service 24 hours a day. You only need to specify the desirable settings. Follows, likes, comments - dozens of settings according to different criteria.</description>
<category>Instagram Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2018 13:31:27 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features unlimit likes per hour unlimit follow per hour unlimit unfollow per hour unlimit comments per hour proxy support multiply accounts</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/110780293?app_id=122963" width="425" height="239" frameborder="0" title="Carbongram Bot short overview - The best Instagram bot ever made" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> unlimit likes per hour<br></li><li> unlimit follow per hour<br></li><li> unlimit unfollow per hour<br></li><li> unlimit comments per hour<br></li><li> proxy support<br></li><li> multiply accounts<br></li></ul><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Instabot PW 1.0.62 Pro"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Money Robot Submitter 7.33</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1171-money-robot-submitter.html</link>
<description>Name : Money Robot Submitter Version : 7.33 Enterprise OS : Windows Type : Link Building Tools Price : $497 Homepage : SalePage The world&#039;s most powerful link building software With Money Robot Submitter the link submission process will be the easiest task and completely automated, you will be able to build unlimited number of links and increase traffic to your websites which will lead to a higher number of customers and much more sales for you. With the best user interface ever, you just need to have simple software knowledge and you will easily be able to make your own SEO link building campaigns. Money Robot Submitter is the best SEO software you will ever own, and we can confidently say that there is no other software on the market that can compete with such intelligent and fully automatic features. The friendly user interface, smart tools and the simplicity of the tasks are making Money Robot Submitter the best tool on the market. SEO Link building is a process that requires a lot of time. If you aren&#039;t using SEO software then you will know the amount of work load involved in creating accounts, confirming emails and submitting your contents to thousands of websites in proper time and completely automated.</description>
<category>Link Building Tools</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-11/1446899270_c0xahpa.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 00:42:12 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features High Speed Submission : Money Robot has multiple threading features (it&#039;s as if you had 100 employees working simultaneously for your website ranking). Smart Submission Process : The account creation process is automatic. You don&#039;t need to press any buttons to start this process, the account creation process is fully automated, including the activation of the e-mails. No human intervention is necessary. Artificial Intelligence : The software uses Inte.com explorer, Firefox or Chrome to simulate real human activity (users action on sites) and it can easily pass any robot detection mechanisms. No more search and scrape needed for website lists : We have massive server resources that are crawling the web in search for any website that can provide quality backlinks to your websites, and you will be able easily to submit your content completely automatically. Article Spinning &amp;amp; Rewriting : Money Robot Submitter software has built-in spinner/rewriter features, so you no longer have to be afraid of duplicate content penalties. You can now automatically rewrite and spin your articles into hundred of unique versions. Backlink monitor feature - your Live link Checker : Easily manage and track all your live backlinks including your anchor texts and all other information related to your backlinks with the speed of up to 500 threads per second. Auto sites list updates : Our crawling servers are finding new websites every day. Therefore, you will receive new lists of websites updated daily. You don&#039;t need to search/scrape for website lists. You will receive fresh list of websites daily, where you can automatically submit your content. Automatic Captcha Solving : Money Robot automatically solves all simple captchas for FREE, such as calculation captchas, photo captchas, text captchas, etc. For the complex captchas, the software offers you support for all major decaptcha services. Our Software supports UNLIMITED website platforms. You can submit your backlinks/content to following main platforms with support built right in: Web 2.0 Blogs Social Network Posts Social Bookmarking Web Directories Wiki Articles Press Release Article Directories Web 2.0 Profiles Forum Profiles RSS :::Free Members ::: Download Now Password : www.tgmember.com :::ViP Only:::</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><div class="dlevideoplayer" style="width:100%;max-width:425px;">
			<ul data-theme="default" data-preload="metadata">
				<li data-title="campaign-creator" data-type="m4v" data-url="http://www.moneyrobot.com/images/campaign-creator.mp4" ></li>
			</ul>
		</div></div><br><p><br></p><br><h3>Features</h3><br><p><br><ul><li> High Speed Submission : Money Robot has multiple threading features (it's as if you had 100 employees working simultaneously for your website ranking). <br></li><li> Smart Submission Process : The account creation process is automatic. You don't need to press any buttons to start this process, the account creation process is fully automated, including the activation of the e-mails. No human intervention is necessary. <br></li><li> Artificial Intelligence : The software uses Inte.com explorer, Firefox or Chrome to simulate real human activity (users action on sites) and it can easily pass any robot detection mechanisms. <br></li><li> No more search and scrape needed for website lists : We have massive server resources that are crawling the web in search for any website that can provide quality backlinks to your websites, and you will be able easily to submit your content completely automatically. <br></li><li> Article Spinning &amp; Rewriting : Money Robot Submitter software has built-in spinner/rewriter features, so you no longer have to be afraid of duplicate content penalties. You can now automatically rewrite and spin your articles into hundred of unique versions. <br></li><li> Backlink monitor feature - your Live link Checker : Easily manage and track all your live backlinks including your anchor texts and all other information related to your backlinks with the speed of up to 500 threads per second. <br></li><li> Auto sites list updates : Our crawling servers are finding new websites every day. Therefore, you will receive new lists of websites updated daily. You don't need to search/scrape for website lists. You will receive fresh list of websites daily, where you can automatically submit your content. <br></li><li> Automatic Captcha Solving : Money Robot automatically solves all simple captchas for FREE, such as calculation captchas, photo captchas, text captchas, etc. For the complex captchas, the software offers you support for all major decaptcha services.<br></li></ul><br>Our Software supports UNLIMITED website platforms. You can submit your backlinks/content to following main platforms with support built right in:<br><ul><li> Web 2.0 Blogs<br></li><li> Social Network Posts<br></li><li> Social Bookmarking<br></li><li> Web Directories<br></li><li> Wiki Articles<br></li><li> Press Release<br></li><li> Article Directories<br></li><li> Web 2.0 Profiles<br></li><li> Forum Profiles<br></li><li> RSS<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-11/1446899270_c0xahpa.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Money Robot Submitter 7.33"></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><span style="font-size:12pt;"><b><span style="color:#006600;">:::Free Members :::</span></b></span><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowfree.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><a href="http://31.220.48.156/engine/go.php?url=aHR0cDovL3VzZXJzZmlsZXMuY29tL2VhYnlnZGNwbDJndg%3D%3D"  target="_blank">Download Now</a><br>Password : www.tgmember.com<br></div></div><br><p><br><br></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><span style="font-size:12pt;"><b><span style="color:#ff0000;">:::ViP Only:::</span></b></span><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>SENuke TNG 5.0.31 Pro</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1721-senuke-tng.html</link>
<description>Name : Senuke TNG Version : 5.0.31 Pro OS : Windows Type : Link Building Tools Price : $1997 Homepage : SalePage RANK #1 IN GOOGLE WITH TODAYS TOP RANKING FACTORS SEnuke TNG, &quot;THE NEXT GENERATION&quot; of SEO Automates todays most CRUCIAL ranking factors to EFFORTLESSLY boost your websites to the top of Google.. SEnuke TNG lets you quickly and easily dominate the SERPS like never before, effortlessly putting you in complete control of your websites rankings. Tried, tested and proven, SEnuke is always A SUPER EASY sell for anyone and this exciting version release is no exception. Previous version launches since 2008 have generated nearly eight figures in combined sales with MILLIONS being paid out in commissions to respected and valuable JV partners just like you… In fact, some are still being paid BIG monthly commissions TODAY for sales they made years ago. SEnukes high EPC, low refund rates, amazing retention rate and a proven funnel practically guarantees that you will see massive commissions by partnering with us for the TNG launch.</description>
<category>Link Building Tools</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.senuke.com/tng41AE/images/banner-box.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 00:42:09 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features 30 second Turbo Wizard Wizard &amp;amp; Diagram Designer Proxies Included Unlimited Captcha Solving CrowdSearch Niche Research Premium Social Network Social Network Social Bookmark RSS Web 2.0 Profile Forum Profile Press Release Wordpress Google Places PDF Wiki Macro Recorder Script Portal Indexer Pinger Whats News ? Crowd Searcher: Simulate thousands of people searching for your keyword on Google and clicking on your site. Increasingly Google is looking at how many people who search for your keyword click on your site. So this will give you an easy boost in rankings. Built in Proxies: No need to pay for external proxies. SEnuke comes with thousands of proxies to simulate real people from all over the world. Blog Network Module: Seamlessly integrate your existing private blog.comwork and manage it from within SEnuke. Built in OCR: Our built in Optical Character Recognition technology solves about 50% of captchas without needing any human intervention. For the rest, it integrates with various human captcha solving systems. Loop Mode: Create a campaign once and it will run forever on it&#039;s own building links to your site until you choose to stop it. Super Fast Turbo Wizard: Set up complex SEO campaigns within 30 seconds even if you &#039;re a complete newbie! No SEO knowledge necessary! Powerful Scheduler: Set it up once and take a trip to Hawaii and it&#039;s gonna do everything on it&#039;s own! If it ever crashes, it will auto-resume. Step-by-step Wizard: Want more control than the 30 second turbo wizard provides? Our 15 minute step-by-step wizard gets everything just right. Easy to Use Interface: Unlike other competitors, we strive to make the software extremely easy to understand and use Doing Local SEO? The new Google Places module helps you build citations for your business to get you first page rankings on Google Local! Powerful Macro Recorder: Automate getting a link from any website on the Inte.com without having to write a single line of code! Promotion Strategy Mapper: Create diagrams to show SEnuke exactly how you&#039;d like your link building to work. Or pick from one of the provided strategies! :::::::::SenukeTNG Zont SEO Template:::::::::</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/1kTz4rU6O4o?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> 30 second Turbo Wizard		<br></li><li> Wizard &amp; Diagram Designer		<br></li><li> Proxies Included		<br></li><li> Unlimited Captcha Solving		<br></li><li> CrowdSearch		<br></li><li> Niche Research		<br></li><li> Premium Social Network		<br></li><li> Social Network		<br></li><li> Social Bookmark		<br></li><li> RSS		<br></li><li> Web 2.0 Profile		<br></li><li> Forum Profile		<br></li><li> Press Release		<br></li><li> Wordpress		<br></li><li> Google Places		<br></li><li> PDF		<br></li><li> Wiki		<br></li><li> Macro Recorder		<br></li><li> Script Portal		<br></li><li> Indexer		<br></li><li> Pinger<br></li></ul><br><b>Whats News ?<br></b><ul><li> Crowd Searcher: Simulate thousands of people searching for your keyword on Google and clicking on your site. Increasingly Google is looking at how many people who search for your keyword click on your site. So this will give you an easy boost in rankings.<br></li><li> Built in Proxies: No need to pay for external proxies. SEnuke comes with thousands of proxies to simulate real people from all over the world.<br></li><li> Blog Network Module: Seamlessly integrate your existing private blog.comwork and manage it from within SEnuke.<br></li><li> Built in OCR: Our built in Optical Character Recognition technology solves about 50% of captchas without needing any human intervention. For the rest, it integrates with various human captcha solving systems.<br></li><li> Loop Mode: Create a campaign once and it will run forever on it's own building links to your site until you choose to stop it.<br></li><li> Super Fast Turbo Wizard: Set up complex SEO campaigns within 30 seconds even if you 're a complete newbie! No SEO knowledge necessary!<br></li><li> Powerful Scheduler: Set it up once and take a trip to Hawaii and it's gonna do everything on it's own! If it ever crashes, it will auto-resume.<br></li><li> Step-by-step Wizard: Want more control than the 30 second turbo wizard provides? Our 15 minute step-by-step wizard gets everything just right.<br></li><li> Easy to Use Interface: Unlike other competitors, we strive to make the software extremely easy to understand and use<br></li><li> Doing Local SEO? The new Google Places module helps you build citations for your business to get you first page rankings on Google Local!<br></li><li> Powerful Macro Recorder: Automate getting a link from any website on the Inte.com without having to write a single line of code!<br></li><li> Promotion Strategy Mapper: Create diagrams to show SEnuke exactly how you'd like your link building to work. Or pick from one of the provided strategies!<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://www.senuke.com/tng41AE/images/banner-box.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="SENuke TNG 5.0.31 Pro"><br><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br><br>:::::::::SenukeTNG Zont SEO Template:::::::::<br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Socinator 1.2</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3634-socinator.html</link>
<description>Name : Socinator Version : 1.2 OS : Windows Type : Instagram, Facebook, Twitter, Quora, LinkedIn, YouTube, Pinterest, Google+, Reddit, Tumblr Automation Price : $145 Homepage : SalePage Easy Automation For Busy Marketers - Manage and Grow All Your Social Accounts - dfccd d y and Organically Socinator gives you more control over your social accounts and helps you publish regular content over social media. It helps you drive greater level of ENGAGEMENT, reply in REAL TIME and mainly with content in response to specific actions. It makes EASIER to communicate with the audience and make the brand more relatable. Nevertheless, its a terrific Time saver driving more TRAFFIC to your site. Socinator lets you auto publish and schedule your posts on multiple.comworks at once, including Instagram, Twitter, Facebook, Google+, LinkedIn etc. Its also having an ability of content curation by importing content via RSS feeds, monitoring folder etc. making it the smart auto post scheduler.</description>
<category>Social Media</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 13:28:45 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Instagram Automation Features Grow your Instagram accounts 10x faster: Auto Follow, Follow Back, Auto Like, Auto Comment, Auto Repost, Auto Messages, Live Chat and Many More Facebook Automation Features Increase Engagement and Precised Audience Reach: Auto Friend Requests, Auto Accept Friends, Auto Like, Auto Comment, Auto Join Groups, Auto Unjoin, Live Chat and Many More Twitter Automation Features Boost your activities on Twitter for better engagement and ROI Auto Follow, Follow Back, Auto Like, Auto Comment, Auto Retweet, Auto Messages, Live Chat and Many More YouTube Automation Features Schedule your YouTube accounts on Auto-pilot, and watch them growing. Auto Follow, Auto Subscribe, Auto Unfollow, , Auto Like, Auto Comment and Many More Quora Automation Features Everything you need to succeed on Quora: Auto Friend Requests, Auto Downvote Answers, Auto Upvote Answers, Auto Report User, Auto Upvote Questions, Find And Extract Answers, Find And Extract Users and Many More gPlus Automation Features Be 24/7 Engaged with your Audience on gPlus. Auto Follow, Auto Post/Share Content In Your Communities, Auto Unfollow, Auto Unfollow, Join/Unjoin Communities In Your Niche and Many More Pinterest Automation Features Give boost to your Pinterest account for faster growth and 20x more revenue. Auto Follow, Auto Follow Back, Auto Try, Auto Comment, Auto Repin, Auto Create Boards, Auto Unfollow and Many More LinkedIn Automation Features Make your Professional Network more bigger and connect with potential partners and customers on the go. Auto Accept/Cancel Connection Requests, Auto Endorse Connections, Auto Engage with Likes and Comments, Auto Post/Share Content In Your Groups, Auto Reply to new messages, Find And Extract Answers, Find And Extract Users and Many More Reddit Automation Features Boost your activities on Twitter for better engagement and ROI Auto Follow, Follow Back, Auto Like, Auto Comment, Auto Retweet, Auto Messages, Live Chat and Many More Tumblr Automation Features Schedule your YouTube accounts on Auto-pilot, and watch them growing. Auto Follow, Auto Subscribe, Auto Unfollow, , Auto Like, Auto Comment and Many More Auto publish posts from RSS, Auto shorten URLs, Auto Submit captcha verification, Detailed report for each and every activity, Embedded browser for each.comwork, Analytics and Growth Metrics. ScreenShot</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Z-qsfVy-HYQ?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Instagram Automation Features Grow your Instagram accounts 10x faster: Auto Follow, Follow Back, Auto Like, Auto Comment, Auto Repost, Auto Messages, Live Chat and Many More<br></li><li> Facebook Automation Features Increase Engagement and Precised Audience Reach: Auto Friend Requests, Auto Accept Friends, Auto Like, Auto Comment, Auto Join Groups, Auto Unjoin, Live Chat and Many More <br></li><li> Twitter Automation Features Boost your activities on Twitter for better engagement and ROI  Auto Follow, Follow Back, Auto Like, Auto Comment, Auto Retweet, Auto Messages, Live Chat and Many More<br></li><li> YouTube Automation Features  Schedule your YouTube accounts on Auto-pilot, and watch them growing.  Auto Follow, Auto Subscribe, Auto Unfollow, , Auto Like, Auto Comment and Many More <br></li><li> Quora Automation Features  Everything you need to succeed on Quora:  Auto Friend Requests, Auto Downvote Answers, Auto Upvote Answers, Auto Report User, Auto Upvote Questions, Find And Extract Answers, Find And Extract Users and Many More <br></li><li> gPlus Automation Features  Be 24/7 Engaged with your Audience on gPlus.  Auto Follow, Auto Post/Share Content In Your Communities, Auto Unfollow, Auto Unfollow, Join/Unjoin Communities In Your Niche and Many More <br></li><li> Pinterest Automation Features  Give boost to your Pinterest account for faster growth and 20x more revenue.  Auto Follow, Auto Follow Back, Auto Try, Auto Comment, Auto Repin, Auto Create Boards, Auto Unfollow and Many More <br></li><li> LinkedIn Automation Features  Make your Professional Network more bigger and connect with potential partners and customers on the go.  Auto Accept/Cancel Connection Requests, Auto Endorse Connections, Auto Engage with Likes and Comments, Auto Post/Share Content In Your Groups, Auto Reply to new messages, Find And Extract Answers, Find And Extract Users and Many More <br></li><li> Reddit Automation Features  Boost your activities on Twitter for better engagement and ROI  Auto Follow, Follow Back, Auto Like, Auto Comment, Auto Retweet, Auto Messages, Live Chat and Many More <br></li><li> Tumblr Automation Features  Schedule your YouTube accounts on Auto-pilot, and watch them growing.  Auto Follow, Auto Subscribe, Auto Unfollow, , Auto Like, Auto Comment and Many More <br></li><li> Auto publish posts from RSS, Auto shorten URLs, Auto Submit captcha verification, Detailed report for each and every activity, Embedded browser for each.comwork, Analytics and Growth Metrics.<br><br></li></ul><br><h3>ScreenShot</h3><br><img src="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/nV7xWSbxcSvn_Cyf-DKt5ApOtvhp0IjnmGBbdNUlr-1NXWpZoYe4J0eL4HiR6ldXC-CnhATVSTnU96VIUM3GU1YcEXnApecojKfnUDIkMR_8RzGJVckiL5CvUNz9BTZDs5n0_vpA" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Socinator 1.2"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>