<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Local Marketing - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>Local Marketing - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>Lead Power Machine 1.0.13</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1156-lead-power-machine.html</link>
<description>Name : Lead Power Machine Version : 1.0.13 OS : Windows/MAC Type : Lead Marketing Price : $1250 Homepage : SalePage Here&#039;s the best way ever to find prospects... Sell them products they desperately want and need for $500 to $1K each, and... Automatically create the product with 5 mouse clicks. Check this out.</description>
<category>Local Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 15:46:05 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features With Lead Power Machine, I Can Determine Which Ones Have Websites and Mobile Websites, Instantly Create Mobile Websites and Apps, Instantly E-mail and Automatically Follow Up with Leads even with Video E-mail, and More ... All Faster, Easier, and More Effortless Than Ever Before! Get Instantaneous Access to Tens, Hundreds or Even Thousands of Leads- Email All Your Leads with a Touch of a Button No messing around with websites that don&#039;t convert or search engine optimization techniques that don&#039;t work You get immediate access to REAL TIME generated leads that YOU CONTROL No more paying for leads! Identify hundreds even thousands of &quot;targeted&quot; motivated buyers easily and effortlessly, and you can even email them all with the click of a mouse Be Able to run software runs practically on autopilot Gain an UNFAIR ADVANTAGE over your competition in any area in the country or internationally!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/eiQbPMny9f0?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> With Lead Power Machine, I Can Determine Which Ones Have Websites and Mobile Websites, Instantly Create Mobile Websites and Apps, Instantly E-mail and Automatically Follow Up with Leads even with Video E-mail, and More ... All Faster, Easier, and More Effortless Than Ever Before!<br></li><li> Get Instantaneous Access to Tens, Hundreds or Even Thousands of Leads- Email All Your Leads with a Touch of a Button<br></li><li> No messing around with websites that don't convert or search engine optimization techniques that don't work<br></li><li> You get immediate access to REAL TIME generated leads that YOU CONTROL<br></li><li> No more paying for leads!<br></li><li> Identify hundreds even thousands of "targeted" motivated buyers easily and effortlessly, and you can even email them all with the click of a mouse<br></li><li> Be Able to run software runs practically on autopilot<br></li><li> Gain an UNFAIR ADVANTAGE over your competition in any area in the country or internationally!<br></li></ul><br><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Lead Power Machine 1.0.13"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Online Lead Finder 3.5.36</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/909-online-lead-finder.html</link>
<description>Name : Online Lead Finder Version : 3.5.36 Sliver &amp;amp; Social Bot OS : Windows Type : Social Bot and Lead Marketing Price : $797 Homepage : SalePage You&#039;re About To Discover A Software Tool That Tirelessly Works for You To Find HOT Leads and Create Massive Profits!&quot; We all know that you can&#039;t do business without leads that then turn into suspects, prospects, and paying customers. You need lots of leads to work in order to generate your sales, whether it&#039;s Inte.com marketing, insurance, affiliate marketing, real estate, eBay, auto related, or any of a hundred other businesses.</description>
<category>Local Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-07/thumbs/1437773655_olftgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 12:05:33 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Cragislist, BackPage, Ebay Lead Search Yellow Pages Scraper Automated Twitter Marketing Twitter Trends Demand Traffic Facebook Lead Serve Social Lead Detective Google Maps Extractor Yahoo Auto Answer Bot Social Mail Hacker Linked Lead Connect Email Gunner FB Open Graph Investigator Miracle Traffic Bot YouTube Dominator Details Classifieds Posters : Craigslist Poster, Backpage Poster Twitter Marketing : Twitter Trends Finder, Twitter Follow/UnFollow Bot, Twitter Message Bot Google/Plus : Google Lead Sleuth, Google Plus Lead Detective FaceBook Marketing : FB Open Graph Investigator (Graph Search, Facebook Friend Request), FB Lead Server (By Keyword, Events, Groups) Social Email Extractor : Extract &amp;amp; Filter From GooglePlus,Facebook,Twitter,MySpace,Linkedin, Plurk, Reddit, Friendster, Badoo, Ning, Xing Linkedin Marketing : Message to Linkedin Member, Get Linkedin Group Category, Join Linkedin Group, Invite to Linkedin Group, Export Connection Member, Share with Linkedin Groups Facebook Marketing : Search and Like Page, Send Message to Page, Search and Join Group,Export Facebook Group Category, Send Message to Facebook Groups, Send File to Facebook Groups, Create Event For Facebook Groups Instagram Marketing : Search and Follow/UnFollow Yahoo Marketing : Search and Join Yahoo Group, Yahoo Mass Mailer, Post to Yahoo Group SEO Marketing: + Article Submision : Support Articlecube, ezinearticles, Articlecity, Articlebase, Articlestarts, Artipot, Pubartilces + PressRelease Submission : Support BigNews, BriefingWire, Kontax, Pressbox, Postafreepressrelease, PrUrgent, Powerhomebiz + Social Bookmarking : Support delicious, folkd, SocioPost, Startaid, 1look4 + Video Submison : Support bofunk, Veoh, Photobuck, 4Shared, Engagemedia, Vimeo + WordPress Search &amp;amp; Commenter Youtube Send Message and Comments Pinterest Marketing : Gather pin/usernameID&#039;s, Autofollow/unfollow, Auto Like, Auto Comment, Auto Repin, Auto invite Classifieds ADPosters : Support 33 Popular Classified sites, Article Spin, Parse &amp;amp; Auto Register. Bulk Mailer Article Scraper Yellow Pages Lead Scraper HomeAdvisor Lead Scraper US Business Listing Lead Scraper Google Lead Scraper Local SEO Intel Yahoo Answer Bot : Search and Answer, Real Time Questions - Answer, Vote Answer Bot, Best Answer Bot</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="319" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/EpdvDwnNoYY?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><p><br></p><br><h3>Features</h3><br><p><br><ul><li> Cragislist, BackPage, Ebay Lead Search<br></li><li> Yellow Pages Scraper<br></li><li> Automated Twitter Marketing<br></li><li> Twitter Trends Demand Traffic<br></li><li> Facebook Lead Serve<br></li><li> Social Lead Detective<br></li><li> Google Maps Extractor<br></li><li> Yahoo Auto Answer Bot<br></li><li> Social Mail Hacker<br></li><li> Linked Lead Connect<br></li><li> Email Gunner<br></li><li> FB Open Graph Investigator<br></li><li> Miracle Traffic Bot<br></li><li> YouTube Dominator<br></li></ul><br>Details<br><ul><li> Classifieds Posters : Craigslist Poster, Backpage Poster<br></li><li> Twitter Marketing : Twitter Trends Finder, Twitter Follow/UnFollow Bot, Twitter Message Bot<br></li><li> Google/Plus : Google Lead Sleuth, Google Plus Lead Detective<br></li><li> FaceBook Marketing : FB Open Graph Investigator (Graph Search, Facebook Friend Request), FB Lead Server (By Keyword, Events, Groups)<br></li><li> Social Email Extractor : Extract &amp; Filter From GooglePlus,Facebook,Twitter,MySpace,Linkedin, Plurk, Reddit, Friendster, Badoo, Ning, Xing<br></li><li> Linkedin Marketing : Message to Linkedin Member, Get Linkedin Group Category, Join Linkedin Group, Invite to Linkedin Group, Export Connection Member, Share with Linkedin Groups<br></li><li> Facebook Marketing : Search and Like Page, Send Message to Page, Search and Join Group,Export Facebook Group Category, Send Message to Facebook Groups, Send File to Facebook Groups, Create Event For Facebook Groups<br></li><li> Instagram Marketing : Search and Follow/UnFollow<br></li><li> Yahoo Marketing : Search and Join Yahoo Group, Yahoo Mass Mailer, Post to Yahoo Group<br></li><li> SEO Marketing: <br></li><li> + Article Submision : Support Articlecube, ezinearticles, Articlecity, Articlebase, Articlestarts, Artipot, Pubartilces<br></li><li> + PressRelease Submission : Support BigNews, BriefingWire, Kontax, Pressbox, Postafreepressrelease, PrUrgent, Powerhomebiz<br></li><li> + Social Bookmarking : Support delicious, folkd, SocioPost, Startaid, 1look4<br></li><li> + Video Submison : Support bofunk, Veoh, Photobuck, 4Shared, Engagemedia, Vimeo<br></li><li> + WordPress Search &amp; Commenter<br></li><li> Youtube Send Message and Comments <br></li><li> Pinterest Marketing : Gather pin/usernameID's, Autofollow/unfollow, Auto Like, Auto Comment, Auto Repin, Auto invite<br></li><li> Classifieds ADPosters : Support 33 Popular Classified sites, Article Spin, Parse &amp; Auto Register.<br></li><li> Bulk Mailer<br></li><li> Article Scraper<br></li><li> Yellow Pages Lead Scraper<br></li><li> HomeAdvisor Lead Scraper<br></li><li> US Business Listing Lead Scraper<br></li><li> Google Lead Scraper<br></li><li> Local SEO Intel<br></li><li> Yahoo Answer Bot : Search and Answer, Real Time Questions - Answer, Vote Answer Bot, Best Answer Bot<br></li></ul><br><a href="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-07/1437773655_olftgmember.png" class="highslide" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.tgmember.com/uploads/posts/2015-07/thumbs/1437773655_olftgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=''></a></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Online Lead Finder 3.5.36"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Paigham Bot 9.0.7.6</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1973-paigham-bot.html</link>
<description>Name : Paigham Bot Version : 9.0.7.6 OS : Windows Type : Traffic Generator Software Price : $499 Homepage : SalePage Paigham Bot is one of the most effective marketing applications on the market today. It is able to accurately gather data from search engines in any industry or niche and provides contact details for businesses and people that are most important to you i.e. YOUR MOST PRIZED PROSPECTS-AND WILL CONTACT THEM FOR YOU.</description>
<category>Local Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://i.imgur.com/86eAR68.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 07:47:32 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features BRAND NEW USER INTERFACE (allows for easier user application management) New Keyword Management Module(Manually add, edit, delete and track your keywords) New Search Engine Selectors (Additional Google.com extensions) Separate Scraping and Posting Modules (Allows for easier campaign management) Advanced Tag Control Module Tag Collector Enhanced targeting abilities with the Smart Niche &amp;amp; Search Engine Filters. Powerful Short Codes-Incorporate data from each site into your message Updated Captcha Solving API Integration (Use your DBC account to solve captcha’s) Individual Module reports (exportable txt and csv files) Two Proxy Management Integration tools (Upload Proxies or Connect Your HMA Account) Acquire Data From Your Audience (Social Accounts, Phone #’s, emails and more) Directly contact your audience automatically (Has ability to post to 100 sites per minute) Multiple Posting Variations (Send 100% Unique Messages To Each Prospect) Footprint Management Tools (Easily modify your search engine operators) Scraping Throttle (Control how fast Paigham Bot Finds new sites) Multi-Threading Abilities (Run up to 20 Posting threads)</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/oVk064qJ9sg?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><p><br></p><br><h3>Features</h3><br><p><br><ul><li> BRAND NEW USER INTERFACE (allows for easier user application management)<br></li><li> New Keyword Management Module(Manually add, edit, delete and track your keywords)<br></li><li> New Search Engine Selectors (Additional Google.com extensions)<br></li><li> Separate Scraping and Posting Modules (Allows for easier campaign management)<br></li><li> Advanced Tag Control Module<br></li><li> Tag Collector<br></li><li> Enhanced targeting abilities with the Smart Niche &amp; Search Engine Filters.<br></li><li> Powerful Short Codes-Incorporate data from each site into your message<br></li><li> Updated Captcha Solving API Integration (Use your DBC account to solve captcha’s)<br></li><li> Individual Module reports (exportable txt and csv files)<br></li><li> Two Proxy Management Integration tools (Upload Proxies or Connect Your HMA Account)<br></li><li> Acquire Data From Your Audience (Social Accounts, Phone #’s, emails and more)<br></li><li> Directly contact your audience automatically (Has ability to post to 100 sites per minute)<br></li><li> Multiple Posting Variations (Send 100% Unique Messages To Each Prospect)<br></li><li> Footprint Management Tools (Easily modify your search engine operators)<br></li><li> Scraping Throttle (Control how fast Paigham Bot Finds new sites)<br></li><li> Multi-Threading Abilities (Run up to 20 Posting threads)<br><br></li></ul><br><img src="http://i.imgur.com/86eAR68.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Paigham Bot 9.0.7.6"></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>TeKnife Yellow Pages Scraper 1.0.2</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4279-teknife-yellow-pages-scraper.html</link>
<description>Name : TeKnife Yellow Pages Scraper Version : 1.0.2 OS : Windows Type : Yellow Pages Scraper Price : $0 Homepage : SalePage TeKnife Yellow Pages Scraper</description>
<category>Local Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 09:22:41 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Extract Full Data from Yellow Pages based on keywords and locations . Proxy support . 7 Days Free Trial Full Functionality .</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Extract Full Data from Yellow Pages based on keywords and locations .<br></li><li> Proxy support .<br></li><li> 7 Days Free Trial Full Functionality .<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="TeKnife Yellow Pages Scraper 1.0.2"><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Yellow Pages Scraper 1.0.3.21</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1345-yellow-pages-scraper.html</link>
<description>Name : Yellow Pages Scraper (Australia, USA &amp;amp; CA, USA &amp;amp; India, Europe, Global ) Version : 1.0.3.21 OS : Windows Type : Yellow Pages Scraper Price : $90 Homepage : SalePage Use our Yellow Pages Scraper to Build your Own Database for Marketing Purpose This Management-Ware yellow pages scraper software can be used to scrape the name, address, city, state, zip code, phone &amp;amp; fax number, email address (if there is one) and webpage from any listing, city or state (in the USA) posted in the yellow pages. This yellow pages extractor program will help you convert web data into CSV or other format, and save your time instead of collecting manually. You can also use a find email option to look for the email addresses of your contacts.</description>
<category>Local Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 09:10:36 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Targeted search for emails using keywords Using Email Address Finder, you can search email addresses using any keyword or filter type that he or she pleases. Search for email address parameters can be set so that addresses are filtered by gender, age, ethnicity, or another factor. For example, a business with children’s products can search for emails belonging to parents with young children. A company selling items that would interest a senior citizen could choose out emails belonging to senior citizens. Yellow pages extractors features Number of records you can extract (Unlimited) Search/ Extract by keyword (One or many keywords) Search/ Extract by URL (One or many URLs) Search by keyword / by categories / by custom categories Support Proxy (Hide your IP Address) Save search results (CSV, Excel, html, PDF) Support many types of output format If you need other features to satisfy your requirements. Please contact us. Contact List Manager with duplicates check All our yellow pages scrapers not only helps you find leads online but also set up a database with the information. After extracting the yellow pages of your choice, the program will automatically check the database to make sure there are no duplicate entries. The program sets up its own database for the contacts that have been extracted and there is no limit on how long such a list can be. Currently we are offering yellow pages scraper for 4 different countries. Each country are distribute with seperate installer. You can a special edition that is including USA and Canada. Yellow Pages Scraper for Global: Support yellowpages.com Support superpages.com Support yellowpages.ca Support pagesjaunes.ca Support superpages.ca Support yellowpages.com.au Support truelocal.com.au Support yell.com Support thomsonlocal.com Support yellow.co.nz Support finda.co.nz Yellow Pages Scraper for USA: Support yellowpages.com Support superpages.com Yellow Pages Scraper for Canada: Support yellowpages.ca Support pagesjaunes.ca Support superpages.ca Yellow Pages Scraper for Australia: Support yellowpages.com.au Support truelocal.com.au Yellow Pages Scraper for Europe: Support yell.com Support thomsonlocal.com Yellow Pages Scraper for USACanada: Support yellowpages.com Support superpages.com Support yellowpages.ca Support pagesjaunes.ca Support superpages.ca Yellow Pages Scraper for CustomScript: Support superpagespr.com Support iqpf.org Support twilio.com Support rccaq.com Yellow Pages Scraper for UK: Support yell.com Support thomsonlocal.com Yellow Pages Scraper for India: Support yellowpages.co.in Support indianyellowpages.com Yellow Pages Scraper for USAIndia: Support yellowpages.com Support superpages.com Support yellowpages.co.in Support indianyellowpages.com Yellow Pages Scraper for HongKong: Support yp.com.hk Support ypmap.com Yellow Pages Scraper for Yelp: Support yelp.com Yellow Pages Scraper for Facebook: google.com bing.com Yellow Pages Scraper for Linkedin: google.com bing.com Yellow Pages Scraper for NewZealand: Support yellow.co.nz Support finda.co.nz Yellow Pages Scraper for AustraliaAndNZ: Support yellowpages.com.au Support truelocal.com.au Support yellow.co.nz Support finda.co.nz</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/3N-jfmbNkZs?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><b>Targeted search for emails using keywords</b><br>Using Email Address Finder, you can search email addresses using any keyword or filter type that he or she pleases. Search for email address parameters can be set so that addresses are filtered by gender, age, ethnicity, or another factor. For example, a business with children’s products can search for emails belonging to parents with young children. A company selling items that would interest a senior citizen could choose out emails belonging to senior citizens.<br><b>Yellow pages extractors features</b><br><ul><li> Number of records you can extract (Unlimited)<br></li><li> Search/ Extract by keyword (One or many keywords)<br></li><li> Search/ Extract by URL (One or many URLs)<br></li><li> Search by keyword / by categories / by custom categories<br></li><li> Support Proxy (Hide your IP Address)<br></li><li> Save search results (CSV, Excel, html, PDF)<br></li><li> Support many types of output format<br></li><li> If you need other features to satisfy your requirements. Please contact us.<br></li></ul><br><b>Contact List Manager with duplicates check</b><br>All our yellow pages scrapers  not only helps you find leads online but also set up a database with the information. After extracting the yellow pages of your choice, the program will automatically check the database to make sure there are no duplicate entries. The program sets up its own database for the contacts that have been extracted and there is no limit on how long such a list can be.<br><br>Currently we are offering yellow pages scraper for 4 different countries. Each country are distribute with seperate installer. You can a special edition that is including USA and Canada.<br><br><br><b>Yellow Pages Scraper for Global:<br></b><br><ul><li> Support yellowpages.com<br></li><li> Support superpages.com<br></li><li> Support yellowpages.ca<br></li><li> Support pagesjaunes.ca<br></li><li> Support superpages.ca<br></li><li> Support yellowpages.com.au<br></li><li> Support truelocal.com.au<br></li><li> Support yell.com<br></li><li> Support thomsonlocal.com<br></li><li> Support yellow.co.nz<br></li><li> Support finda.co.nz<br></li></ul><br><b>Yellow Pages Scraper for USA:<br></b><br><ul><li> Support yellowpages.com<br></li><li> Support superpages.com<br></li></ul><br><b>Yellow Pages Scraper for Canada:<br></b><br><ul><li> Support yellowpages.ca<br></li><li> Support pagesjaunes.ca<br></li><li> Support superpages.ca<br></li></ul><br><b>Yellow Pages Scraper for Australia:<br></b><br><ul><li> Support yellowpages.com.au<br></li><li> Support truelocal.com.au<br></li></ul><br><b>Yellow Pages Scraper for Europe:<br></b><br><ul><li> Support yell.com<br></li><li> Support thomsonlocal.com<br></li></ul><br><b>Yellow Pages Scraper for USACanada:<br></b><br><ul><li> Support yellowpages.com<br></li><li> Support superpages.com<br></li><li> Support yellowpages.ca<br></li><li> Support pagesjaunes.ca<br></li><li> Support superpages.ca<br></li></ul><br><b>Yellow Pages Scraper for CustomScript:<br></b><br><ul><li> Support superpagespr.com<br></li><li> Support iqpf.org<br></li><li> Support twilio.com<br></li><li> Support rccaq.com<br></li></ul><br><b>Yellow Pages Scraper for UK:<br></b><br><ul><li> Support yell.com<br></li><li> Support thomsonlocal.com<br></li></ul><br><b>Yellow Pages Scraper for India:<br></b><br><ul><li> Support yellowpages.co.in<br></li><li> Support indianyellowpages.com<br></li></ul><br><b>Yellow Pages Scraper for USAIndia:<br></b><br><ul><li> Support yellowpages.com<br></li><li> Support superpages.com<br></li><li> Support yellowpages.co.in<br></li><li> Support indianyellowpages.com<br></li></ul><br><b>Yellow Pages Scraper for HongKong:<br></b><br><ul><li> Support yp.com.hk<br></li><li> Support ypmap.com<br></li></ul><br><b>Yellow Pages Scraper for Yelp:<br></b><br><ul><li> Support yelp.com<br></li></ul><br><b>Yellow Pages Scraper for Facebook:<br></b><br><ul><li> google.com<br></li><li> bing.com<br></li></ul><br><b>Yellow Pages Scraper for Linkedin:<br></b><br><ul><li> google.com<br></li><li> bing.com<br></li></ul><br><b>Yellow Pages Scraper for NewZealand:<br></b><br><ul><li> Support yellow.co.nz<br></li><li> Support finda.co.nz<br></li></ul><br><b>Yellow Pages Scraper for AustraliaAndNZ:<br></b><br><ul><li> Support yellowpages.com.au<br></li><li> Support truelocal.com.au<br></li><li> Support yellow.co.nz<br></li><li> Support finda.co.nz<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Yellow Pages Scraper 1.0.3.21"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Yellow Leads Extractor 1.9.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3848-yellow-leads-extractor.html</link>
<description>Name : Yellow Leads Extractor Version : 1.9.0 OS : Windows Type : Yellow Page Extractor Price : $89 Homepage : SalePage Yellow Leads Extractor allows user to make 100% customizable searches in a browser. When you have this program then you no need to do lots work to get information from the yellow pages. You only need to enter category and location. After entering these information when you will click on the get data option after that all information will be extracted. As you know yellow pages are list of telephone directory of businesses. Basically it is a paper based directory. By the help of yellow pages you can get details of companies, shops, services in a given area. Now yellow pages also started to be used to notify online directory of the businesses. If you want to know some information from yellow pages directory then it could be easily done by the help of Yellow Leads Extractor, a powerful Yellow Pages Scraper for USA, Canada, French, German, Italy, Spain, Switzerland,</description>
<category>Local Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.estrattoredati.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/07/yellowpages-1024x623.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2018 09:13:54 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features ITALY PagineGialle.it FRANCE PagesJaunes.fr GERMANY GelbenSeiten.de SWITZERLAND Local.ch ENGLISH Yell.com AUSTRIA Herold.at ITALY Aziende.virgilio.it SPAIN PaginasAmarillas.es USA YellowPages.com CANADA YellowPages.ca BELGIUM Goldenpages.be POLAND YellowPages.pl OTHER COUNTRIES Infobel.com</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> ITALY PagineGialle.it<br></li><li> FRANCE PagesJaunes.fr<br></li><li> GERMANY GelbenSeiten.de<br></li><li> SWITZERLAND Local.ch<br></li><li> ENGLISH Yell.com<br></li><li> AUSTRIA Herold.at<br></li><li> ITALY Aziende.virgilio.it<br></li><li> SPAIN PaginasAmarillas.es<br></li><li> USA YellowPages.com<br></li><li> CANADA YellowPages.ca<br></li><li> BELGIUM Goldenpages.be<br></li><li> POLAND YellowPages.pl<br></li><li> OTHER COUNTRIES Infobel.com<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://www.estrattoredati.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/07/yellowpages-1024x623.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Yellow Leads Extractor 1.9.0"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Paigham Daily Deal Bot 2.0.1.3</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1975-paigham-daily-deal-bot.html</link>
<description>Name : Paigham Daily Deal Bot Version : 2.0.1.1 OS : Windows Type : Local Marketing Bot Price : $47 Homepage : SalePage This is a separate application from the main Paigham Bot software, designed to collect business details from companies actively advertising their products/services. Although a unique data scraping application itself, it also works in conjunction with the main Paigham Bot software by mining additional contact details on the businesses, looking for contact form pages on their website that one can use to directly load in Paigham Bot and start contacting these companies right away to market your service/products. What Does the Daily Deal Bot Do? A user can geo target companies according to State, City Locality and can even target according to business category. Use this to market to other businesses or for list building (contact form lists for Paigham Bot, email lists, call center phone lists and social media marketing lists etc.) Currently it scrapes, crawls and mines Groupon’s entire US database of active advertisers currently marketing their businesses. (We have future updates planned to also include other ad/business.comworks, such as Living Social etc).</description>
<category>Local Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://i.imgur.com/V170nMZ.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 22:54:37 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features What Data Does It Collect? The listed Groupon offer for the Business (Deal Link Page included) Website Details Email Details Phone Number Details Facebook Details Twitter Details Linkedin Details</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/8s0blNVfaek?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br>What Data Does It Collect?<br><ul><li> The listed Groupon offer for the Business (Deal Link Page included)<br></li><li> Website Details<br></li><li> Email Details<br></li><li> Phone Number Details<br></li><li> Facebook Details<br></li><li> Twitter Details<br></li><li> Linkedin Details<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://i.imgur.com/V170nMZ.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Paigham Daily Deal Bot 2.0.1.3"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>G-Business Extractor 1.0</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3957-g-business-extractor.html</link>
<description>Name : G-Business Extractor Version : 1.0 OS : Windows Type : Google Map Extractor Price : $90 Homepage : SalePage G-Business Extractor is a powerful tool that help you to find business leads from Google Maps Google Maps is a source where you can find millions of business leads classifieds by categories and locations. You can search by your target keywords in your locations. This software will search and find business information like website, email addresses, phone, fax, etc..</description>
<category>Local Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.adsmcard.com/images/estrarre-indirizzi0.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 13:48:36 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Extract Data (e-mail addresses, phone, fax, business name, etc) from Google Maps dorectory in seconds with just one click. User can search in any category and location. Support proxies for connection. &amp;gt; Automatic updates when sources sites change. Export results to CSV or XLS</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3><br><ul><li> Extract Data (e-mail addresses, phone, fax, business name, etc) from Google Maps dorectory in seconds with just one click.<br></li><li> User can search in any category and location.<br></li><li> Support proxies for connection. &gt; Automatic updates when sources sites change.<br></li><li> Export results to CSV or XLS<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://www.adsmcard.com/images/estrarre-indirizzi0.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt="G-Business Extractor 1.0"><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div><br></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Web Contact Scraper 4.5.20</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1668-web-contact-scraper.html</link>
<description>Name : Web Contact Scraper Version : 4.5.20 OS : Windows Type : Lead Generator Tools, Yellow Pages, White Pages, Yelp, 411, Kompass, Yell and more Price : $40 Homepage : SalePage Web Contact Scraper is a fully automated software application for gathering targeted business contact information! You can search and gather thousands of business details matching a chosen profession within any location worldwide! Build your own targeted Email Marketing Lists yourself! You can instantly retrieve 1000 Plumbers in New York or 10,000 Dance Instructors in Australia, the possibilities are endless! Export emails, phone numbers, websites, addresses to CSV and start your targeted business campaign today!</description>
<category>Local Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://www.ginkosolutions.com/web-contact-scraper/img/app/1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2017 19:35:00 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Search for multiple business key words (I.e. Construction, Dentist, Lawyer) Search within multiple cities, states and countries! See the search results appear in real-time! In-built tool to remove duplicate contact information Supports Yellow Pages, Yelp, 411.ca, White Pages, Kompass, Yell and more! Supports: USA, Canada, UK, Australia, Germany, Switzerland, New Zealand, France, Austria, South Korea, Thailand, Malaysia, Indonesia, Cambodia, Brunei and Laos (Further countries can be added by request!) Export results to CSV on-the-fly Export to multiple log files on-the-fly Searches can be paused and resumed with ease Inte.com connection drops do not affect searches in progress Intelligent Proxy IP Support to scrape anonymously! Support Ind.comwork, Thomsonlocal,Cylex,bizdirlib.com, stclassifieds.sg</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/hjxQv3DAHDQ?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><p></p><br><h3>Features</h3><br><p><br><ul><li> Search for multiple business key words (I.e. Construction, Dentist, Lawyer)<br></li><li> Search within multiple cities, states and countries!<br></li><li> See the search results appear in real-time!<br></li><li> In-built tool to remove duplicate contact information<br></li><li> Supports Yellow Pages, Yelp, 411.ca, White Pages, Kompass, Yell and more!<br></li><li> Supports: USA, Canada, UK, Australia, Germany, Switzerland, New Zealand, France, Austria, South Korea, Thailand, Malaysia, Indonesia, Cambodia, Brunei and Laos (Further countries can be added by request!)<br></li><li> Export results to CSV on-the-fly<br></li><li> Export to multiple log files on-the-fly<br></li><li> Searches can be paused and resumed with ease<br></li><li> Inte.com connection drops do not affect searches in progress<br></li><li> Intelligent Proxy IP Support to scrape anonymously!<br></li><li> Support Ind.comwork, Thomsonlocal,Cylex,bizdirlib.com, stclassifieds.sg<br></li></ul><br><img src="http://www.ginkosolutions.com/web-contact-scraper/img/app/1.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Web Contact Scraper 4.5.20"></p><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Google and Bing Maps Extractor 2.07</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/1076-google-and-bing-maps-extractor.html</link>
<description>Name : Google and Bing Maps Extractor Version : 2.07 OS : Windows Type : Local Marketing Bot, Email Extractor Price : $120 Homepage : SalePage Google maps contact extractor - Grab and manage Google Maps information. Download a demo of our Google Maps Extractor software today for free! Use our Google Maps extractor to capture contact information from Google Maps Website today! Use Google and Bing Maps Contact Extractor to create your own list of leads in a few seconds. Grab and manage Google and Bing Maps contact information with our web data extractor software. Download a demo of our Google and Bing Maps Contact Extractor software today for free! Use our Google and Bing Maps Extractor software to capture contact information from Google and Bing Maps today! Get the information directly from the source with our Web scraper software. Google and Bing Maps Contact Extractor: The program that can automatically download Google and Bing Maps Business information. Fresh propect list ready for you… Inte.com has many sources of free leads that you can use to market your product or service. Google and Bing Maps Contact Extractor allows you to build your own contact list / prospect list from Google and Bing Maps database. If you are looking for a quick and easy way to capture contact information such as business name, address, Website, emails, phone number from Google and Bing Maps then, Google and Bing Maps Contact Extractor is the marketing tool that you need for telemarketing. No special knowledge is required to learn. With Google and Bing Maps contact Extractor, purchase process will never be that complicated. Find your suppliers and prospects online from Google Maps and send them your promotions! Stop copying manually the details from Google and Bing Maps. Let Google and Bing Maps Extractor do it for you! Don’t spend money to buy outdated information, using our Web data extractor software to get updated information from the Google and Bing Maps database! Do not buy mail lists unless you have tried to use the Google and Bing Maps Contact Extractor. Don’t use your hand to enter your prospect details, the information can be extract automatically with our Web data extractor program.</description>
<category>Local Marketing</category>
<enclosure url="http://i.imgur.com/yFp79W5.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2017 17:46:13 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features Google and Bing Maps Contact Extractor features &amp;amp; benefits Extract business and geographical data. Use for Direct Marketing and Tele-Marketing Campaigns… Capture contact lists from Google and Bing Maps. Total control over the search (Start, pause and continue the search, you can also control the page you want to extract). Search using unlimited categories and locations. Search by keyword / by categories / by custom categories. Multi-keywords search (this feature automate the search process) Multi-location search (Combined with the keywords, the search process is automated). Support proxies for identity protection. (The application can change randomly the current proxy in each request from a list that you provide.) Free proxy server provide by Management-Ware Solutions Save and Export the extracted contact lists in the most popular formats: CSV, XML, Excel (XLS), PDF, HTML and RTF. Perfect for building your businesses mailing list. Very EASY to use, convenient and offers an outstanding performance. Supported countries and languages by Google and Bing Maps Contact Extractor Our Contact extractor software support all the countries and the languages supported by the Google and Bing Maps Websites. So you can get the information you want. Supported Google Maps countries by our Google Maps Software. Supported Language by our Google Maps contact extractor Software. Why do I need this Website data extractor software? To move ahead successfully with direct marketing and tele-marketing campaigns, you need a lot of contacts. With the Google and Bing Maps Extractor you can collect hundreds of thousands of contacts from your target group within days or even hours. Google and Bing Maps Contact Extractor is a very fast program and supports multi-threaded page loading. Our web data extractor software collects contacts easily using Google and Bing Maps database. DON’T BUY OUTDATED LEADS DATABASE…BUILD YOUR OWN, USE OUR CONTACT EXTRACTOR SOFTWARE!!!</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/BvBEfC9jmRI?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div>
<p></p>
<h3>Features</h3>
<p><br>Google and Bing Maps Contact Extractor features &amp; benefits<br><ul><li> Extract business and geographical data.<br></li><li> Use for Direct Marketing and Tele-Marketing Campaigns…<br></li><li> Capture contact lists from Google and Bing Maps.<br></li><li> Total control over the search (Start, pause and continue the search, you can also control the page you want to extract).<br></li><li> Search using unlimited categories and locations.<br></li><li> Search by keyword / by categories / by custom categories.<br></li><li> Multi-keywords search (this feature automate the search process)<br></li><li> Multi-location search (Combined with the keywords, the search process is automated).<br></li><li> Support proxies for identity protection. (The application can change randomly the current proxy in each request from a list that you provide.)<br></li><li> Free proxy server provide by Management-Ware Solutions<br></li><li> Save and Export the extracted contact lists in the most popular formats: CSV, XML, Excel (XLS), PDF, HTML and RTF.<br></li><li> Perfect for building your businesses mailing list.<br></li><li> Very EASY to use, convenient and offers an outstanding performance.<br></li></ul><br><b>Supported countries and languages by Google and Bing Maps Contact Extractor</b><br><br>Our Contact extractor software support all the countries and the languages supported by the Google and Bing Maps Websites. So you can get the information you want.<br><ul><li> Supported Google Maps countries by our Google Maps Software.<br></li><li> Supported Language by our Google Maps contact extractor Software.<br></li></ul><br><b>Why do I need this Website data extractor software?</b><br><br>To move ahead successfully with direct marketing and tele-marketing campaigns, you need a lot of contacts. With the Google and Bing Maps Extractor you can collect hundreds of thousands of contacts from your target group within days or even hours.<br><br>Google and Bing Maps Contact Extractor is a very fast program and supports multi-threaded page loading. Our web data extractor software collects contacts easily using Google and Bing Maps database.<br><br><b>DON’T BUY OUTDATED LEADS DATABASE…BUILD YOUR OWN, USE OUR CONTACT EXTRACTOR SOFTWARE!!!</b><br><img src="http://i.imgur.com/yFp79W5.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Google and Bing Maps Extractor 2.07"></p>
<div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>