<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>GB WordPress - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/</link>
<language>en</language>
<description>GB WordPress - Make Money Online From 0&#036; - tgmember.com</description>
<yandex:logo>http://31.220.48.156/yandexlogo.png</yandex:logo>
<yandex:logo type="square">http://31.220.48.156/yandexsquarelogo.png</yandex:logo>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item turbo="true">
<title>Pintra + OTOs</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4525-pintra-otos.html</link>
<description>GB Name : Pintra + OTOs Version : Last OS : Anything Type : Pinterest Wordpress Software GB Price : $27(FE) + $32(OTO1) + $37(OTO2) + $27(OTO3) + $97(OTO4) = $220 GB Cost : 11$/20 peoples + 1$ Fee GB Joined : 0/20 Peoples GB Status : Going Homepage : SalePage Inside Pintra we show you a way to get Free traffic by posting content that is relevant to your niche and help you generate leads and sales, using our software and over the shoulder&#039;s training, in 3 easy steps. Instead of slaving away trying to manually post new content to your new niche blog, or to create a high-traffic Pinterest account, or even spending a small fortune on paid ads… We&#039;ve developed a fully Automated &quot;One Click&quot; Pinterest Wordpress Software. We have also included inside exclusive Video Training To Maximize your Profits With Pinterest and Wordpress, Quickly &amp;amp; Easily by Finding Great Content Online and Posting it in Seconds! Our Software will Post Images, ,Full Blog Posts, Certain Features and More With One Click!</description>
<category>GB WordPress</category>
<enclosure url="https://i.imgur.com/OmmYCST.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="https://i.imgur.com/kJy8kQl.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="https://i.imgur.com/egJHecV.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="https://i.imgur.com/vfT9KFE.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 05:57:31 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>[mdeia=https://youtu.be/MEPbPsvfqpw] Features FE - Pintra Empire - $27 You can also Create Proper Links that &quot;Source Back&quot; to the original content taken! We also show you how to copywrite your content to Avoid the dreaded Google Slap! We take you by the hand and show you how you can Easily Generate Your Own Niche Blog With Amazing Content You Can M.comize! This means more Targeted Traffic to Your Ecom Store, Affiliate Offers, or Create More Leads! Our Easy To Follow “Over The Shoulder” Training That Covers Everything You’ll Need! Anyone can do this, easily, and effortlessly. This is for the experienced, advanced and newbie in mind. You can get started without any experience, but it&#039;s also made for the advanced user too. As a marketer, blogger or ecommerce website owner you want to be able to generate the most targeted traffic you can, as well as the most ideal content, FAST &amp;amp; EASILY. Luckily for you, we’ve taken all the headaches and hassles out of tapping into the traffic and content goldmine that is and simplified the entire process for you… Perfect for: eCom, CPA Marketing, Affiliate Marketing, List building. You can create a sustainable income depending on the work you put out and the content you bring out should be consistent and persistent. OTO1 - Pintra Scheduler - $32 OTO2 - Pintra Expansion - $37 OTO3 - Pintra Robo - $27 OTO4 - Pintra Fusion - $97</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;">[mdeia=https://youtu.be/MEPbPsvfqpw]</div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><a href="https://www.d-papa.com/pintrajvs" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>FE - Pintra Empire - </b></a><br><ul><li> You can also Create Proper Links that "Source Back" to the original content taken!  <br></li><li> We also  show you how to copywrite your content  to Avoid the dreaded Google Slap!    We take you by the hand and show you how you can Easily Generate Your Own Niche Blog With Amazing Content You Can M.comize!  <br></li><li> This means more  Targeted Traffic to Your Ecom Store, Affiliate Offers, or Create More Leads!<br></li><li> Our Easy To Follow “Over The Shoulder” Training That Covers Everything You’ll Need!<br></li><li> Anyone can do this, easily, and effortlessly.<br></li><li> This is for the experienced, advanced and newbie in mind.<br></li><li> You can get started without any experience, but it's also made for the advanced user too.  <br></li><li> As a marketer, blogger or ecommerce website owner you want to be able to generate the most targeted traffic you can, as well as the most ideal content,  FAST &amp; EASILY.<br></li><li> Luckily for you, we’ve taken all the headaches and hassles out of tapping into the traffic and content goldmine that is and simplified the entire process for you… <br></li><li> Perfect for: eCom, CPA Marketing, Affiliate Marketing, List building.  <br></li><li> You can create a sustainable income depending on the work you put out and the content you bring out should be consistent and persistent.    <br></li></ul><br><a href="https://www.d-papa.com/pintrajvs" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO1 - Pintra Scheduler - </b></a><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="https://i.imgur.com/OmmYCST.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Pintra + OTOs"></div><br><br><a href="https://www.d-papa.com/pintrajvs" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO2 - Pintra Expansion - </b></a><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="https://i.imgur.com/kJy8kQl.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""></div><br><br><a href="https://www.d-papa.com/pintrajvs" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO3 - Pintra Robo - </b></a><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="https://i.imgur.com/egJHecV.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""></div><br><br><a href="https://www.d-papa.com/pintrajvs" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO4 - Pintra Fusion - </b></a><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="https://i.imgur.com/vfT9KFE.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""></div><br><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Viper Cache + OTOs [Instant Deliver]</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4307-viper-cache-otos.html</link>
<description>GB Name : Viper Cache + OTOs Version : Last OS : Anything Type : WP Cache Plugin, Optimize Plugin GB Price : $47(FE) + $47(OTO1) + $39(OTO2) + $37(OTO3) = $170 GB Cost : 17$/10 peoples + 1.5$ Fee GB Joined : 8/10 Peoples GB Status : Delivered Homepage : SalePage Viper Cache is the WP Plugin that makes your WP Sites up to 10X faster in one click. It is the easiest and fastest cache plugin with almost no server lag. It will speed up any WP site while other plugins have problems affected experience and site performance.</description>
<category>GB WordPress</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 05:55:30 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FE - Viper Cache - $47 Smart Cache Clearing Viper Cache can monitor all site changes including loading new themes, plugins, widgets, graphics, new posts, and pages. Even any major change to your site will automatically clear and rebuild your cache. Smart Cache rebuilding If the change is minor like a small text change on a page, this tool will sense that and rebuild the cache on that page. It will reduce your server load and the needs for upgrading your hosting plan. Now you can keep your site fast. Traffic protection technology It blocks more than 1000 bad bots and auto blocks hotlinking. You have the option to block known bad bots and site scrapers that eat your resources and slow your site down. OTO1 - WP Optimiser - $47 It is a combination of quick fixes and diagnostics to fix your site speed issues. It covers all six primary site optimization factors. OTO2 - WP Easy Pages - $39 This first landing page builder is for WP and bypasses the theme and the plugins CSS making it up to 16 times faster OTO3 - WP Conversion Boost - $37 Increase Conversions : By creating keyword relevant landing pages you are much more likely to increase on page time as the page is highly relevant to the visitors search / needs. Build Lists Faster : By adding personalization to your optins you are much more likely to get subscribers. Familiarity &amp;amp; comfort are key criteria in our decision making. Increase Visitor Spend : By using personalized landing pages you can draw attention to the products they have bought + make bespoke landing pages that mention these. Boost Engagement : By using attention grabbing pages pages that interrupt normal behavior. Visitors simply see something different &amp;amp; unusual &amp;amp; stay longer on page. Use on Your Own &amp;amp; Client Sites Commercial License Works on WordPress 4.x Full Tutorial Videos Instant Download Ongoing Support &amp;amp; Updates Unlimited Sites Annual Payment</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/TkOQxgZdxXI?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><a href="http://vipercache.com/comingsoon/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>FE - Viper Cache - </b></a><br><ul><li> Smart Cache Clearing<br></li><li> Viper Cache can monitor all site changes including loading new themes, plugins, widgets, graphics, new posts, and pages. Even any major change to your site will automatically clear and rebuild your cache.<br></li><li> Smart Cache rebuilding<br></li><li> If the change is minor like a small text change on a page, this tool will sense that and rebuild the cache on that page. It will reduce your server load and the needs for upgrading your hosting plan. Now you can keep your site fast.<br></li><li> Traffic protection technology<br></li><li> It blocks more than 1000 bad bots and auto blocks hotlinking. You have the option to block known bad bots and site scrapers that eat your resources and slow your site down.		<br></li></ul><br><a href="https://vipercache.com/step1/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO1 - WP Optimiser - </b></a><br><ul><li> It is a combination of quick fixes and diagnostics to fix your site speed issues. It covers all six primary site optimization factors.<br></li></ul><br><a href="https://vipercache.com/step2/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO2 - WP Easy Pages - </b></a><br><ul><li> This first landing page builder is for WP and bypasses the theme and the plugins CSS making it up to 16 times faster<br></li></ul><br><a href="https://vipercache.com/step3/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO3 - WP Conversion Boost - </b></a><br><ul><li> Increase Conversions : By creating keyword relevant landing pages you are much more likely to increase on page time as the page is highly relevant to the visitors search / needs.<br></li><li> Build Lists Faster : By adding personalization to your optins you are much more likely to get subscribers. Familiarity &amp; comfort are key criteria in our decision making.<br></li><li> Increase Visitor Spend : By using personalized landing pages you can draw attention to the products they have bought +  make bespoke landing pages that mention these.<br></li><li> Boost Engagement : By using attention grabbing pages pages that interrupt normal behavior. Visitors simply see something different &amp; unusual &amp; stay longer on page.<br></li><li> Use on Your Own &amp; Client Sites<br></li><li> Commercial License<br></li><li> Works on WordPress 4.x<br></li><li> Full Tutorial Videos<br></li><li> Instant Download<br></li><li> Ongoing Support &amp; Updates<br></li><li> Unlimited Sites<br></li><li> Annual Payment<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Viper Cache + OTOs [Instant Deliver]"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>WP Shield Mate v2 + OTOs</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4527-wp-shield-mate-v2-otos.html</link>
<description>GB Name : WP Shield Mate v2 + OTOs Version : Last OS : Anything Type : WordPress Security Plugin GB Price : $11.52(FE) + $30.54(OTO1) + $37(OTO2) + $79(OTO3) + $9.95(OTO4) = $158.06 GB Cost : 15.8$/10 peoples + 1.2$ Fee GB Joined : 6/10 Peoples GB Status : Going Homepage : SalePage WP Shield Mate v2 is a WordPress Security plugin that created by BCBiz Team. This proven security plugin on your WordPress blog, even if somehow the hacker manage to crack your password, he still won&#039;t be able to login to your WordPress account!</description>
<category>GB WordPress</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 05:55:00 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FE - WP Shield Mate v2 - $11.52 Protect your WP site in 3 easy steps Your site WILL STAY SAFE and SECURE even if somebody know your password Unlimited sites Developer License included 1-click automatic update OTO1 - WP AmazeNiche Theme - $30.54 Responsive &amp;amp; Mobile Friendly Design The AmazeNiche WP Theme is fully mobile friendly and comes with responsive design. Meaning your website will perfectly optimized for every browser, device and screen size the visitors use. Theme Customizer: Easy to Customize The theme customizer allows you to tweak the theme&#039;s settings, color schemes, and content and see a preview of those changes in real time. Localisation / Translation Ready AmazeNiche theme is easy to translate to any native language. It&#039;s 100% ready for translating into multiple languanges in just a few minutes. You can use WP AmazeNiche theme to build a site in any language Clean Code The theme code is profesionally written to ensure the theme is clean and lightweight. That make it easy for you to tweak any code and in overall it will improve the loading speed of your website. Speed Optimized AmazeNiche is a lightweight WordPress theme that gives your website a very fast page load speed. Each feature has been tested for speed to ensure it loads optimally which improves your SEO score and the user experience. Search Engine Optimized (SEO) In the design and development of the AmazeNiche theme, SEO was the top priority. This theme comes with all essential on-page SEO features that guarantee your site high rankings in Google. OTO2 - 3 Premium PRO WordPress Bullder - $37 Premium WP Tools #1 : WP AZON AFFILIO BUILDER - Harness the power of WP + WooCommerce + Amazon - Research &amp;amp; Import Amazon Products With 1-Click - Bulk Import Amazon Products By ASIN - Set The Plugin To Import Amazon Items On Autopilot - Spin Title and Product Description For Better SEO - And Lots of More! Premium WP Tools #2 : G-NEWS CURATOR WP PLUGIN - Get fresh articles from Google News in 1-click - Get traffic from people who&#039;re looking for trending topics/news - Curate content based on ANY keywords you wish - And Lots of More! Premium WP Tools #3 : G-RANK MONITOR WP PLUGIN - Track your website&#039;s keyword ranking on autopilot - Shows you the rank statistic straight from your WP Admin Dashboard - Must have WP plugin for niche marketers - And Lots of More! OTO3 - WP ShieldMate Reseller - $79 Resell license</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Inv46-1khxE?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><a href="https://wphaven.co/wpsm-v2/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>FE - WP Shield Mate v2 - .52</b></a><br><ul><li> Protect your WP site in 3 easy steps<br></li><li> Your site WILL STAY SAFE and SECURE even if somebody know your password<br></li><li> Unlimited sites Developer License included<br></li><li> 1-click automatic update<br></li></ul><br><a href="https://exclusivebonusblog.com/oto-amazeniche/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO1 - WP AmazeNiche Theme - .54</b></a><br><ul><li> Responsive &amp; Mobile Friendly Design<br></li><li> The AmazeNiche WP Theme is fully mobile friendly and comes with responsive design. Meaning your website will perfectly optimized for every browser, device and screen size the visitors use.<br></li><li> Theme Customizer: Easy to Customize<br></li><li> The theme customizer allows you to tweak the theme's settings, color schemes, and content and see a preview of those changes in real time.<br></li><li> Localisation / Translation Ready<br></li><li> AmazeNiche theme is easy to translate to any native language. It's 100% ready for translating into multiple languanges in just a few minutes. You can use WP AmazeNiche theme to build a site in any language<br></li><li> Clean Code<br></li><li> The theme code is profesionally written to ensure the theme is clean and lightweight. That make it easy for you to tweak any code and in overall it will improve the loading speed of your website.<br></li><li> Speed Optimized<br></li><li> AmazeNiche is a lightweight WordPress theme that gives your website a very fast page load speed. Each feature has been tested for speed to ensure it loads optimally which improves your SEO score and the user experience.<br></li><li> Search Engine Optimized (SEO)<br></li><li> In the design and development of the AmazeNiche theme, SEO was the top priority. This theme comes with all essential on-page SEO features that guarantee your site high rankings in Google.<br></li></ul><br><a href="https://exclusivebonusblog.com/oto-3premiumpluginsbundle/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO2 - 3 Premium PRO WordPress Bullder - </b></a><br><ul><li> Premium WP Tools #1 :<br></li><li> WP AZON AFFILIO BUILDER<br></li><li> - Harness the power of WP + WooCommerce + Amazon<br></li><li> - Research &amp; Import Amazon Products With 1-Click<br></li><li> - Bulk Import Amazon Products By ASIN<br></li><li> - Set The Plugin To Import Amazon Items On Autopilot<br></li><li> - Spin Title and Product Description For Better SEO<br></li><li> - And Lots of More!<br></li><li> Premium WP Tools #2 :<br></li><li> G-NEWS CURATOR WP PLUGIN<br></li><li> - Get fresh articles from Google News in 1-click<br></li><li> - Get traffic from people who're looking for trending topics/news<br></li><li> - Curate content based on ANY keywords you wish<br></li><li> - And Lots of More!<br></li><li> Premium WP Tools #3 :<br></li><li> G-RANK MONITOR WP PLUGIN<br></li><li> - Track your website's keyword ranking on autopilot<br></li><li> - Shows you the rank statistic straight from your WP Admin Dashboard<br></li><li> - Must have WP plugin for niche marketers<br></li><li> - And Lots of More!<br></li></ul><br><a href="https://exclusivebonusblog.com/oto-wpshieldmaterr/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO3 - WP ShieldMate Reseller - </b></a><br><ul><li> Resell license<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="WP Shield Mate v2 + OTOs"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Membro + OTOs [Delivering]</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4528-membro-otos.html</link>
<description>GB Name : Membro + OTOs Version : Last OS : Anything Type : Membership/Subscriptions Based WordPress System GB Price : $47(FE) + $27(OTO1) + $37(OTO2) = $121 GB Cost : 12.5$/10 peoples + 1$ Fee GB Joined : 6/10 Peoples GB Status : Going Homepage : SalePage M.comize your skills, products and services in the form of premium content and create a loyal customer base with the help of InkThemes latest WordPress solution</description>
<category>GB WordPress</category>
<enclosure url="https://i.imgur.com/GUoISw9.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="https://i.imgur.com/edsZwpn.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="https://i.imgur.com/Ej9j1fN.png" type="image/png" />
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 05:54:49 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>[mdeia=https://youtu.be/9e9WRri8keA] Features FE - Membro WordPress Solution - $47 OTO1 - Digital Affiliate Box - $37 OTO2 - Vendorpro WordPress System - $37</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;">[mdeia=https://youtu.be/9e9WRri8keA]</div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><a href="https://www.inkthemes.com/offers/membro-jv/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>FE - Membro WordPress Solution - </b></a><br><img src="https://i.imgur.com/GUoISw9.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Membro + OTOs [Delivering]"><br><a href="https://www.inkthemes.com/offers/membro-jv/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO1 - Digital Affiliate Box - </b></a><br><img src="https://i.imgur.com/edsZwpn.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><a href="https://www.inkthemes.com/offers/membro-jv/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO2 - Vendorpro WordPress System - </b></a><br><img src="https://i.imgur.com/Ej9j1fN.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>GDPR Pro + OTOs [Instant Deliver]</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4254-gdpr-pro-otos.html</link>
<description>GB Name : GDPR Pro + OTOs Version : Last OS : Anything Type : WordPress Plugin to Help Website be GDPR Compliant GB Price : $27(FE) + $47(OTO1) + $67(OTO1) + $37(OTO1) + $27(OTO1) = $205 GB Cost : 14$/15 eoples + 1$ Fee GB Joined : 13/15 Peoples GB Status : Delivered Homepage : SalePage It is not wise or necessary to spread fear, since the simple facts are enough to motivate most marketers to take action. Bottom Line: You can avoid GDPR fines, get into compliance and sleep well if you follow some proven steps. And our new software can make the whole process very easy, but more about that in a moment.</description>
<category>GB WordPress</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 05:35:32 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FE - GDPR Pro - $27 Use on 5 Sites Software brings your site into compliance on 8 Key GDPR requirements. Works with your blog or any other custom implementation of WordPress. Works with E-Commerce stores. The cookie requirement compliance assures your EU visitors are briefed about cookie policy. &#039;Terms and conditions&#039; policy compliance gets your visitors consent to your T&amp;amp;C. &#039;Privacy policy&#039; compliance creates consent requirement for your Privacy Policy. &#039;Right to Forget&#039; compliance lets you delete your user data manually. Option to refuse to accept EU traffic on your site (built into the plugin). User consent log, incase regulators come knocking on your door! OTO1 - Upgrade 1 - $47 UNLIMITED LICENSES Only Feature YOUR Branding On Your Domains Multiple Opt-In Forms Designs &amp;amp; Styles More Variety &amp;amp; More Flexibility Mix &amp;amp; Match With Your Websites Installs quickly / easily on any WordPress site Become GDPR compliant in a few clicks Prevent potentially catastrophic fines PRIORITY SUPPORT As A Pro Version Owner OTO2 - Upgrade 2 - $67 Agency License Unlimited Clients Sites The added value of an &quot;Agency License&quot; Full Commercial License Unlimited installs on your client sites Create pop-ups for clients sites Option to charge clients retainer fees ALL the features of the standard Today, you can take advantage of this powerful Special Upgrade and give your business... More trust for your sites. Visitors will feel more secure and more likely to buy. More credibility for your sites. Your sites will enjoy increased authority in the marketplace. Safety &amp;amp; security across your and your client’s sites Professional positioning in your subscriber&#039;s eyes Start your own agency by offering GDPR Compliance services Build a new income stream offering a valuable service Leverage the client relationship for even more business OTO3 - Upgrade 3 - $37 Trust-builder Emails to Establish Authority: Professionally written to give you credibility and enhance your image. A Done-For-You Lead Ma.com: Perfect to attract new clients quickly and effortlessly. Done-For-You Prospecting Emails: Proven and high-converting emails. Why reinvent the wheel? Done-For-You Marketing Hotsheets: Can be used as blog posts, emails, Lead ma.coms or in print media. Hard-hitting and attention-grabbing. Done-For-You GDPR Slide Deck Presentation: We&#039;ve done all the hard work for you by converting the GDPR in Plain English presentation into a editable slide deck so you can quickly create live presentations, workshops, and webinars. ALL created by Professional Designers at considerable expense. Instantly create your agency with these materials instead of waiting weeks or months. It would cost THOUSANDS to create all this professional-level material and take weeks to get it. It’s no exaggeration to say you&#039;ll save a fortune. You will convert more prospects into clients... faster, too. You&#039;ll position yourself as the authority in your market. You&#039;ll be able to charge higher fees. You&#039;ll grow your agency faster and easier. OTO4 - Upgrade 4 - $27 The secret structure to setting up your SSL business that&#039;ll have prospects begging to sign up! Exactly Where to Find the ideal client for your business style How to perform and deliver the SSL service and charge for monthly maintenance. The Misunderstood Secret Of Why Google Is Pushing SSL So Much Caution! Why people fail with just SSL software The simplest, easiest way to close a Client with NO PRESSURE The WORST mistakes you can make with SSL Marketing How to pay a little to get others to do the &#039;dirty work&#039; for you. The clever way we go from &#039;little starter sale&#039; to bigger and bigger sales. What SUCKS And How To Avoid It The sexy way Google will FORCE all your clients and prospects to sign up with you. Believe it or not there are ways to NEVER meet or talk to a client. Why the public&#039;s brainwashing by Google Only helps you make money</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/270879819?app_id=122963" width="425" height="239" frameborder="0" title="GDPR Pro JV Video" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><a href="https://www.gdprpro.io/gdpr-pro-sales-page-revised" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>FE - GDPR Pro  - </b></a><br><ul><li> Use on 5 Sites<br></li><li> Software brings your site into compliance on 8 Key GDPR requirements.<br></li><li> Works with your blog or any other custom implementation of WordPress.<br></li><li> Works with E-Commerce stores.<br></li><li> The cookie requirement compliance assures your EU visitors are briefed about cookie policy.<br></li><li> 'Terms and conditions' policy compliance gets your visitors consent to your T&amp;C.<br></li><li> 'Privacy policy' compliance creates consent requirement for your Privacy Policy.<br></li><li> 'Right to Forget' compliance lets you delete your user data manually.<br></li><li> Option to refuse to accept EU traffic on your site (built into the plugin).<br></li><li> User consent log, incase regulators come knocking on your door!<br></li></ul><br><a href="https://www.gdprpro.io/upgrade-120720910" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO1 - Upgrade 1 - </b></a><br><ul><li> UNLIMITED LICENSES<br></li><li> Only Feature YOUR Branding On Your Domains<br></li><li> Multiple Opt-In Forms Designs &amp; Styles<br></li><li> More Variety &amp; More Flexibility<br></li><li> Mix &amp; Match With Your Websites<br></li><li> Installs quickly / easily on any WordPress site<br></li><li> Become GDPR compliant in a few clicks<br></li><li> Prevent potentially catastrophic fines<br></li><li> PRIORITY SUPPORT As A Pro Version Owner<br></li></ul><br><a href="https://www.gdprpro.io/upgrade-2-lai20720912" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO2 - Upgrade 2 - </b></a><br><ul><li> Agency License<br></li><li> Unlimited Clients Sites<br></li><li> The added value of an "Agency License"<br></li><li> Full Commercial License<br></li><li> Unlimited installs on your client sites<br></li><li> Create pop-ups for clients sites<br></li><li> Option to charge clients retainer fees<br></li><li> ALL the features of the standard<br></li><li> Today, you can take advantage of this powerful Special Upgrade and give your business...<br></li><li> More trust for your sites. Visitors will feel more secure and more likely to buy. <br></li><li> More credibility for your sites. Your sites will enjoy increased authority in the marketplace.<br></li><li> Safety &amp; security across your and your client’s sites<br></li><li> Professional positioning in your subscriber's eyes<br></li><li> Start your own agency by offering GDPR Compliance services<br></li><li> Build a new income stream offering a valuable service<br></li><li> Leverage the client relationship for even more business<br></li></ul><br><a href="https://www.gdprpro.io/oto-3" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO3 - Upgrade 3 - </b></a><br><ul><li> Trust-builder Emails to Establish Authority: Professionally written to give you credibility and  enhance your image.<br></li><li> A Done-For-You Lead Ma.com: Perfect to attract new clients quickly and effortlessly.<br></li><li> Done-For-You Prospecting Emails: Proven and high-converting emails. Why reinvent the wheel?<br></li><li> Done-For-You Marketing Hotsheets: Can be used as blog posts, emails, Lead ma.coms or in print media. Hard-hitting and attention-grabbing. <br></li><li> Done-For-You GDPR Slide Deck Presentation: We've done all the hard work for you by converting the GDPR in Plain English presentation into a editable slide deck so you can quickly create live presentations, workshops, and webinars.<br></li><li> ALL created by Professional Designers at considerable expense.<br></li><li> Instantly create your agency with these materials instead of waiting weeks or months.<br></li><li> It would cost THOUSANDS to create all this professional-level material and take weeks to get it.<br></li><li> It’s no exaggeration to say you'll save a fortune.<br></li><li> You will convert more prospects into clients... faster, too.<br></li><li> You'll position yourself as the authority in your market.<br></li><li> You'll be able to charge higher fees. <br></li><li> You'll grow your agency faster and easier.<br></li></ul><br><a href="https://www.gdprpro.io/ssl-upgrade-4" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO4 - Upgrade 4 - </b></a><br><ul><li> The secret structure to setting up your SSL business that'll have prospects begging to sign up!<br></li><li> Exactly Where to Find the ideal client for your business style<br></li><li> How to perform and deliver the SSL service and charge for monthly maintenance.<br></li><li> The Misunderstood Secret Of Why Google Is Pushing SSL So Much<br></li><li> Caution! Why people fail with just SSL software<br></li><li> The simplest, easiest way to close a Client with NO PRESSURE<br></li><li> The WORST mistakes you can make with SSL Marketing<br></li><li> How to pay a little to get others to do the 'dirty work' for you.<br></li><li> The clever way we go from 'little starter sale' to bigger and bigger sales.<br></li><li> What SUCKS And How To Avoid It<br></li><li> The sexy way Google will FORCE all your clients and prospects to sign up with you.<br></li><li> Believe it or not there are ways to NEVER meet or talk to a client. <br></li><li> Why the public's brainwashing by Google Only helps you make money<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="GDPR Pro + OTOs [Instant Deliver]"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Conversionizer + OTOs [Instant Deliver]</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4212-conversionizer-otos.html</link>
<description>GB Name : Conversionizer + OTOs Version : Last OS : Anything Type : Conversion Tracking GB Price : $37(FE) + $97(OTO1) + $97(OTO2) + $67(OTO3) = $298 GB Cost : 15$/20 Peoples + 1.2$ Fee GB Joined : 18/20 Peoples GB Status : Delivered Homepage : SalePage It Is a solution that tracks site visitors, sales and subscribers and auto optimizes website content to get even more sales from existing traffic. Conversionizer has been designed from the ground-up to achieve conversion based outcomes for your online marketing. Our focus is always: Advanced Conversion Tracking Made Simple.</description>
<category>GB WordPress</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 05:35:11 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FE - Conversionizer - $37 Attract &amp;amp; Convert Free Traffic with Conversionizer Inbound Organic Tracking Extract Optimum Sales and Subscribers with Conversionizer Split Testing - made simple Get Profitable and Scale-Up Advertising with Conversionizer Inbound Link Tracking NOW Supports Sendlane,Market Hero AutoResponders E-commerce and Affiliate Marketing Conversionizer Integrations Action Links (call-to-action optimization) Instant Conversion Notifications Via Email OTO1 - Conversionizer Pro - $97 UNLIMITED DOMAINS, CAMPAIGNS, PRO FEATURES OTO2 - CONVERTIFY - $97 Live Updating Sale Display Simple Shortcode Live Sales Notifications Revenue Calculator Strategy Suggestions Payment Integration Simple Edit &amp;amp; Preview Button Selection &amp;amp; Custom Support &amp;amp; Tutorials OTO3 - Conversionizer Reseller - $67 sell Conversionizer and keep 100% profits to yourself.</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/y0ATkTIcnuM?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><a href="https://sales.conversionizer.com/buy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>FE - Conversionizer  - </b></a><br><ul><li> Attract &amp; Convert Free Traffic with Conversionizer Inbound Organic Tracking<br></li><li> Extract Optimum Sales and Subscribers with Conversionizer Split Testing - made simple<br></li><li> Get Profitable and Scale-Up Advertising with Conversionizer Inbound Link Tracking<br></li><li> NOW Supports Sendlane,Market Hero AutoResponders<br></li><li> E-commerce and Affiliate Marketing Conversionizer Integrations<br></li><li> Action Links (call-to-action optimization)<br></li><li> Instant Conversion Notifications Via Email<br></li></ul><br><a href="https://sales.conversionizer.com/pro/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO1 - Conversionizer  Pro - </b></a><br><ul><li> UNLIMITED DOMAINS, CAMPAIGNS, PRO FEATURES<br></li></ul><br><a href="http://sales.conversionizer.com/upsell2/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO2 - CONVERTIFY - </b></a><br><ul><li> Live Updating Sale Display<br></li><li> Simple Shortcode<br></li><li> Live Sales Notifications<br></li><li> Revenue Calculator<br></li><li> Strategy Suggestions<br></li><li> Payment Integration<br></li><li> Simple Edit &amp; Preview<br></li><li> Button Selection &amp; Custom<br></li><li> Support &amp; Tutorials<br></li></ul><br><a href="https://sales.conversionizer.com/reseller/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO3 - Conversionizer Reseller  - </b></a><br><ul><li> sell Conversionizer and keep 100% profits to yourself.<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Conversionizer + OTOs [Instant Deliver]"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Push Button Traffic 3.0 + OTOs [Instant Deliver]</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4501-push-button-traffic-30-otos.html</link>
<description>GB Name : Push Button Traffic 3.0 + OTOs Version : Last OS : Anything Type : WordPress Plugin GB Price : $17(FE) + $32(OTO1) + $37(OTO2) + $27(OTO3) + $47(OTO4) = $160 GB Cost : 16$/10 Peoples + 1$ Fee GB Joined : 8/10 Peoples GB Status : Delivered Homepage : SalePage Web Based Application That Lets You Create An Affiliate Review PDF With A Few Clicks...</description>
<category>GB WordPress</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 05:34:57 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FE - Push Button Traffic 3.0 - $17 Web Based Application That Lets You Create An Affiliate Review PDF With A Few Clicks... 1 Click Connect Customers Can Add Their Social Accounts With 1 Click Unlike Other Software That Require Complex Setup... Syndicate PDF&#039;s To 8 Social Media Sites For Instant Traffic &amp;amp; Sales... Modulated Video Tutorials Includes A Comphrensive Training Program So Your Customers Can Get Traffic, Leads &amp;amp; Sales... Highly Congruent Bonuses Customers Will Get A Suite Of Awesome Bonuses Designed To Enhance Their Purchase &amp;amp; Get Them Results That Much Quicker. Dedicated Support Desk Full-Time Support To Help Your Customers Should They Need It... OTO1 - Push Button Traffic 3.0 ELITE EDITION - $32 Push Button Traffic 3 - Elite Edition Software - $997 Value Run Unlimited Traffic Campaigns - $997 Value Unlock 2 Additional Traffic Sources - $1,997 Value IMAGE POSTING For More Profits - $997 Value Step-By-Step Tutorials - $197 Value 1-1 Chat With Billy Darr - $997 Value 5 Premium Bonuses - $2,085 Value Developer Rights - $497 Value OTO2 - Push Button Traffic 3.0 - Automation Edition - $37 Automate the entire Push Button Traffic 3.0 software... Free up your time so you can do what you enjoy most... Get you hands-free traffic, leads an sales... A easier and faster way to get more traffic and money now... Let you live a life of freedom and abundance... Put the software to work for you even whilst you sleep... And too much more to reveal here... The Automation Edition - $997 Value 5x Sub Accounts - $997 Each Value Step-By-Step Video Training - $297 Value Commercial Rights - $497 Value 6 Premium Bonuses - $1782 Value OTO3 - Push Button Traffic 3.0 - 100 Done For You Campaigns - $27 Literally Copy, Paste &amp;amp; Profit... Each Campaign Is Proven To The Tune Of $100 To $1,000 Each... Finally Breakthrough To Results... The Price Is Increasing To $297... Lazy Way To Profit Fast Save Time &amp;amp; Save Money Easily Build A Profitable List AutoPilot Income OTO4 - Push Button Traffic 3.0 - 500K Affiliate Method - $47 Show you how to make up to $200 per day in.com profit... Reveal our simple 20 minute strategy that allows even the most greenest of newbies to make a profit online... Ever thought you need a list, tech skills or previous experience? WRONG we&#039;ll show you how you can start earning today... We&#039;ll show you step by step, click by click what todo in order to start earning money with Affiliate offers... Why Affiliate offers are BAR NONE the fastest way to make money online and how you can tap into this billion dollar industry today... How anyone from anywhere can start making money even if you only have 20 - 30 minutes a day... How you can generate enough consistent daily income to even replace your day job... $500K Affiliate Edition - $997 Value 4 Module Coaching Program - $997 20 Step-By-Step Video Tutorials - $997 Value Templates &amp;amp; Resources - $497 Value Bonus Module - Get Money Now - $997 Value $1,429 In 36Hrs Case Study - $1,429 Value</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/1p2frJBU-eQ?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><a href="http://pushbuttontraffic3.com/brand-new" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>FE - Push Button Traffic 3.0 - </b></a><br><ul><li> Web Based Application That Lets You Create An Affiliate Review PDF With A Few Clicks...<br></li><li> 1 Click Connect Customers Can Add Their Social Accounts With 1 Click Unlike Other Software That Require Complex Setup...<br></li><li> Syndicate PDF's To 8 Social Media Sites For Instant Traffic &amp; Sales...<br></li><li> Modulated Video Tutorials Includes A Comphrensive Training Program So Your Customers Can Get Traffic, Leads &amp; Sales...<br></li><li> Highly Congruent Bonuses Customers Will Get A Suite Of Awesome Bonuses Designed To Enhance Their Purchase &amp; Get Them Results That Much Quicker.<br></li><li> Dedicated Support Desk Full-Time Support To Help Your Customers Should They Need It...<br></li></ul><br><a href="https://billydarr.clickfunnels.com/oto-120914429" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO1 - Push Button Traffic 3.0 ELITE EDITION - </b></a><br><ul><li> Push Button Traffic 3 - Elite Edition Software - 7 Value<br></li><li> Run Unlimited Traffic Campaigns - 7 Value<br></li><li> Unlock 2 Additional Traffic Sources - ,997 Value<br></li><li> IMAGE POSTING For More Profits - 7 Value<br></li><li> Step-By-Step Tutorials - 7 Value<br></li><li> 1-1 Chat With Billy Darr - 7 Value<br></li><li> 5 Premium Bonuses - ,085 Value<br></li><li> Developer Rights - 7 Value<br></li></ul><br><a href="https://billydarr.clickfunnels.com/oto-320914431" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO2 - Push Button Traffic 3.0 - Automation Edition - </b></a><br><ul><li> Automate the entire Push Button Traffic 3.0 software...<br></li><li> Free up your time so you can do what you enjoy most...<br></li><li> Get you hands-free traffic, leads an sales...<br></li><li> A easier and faster way to get more traffic and money now...<br></li><li> Let you live a life of freedom and abundance...<br></li><li> Put the software to work for you even whilst you sleep...<br></li><li> And too much more to reveal here...<br></li><li> The Automation Edition - 7 Value<br></li><li> 5x Sub Accounts - 7 Each Value<br></li><li> Step-By-Step Video Training - 7 Value<br></li><li> Commercial Rights - 7 Value<br></li><li> 6 Premium Bonuses - 82 Value<br></li></ul><br><a href="https://billydarr.clickfunnels.com/oto-620914439" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO3 - Push Button Traffic 3.0 - 100 Done For You Campaigns - </b></a><br><ul><li> Literally Copy, Paste &amp; Profit...<br></li><li> Each Campaign Is Proven To The Tune Of 0 To ,000 Each...<br></li><li> Finally Breakthrough To Results...<br></li><li> The Price Is Increasing To 7...<br></li><li> Lazy Way To Profit Fast <br></li><li> Save Time &amp; Save Money<br></li><li> Easily Build A Profitable List<br></li><li> AutoPilot Income<br></li></ul><br><a href="https://billydarr.clickfunnels.com/oto-320940597" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO4 - Push Button Traffic 3.0 - 500K Affiliate Method - </b></a><br><ul><li> Show you how to make up to 0 per day in.com profit...<br></li><li> Reveal our simple 20 minute strategy that allows even the most greenest of newbies to make a profit online...<br></li><li> Ever thought you need a list, tech skills or previous experience? WRONG we'll show you how you can start earning today...<br></li><li> We'll show you step by step, click by click what todo in order to start earning money with Affiliate offers...<br></li><li> Why Affiliate offers are BAR NONE the fastest way to make money online and how you can tap into this billion dollar industry today...<br></li><li> How anyone from anywhere can start making money even if you only have 20 - 30 minutes a day...<br></li><li> How you can generate enough consistent daily income to even replace your day job...<br></li><li> 0K Affiliate Edition - 7 Value<br></li><li> 4 Module Coaching Program - 7<br></li><li> 20 Step-By-Step Video Tutorials - 7 Value<br></li><li> Templates &amp; Resources - 7 Value<br></li><li> Bonus Module - Get Money Now - 7 Value<br></li><li> ,429 In 36Hrs Case Study - ,429 Value<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Push Button Traffic 3.0 + OTOs [Instant Deliver]"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Covert Copy Traffic Pro + OTOs [Instant Deliver]</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3467-covert-copy-traffic-pro.html</link>
<description>GB Name : Covert Copy Traffic Pro + OTOs Version : Last OS : Anything Type : WordPress plugin GB Price : $27(FE) + $47(OTO1) + $47(OTO2) + $97(OTO3) = $218 GB Cost : 22$/10 Peoples + 2$ Fee GB Joined : 7/10 Peoples GB Status : Delivered Homepage : SalePage Covert Copy Traffic is a WordPress plugin which will append your links as well as text below or above the copied content. It means when people paste it on social.comworks or on emails, you immediately get traffic effortlessly. Of course, the product comes with many advanced features which allow you to choose the text as well as the link attached. The great part about it is that you can use it on any website you want, even if it is not a WordPress site.</description>
<category>GB WordPress</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 05:34:44 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FE - Covert Copy Traffic Pro v2 - $27 This plugin allows you to automatically insert links and text when people copy and paste or scrape your blog content. The Pro version includes the ability to use the plugin outside of WordPress. OTO1 - Covert Messenger Pro v2 - $47 Create as many profit pulling ads as you like... Today and from this page only, you get an unlimited site license for the Covert Messenger plugin! No technical skills required... the plugin installs with just a single click and setting up an ad is as easy as creating a new WP post. You can have your first ad up and running in minutes from right now, with just a few clicks! Enjoy click through rates like never before... people will notice your ads and they will click on them - guaranteed! Promote your affiliate link, build your list or promote your own products and sites... it doesn&#039;t matter what niche you are in, Covert Messenger is the most effective ads you can put on any WP blog! OTO2 - Covert Geo Targeter Pro v2 - $47 The PRO version of Covert Geo Targeter is designed to maximize your results &amp;amp; instantly boost your clicks and profits to insane levels and all this at a fraction of the normal cost OTO3 - WP Toolkit Dev Lifetime - $97 Developer Rights to ALL Premium Themes &amp;amp; Plugins Lifetime UNLIMITED updates Install on UNLIMITED Personal &amp;amp; Client Sites Pay ONCE - never pay again</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><div class="dlevideoplayer" style="width:100%;max-width:425px;">
			<ul data-theme="default" data-preload="metadata">
				<li data-title="dc19e53612483de7cc86e53212a0c312fd91a846" data-type="m4v" data-url="https://embedwistia-a.akamaihd.com/deliveries/dc19e53612483de7cc86e53212a0c312fd91a846.ts" ></li>
			</ul>
		</div></div><br><br><h3>Features</h3><br><a href="http://covertcopytraffic.com/v2pro/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>FE - Covert Copy Traffic Pro v2 - </b></a><br><ul><li> This plugin allows you to automatically insert links and text when people copy and paste or scrape your blog content. The Pro version includes the ability to use the plugin outside of WordPress.<br></li></ul><br><a href="http://covertcopytraffic.com/v2oto/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO1 - Covert Messenger Pro v2 - </b></a><br><ul><li> Create as many profit pulling ads as you like... Today and from this page only, you get an unlimited site license for the Covert Messenger plugin!<br></li><li> No technical skills required... the plugin installs with just a single click and setting up an ad is as easy as creating a new WP post. You can have your first ad up and running in minutes from right now, with just a few clicks!<br></li><li> Enjoy click through rates like never before... people will notice your ads and they will click on them - guaranteed! Promote your affiliate link, build your list or promote your own products and sites... it doesn't matter what niche you are in, Covert Messenger is the most effective ads you can put on any WP blog!<br></li></ul><br><a href="http://covertgeotargeter.com/v2/pro.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO2 - Covert Geo Targeter Pro v2 - </b></a><br><ul><li> The PRO version of Covert Geo Targeter is designed to maximize your results &amp; instantly boost your clicks and profits to insane levels and all this at a fraction of the normal cost<br></li></ul><br><a href="https://wptoolkit.com/cgt.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>OTO3 - WP Toolkit Dev Lifetime - </b></a><br><ul><li> Developer Rights to ALL Premium Themes &amp; Plugins<br></li><li> Lifetime UNLIMITED updates<br></li><li> Install on UNLIMITED Personal &amp; Client Sites<br></li><li> Pay ONCE - never pay again<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Covert Copy Traffic Pro + OTOs [Instant Deliver]"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Ultimate Addons for Elementor</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/4493-ultimate-addons-for-elementor.html</link>
<description>GB Name : Ultimate Addons for Elementor Version : Last OS : Anything Type : Elementor Widgets GB Price : $199 GB Cost : 25$/10 Peoples + 2$ Fee GB Joined : 6/10 Peoples GB Status : Going Homepage : SalePage A library of unique Elementor Widgets to add more functionality and flexibility to your favorite page builder.</description>
<category>GB WordPress</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 08:31:55 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FE - Ultimate Addons for Elementor - $199 Unlimited Sites License Lifetime Updates and Support One Time Purchase Money-back Guarantee Top Features: - Ever-growing library of Widgets - White Label Branding - WooCommerce Compatible - RTL Support</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/6xH5n6YYNJE?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><a href="https://uaelementor.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>FE - Ultimate Addons for Elementor - 9</b></a><br><ul><li> Unlimited Sites License<br></li><li> Lifetime Updates and Support<br></li><li> One Time Purchase<br></li><li> Money-back Guarantee<br></li><li> Top Features:<br></li><li> - Ever-growing library of Widgets<br></li><li> - White Label Branding<br></li><li> - WooCommerce Compatible<br></li><li> - RTL Support<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Ultimate Addons for Elementor"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item><item turbo="true">
<title>Ultimate Addons for Beaver Builder Lifetime</title>
<link>http://31.220.48.156/3964-ultimate-addons-for-beaver-builder-lifetime.html</link>
<description>GB Name : Ultimate Addons for Beaver Builder Lifetime Version : Last OS : Anything Type : Beaver Builder Modules and Templates GB Price : $249 GB Cost : 25$/10 peoples + 2$ Fee GB Joined : 6/10 Peoples GB Status : Going Homepage : SalePage Ultimate Addons for Beaver Builder Transform your productivity with custom Beaver Builder modules and templates.</description>
<category>GB WordPress</category>
<enclosure url="/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" type="image/png" />
<pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 08:23:44 -1000</pubDate>
<yandex:full-text>Features FE - Ultimate Addons for Beaver Builder Lifetime - $249 Unlimited Sites License Lifetime Updates and Support One Time Purchase Money-back Guarantee Top Features: - 45+ Custom Modules - 200+ Row Templates - 100+ Page Templates - Template Cloud - White Label Branding</yandex:full-text>
<turbo:content><![CDATA[<div style="text-align:center;"><iframe width="425" height="239" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/J7gCG-vpZ8k?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br><h3>Features</h3><br><a href="https://www.ultimatebeaver.com/pricing/" target="_blank" rel="noopener external noreferrer"><b>FE - Ultimate Addons for Beaver Builder Lifetime - 9</b></a><br><ul><li> Unlimited Sites License<br></li><li> Lifetime Updates and Support<br></li><li> One Time Purchase<br></li><li> Money-back Guarantee<br></li><li> Top Features:<br></li><li> - 45+ Custom Modules<br></li><li> - 200+ Row Templates<br></li><li> - 100+ Page Templates<br></li><li> - Template Cloud<br></li><li> - White Label Branding<br></li></ul><br><br><div style="text-align:center;"><br><img src="http://31.220.48.156/uploads/downloadnowvip.tgmember.png" style="max-width:100%;" alt="Ultimate Addons for Beaver Builder Lifetime"><br><div class="quote"><br><br></div></div>]]></turbo:content>
</item></channel></rss>